Hello, all, and welcome to the best radio show in town.
It's 694.2 PTBP, and I'm your host, Wolf the Dog.
I'm here to say things, and you are here to listen.
A perfect relationship.
Sometimes, you're here to say things,
and I'm here to listen.
This episode's Howlin' with Wolf is from Cupcake Sinclair
in Las Vegas, Nevada, who tweeted about the show
and tagged at PretendingPod, an easy and nice thing
you can also do to spread the love and joy of 694.2 PTBP
with your online friendos.
Cupcake Sinclair writes, PTBP equals amazing.
I'm hooked, and I love the reminder
that sex work is real work.
There is discrimination not only from society,
but credit cards dictating what can appear.
For example, TV can film sleeping, hypnosis, et cetera,
but we cannot.
I ask listeners to please consider
how hypocritical laws passed against sex workers
are a canary in the coal mine for wider changes that will
affect us all down the road, especially
in terms of what consenting adults do.
And that's just porn.
You know a sex worker whether you realize or not.
Thank you guys for your hard work, the hilarity you bring,
and the consideration of my announcement.
XOXO, submissive Cupcake Sinclair.
Well, damn, Cupcake Sinclair.
Thanks for all the shout outs and praise.
Let's make sure we all support sex workers' rights.
If you wanna write up something for your little Wolfie
to how, tag at pretending pod on Twitter,
tag at pretending pod on instant gram,
and tag pretending to be people on Facebook.
Or write up a five star review on the podcast app
of your choice.
If you give ol' Wolfie a shout out,
I might read that dang review right here
in the wettest broadcasting studio
this side of the Mississippi.
And this side, it means under.
Do you wanna check out our shit
without having to type a single letter?
All of our links are where?
Say it with me, children.
In the show notes.
Seriously, go look at the show notes.
It's wild stuff in there.
And it takes me about four hours to type them up
with these big ol' nasty paws.
Please acknowledge my hard work
and excellent use of language.
Now dial up for some vile fluff.
It's time for the news.
Last time, we met Shelly St. Blythe,
a crystal doctor with a penchant for puppetry
who witnessed something wildly unnatural back in the day.
He was at a dig site with the charming and capable
Dr. Brock Hargrave, as well as Jimmy Corrigan,
a badass merc with a soft spot for his wife and children.
A woman with myriad names, a shrinking frame,
and the voice of Jennifer Jason Leigh
continued building her personal strike team
with the owner of Boeri Security, Vincent T. Boeri,
who has an eye for fashion
and an even better eye for new employees.
And for this particular mission,
she rounded out the squad with a vagabond called Meat Hook.
They received their assignment
in this emaciated woman's house
that reeked of cat piss, sans the cats.
The briefing was as follows.
Dr. Brock Hargrave and one of his coworkers
at Holy Cow Farms have gone missing.
Dr. Hargrave headed out after work
and just didn't come back,
but his missing coworker seemingly never left
the office building of Holy Cow Farms,
taking us now to the death two-car convoy
of Jimmy Corrigan's Jeep and a, Jesus, a stretch Escalade?
Well, this team may be fucked,
but at least we have Hudson Freeman
with Muscles R. Spreems.
Let's go.
What's up, everybody?
I was thinking the same thing.
I am now mechanization.
All my muscles work like screams.
What's up, everybody?
Welcome to episode two of this short story here
on pretending to be people.
It's Holy Cow Farms time.
Holy Cow Farms.
Holy cow.
You know, we looked that up
and Zach, there's only two businesses in the country
that are currently named that.
So pretty good pun.
Pretty good.
And one of them is close enough
where we can go take a picture with the sign.
Yeah.
Or we can go break into their facilities.
We should do that.
We should break into the Holy Cow Farms
that's in Arkansas just as a tribute to this episode.
We should role play inside.
And cause we found out we're all cousins.
We are all cousins.
Us, Paul Rudd, who else?
The Royals.
Jon Hamm.
That's right.
Lord.
Mark Twain.
Ellie Kemper.
John Goodman.
Oh, Disney.
Jenna Fisher.
Good pull, yes.
Janelle Monae, but she won't claim it.
Ah, damn.
She's from KC though.
Did you say John Goodman?
No, I said John Goodman.
John Goodman.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, Brad Pitt.
Brad Pitt, he's from our town.
Our friend, Brad.
I found out something terrible about Brad Pitt.
What?
He was born in Oklahoma, not Missouri.
Even though he grew up here
and spent his formative years in Springfield.
You really scared me for a minute there.
I really thought you were going to say something
to harm the reputation of our Lord and Savior, Brad Pitt.
Hey, hey, hold on.
This is the Jesus podcast.
Okay, any Jesus lover can admit
that Brad Pitt is as close as we got on this planet.
I want him opening the gates of heaven.
You know what I mean?
I recently watched him murder so many people on a train.
But did he feel bad about it?
He kind of did, honest.
Did any of you see that?
I did see it.
I still haven't seen it.
Bullet train, so fucking good.
Did you see it Becca?
Not yet, no.
You should.
It's a fun one.
I heard Luke and Joe liked it.
I heard it was more ensemble than Brad Pitt.
Yeah, he was the string that ran through the whole movie,
but it was great.
It was like a live action anime starring Brad Pitt.
That's all I need.
That's a great pitch.
Becca, I'm curious to hear a little bit more
about your role-playing history.
I'm sure you've shared this many, many times before,
but what brought you to this lovely hobby
that we all share?
The money, baby.
Fuck yeah, bro.
Pray the bills.
No, hey, I was just a bystander when crit role started.
Having snacks in the kitchen with them at Geek and Sundry,
and we played all kinds of other role-playing games there.
And at first, so competitive board gaming is my jam.
I love it.
Love me some magic, love me any competitive board game.
But once I understood intellectually
that you don't need to win,
in fact, it's way more fun to lose terribly,
that's when role-playing really clicked for me.
And I also have an acting background
from the University of Missouri, Kansas City.
I've driven by there.
So, you know, I just get to act,
but with only my voice and that's real fun.
Hell yeah.
Do you act with your whole body anyway
while you're doing voice acting?
Not today, because I kept my camera off.
But I mean, you've seen us waving our arms around wildly.
Are you doing that like just for no one?
Fun fact, when I do like a commercial voiceover,
I do wiggle my arms in the air.
Like they're little serpents
that are helping me to explain the product.
It's your favorite product you've sold with your voice?
Magic the Gathering.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, that's sick.
And it's a good tie-in for Delta Green,
because one of the artists
on the original Magic the Gathering run
was one of the creators of this game
that we're playing this evening, Delta Green.
Oh shit, I hope it's not one that was canceled.
I hope not.
Me too.
You know those OG artists,
there's some fucked up shit in some of that card stuff.
I'll Google Dennis Stettwiller canceled later
and we'll find out.
That's a leading question.
Does Meat Hook have a collection of banned Magic cards?
Meat Hook made her own banned Magic cards.
And she's remembering going through the cards in her mind
as you're driving, sitting in this car,
because it feels like Magic being inside a vehicle
for the third time in your life, Meat Hook.
And we see the holy cow of magic cards
and we see the holy cow farms office building,
except for holy cow farm seems to share this office building
with a few other companies listed on the sign out front.
It is a very boxy, nondescript office building
with a large parking lot
where you can park wherever you would like.
Today is a Tuesday.
It is 8.57 PM, almost nine o'clock.
The parking lot is dark.
There are orange lights, lighting up specific segments.
And there is a van parked up near the door
that says trolleys cleaning service.
And it's the van has like a paint job,
like it's a trolley car.
Goomba.
I've used those guys a hell of a lot.
They keep the mouth shut.
Wait, you say that like they're that kind of cleaner?
They do all sorts.
Well, they do my townhouse.
I'm sure they do a fricking fantastic job.
Perhaps they'll have a card.
You got a whole townhouse?
Oh, of course, yes.
Do you need someone to live in the basement or something?
Do you need?
It does get lonely there at times.
It would be fun to have a roommates of sorts, yes, sure.
Yeah, like a little basement creep.
Okay, well, maybe we could talk about me
being your basement creep.
Sure, exchange details.
I would love to have a basement creep, yes.
Okay, well, I live in the hold.
That's all the details I can really tell you.
The hold, is that ever on the third street or?
It's like way far outside of town.
There was a street sign once,
but somebody ripped it down and nobody ever fixed it.
Well, I'll give you my address and one day you'll be there
and I'll say, oh, there's the basement creep.
That's how I know you found the place.
This plan works out really well for me.
To be honest, I think this works out for the doc too.
You know, it could really use some companies.
He's going a little bit batty.
Oh, well, you know, we're all going a little batty.
I mean, people tell me I'm batty all the time
just because I stand on street corners handing out leaflets.
Leaflets?
Yeah, you want a leaflet?
Here.
If you've got one, of course, yes.
Let me read your literature.
Yeah.
And what's it about, this one?
That one?
That one's about how we need to be teaching kids
about the underground digging
because we're all gonna have to be mole people someday.
Oh my, you're a basement creep after my own heart.
Yes, get the children digging early on.
They might find things in the ground
and that ties directly into my profession.
We need more kids digging in the ground.
Yeah, I'd like to see one of those pamphlets too.
Oh right, you're like a gym guy, right?
I am an anthropologist, archeologist, historian.
Oh.
But yes, I guess you could call me a gym guy, sure.
We've got some uncut gyms, you know,
that you find there sometimes.
But that's not the real purpose.
The purpose is if we don't teach our kids
to be mole people now, they're gonna be really not used
to living without sunlight.
You know, I kind of thought you might be a little kooky,
but I am 100% in agreement with you
on the mole people issue.
Well, we could get started with your two kids.
Do you wanna put them underground?
I desperately want my kids underground.
Yeah, you could use this pamphlet.
I'm gonna teach those little fuckers to dig.
Enough about this underground shit.
I've got my eyes up to the skies.
They call me the Rock Man, if you didn't know that.
The Rock Man?
The Rocket Man.
Oh.
Rocket Man.
Yeah, I think that's someone else.
No, in this universe, there is no piano playing musicians
at all, except Billy Joel.
Anyway.
The only piano playing musician in this universe.
Vincente only listens to Billy Joel.
Bach never existed.
It can't be, right?
There must've been a piano player at some point.
Hey, Becca, can you roll a 50-50 up and down roll for me?
If he knows what's good for him.
So if you roll under 50, it'll be a luck success.
If you roll 50 or over, it'll be a luck failure.
Wolfgang Amadeus who?
Those words mean literally nothing to me.
How'd you roll, Becca?
Oh, sorry, I thought someone else was rolling.
Oh, no, sorry.
47.
That is, hell yeah, that is a success.
And so one of the cleaners comes down
and you see that they open up the front door
and walk over to the van
and they go into the back of the van.
If you continue watching, they pop out of the van
and they're smoking a cigarette
and they get on their phone and start chatting with someone.
I slip out the limousine Escalade
and I creep up behind them
and I wanna attack by jumping
from flat footed on the ground to onto their shoulders
and put them in a headlock, because I'm pretty small.
Okay, would you rather roll athletics
or unarmed combat for this?
I would like to roll the same thing, doesn't matter.
A classic would you rather?
Yeah, I wish there was hard success in this game
because I rolled a 12 under 50.
Nice. Nice.
They failed on their check,
so you can easily jump.
Meat Hook, they start sniffing the air as you approach,
but don't look back in time
and suddenly there's a tiny little dirty person
on this cleaner's back and they're on their phone.
Cleaner's worst enemy.
I squeeze their throat with my little arm
until they can't yell anymore.
Okay, go ahead and roll damage.
So that'll.
I squeeze with my little arm.
Someone who can't yell.
Go ahead and.
Wait, my damage is one D4?
Yeah, one D4 minus one,
and I'll give you an additional D4
because you snuck up on them.
I rolled a four on the first one
and a four on the second one.
This die is busted.
That's, was it minus one for each die?
It is, so with six hit points,
that actually takes down half of their hit points
in one fell swoop,
and they failed their constitution check to stay conscious,
which works out quite well for your plans.
As this person hits the ground
and their cell phone with it smashes onto the ground
and you just hear a voice coming out.
That's like, Dorothy, Dorothy, Dorothy.
It was a woman?
Yeah, it was a woman that you jumped on.
I feel like I've, you know, our sisterhood.
I betrayed her.
Well, too late.
Yeah, but you won one for the class struggle.
She's a-
Those cleaners.
I know, but urchins. City cleaners.
Urchins are pitted against the working class.
Yeah, but she's got a leg up on me.
I see what you're saying.
Vincente walks over and does she have like a key ring?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You see that there is a key ring
with basically some normal keys,
as well as some like scan cards
that are attached to this ring.
And you see this phone also on the ground that-
Dorothy, Dorothy, should I, what do I do?
I look at Vincenzo, whatever your name is.
Close enough.
Should I pretend to be her?
Hold on.
Yes.
He rolled to say that.
You had to roll to see
if she should do the name of the podcast.
It could pretend to be people.
No, you can't do that.
Barrel down the camera.
Hi, it's sorry, I think I need a rest.
I was going to say it's me, Dorothy, but I made that one in.
Convince her.
Oh my God, Becca, please roll disguise.
Great.
Yeah, the skill you didn't take.
I added nothing to this skill.
Okay, so that's a 56 and I have a 10%.
That's a big failure.
Oddly enough.
The voice on the other end of the phone is like,
yeah, okay, all right.
Well, I have to take a nap in my van now.
Okay, Dorothy, sleep well.
Wait, can you remind me what we were just talking about?
And that's the scariest thing
this person on the other end has ever heard.
A different voice than their friend, Dorothy,
has taken the phone, says that,
and you hear a deadline on the other end of this.
I think I got away with it.
Very good performance there, Meathook.
Thank you, doctor.
You're going to be a really valuable asset
to the family after this, if you survive.
We don't even know why the cleaners were here.
This kid's going to get us all killed.
Things are really turning around for me.
I already get to be somebody's basement troll.
We're friends, a guy with spats on his shoes,
and this guy's, he's going to let me teach his kids
to dig on the ground.
You really ingratiated yourself with this group.
And to think we almost killed you.
What?
He thinks to himself.
He says out loud.
You've got an interior monologue problem, I think.
It's just coming out.
No one ever tells me no.
Okay, glad we're friends.
He starts swinging the key ring around his finger
and just kind of jaunts into the open door
that Dorothy came out of.
Did we take Moses up on getting
some laminated name tags printed out?
Yeah, what did you want on those?
Mrs. Milk Woman.
No, I don't know.
What do you think I should write?
Maybe not that, maybe.
Nobody looks at these things too hard.
Just give me a normal name, you know, like Meat Hook.
Milk Hook.
Milk Hook is perfect.
Mine just says Milk Hook one way.
They'll never know who it is.
I'd like my badge to say I'm a cleaner named Dorothy.
A well-timed flashback.
Oh, do you read minds?
Are you going with cleaners?
Are you going with some sort of governmental agency?
What kind of cover would you have?
Bug spray?
I think I just want to be a milk tech.
Classic milk tech.
I'm a milk tester.
I always infiltrate dairy offices as a milk tech crew.
That's right.
So classic milk tech group here.
You got your tester and three texts.
Yeah, and like Luke said,
the door is open and unlocked as you go over there.
I think you're the only one over there with the door open
as you call back to the rest of the group.
Hey, door's open.
Jimmy, can you do something about this body
that I incapacitated?
You got to learn how to deal with those mistakes
on your own.
Damn it, okay.
I put my arms under the armpits
and try and drag her into the back of the van.
Drag her into the van, just like that.
You're a natural.
You're a good father.
Thank you.
You teach, you don't do for it.
You know, you got to teach me to fish.
Hers says milk, hers says milk tech,
your name tag says bean dad.
Bean dad?
I just learned what this was today.
Oh no.
Bean dad's a wild internet.
Oh, I remember bean dad.
It's pretty sad.
When she says, teach me to fish, fish face pops his head off.
Now you fish face.
Okay, sorry.
Wait, fish face?
Yeah.
You remember that time we were sitting on that dock?
Looking at the moon.
Nevermind.
It can never work.
Yeah, you're right.
Okay, bye.
Get back in the front seat next to Goomba.
Hey, get over here, Miwok, okay?
All right, let's do it.
Come on, let's hang out.
Okay, Miwok, all right.
Hey, Goomba, start turning the car around.
It's going to take a while
and we're going to have to get out of here quick.
That's like a 36 point turn.
I would imagine had I ever seen a ridden in cars before.
Wait, hold on, kid.
That's exactly right.
I think you're a natural.
Wait, are you some kind of math nerd?
No, it's just that, okay, it sounds silly,
but the spirits speak to me.
I think they're from another planet,
but it's more like another dimension.
I got a pamphlet about it.
Here.
Let's review this pamphlet.
Well, maybe we should go into this dairy farm
before whoever was on the line to Dorothy
comes looking for her.
No, what do these spirits say?
As Vincenti walks into Holy Cow Farms,
he reads aloud, just sometimes spirits talk to me.
Oh, nice.
Fascinating.
Cool, kid.
You're a little out there,
but I haven't seen anything in these pamphlets
that would disqualify you from a career
in extensive stretch limousineery.
As you guys are looking at the map on the wall
of this office building inside,
it's just got the different names
on which floors they're on.
And you see that Holy Cow Farms is on the eighth floor
of this building, and there are 12 floors total.
If I look at these other businesses
in having known Hargrave and being a colleague,
are there any other businesses that stand out
as maybe something else that he would have been
maybe here to look for or into?
Interesting.
Go ahead and roll.
While I think of something.
Yeah, exactly.
Makes a lot more sense than what I had.
I rolled a 49 on a 50 anthropology is what I rolled.
Okay, yeah, so.
For being aware of the profession.
Not that I'm using an anthropological skill.
With all of your knowledge of the field of anthropology.
Which includes all the articles about Dr. Hargrave
that he's obsessively like,
he knows the man through his study.
I mean, you see there's like a dermatologist
on the first floor, there's a cafe on the second floor,
on the third floor, there's a psychic
holding the same floor as a kid's play land.
And on the fourth floor, there's a massage parlor.
On the fifth floor, there's a karaoke place.
There's a bunch of places, none of which stand out to you.
But you're confident that whatever he was looking for
connection wise, it's probably at holy cow farms.
The kids, they're training to be psychic.
Now we know, he was here for the milk.
Which is what the handler had circled
in the name of the scenario.
I bet that's just a red herring.
And on the seventh floor, it says psychic kids.
Psychic children.
Psychic kids in adult play bed.
Play bed.
It just has bigger, it's a ball pit, but with bigger balls.
It's a child's sidekick in a disgusting ball pit.
It's not a bigger pit, it's the balls that are bigger.
Yeah.
Yeah, the other tracks.
One adult fits in at a time.
Does Trolley's cleaning service
have an office in the building?
No, they seem to have been here cleaning.
Good question.
I've done a little detective work.
These cleaners?
Probably cleaning.
Yes, very good.
Very good deduction, I see why we brought you along.
And as you all get into the elevator,
you see the same kind of sign
with all the different listings for the floors
as well as the buttons on elevators
where you click them to make it go up.
There's also the closed door button,
but it doesn't do anything.
Hey look, there's no 13th floor button in this one.
Yeah, you can't put a 13th floor button in an elevator.
No, especially if there's only 12 stories to it.
And he clicks the eighth button.
I have to go pee really bad, I'm sorry.
Hold it.
Okay, sounds good.
So the elevator doors open and you see a dark office.
We're gonna use the layout for the office office.
Tight.
So in front of you, you see-
A UK or American.
Good question.
I don't know the layout of the UK one nearly as well.
Pretty similar.
That makes sense.
Based on the scripts of the first season.
And so you see the round desk ahead of you,
coat rack on the right.
And yeah, the lights are off.
There seems to be no one here.
You fumble around with the keys.
You're looking at that all through the glass door.
Looking around the keys,
you see that one of the key cards is for Holy Cow Farms.
He sticks it in the keyhole and turns the key.
The light turns green, door opens.
On the other side, you hear the van.
Way outside running still.
It's a loud van.
It's a really loud van.
When the windows are open, it's hot, it's July.
They're trying to air it out.
I'm glad the windows open on the eighth floor
of this building.
It would make my job a lot easier
if I came here to do my normal job.
Oh, what sort of line of work are you in?
Window cleaning.
And you find that to be easier with the windows open?
Some strange world window cleaning.
I guess I've never thought about it much.
It must be.
Hold on.
With these windows open,
I wonder what they're trying to air out.
Can I do a check for smell?
Yeah, absolutely.
Go ahead and roll alertness or search.
Let's see.
Search.
Nope, it's a 56.
And I needed a 50.
Damn.
Sniffing the air, meat hook,
you smell something burning or burnt.
And Vincent is smoking a cigarette right next to you.
Okay.
There's a thick smoke next to you.
Obviously share the information.
And you notice that there's a trash can nearby
with a bunch of burnt popcorn that's been tossed into it.
Vincent would like to do a smell with his eyes around.
Yeah, I kind of figured this is a,
there's no one in here that you can see.
So this is going to be kind of an exploration kind of thing.
What are you looking for?
Where are you going?
I'm just kind of wandering through
and just like looking for blood.
What did you roll?
He's just not looking too hard.
Well, you don't find any blood.
Jimmy lets out a huge sigh and he's like,
all right, I'll teach you how to smell.
And he's going to roll an alertness nine.
Yeah, with a nine,
your sniffer smells the exact same cigarette smoke
and burnt popcorn that the others have been smelling.
But your alertness pass shows you to one of the desks nearby
that you see some paperwork strewn about.
And you notice, oh, this is-
It's covered in blood that he missed.
It's hand prints all the way up.
Big bloody arrows on the floor pointing to the desk.
This is help.
No, you see Dr. Brock Hargrave's desk
here at Holy Cow Farms.
You see a picture of him.
You see lots of papers all over his desk
that have his name on them.
And there is a computer at his workstation
as well as a large file cabinet.
Yeah, you're at his desk.
You see that there are probably what,
like 14, 16 desks around the office and little pods.
This guy sat in Dwight's desk.
Nice.
Yeah, I pick his phone like of Jell-O, toss it aside.
Doc, I think you better get over here
and look at some of these files.
Yes, I'm very curious what Brock Hargrave was doing
here at Holy Cow Farms.
And you see a picture of him holding up this artifact
on this expedition that you are in the picture,
you were in the expedition,
but the way he's holding out his arm in gleeful triumph
is blocking your face from being seen in the picture.
Look, see, this is me and Brock.
I promise, that's me there.
You can't quite see my face,
but I was once a person who would go
on these expeditions like this.
It's him, Meat Hook, I was there.
Oh yeah, yeah, no, you got the kind of same chunky middle.
Yeah, I see.
Yes, yes, yes, the chunky middle, yes.
Stand aside, let me look,
and I start rummaging through his papers.
Rummaging through his papers, I'm gonna go pee.
I have to.
Yeah, I was just joking earlier when I said don't pee.
I'm very sneakily eating.
Do it less sneaky.
You want a mukbang?
You don't know about mukbangs?
No, I do.
We know.
The whole idea, really, I dislike.
You asked for it.
Crunch.
You can chew as lot as you fucking want.
Boy, that's a whole lot of papers.
It's taking me quite some time to get through these.
Read all his notes while he's gone.
We'll just totally ruin the adventure
and say go exactly where you...
Skip to the last page to see who did it.
Now that's the way to choose your own adventure.
I choose to win.
I'm not gonna let a stupid book beat me.
That's what we call Zach.
Becca, I saw that you played Bleak Prospect
with the Glass Cannon crew,
and it was like a week after we had just got done playing it
with Scott Dorwood, the guy who wrote it.
And it was really fun to see you guys do
a totally different...
Oh man, yeah, that was a Bleak one.
That was so fun.
I can't believe you played with Scott Dorwood.
That's amazing.
It was super cool, yeah.
We've played with him a couple of times now.
He's run us through some of his stuff.
He's like our podcast grandpa.
I played with him once.
It hasn't come out yet though.
Did you guys play some Call of Cthulhu?
On an award-winning podcast.
Oh, an award-winning podcast you say?
They won best podcasts at the Innies.
Nice.
Was it on The Daily?
It was The Daily.
I played Call of Cthulhu.
I'm Michael Barbaro.
This is Call of Cthulhu.
Here's what else you need to roll today.
Love it.
Boy, it's taken you quite a while
to shuffle through all those papers.
There's just a lot here, it's a lot to get through,
but I'm not seeing exactly...
Emma?
Lights start going off.
Red lights illuminate the entirety of this office.
And a small voice says,
Hello, an intruder has been found here.
Please call the security company if this is an alarm.
Hello, an intrusion has been found here.
Please call security if this was a mistake.
Jeremy, I'm going to try this again.
I've never heard a more confused automated message,
but I'm going to give it a try
and I take the phone out of the jello and press like those.
It says call security if it's a break-in.
If we don't call, the security won't come?
You're right.
I think you're right.
That is correct, yes.
That's what they said.
That is what the voice said very explicitly, yes.
Those were great instincts, Meathook.
I hang up the phone.
Okay, wow, we really dodged that bullet.
Phew, that was a close one.
Wow, I'm not used to all these indoor lights.
Pfft.
With the flashing red lights
continuing to illuminate your search,
I need everyone who is searching
to go ahead and roll a search check for me.
We'll see what you find in this place.
Ooh, a crit pass.
It's a 22 on a 60.
Well, that will fucking do it, huh?
Vincenty regular passes as he smiles,
knowing that this building
bought one of his security systems.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Meathook fails.
You know, computers, not my thing.
Are you doing the Zoolander thing on one of them?
And the pages are too big.
Eight and a half by 11,
I need a four by six square leaflet.
I love that.
Scott, you might have a future
in the printing industry too,
if limousining doesn't work out.
Well, thank you.
You've learned a lot about leaflets in your time.
Well, you know, I dabble.
I dabble in zines.
How long have you been dabbling in the anarchy scene?
No, zines with a Z.
Oh, zines.
Zines, which is part of the anarchy scene.
Oh yeah, all my life, baby.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Okay, so Shelly St. Blythe,
with your critical success,
we're going to come back to you.
Okay.
The success was Vincenti Boeri.
Yes?
Yes.
Thank you.
As you're going through the desk,
you're kind of feeling around
and you feel underneath,
there's this kind of wooden piece that is sticking out.
And when you flick it,
a false bottom comes out from the main drawer of this desk.
When it pops down,
you see it's full of notes about things
that have been brought to Trigate Supply.
You see a map of the city with little dots poking around
in a specific kind of layout at the Zeitgeist,
which is an abandoned space needle here in the city.
That's cool.
Yeah, it is.
Shout out to Dylan B from Deadwood, South Dakota,
for giving us the Zeitgeist.
Nice.
And while we're here,
shout out to Zakharov Salyer,
another $10 up patron for Trigate Supply.
And finally,
you see a handwritten note scrawled on the bottom corner
of one of these pages that says,
Strummer's Crystal, question mark.
Doctor, you know almost as much as this guy,
but definitely not as much about crystals
and stuff found in the earth.
What's this Strummer's thing?
Did you say Strummer's?
You would know that there is a shop in town
called Strummer's Resonating Crystals,
and it is owned by Aaron Strummer.
Shout out to Dale Armont from Arkansas.
Yee-haw.
The land of actual crystal shops.
The land of crystal shops and holy cow farms.
Yeah.
Whoopee.
Yes, that's Aaron's establishment.
That's where I do most of my gym shopping.
What could Hargrave want with a gym shop that I frequent?
Is he trying to do me in?
Is he trying to finish me off for good?
Or maybe just prank you.
He really likes to mess around.
I mean, I think you gotta just let this guy stop having...
Obviously we have to finish this mission,
but in general,
this guy needs to have less space in your head.
Shelly needs a minute to clear his head,
and he walks off into the other room
and walks directly into the security room
with some TVs around and different like VHS tapes
lining the wall with different dates on it
and tiny little security TVs that you could play them on.
Nobody here though?
There's nobody here now.
You just walk right into this room.
Looking around,
it just seems to be looking at holy cow farms only,
not the rest of the building.
I kind of turn...
There's only like three cameras in here.
I kind of turn to the rest of the room.
I believe I found the nerve center
for the security operation.
We might be able to see what may have happened that day
that Hargrave left and his coworker disappeared.
Well, if the security system is all my security system,
it's probably not gonna work great,
but we can try.
But it looks so expensive.
It does look expensive, yes.
It is expensive.
It is very expensive, yeah.
You guys keep having this conversation
as the red lights are just like blinking and flashing.
Vincenzi just makes a call.
The lights...
Roll bureaucracy real quick, Vincenzi.
Crit fail.
Oh shit, I thought it was a crit pass.
22 on a 10.
Very cool.
Is there something better than bureaucracy
you could justify?
I'm sure there is.
How about...
Really feels like it would be bureaucracy.
You seem like you're really trying
to come up with something.
Italian.
It's an Italian security system.
And I speak to the security guys in Italian on the phone.
I'm gonna go with a no.
This is one of those excellent times
when you have to put your foot down and say no.
I love saying yes.
Not a chance in this case.
As you call your own security company,
they have your direct number.
So someone picks up there.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, no one's breaking into the building
that Holy Cow Farms is in.
So turn off the alarm.
Oh, okay.
No, what do you mean?
How do you know?
What do you mean?
Who called you?
I'm sorry to kind of bark up the ladder,
but I feel like maybe following orders
isn't what you hired me to do.
You hired me because I'm a small individual
who thinks of myself, you know?
Damn it.
You'll never make that mistake again.
Fuck.
And he hangs up.
I think you gotta kill that guy.
Fantastic.
Oh, hey, that might be your first job out of here.
Oh.
I call back and get that guy's name.
I thought you were offering this kid
a legitimate job and moon rocks.
Yeah, I've never killed before.
It's not really my thing.
God willing, you'll never have to.
Forget I said anything.
We'll talk about it afterwards.
And then he just writes down the guy's name
that was on the phone.
We're gonna have a real wacky dynamic
when we're three grandfathers living.
Yeah, wack.
It's Shelly's family.
Exactly wacky.
The rat that lives in the basement.
It's a sitcom.
Dinner's ready, basement rat.
As you guys are having this conversation.
Broccoli again.
Shelly St. Blythe.
Now, now.
Shelly St. Blythe has been dutifully going through
the different VHS cassettes and finding the day
that is just from two days ago.
The day that was the last time
that Dr. Brock Hargrave had come into Holy Cow Farms
and the day that his coworker did not ever clock out.
And you see on the security footage,
the two of them around, I don't know, 3.30,
walk into the kitchen area where there's no camera present.
Damn it.
It's so important to have a camera in the kitchen.
You gotta see who steals your yogurt, I imagine,
if you have a refrigerator.
That's the prime place where most office thefts occurs,
the kitchen.
And except for bathrooms, it's where most accidents occur.
Yeah.
And you see Dr. Brock Hargrave at Holy Cow Farms.
He is wearing the exact same clothes
that you've always seen him in.
He is in full-blown field archaeologist gear
working at this office.
And a cowboy hat?
Yep, cowboy hat included.
And when he walks out of this kitchen area
back into frame, into the office,
he is holding an open yogurt container.
The spoon is just like hanging limply in his other hand,
his mouth agape as it looks down.
And the hand with the spoon in it kind of rubs at his belly,
looks up directly into the security camera,
turns around, looks back at the room where he came from,
looks back at the security camera, nervously smiles,
looking at his belly and rubbing it continuously
as he walks back.
And is this the last time we've seen
this the friend appear again on cameras?
For the rest of that day and for the next day,
as you skim through, you do not see this coworker.
Well, he fucking ate him.
Shelly, you know this guy.
Is that his normal sort of behavior?
I've never seen how he reacts to yogurt himself,
but no, in general, he does not rub his belly,
satisfied after a meal.
The only time I ever saw him rub his belly like that
was when he ate a man.
As he is wont to do.
The more alarming thing is that his friend did not re-emerge.
That friend could still be somewhere in that kitchen
as we speak.
Let's go open the fridge.
As you guys walk over to the kitchen,
you hear sirens in the distance through the open windows
of the eighth floor of this office building.
Oh, right.
That time we called security
and then they clearly knew we were lying.
And that other time where I took the phone
and pretended to be someone.
And now I'm thinking maybe she knew
I wasn't pretending to be people so good.
As we all look into the camera.
Everyone, Jim's the camera, since we're here.
So quick search the kitchen before we've run.
I can show y'all how to climb down a fire escape.
What's the fastest way to the sewers?
You are definitely going to be able to get out of here
cleanly if you leave now.
If you search the kitchen, you're going to maybe risk it.
Just like a quick pop open the fridge
to see if there's not a body in there.
Oh, there's no body in the fridge.
All right, let's get the fuck out of here.
Vincenty pulls his gun out of his briefcase
and wants to look around just a little harder.
Okay, are the rest of you staying or going?
I'll scope things out from the roof.
Even though, let me tell you,
the fastest way to the sewer is through the toilet.
Since you asked.
Vincenty agrees, he's like.
Vincent.
We'll flush ourselves down the toilet to escape the cops.
They'll never expect it.
In a place like this,
they might have an industrial sized one.
They got cows here.
For Kevin.
They've got cow shitters here, I'm sure of it.
Here in the office office,
on the eighth floor of this office building.
Yes, definitely.
Well, yeah, that's why there's not cow shit everywhere.
That's exactly right, because the cow shitter,
the single one.
Okay, so are we flushing ourselves down this cow shitter?
Are we running out the back door?
Looking at this slightly large toilet,
do you think, I don't know if I'm gonna live.
Vincenty wants to look in the kitchen first.
Go ahead and roll search, I suppose.
Yeah, he thinks back to all of the crimes
he has cleaned up in kitchens.
Natch.
And he's like, I've never committed a crime
in a kitchen, I guess.
We can't hear you, we're far down the cow shitter.
That's right.
Wait, where'd you guys go?
You guys take off running out of this office,
closing the door behind you.
Is anyone trying to clean up any of the mess
that you've made since you've been here,
shoving everything kind of back where it was?
The only mess would be Hargrave's desk, right?
That's right, yeah.
Then yeah, probably as we're running past it,
he would try to at least close up the secret panel
that had the stuff inside it.
Done.
And you guys head down the hallway,
you're taking the stairs to the elevator.
Smart, elevator's out when the alarm's on.
I'll meet you guys down there, I'm taking the elevator.
No, I'm not really.
You click the button.
I comically grabbed the doctor by his shirt,
falling down the stairs.
Eight floors down.
Go ahead and roll athletics.
Well.
Everybody, everybody, everybody, athletics.
This is what I'm made for.
Nope.
With the doctor on my back, I trip.
Oh no, did we all fail?
I failed.
I forgot to eat any food for days.
For some dry ramen.
And now I'm out of energy.
Vincenti passes.
Oh, he just fucking dies?
Oh, wait.
You definitely run down the stairs easy peasy
and you look back and we're all just like
hanging off the railing in awkward angles.
Just exhausted, covered in flop sweat
as you've made it down the end of this
un-air conditioned stairwell in July heat here in the city.
It is sweltering and you all are dripping mops
when you arrive at the bottom.
In the meantime, I turn around and saw
that they were not gonna make it out quick enough.
So, Vincenti runs out the door they came in.
Yep.
Runs a couple streets down and fires off
a couple shots on his gun.
That is a long turn that you just did.
Yeah, you ran two blocks.
A block away.
I wanna draw attention elsewhere.
Okay, sounds good.
So, Vincenti, you are a block away,
away from the parking lot
and you are firing your gun in the air
as the rest of you get into the...
To like the level five is on the wall.
It feels a lot faster when you take the elevator.
Trust me, it's not.
This way is a lot speedier.
I feel like I should have been able to do this.
This is the thing I'm good at.
Yeah, me too.
But we've got the doctor care like stretched between us.
Oh yeah.
Believe it or not, I'm pretty fit for my age.
I just am having trouble today.
65.
Okay.
I've never been in that good a shape.
I just got lucky today.
Which explains why you are far off.
You see sirens in the distance, they turn
and as they're heading down the street
that would lead them to the parking lot
for this exact reasoning, they hear the gunshots
and immediately make a turn
and begin heading in your direction.
You also see the stretch Escalade
pull up to the front of the office building.
I ran in to grab my Jeep.
You sprint across the parking lot to your Jeep
as these sirens are getting closer
and they are barreling down on Vincente Bowery.
He puts his gun back in his briefcase
and just walks towards the Escalade casually.
I mean, you did a sacrifice move for the other three
and so the security car pulls up in front of you
and the window rolls down and I want you to roll
a charisma real quick right off the bat.
Actually, no, don't roll.
Tell me what your charisma is.
Passive.
80.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, could my 80 athletics have gotten me
a passive success to go down the stairs?
No.
And so the security guy rolls down the window
and is like, hey there mister, did you see anyone
firing off a gun up in the air over?
And he points right to where you just were
like two minutes ago.
Bitch face?
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I saw, it was a super, super tall guy
with like super long hair and really huge long fingernails
and he wasn't wearing any clothes and he screamed,
I'm gonna run all the way that way.
And he took off running in the opposite direction
of where I, I heard him say he's going that way.
I said, I'm getting way far away from him, he's scary.
And so that's why I'm walking this way.
Anyway, you better go get him.
I think with your 80 charisma and just seeing
the vision of you.
And it was such a good lie.
It was such a good lie.
Also, this was before I started hiring smart people
to work for me and this was just one of the goons
that works for my security company.
Yeah, the inside of every one of the security cars
has a picture of you hanging from the rear view mirror
to remind them who they work for.
And the logo is like a badge with his face on it.
And he's like, oh, oh, you're, wow, I didn't think
I'd get delicious information from my boss
not like tonight.
You better go catch him.
And immediately pedal to the metal
and press his boss.
I can't do everything around here.
Perfect getaway.
Clean as a whistle.
You see, you see there's the van.
There seems to be like some rummaging about
in the cleaning van that is parked right outside
the front of this office building as you're walking over
to meet the stretch escalate that is now meeting you
in the parking lot.
Did any like mops or brooms happen to fall out
of the back of that van when the doors were open
during the struggle?
Dozens.
Multiple dozens.
It is, you know, an office building.
There's a lot of cleaning.
A lot of sweeping up, a lot of mopping.
You need a different broom for each room.
I mean, yeah, the van, the cleaning van was open
at one point.
Yeah, and dozens of mops and brooms fell out.
I grab, I grab a broom.
I know that this isn't how car doors work,
but I stick it in the, in the handle.
So she can't get out of the back of the van.
Oh, is that what the rummaging was?
I thought the police were another like detail.
No, just someone coming to inside.
Gotcha, gotcha.
So I do that and it works.
Oh, congratulations.
I want to talk through the door.
Hey, Dorothy.
You guys are now pulled up next to this cleaning van
and you've pulled up in such a way to where
that she can't get out of the driver's side,
which is the seat that she's kind of gotten herself into.
And she's looking at you kind of horror,
trying to figure out whether she should roll
down the window or not.
Roll it down.
Have you any Grey Poupon?
I always wanted to say that.
Oh yes.
Very good one.
And she just lifts up a bottle of Evian
and holds it up to you.
Calm down.
Is that poison?
Don't, don't do it Dorothy.
What's the pH?
Cause I can tell you some things.
You see a TED talk about like water levels?
Sweetie, I am your TED talk.
Now tell me, what were you here cleaning up?
Cause I know a company like Trolley's,
they don't do your normal messes.
Do you want a taste of this arm around your neck
one more time?
She rolls up the window quickly.
Don't do that.
Don't do that Dorothy.
Rolling it back up.
Normal cleaning.
Just a regular cleaning, huh?
It breaks down, starts crying.
You guys can roll him it.
Dorothy the kid's right.
You don't need all these brooms and mops
for normal cleaning.
I failed a 19 on a 10.
Damn.
I failed as well.
I failed real bad.
Damn, damn, damn.
Damn, damn, damn, damn.
She seems like she's fine.
She's just crying.
She's like, it's real cleaning.
Well, I don't know why anybody would lie about that.
I don't know what else she can teach us.
No, I'm not a, I'm not doing a TED talk.
I don't have your grapefruit pot.
I just have it in me yard.
That was a joke, Dorothy.
Just a joke.
Okay.
Will you leave?
Yeah.
Should we go to the crystal store?
Should we go to the, the doc's house?
Well, there's also Tri-gate supply.
That is also true.
Good thinking.
Plus this map we got with this space needle.
It's abandoned.
It does seem like his search was concentrated
within that area exactly.
Perhaps we would find more there.
Is any of that stuff near his house?
Oh yeah.
For sure.
People don't go too far out their neighborhood
here in the city, or at least Dr. Brock Hargrave
seems to stay within his area around his house.
I also have a close personal relationship
with Aaron Strummer so I could give him a call
while we're on our way to another site.
All right, let's check out the house first
and you call this Aaron boy.
He is an Aaron boy of sorts, yes.
Now doc, you be real cool when you call him.
Don't get on a rant about Hargrave.
Don't talk about how he's been seen shopping around
where you shop, or do, but just don't,
don't get angry about it.
I was gonna say that's kind of my inroad.
Yeah, that is the entire line of questioning, I understand.
Do you have any of these crystals you can maybe
put your bad negative energy into
before you give him a call?
Yeah, if any of your crystals have been charging.
Oh, I always have them charging
at least when the phase of the moon aligns, of course.
I wouldn't charge a lapis lazuli
on a waxing crescent, of course.
No, that'd be stupid.
Ridiculous, but I do have this tiger's eye here
and it is charged.
I'd say this is the prime time to be using that.
Wait a minute, doc, has he ever met Craig?
He has not met Craig Mile, no.
Perhaps Craig could call as a potential customer.
That's a great idea.
A career-defining performance, yes.
It's gonna be tough, doc, but I know you can do it.
You're a real artist with those things,
no matter how much they get in the way on the missions.
I'll do this, but in the meantime,
we are on our way to Hargrave's home.
Is that what we decided, or was it the Space Needle?
Hargrave's home.
I see the Space Needle is kind of
potentially an epic conclusion.
Yeah.
It seems like a very dramatic location.
Then yeah, so that's on our way then.
Boing, boing.
Strummer's Crystals, this is Arren speaking.
Arren?
Hello, hello Arren.
Yes, no, this is Arren.
Arren, this is a friend of Mr. St. Blythe.
He told me to call you.
Oh yes, that adds up.
Mr. St. Blythe always calls me Arren.
He's a bit of a, you know.
And St. Blythe is giving big eyes to everybody in the car.
Am I on the right track?
Just keep going, just keep going.
Thumbs up, all right.
You are the puppet.
You might have gotten me confused with my brother Arren.
Oh, either one I think works if your last name is
Strummer.
Strummer, and that's the name on the door, right?
That's the one, yes.
Arren Strummer's Resonating Crystals,
though it doesn't say Arren,
just says Strummer's Resonating Crystals above the door
and on all of my marketing.
But you see, I'm a mutual friend there of Mr. St. Blythe
and one Brock Hargrave.
And we were trying to discern if he's been in lately.
What was the name?
I'm not supposed to say these kinds of things,
but I love tea, so spill it if you must.
It's Brock Hargrave.
Brock Hargrave, let me look through.
No, no, I'm not seeing this name anywhere on my list.
Ask him if anything's gone missing lately.
Have you had anything, you know,
that of maybe great value or historical significance
go missing lately?
Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, go Craig, go Craig.
I mean, that's something,
that sounds like something that, you know,
St. Blythe would say, right?
Oh, disguise.
Also, I want the two criminals
and the mercenary to roll criminology.
I would like to roll my puppet skill, thank you.
Yes, please roll your puppet skill.
Oh, fuck.
I got a seven.
That's definitely a pass. Oh, fuck yeah, nice.
I fail a 49 on a 40 puppetry.
Damn, we probably shouldn't have done a FaceTime.
I failed my criminology roll.
He's made the puppet hang up.
Yeah, I failed my criminology roll too.
I guess take off your headphones,
the three of you that are in the room.
And Becca, since you succeeded on your criminology check,
this is knowledge that will just be for you.
Oh, I get a secret.
Wait, you're in the same room?
They're all doing this thing
where they put their fingers in their ears
and then rub them around to make the consistent noise
to not hear my voice.
Excellent.
It also hurts their ears the longer we talk.
So, Becca, it actually makes a ton of sense
that me hook would know Aaron Strummer,
which is Aaron Strummer's brother.
And Aaron Strummer isn't a purveyor of crystals
at the resonating crystal shop.
He is a seller of crystal methamphetamine.
Yeah, I know a guy.
I know, yeah, I know that guy.
That's the guy that I know.
Yep, that's the guy that you know.
And this kind of comes to you
as this conversation is happening on the phone.
Not for me, but many people at the hold
know a thing about that.
So, who is this that I'm speaking to then?
It's Craig Mile.
Yeah, are you sure this isn't some sort of
crystalline knowledgeable man,
some sort of client of mine?
Ask him where his brother is.
I was wondering if I could speak to your brother.
Aaron, let me see if he's here.
Oh, Aaron.
Let me remind you, it's like 9.45 p.m. now at night
and you called the crystal shop.
That's like their busiest hour.
Oh yes, all right, he'll be here.
Yes, he's coming, he's coming.
Hey y'all, who is this?
Oh, it's Aaron, is it?
Yes, Aaron, who called for me?
I think you should give me the phone, actually.
I've got someone here who would like to speak to you.
It's, hang on.
He can see me, it's FaceTime.
Yeah, you just hold the phone right there, doc.
Is that, is this?
You know me, Stromer, but don't say my name.
Oh, nice, intimidation over FaceTime.
Immediately though, like, okay.
You owe me a favor.
Oh, okay, like I owe you a favor after the last time?
Yeah, that wasn't my fault while we went down.
Yeah, telling me that that little fish fella of yours
isn't still hanging about?
You're not still protecting him?
Yeah, we scoot him out of the frame.
Fish face?
Fish face, shut your fucking mouth.
Fish face.
Haven't seen him.
Don't know anything about his whereabouts.
He's not at the hold, that's for sure.
But you know who is?
A lot of your former clients.
Yeah, so what, what's it to you?
All they need is one rock slipped in their water
and they'll be back on the choo-choo train.
You know what I mean?
Yes, I understand what you mean.
What do you want?
I wanna know what you know about Dr. Brock Hargrave,
cause he had some questions for you.
Questions like, can he get some more?
What do you want?
He's trying to get some crystal.
I don't know what you want.
Dr. Brock Hargrave is on the crystal?
Why wouldn't he be?
Yeah, no, I guess we are in the city.
Oh, you think my crystal's not good enough for a doctor?
Should've known better.
Took me a while to kick the habit.
Why would it be any different for some hob-nosing jungle
seeking cat piss smelling cowboy hat wearing guy?
Well, if he smells like cat piss,
he's probably, you know, I don't know.
Maybe that's why he hasn't made another order in a while.
Trying to make his own.
Okay, well maybe tell me when the last order he got was.
I don't know, like two weeks ago.
Weeks, hmm, okay.
Doesn't help me, man.
Doesn't help me.
Y'all got any questions for this fella?
I turn the camera around.
This is everybody in our car, by the way,
in case, don't tell anybody what the place guys call me.
Hello.
Hey, it sounds like you guys are still here.
I'm Jimmy Corrigan, this is Dr. Shelley,
and this is Craig.
There's also a mob man whose name keeps changing.
It's been Vincente the almost the whole time.
Nearly the whole time, but.
Nearly the whole time.
It sounds like maybe you're selling drugs in my city.
Yeah, are you selling crystals or crystal?
I think you want to talk to my brother, Oren, maybe.
He sells crystals.
Yeah, but.
And you sell crystal methamphetamine.
But that was a different conversation
I was trying to have with, you know,
I'm not gonna say a name.
I picked up on it pretty fucking quick,
and we're gonna have to have a separate conversation
outside of this because either I get a cut or you get cut.
That seems fair.
His eyes get pretty big and he's like, good to know.
Good to know.
I will be in touch.
So you've been, what?
You've been selling this shit to Hargrave?
Yeah, so what?
A perversion of crystals.
Aaron, I think you need to tell people around town
that Meat Hook is in with some classy folks now.
I got shackles on my shoes or whatever she said.
Yeah, you can see.
We're a classy bunch.
And if you keep selling, to our friend Meat Hook.
You're gonna what?
Hurt you.
You look like a scary guy.
So I'm not gonna mess with you, okay?
I'm not gonna mess.
In fact, I'll stop.
I'll stop selling drugs.
I don't know, it sounds like maybe we could benefit
from each other.
I'll call you later.
You don't have to stop.
You just gotta cut me in on it.
I'll just keep doing what I'm doing and we'll talk later.
Does he like to do drugs up in a tall tower?
Does he like to do drugs up in a tall,
I don't know what you're talking, I mean,
oh, you're talking about his, the zeitgeist?
You ever go to the zeitgeist?
His crazy, yeah, where he's doing all the digging.
Yeah.
He's doing digging in a tower in the sky?
He's got my children digging at the zeitgeist.
I don't know, last time I went out there,
I was like trying to maybe, you know,
boom, just be a good fella and drive it out to him,
you know, and I happened to see what he was doing out there,
doing some digging with his sharp shovel.
By the space needle?
Yeah, you know, zeitgeist.
Sharp shovel, doc, it sounds like him.
It's a telltale sign, he never leaves home without it.
Would Vincente know if there's a,
like a telescope in this tower?
Oh yeah, there's definitely a telescope in this tower.
Yeah, he really fucking wants to go there now.
Let's go see where he's been doing his ground fucking.
Is it just food?
All my muscles work like swims