Beep bop, beep boop, beep bop boop.
It's Wolf the Robot here to give y'all the scoop.
PTBP 694.2, y'all know the drill
and y'all definitely know what time it is.
But wait, do y'all actually know what time it is?
Cause I have never once looked at a clock.
I hope we broadcast at a decent time
where people can tune in in mass droves.
Today's Howlin' with Wolf comes from at SexyBaconStrip,
who tweeted about the show and tagged at PretendingPod,
a delicious, smoky, and salty thing to do
if I do say so myself.
They right.
Howdy, Wolf, just a heads up.
Ever since all that weird stuff
started here in contention,
the dumpster behind Al's Tires and Tiger Sanctuary
has turned into some Grade A quality eats.
Much like this podcast, it's got all the goo and slime
in all the right places.
Really though, this podcast has become
one of the main things I look forward to.
It's so great I even got my own slip case for Delta Green
and I can't wait to put my players through hell.
Thank y'all and fuck Jeff Bezos.
Thank you for writing SexyBaconStrip.
I ain't never met a bacon strip
that I didn't find at least somewhat erotic.
I appreciate you saying those positive things,
but the way that none of those positive things
were directed at y'alls truly
specifically has me feeling some kind of way.
Time to hit up Al's Tires and Tiger Sanctuary
for some delicious rubber
and possibly endangered mystery meat.
Remember to tag us in some nice things on the social things
if you want us to probably read a thing that you said.
Spread the love, spread the goo,
and remember to spread the word of wolf too.
Now prepare a warm spot on the floor
to vore even more of this hardcore lore with Gorgolore
and I'll roar and roar for an encore
from the troubadours that I adore.
It's kudzu with no backbone.
In a high school classroom,
the analog clock on the wall said 3.30
and the chalkboard said detention.
Sat at the only occupied desk in the room
was a boy of 13 or 14.
Jeremy Pettymore wore a denim cutoff jacket,
a raggedy thin Western shirt, wrangler jeans,
some punky boots, and a perpetual scowl.
There was a knock on the door
and two more boys of a similar age entered the room.
The first was Ken Krenkelhoff,
wearing a letterman jacket bought for him by his dad.
Ken was tall, fit, had great hair,
and walked with his head held high.
The teacher greeted Ken warmly,
then happily acknowledged the second boy, Ash Hornbeam,
with his black, messy hair, white t-shirt,
cheetah print vest, acid-washed jeans,
and scuffed tennis shoes.
The teacher administering detention
was confident the new arrivals didn't belong,
but Ken said they wanted
to keep their friend Jeremy company.
The teacher was reluctant, but said,
"'These two boys are allowed to do whatever they want.'"
Jeremy said his schoolwork necessitated his friends,
so if he was supposed to get anything done,
he had to go with them.
The teacher was relieved to have an excuse to end detention,
and Jeremy flipped him off on the way out.
The young Pettymore asked the other two
if they were ready for the woods that night,
and Ash opened his jacket
and revealed a bunch of water dynamite.
Ken seemed a bit reluctant, but agreed to go,
since this year was their last hurrah.
Ken would have to meet them in the woods, though,
since his mom would still wanna drive him there herself.
As they walked through the hall,
an upperclassman asked them what they were up to that night.
Jeremy said they were going to the woods,
that's their thing.
Once a year, they go into the woods
to look for some folktale legend called Ol' Madge.
They left Silas Cole K through 12,
slapping the banner sporting their mascot,
a minor, on the way out.
That evening, Ash drove Jeremy to the woods
in his older brother's car.
A 1991 Firebird painted a weird, ugly gold.
They turned onto a dirt road,
and a squirrel ran into the path of the car.
Ash was able to quickly swerve and miss it.
They pulled into the gravel parking lot
for the contention woods,
and there were two cars in the lot already.
One had a boot on the back left wheel,
and the other had a notice taped on the driver's side window
that threatened to boot if it wasn't moved.
There was also a Ford Bronco with a lift kit on it
over next to the small, usually unoccupied,
park ranger shack at the entrance to the woods.
Ash left a note under his windshield wiper
that said, please don't boot my car, signed Ash Hornbeam.
They checked if the two cars were unlocked, both were.
In the first car, there was almost nothing,
as if it had already been cleaned out.
In the second car, there was a bunch of camping equipment
and a title for the vehicle,
which listed a Stuart Feldman as its owner,
registered in the city.
Jeremy found some liquor and a pistol.
Ash grabbed some of the camping equipment
and headed over to the shack where he saw an elderly man
wearing a state issued uniform sitting on a stool,
just waking up as Ash approached.
The boys realized this wasn't the normal forest ranger
of contention, he introduced himself as Woodrow
or Buzz for short.
In addition to the normal ranger paraphernalia,
there was a big thing, a hand sanitizer and a board
behind Buzz covered in pictures
and pieces of paper thumbtack to it.
Buzz took out a Polaroid camera, took their pictures,
took down their information, citing a recent string
of disappearances in the woods as his reason
and placed the pictures and information up onto the board.
Ash asked if they could borrow the first aid kit
and Buzz gave it to them.
Ash shot an M80 into the distance with his slingshot
and Buzz about shat his pants.
So he went to the bathroom and Jeremy seized the opportunity
to grab a fire extinguisher, two machetes,
three flashlights and hand sanitizer
and they shoved it all into their bags.
They looked over the missing persons board,
there were 18 missing people,
several of whom the boys recognized.
They saw Stuart Feldman on the board,
he was an older bald British man in incredible shape
with a thick jawline.
He had claimed to be in the woods on business.
Jeremy also saw the keys to both the Bronco
and the shack itself and snagged them.
Buzz returned and the boys asked if they could take a picture
of the missing persons board so they could have
a reference if they ran into any of the people in the woods.
Buzz agreed and gave them a Polaroid picture
of the board of Polaroid pictures, woof.
The two boys gathered their things and headed off
to their usual camping spot on foot.
As they hiked, Jeremy noticed tracks.
It looked like a car and a smaller vehicle,
like a four-wheeler had driven down the trail.
When they arrived at their spot,
there was unusually no firewood waiting for them.
Ash went to chop at a big log
and Jeremy started looking around,
frustrated at the lack of logs.
Ash heard a rustling nearby and saw a man's head pop up
from behind some bushes.
The man made dead eye contact with Ash
and popped back down into the thicket.
Ken Krinklehoff's mom, Krista Krinklehoff,
drove him to the woods in her minivan
and explained she didn't like the tradition
he and his friends had of going to the woods once a year
for their silly game.
Ken said not to worry,
but a baby fox jumped out trying to cross the road.
Ken's mom hid it and crushed the fox without remorse.
They pulled into the parking lot
and saw the same cars Ash and Jeremy saw
plus the 91 Firebird Ash had borrowed.
Ken's mom mentioned how multiple people
who had gone into the woods recently were missing
and she especially wasn't happy
he was going into the woods with Ash and Jeremy.
Ken grabbed his gear, said goodbye,
and headed to the ranger shack.
Buzz introduced himself, took Ken's picture,
asked for his information, and posted it on the board.
After talking about the missing people for a few minutes,
Ken headed off into the woods.
A group of three high school girls
walked into the contention public library.
Judy Krinklehoff, a senior at Silas Cole,
and the older sister of Ken Krinklehoff
still wore the same clothes she bought for freshman year.
She was very anxious, never said the right thing,
and wanted to be in a relationship
with the coolest girl at school,
a rebel who bullied Judy named Elizabeth Liz Lonklin.
Liz wore a leather jacket and Doc Martens,
she smoked cigarettes,
and she was a self-described bitch.
The final girl, Sharon Shadow Berryman,
formerly a popular cheerleader,
was now obsessed with going to graveyards,
funerals, and hospitals
to engage with all forms and stages of death.
Shadow asked Steven Page for the location
of occult books related to voodoo,
and he led them to a small room in the back
with a small sign that read occult.
Inside, they found a book titled Voodoo.
Shadow said they would find what they were looking for
on page 419, and Liz revealed she wanted to torture
someone named Brittany for sleeping with her boyfriend,
all while Judy went on about how beautiful Liz was.
Page 419 described a ritual that must be performed
while surrounded by trees at night.
There were a few ingredients necessary for performing it.
The left pinky toe of a dead squirrel,
dirt scraped from the earth
after it had been stepped on by a menstruating calf,
the blood from a former cheerleader gone goth
who goes to Silas Colquet through 12, and bird pee.
Smash cut to the group leaving the library with the book.
Smash cut to them on the side of the road,
bent over a dead squirrel cutting off its pinky toe.
Smash cut to them in a field,
scooping up dirt under a cow bleeding from its lady butt.
Smash cut to them standing in a parking lot
waiting for a bird to pee slash poo on them.
Smash cut to Shadow scratching herself
with the dead squirrel toe
and dripping her blood into a vial.
Smash cut to two days ago when Shadow told Liz
her boyfriend was cheating on her with Brittany
from Spinkbonk High in the city,
and Shadow and Judy agreed to help Liz
get back at her boyfriend.
Smash cut back to the present,
and the girls were on their way to the woods
with all the necessary ingredients.
Shadow turned onto a gravel road
and a possum walked out in front of the car.
Shadow drove straight for it and crushed it under the car.
She was happy for the possum
since it was in a different place now,
but Judy worried it wasn't going to heaven.
They buried the possum real quick
and then arrived at the contention woods parking lot.
Already in the parking lot were five cars,
the four we expected, plus Krista Krinklehoff's minivan.
Judy freaked out a little
because she saw her mom's minivan
and she was out past her curfew.
Liz and Shadow promised to shove Judy into a ditch
if they saw Krista Krinklehoff,
which assuaged Judy's worries.
An old man wearing a state forest ranger uniform
jumped out and scared the girls.
He introduced himself as Woodrow or Buzz for short
and asked them to fill out some forms in the shack.
Shadow whispered to the rest to not use their real names.
Ash Hornbeam walked over to investigate the bush
after seeing the man's face disappear back behind it,
his ax in hand.
He heard rustling and a chattering sound,
so he ran back to find Jeremy Pettymore,
who was standing at their campsite,
still frustrated at the lack of pre-prepared firewood.
Ash sprinted back and squawked about a man in a bush
by a log making animal noises.
Jeremy readied the gun he found
and Ash led him to the bush.
It was still rustling with movement
and the animal-like noises were still audible.
Ash picked up a long stick and poked at the bush.
Stepping back from the bush was a naked human man
covered in scratches and cuts,
some of which were still bleeding.
He looked at the boys with huge eyes and froze.
Jeremy took out the Polaroid of the Polaroids.
They could tell this was one of the people
who'd gone missing,
though they couldn't quite read his name.
The boys called out to him,
suggested he put on pants and offered to help
with a first aid kit.
The man scampered up to them hastily.
Jeremy pointed the gun at him to no effect.
The man pushed his fingers together,
made sad puppy dog eyes and mewled.
Ash and Jeremy discussed what to do with the animal man
as he sniffed the air and headed to their campsite.
The boys tried to Red Rover him,
but the situation finally sunk into Ash.
He freaked out, backed away and tripped backwards on a log.
Jeremy tried to stop the man alone but wasn't able to.
Both boys had the realization though
that this man did not act or run like a normal human man.
He was too fast.
He was crouched and he used his front legs or arms
to aid his movement toward their campsite.
The boys ran back to their spot,
still holding their weapons.
When they returned,
they saw the man hunched over their bag with food,
going to town on the snacks they brought.
Jeremy cried out for his little Smokies.
After a small tussle between the boys and the naked man,
Ash kicked away the can of Smokies,
kneed him in the face and full nelsoned him
down into the mud, immobilizing him.
Jeremy took a rope, tied him to a tree
and tried to calm him down with more Smokies.
Ash used some hand sanitizer
and headed back down the trail to get buzz.
As Ash headed back to the shack,
the trees around him began to warp.
The trail became nearly non-existent
and he was suddenly looking at a thicket of woods
instead of the trail in front of him.
The sun was going down
and Ash was all by himself
and he had no fucking clue where he was.
Ken Krenkelhoff walked down the trail
and made it to the usual campsite.
When he arrived, he saw Jeremy waving little Smokies
in front of the face of a naked, bloody man
tied up to a tree.
Ken shouted as he entered the clearing,
startling Jeremy Pettymore.
Ken asked if the man could hear him
and if he was all right
and the man made some more chattering noises.
Jeremy indicated this was one of the people
who had gone missing in the woods.
Ash was on his way back to the ranger station to get buzz.
In the meantime, Jeremy was trying to tame the animal man
with tiny meat fellows.
Ken realized that if Ash was going from the campsite
to the ranger shack, they should have crossed paths,
but they didn't.
Ken called out for Ash but stopped
when he looked back at the man and no longer saw humanity.
Only animalistic intent behind the eyes
of this bloody, muddy, tied up naked human body.
Ken freaked out and backed away,
claiming the man wasn't a person.
Jeremy tried to convince him the man was still a man,
but Ken wasn't convinced.
He went back to calling out for Ash's panic rising.
Jeremy wasn't sure why Ken was scared of this man,
whom he had named Rusty.
Shadow, Liz, and Judy were in the contention woods
parking lot talking to Buzz.
Judy worried about her mom
and wondered if she'd also gone missing.
Shadow and Liz calmed her down by suggesting
that perhaps Chris's car was stolen
and so it wasn't actually her that drove it to the woods.
Now back in the shack, Buzz asked the young ladies
to come over and take care of business
so they can be on their way.
They wondered if they should trust the man,
but decided to have their pictures taken anyway.
Glancing around the shack,
they saw various ranger equipment
and the bulletin board of missing people,
as well as a massive jug of hand sanitizer on the windowsill.
Judy furiously pumped hand sanitizer into her hand,
so much so that it overflowed onto the floor.
Liz looked at Judy appalled
and asked Buzz if they could have a machete
to protect themselves from something killing people,
like maybe Judy's mom.
Judy freaked out and started licking the hand sanitizer
from her hands.
Buzz offered the hand sanitizer to the other two girls.
Shadow refused, but Liz put her hand out
and as Buzz started to pump out the hand sanitizer,
she tried to pull her hand away,
but plenty still landed on her,
so she unhappily rubbed it in.
As Buzz pinned all their information and pictures
on the not missing side of the board,
the girls noticed a slight trickle of blood
going down the back of his neck, staining his uniform.
Ash looked around at the ever darkening tree
surrounding him as the sun went down.
He heard a noise and saw a tree
emitting a bright light from a hollow point.
He looked around suspiciously,
saw a trip wire between him and the tree
and carefully avoided it
as he walked up to the light emanating knot.
It was so bright, Ash couldn't see what was inside,
but he knew something was deep in there.
Ash pushed his arm into the arm shaped hole
up to his elbow, felt around, found nothing,
pushed in deeper and when he attempted to pull his arm out,
he felt a great pain on his skin,
like he was noodling a razor sharp catfish
all the way from elbow to fingertip.
Ash pulled out about a centimeter
and the bit of arm revealed only raw muscle and tendons.
It lacked skin completely.
He realized he was trapped
and for the first time in his life,
Ash Hornbeam had no idea what to do.
Shadow told Buzz he was bleeding from his head.
She offered to trade her first aid kit for his machete
and he gladly accepted.
She grabbed the kit in a vial and patched him up
while discreetly taking a sample of his blood.
The group then took stock of their possessions
and headed to their designated camping spot
to perform the ritual.
Upon arrival, there were no rocks
around the designated fire pit
in order to keep the fire contained.
This was very concerning to Judy.
Liz went to find some rocks
and Shadow swayed in the wind to attune with nature.
Judy, worried about her mom
and the pond water she just used to brush her teeth,
suffered a bout of insanity.
She saw reality warp.
Shadow blended into the trees and the ground became the sky.
Judy promptly ran into the woods in her footy pajamas.
Shadow sighed and followed with her machete,
leaping and dancing as she went.
Liz's reality glitched
and she suddenly found herself lost
in an unrecognizable part of the woods.
Behind some rocks, she saw a fit looking bald man
in his forties walking in circles, waving his hands
and talking to himself.
All on the other side of a thick line of white powder.
A branch like sigil was carved into every tree in sight.
Liz tried to get away quietly, but she stepped on a stick
and he beckoned her over to his little camp
with some semi-intelligible,
mostly English accented instructions.
She went over partly because she found him attractive.
He was concerned about two things, the sky turning
and keeping the lady in the wood away.
A tattoo of a stylized H was slightly hidden
on the back of his neck.
After a little more discussion,
Liz decided she was too worried by the situation
and didn't trust him.
She ran away as he shouted,
she was definitely going to get go.
Lost in the woods, Liz Lonklin stumbled upon Ash Hornbeam
stuck in a tree with tears streaming down his face.
They were understandably surprised to see each other.
Ash warned her about the trip wire just in time,
but the helpless situation caused him to lose it
and pull his arm out a little bit more.
The loss of skin was staggering.
He threw up at a sheer panic.
Liz dipped out, shouting for help.
She was leaving Ash alone with the tree once again,
staring at his lacerated, dripping arm.
Judy ran haphazardly through the woods,
but thankfully stopped just before
a suspicious looking pile of leaves.
Shadow almost danced directly into the dubious detritus,
but Judy pulled her out of the way,
revealing the 10 foot deep pit underneath the leaf pile.
Shaken, but not yet broken,
the two headed back to their campsite.
They didn't see Liz, but they did see a raccoon
sitting there eating just like a person would.
The little trash panda indicated that hand sanitizer
should not be used, might be deadly.
Judy looked into the raccoon's eyes,
saw the soul of a human and decided to trust it.
Shadow tottered along with T-Rex arms,
imitating the raccoon as the trio headed back
to the entrance of the woods.
After searching through the woods
in the dwindling twilight, Liz finally found the trail
along with Jeremy Pettymore and Ken Krinkelhoff
at their campsite.
She saw them talking to a feral man,
feeding him little winkies.
She told them Ash was in trouble with a tree
while Jeremy fed Rusty more smokes.
They debated whether or not to take Rusty along
for the search.
Ken finally agreed to it and Liz Lonklin led the party.
Shadow, Judy and the raccoon made their way
back to the parking lot and were confronted
by Judy's mom's voice coming out of the shack.
Judy instinctively ran to get more hand sanitizer
from her mom and succeeded in doing so
despite the raccoon physically trying to stop her.
Krista told the girls that Buzz had asked her
to watch the shack while he went to investigate an argument.
The raccoon indicated they should get the fuck out of Dodge
but Shadow wanted to go back and get Liz.
She persuaded Krista to help her find Liz.
Judy could stay in the shack with the raccoon.
When Shadow and Krista skipped into the forest together,
Judy hit the restroom.
There she saw the limp, neatly folded body
of Ranger Buzz on the floor.
Ken Krinklehoff, Jeremy Pettymore, Liz Lonklin and Rusty
walked through the woods looking for Ash Hornbeam
whose arm was stuck in a tree.
The sun had now gone down and they were in total darkness.
Too far off the trail, the group began to realize
none of them knew where they were.
They walked deeper into the woods
and eventually saw through the moonlight
a picture frame hanging on a tree.
Flashback to Ken Krinklehoff a couple years ago.
He and his friends were out in the woods
on their annual outing to look for Ol' Madge.
He popped away to pee behind a tree
and as he looked up from his stream of urine,
he saw a frame like of a painting
hanging there in the woods.
It looked like nothing was in the frame.
Ken approached and noticed that somewhere along
the edge of this frame, something didn't line up
as if what was behind the frame wasn't the same
as what he could see through it.
He strafed to the side to get a better look
and saw that beyond the frame was a cabin.
Ken walked up to this frame to put his hand through it
but at the last second noticed a trip wire
he was about to step on.
Ken jumped back, grabbed a rock
and threw it at the trip wire.
A giant wooden spear came flying through the canvas
of the painting and stabbed directly into a tree
just missing Ken.
He rushed back to the camp while convincing himself
it wasn't real.
Flashback forward to Jeremy, Liz, Ken and Rusty
standing in the clearing looking at the weird frame.
Ken yelled out for everyone to stop and not go any closer.
He pointed at the ground and next to the frame
there was a trip wire.
He tossed a small log onto the trip wire
and a massive spear shot through the frame
directly into a nearby tree.
Ken shared his memory with the rest of the party
and as they all looked at this frame
they could see a cabin in the woods
through the spear made hole.
Ken snapped, grabbed the spear and raced toward the cabin.
As Jeremy yelled at him to stop,
Ken stepped on a pile of leaves covering a hole
and disappeared into the ground.
Ash Hornbeam stood in the woods terrified.
His arm stuck halfway into the hollow of a tree.
Part of his arm that he could see had been stripped
of every layer of flesh.
The sun finished going down and Ash stood alone
in the moonlight.
He heard the snap of a branch nearby
and out of the trees approached a man
in a black suit, white shirt and bolo tie.
He was a fit man in his late 20s or early 30s
with a glorious mustache and pants
that were a bit too tight.
He flashed an FBI badge and introduced himself
as Agent Kevin.
He asked Ash why he was out in the woods.
Ash said he and some friends come out to the woods
every year to camp and look for old Madge,
a woman in the woods from local legend.
Kevin cursed, thanked him and with a trembling hand
pressed a gun to the back of Ash's head.
Acting on pure instinct, Ash reached into his pocket,
pulled out a lighter and some firecrackers,
lit them with one hand and held them against Kevin's head.
Kevin lowered his gun, grabbed the fireworks
and threw them away.
On closer inspection, Kevin recognized Ash as a local kid
who was celebrated in the community
after he defended his home from a couple burglars.
Flashback!
To a younger Ash Hornbeam sitting on his front porch
wrapped in a crisis blanket,
talking to a contention police officer.
Ash had heard noises in his basement
and it sounded like two men's voices,
one tall and skinny, the other short and fat.
Ash thought they were after his dad's coin collection.
Flashback!
To a few hours before this to Ash home alone watching TV.
On the screen is a commercial for a CD player
Ash desperately wanted but couldn't afford.
So he hatched a plan to steal
some of his dad's rare coin collection.
He tried typing in birthdays into the lock box
that contained the coins and his birthday worked.
Ash took a handful, roughly $600 worth of coins.
Flashback forward!
To the officer asking Ash about the paint cans
hanging from strings.
Ash said he set up traps and tripwires
and told an epic story of utilizing these common objects
to hassle the robbers until they gave up and left.
Flash a bit more forward!
To Ash carrying his new CD player with him
everywhere he went.
Flash fully back forward!
To Kevin returning to the trapped Ash
along with a woman wearing a black suit,
white shirt and a black tie.
She held a machete and she chanted
while she rubbed a hand on the blade.
The woman smiled a cold, vacant smile
behind asymmetrical bangs covering one of her eyes.
Agent Kevin introduced her as Agent Karen
and she immediately lifted the machete above her head
and brought it down through Ash's elbow.
Out of shock, Ash stepped back, looked down
and saw his arm had been cut off.
The end of it was completely cauterized
and the skin around the stump began to grow back
as he watched.
Agent Karen said nothing, just smiled,
turned around and walked away.
Agent Kevin put his arm around Ash
and led him to a black sedan sitting next to a four wheeler
in the middle of the woods.
Through some brush and trees, they could see a cabin.
Shadow and Krista Krinklehoff walked down the trail
and Shadow sang a song about death.
The sun finished setting and they continued to walk
lit only by a flashlight.
Krista said she saw Liz and shot off with the flashlight
into the woods followed by a giggling Shadow.
But then Shadow watched the flashlight go completely dark
and felt a rope tighten around her ankle.
She was hoisted into the air upside down
hanging by one foot.
Krista turned on the flashlight under her chin
like it was spooky story time.
She said, my darling, it is certifiably unfortunate
that your demise is seemingly necessary
despite my finding your demeanor so appropriate
for your kind.
From your personal hymns, I can assume and do hope
that a lack of existence is your preference?
Shadow whispered to herself, finally.
And she watched a long silver tendril grow from the back
of Krista Krinklehoff's neck and then another
and another and another.
The limbs extended towards Shadow's pinoted body
and the camera panned down to show the long shadows
play out the grizzly scene.
One of the shiny tentacles sliced into the soft tissue
on the back of her neck.
Another snapped her head forward and a third reached in
and gripped her spinal cord and ripped it out of her body
delivering Shadow to her finish line, her goal,
her lack of a destination and finally she felt nothing.
The sun had set and as it began to rain outside
Judy Krinklehoff stood at the doorway to the bathroom
and stared at the lifeless folded crumpled body of Buzz.
She could tell by looking around there'd been a tussle
and she found a stick of her mom's favorite brand
of chapstick behind the toilet.
The raccoons stood in the doorway motioning
to get the fuck out of there.
Judy followed the raccoon into the rain into the darkness
and a lightning bolt flashed in the distance.
It was just bright enough to illuminate a blood covered
Krista Krinklehoff walking directly toward her.
The raccoon at Judy's side shivered
and tried to communicate tugging at Judy's arm
but eventually ran away when Judy went to help her mother.
Judy guided her back to the shack to clean up
her blood drenched mother but when she closed the door
Judy felt a pinch on the back of her neck.
She turned and saw her mom's body had crumpled to the ground
and standing in front of her was a small one inch
silver sphere with metallic arms grounding itself
in the walls and ceiling of the shack.
Shiny tendrils reached out, snapped Judy's neck forward
and ripped out her spine shoving itself
into her spinal column.
Judy Krinklehoff was no longer Judy Krinklehoff.
She was an objective based entity
and its current objective was to collect
as many bodies as possible.
After falling into the hidden hole under the pile of leaves
Ken Krinklehoff slid on his back down an earthy viscous slide
for some time until he finally landed in a pit
of cold dirt and perfect darkness.
He was in a small crawl space with what looked like
floor supports though they were translucent tubes
filled with a squamous black ooze that traveled down
from the cabin into the ground below.
Ken also saw a door above him and he cautiously listened
for any sound on the other side.
Ash Hornbeam followed agents Kevin and Karen
to the black sedan and four wheeler hidden in the brush.
There was another agent in the backseat wearing
the same black suit with a white shirt.
The man in his early 30s had buzzed blonde hair
and introduced himself as Agent Kyle.
As Ash looked out ahead of him he saw the cabin
in a small clearing.
Next to the cabin sat a small shipping container
and a large yellow excavator.
A moat surrounded the clearing.
Ash saw movement just outside the moat.
Liz, Jeremy and Ken stopped to talk.
Ken picked up a small log, threw it
and a long wooden spear flew in their direction
and hit a tree.
Ken grabbed the spear, took off running, fell into the
ground and disappeared.
Kevin turned back to Ash and broke his mind
with two sentences.
The woods are full of traps and Ol' Madge,
the local legend the boys searched for annually was real.
Ash couldn't handle it, something snapped,
he bailed out of the car, ran and disappeared
into the night.
Jeremy and Liz stood in the dark of the woods
when they saw Ken disappear into the ground
and it began to rain.
They looked forward, the cabin lights turned on
and they noticed a storage container and a big yellow
excavator next to the cabin all encircled by a moat.
The pair moved forward to investigate the cabin
and found the moat was about five feet across.
Jeremy threw some smokies onto the other side
and held Rusty's feet as he lunged across to grab
the small sausage boys.
Liz crossed Rusty's back without issue but Jeremy
and Rusty fell into the fish filled moat.
They crawled out near Liz, a wet mess.
The trio approached the cabin slowly.
Liz stumbled up the stairs to look through the window
and she saw strange lab equipment and translucent tubes
that ran down into the floorboards filled with a
squamous black viscous goo.
Papers were scattered across tables and a desk
and in the corner sat a large wooden trunk.
Jeremy edged toward the storage unit, opened the door
and saw on one side a closet full of clothes
and on the other side lined up against the wall
the bodies of roughly 15 people hung limply on hooks
from a pole in the back of each neck.
Jeremy turned and screamed at Liz they needed to get
the fuck out of there and the pair bolted across the moat.
As they ran Liz heard a click under her foot.
She tried to stop in time but a giant metal cloth
swung down from the branch above and removed her head
from her shoulders.
Jeremy knew she was dead, he kept running.
Ash Hornbeam also ran through the dark rainy night.
He found the trail and in the distance he saw
Judy Krinklehoff walking toward him.
Ash grabbed her arm and kept running, pulling her with him.
They arrived at his usual campsite.
Ash fell to his knees, gasped for air and told Judy
her brother disappeared into a hole in the ground.
Judy seemed unworried by this news and suggested finding
some large rocks.
Ash continued to panic and freak out and Judy went to go
find some rocks.
Ash considered his options but decided to stay with Judy
for now since he did have a crush on her.
Judy found a huge rock, walked up behind Ash and crushed
his head in.
Ken Krinklehoff crouched in the crawl space under the cabin
lit only by his flashlight.
He gently put his ear to the door above him and heard
a muffled yell in the distance.
It was Jeremy screaming for Liz to get the fuck out of here.
Ken poked his head up through the door.
This was not a cabin, it was a lab.
The same translucent tubes full of black ooze were all
around the room going into the floor and Ken saw the tubes
were coming from small coffin shaped boxes.
There was a desk littered with papers, a bulletin board
and a large wooden trunk.
Ken heard a guttural scream cut short and looked out the
window at the exact moment Liz Lonklin was stopped dead
in her tracks by the decapitation from a massive metal claw.
Having convinced himself that what he just saw could not
have been real, Ken turned back around and investigated
the scene.
He found articles of organization for a new business called
Cole's Orphanage, New School Under Modern Etiquette.
All the other papers were blueprints for an odd looking gun
which seemed to have been recently completed.
There were also plans for small metal spheres one inch
in diameter which were being placed into small human bodies.
Ken took a wary glance at the little coffins.
He opened one and a black viscous goo began pouring out of it
onto the table and floor.
Inside the coffin there sat the body of a two year old
that was not quite fully human looking as if it was being
3D printed and was not yet finished like a face with a
plastic bag over it.
Ken freaked the fuck out and ran for the front door
of the cabin.
Jeremy Pettymore ran desperately through the woods
and eventually found Judy Krinkelhoff walking toward him.
Judy said she didn't know what to do since the other girls
had left her alone.
The two decided to head back to the ranger shack.
Jeremy took the lead.
Judy pulled out the machete she was hiding and lunged
at the Pettymore boy but she slipped on the muddy rocks
below, fell face first onto the machete and split her skull
wide open enough for Jeremy to see a small one inch
in diameter silver sphere in the middle of her head.
Black ooze began to leak onto the trail and Jeremy ran.
Ken stumbled out of the cabin and saw three figures
approaching.
Through the rain and darkness a lightning strike in the
distance revealed the trio.
All wearing black suits with white shirts, two with black
ties and one with a bolo tie.
The tall one had buzz blonde hair, the man with the bolo
tie was shorter, sported tight pants and a thick mustache
and the last was a woman smiling a cold, vacant smile
behind asymmetrical bangs covering one of her eyes.
They saw Ken and the woman began chanting.
Ken turned to rush back into the cabin, his arm reached out
for the door and his hand phased into and through the wood.
He felt an aberrant push in the back and his body too
was forced into the door.
Ken Krinklehoff was trapped halfway in and halfway out
the entrance and exit of this cabin.
His mind worked just long enough to watch the suits
ransack the lab.
One grabbed a bucket of water filled with fish to splash
and repel the ooze.
The other two took some papers in the trunk and they left
but not before the woman chanted once more and ignited
the cabin in unnatural flames.
Ken Krinklehoff died burning part of the cabin
in the contention woods.
Jeremy Pettymore now all alone ran back to the ranger shack
in the parking lot.
He got to the Bronco with the keys he had nabbed earlier
but the car wouldn't start.
He got out and then the heavy rain and darkness of night
he ran down the road toward town.
Behind Jeremy, the black sedan drove furiously into view
and behind it the four wheeler.
As they approached, the four wheeler overtook the sedan
and pulled up next to Jeremy as he desperately sprinted.
Jeremy looked over and the man who drove this ATV
was pretty fit for his early 40s and he wore a black suit
with a white shirt and a bolo tie below a face
with a badass mustache.
He recognized the man as John Lee Pettymore III,
his second cousin.
The two came to a stop and Jeremy waved and tried to hop
on the four wheeler.
John, John, Uncle John, Uncle John.
John stopped, saw Jeremy and his heart sank.
Uncle John, thank God you're here.
What's wrong, Uncle John?
John Lee Pettymore III lifted a pistol
and put it to his second cousin's head.
Jeremy Pettymore, 14 years old, closed his eyes tight,
shaking, he felt the gun against his head trembling.
And then there was nothing.
Now, back to the contention boys.
Clark Bishop, Keith Vigna and John Lee Pettymore IV
and the body of John Lee Pettymore III
woke up, bodies fully in shock, ears ringing,
bellies weirdly satisfied and an uncomfortably savory smell
in their nostrils as their eyes adjusted to see
the inside of a mausoleum splattered in blood.
They remembered everything that had happened to them before
but they seemed to be back in the same physical
and mental state they were in just after meeting
the chanting cloaked old Clark.
According to Clark's watch, it was the day of the funeral
at 1 p.m. again.
Keith ripped his shirt off and found the word Marvin
that had been burned into his chest had been crossed out.
The other names, Tildy on their dominant palms,
Drew on their backs and Maggie on the bottom
of their left feet were still branded
on each of their bodies the same as before.
They wondered whether Marvin would still be dead
and theorized that they'd have to work their way
through the other names as well.
Would they have to kill Maggie and Drew?
And how would they find Tildy?
John called Rosemary, she picked up
and he immediately hung up.
John recalled the vision he'd had the last time
they were at the cemetery.
Keith told the others about the visions he had
while wearing his father's watch.
Clark suggested calling Maggie and reporting
that he'd successfully killed Stan Manstein
but first he tried to summon old Clark.
He only succeeded in driving himself into a rage
and he charged John.
When they finally sorted themselves out,
the CPD-3 exited the mausoleum and again
encountered the old lady who freaked out.
She'd already seen them leave the tomb earlier.
The gang of risen ex-cops scared her off
and discussed the implications of this news.
They considered just waiting around
for their next iterations to come out of the mausoleum
but decided instead to call Maggie.
The vision Clark received when he tried to summon himself
became instantly clear in his mind.
A candlelit stone room contained a hooded figure
scribbling furiously into an ornately decorated book
made of strange leather.
This figure was an elderly decrepit Clark Bishop.
There was a knock on the door and a voice called,
my Lord, my Lord, as the door opened up.
Cut to a silver accord flying down the highway
driven by a frantic Maggie Cook.
He saw her call him on her phone.
Clark blinked away this unnatural vision
and suddenly the phone in his pocket began to buzz.
Clark answered and Maggie told him
to get to the parking lot immediately to meet her.
John and Keith joined even though they disagreed
with Clark about trusting her.
Maggie sped into the parking lot and pulled up next to them.
She tasked them with taking out a man named Bruce Robin
as he had gone fully insane
and was a danger to the world at large.
She was shook by the appearance of John Lee Pettymore III
and they quickly explained that whole situation.
She did not take it well and they had to calm her down.
Clark grabbed the burner phone from his car
and saw a text that read,
your parents owned an artifact of immense power,
too much power for them to be trusted with.
He responded, what artifact?
Maggie asked her former coworkers to murder Bruce Robin,
owner of Bar Corp and former business partner
of Keith's brother, Ferguson Beans.
John began to question Maggie on how she was still alive,
but the ringing of her cell phone cut off Maggie's reply.
As Clark rejoined the group,
he noted a second cell phone vibrating
from within the chief's car.
On the call, Maggie berated Leon,
told him to do his fucking job.
He needed to knock the dust off his knuckles
because he knew what needed to be done.
She hung up and explained,
she never died, just had to disappear.
She implied the body they'd found
in the remains of her house was a decoy.
Maggie tossed the officers a manila envelope,
reminded them she was counting on this and drove away.
The manila envelope had a manila folder inside
labeled Operation Hole Puncher, Bar Corp.
It contained information on Bar Corp,
including its three subsidiaries, Jesus Christ Ministries,
Health and Rehabilitation Unlimited,
and The Learning Center.
It also showed finances for the last five years
and profits had been steadily rising.
The previous year, they made over $850 million
and paid zero in taxes,
and they were projected to make over $2 billion
in the current year.
It was also noted that after being declared deceased,
Ferguson Beans' majority share was split
between his wife Stacy, daughter Frances,
and the mill on the other side of the city,
which secured Bruce Robin as the majority owner.
John mentioned he recently sold that cocaine
they'd found in the storage units
to Jesus Christ Ministries,
a church camp just outside the city.
Clark told John they saw Marvin Glass split his body in half
to reveal a silver ball inside his head.
John explained his working theory
was that all the officers might be bald.
He explained that upon the death of his original body,
he burst out and went into John Lee Kevinmore's body.
He believed this was possible
because he was just a little silver ball.
Clark described the actions of Rosemary
in her final moments inside the flooded Glass office.
John asserted her turn on Marvin
may have been due to her infatuation
with Marvin's son, Jermaine Glass,
the man who disappeared when he used the odd-looking gun.
After a quick confession from Keith
detailing the murder of his own brother by proxy
as well as the firsthand murder of Bruce Robin's mother,
the former contention police officers
traveled to Robin's home address downtown in the city,
hoping to find personal files and or Bruce Robin himself.
However, when they arrived,
they found police tape across the door
of Robin's brownstone.
The residence was wrecked
and human excrement was strewn throughout.
The stench was overwhelming.
Spray paint covered the walls.
It repeated the same number pattern over and over.
8118189520131181119.
John checked upstairs.
His hair stood on end with the feeling of a heavy presence.
In a room deemed to be a former office,
the same set of numbers was carved into the walls
again and again and again on every surface in the room.
Clark investigated what he thought
might once have been the master bedroom
and found various sleeping pallets.
It was clear as many as 20 people
had been sleeping in this room at one time.
John called the city PD
under the cover of having tracked a drifter to this home.
He requested any information they'd uncovered at the scene.
The city officer shared
that Bruce Robin went missing two days ago.
His neighbors spoke about how crazy Bruce had been recently.
He'd had all kinds of people coming in and out
at all times of the day and night.
The steep decline of Bruce Robin
had been a rapid transformation.
On their way out to the car,
they noted again the sickly green hue
of the city around them.
The putrid smell, the oppressive grays,
the bloated and lifeless faces of the people on the streets.
And in contrast to all this,
the beautiful blooming flowers on every corner
and from every crack in the sidewalk.
John asked a passerby why he was so pallid and corpse-like.
The man explained that work at Bar Corp
had been hard as of late,
though they'd just been given some days off.
He felt the color was actually probably better now
than it had been recently.
Bar Corp was surprisingly paying all employees
time and a half to take two weeks off.
John asked why a big corporation like that
would pay its staff to take time off.
The man wasn't sure,
but it might have to do with the new CEO.
Bruce Robin announced he would renovate every building
and provide everyone a livable wage,
benefits and better working hours.
Clark asked what exactly Bar Corp does.
Do they sell something?
The man asked Clark to pull anything out of his pockets.
Clark produced a pin
and the man said Bar Corp made it.
Sure enough, the pin read Bar Corp there along the side.
The party hatched a plan.
Keith would call Bruce Robin directly
under the guise of commiseration
over the death of Ferguson Beans.
But a woman named Winifred Worth
answered for Bruce Robin's office.
Keith explained Ferguson Beans was his brother
to which Winifred expressed condolences.
Keith requested to speak to Bruce
to ask him some questions.
Winifred promised she would pass along the questions
to Bruce for him.
Keith pressed her.
He'd hoped to have a conversation
with his late brother's business partner.
She insisted.
While Bruce was currently in the office,
he was currently unavailable.
Keith found out Bruce's office
was on the 17th floor and hung up.
He then called the number for Ferguson's office,
but he was greeted again by Winifred.
Keith tried to disguise his identity as Ferguson,
but Keith, caught in the act, just hung up.
The group decided since they knew where Bruce Robin was,
they would head that way and barge in
as officers of the law to question him.
On the way to Bar Corp,
the fellas noticed both flowers and sickness everywhere.
After a diversion to acquire blue windbreakers,
coveralls, and fancy hats,
they pulled up to the 17-story building
and walked through the revolving doors
into a massive foyer with marble columns.
A security guard and a receptionist
stood at a large marble desk,
behind which hung a giant mural
of Washington crossing the Delaware,
but all the guns were replaced by flowers.
The building directory showed only 12 of the 17 floors.
John fast-talked the security guard
and the group found their way into the only elevator
that actually went all the way to the 17th floor.
On 17, they were met straight away
by a small older woman with a shock of white hair.
Winifred Worth wore a white satin blouse
with black vertical stripes on the left-hand side,
high-waisted pants with horizontal stripes
on the right-hand side,
white platform shoes with studded soles,
and interconnected silver rings across her right hand.
She knew they were the disgraced police officers
from contention and she demanded to know their business.
John attempted to persuade her
to let them into Bruce Robin's office.
She was not convinced.
John's solution was to push this 71-year-old lady
to the ground and holler for the others to run past.
John called an ambulance for her
and gave Keith's name as the caller.
Keith picked the lock to get into Bruce's office,
which was in a state of disarray.
A large bookcase had been ransacked.
A conference table was absolutely covered
in binders, files, and papers.
Behind an equally cluttered desk,
a panicked Bruce Robin paced back and forth
and muttered numbers to himself.
He wore a disheveled but well-tailored suit
and his hair was a disaster.
Bruce greeted them
and the officers asked him about the numbers.
He denied he was even saying numbers
and became aggravated when pushed.
They asked if he knew who Keith was.
While Bruce considered this,
they noticed his bleeding knuckles
and the silver ring with a flat blank top
on his middle finger,
exactly like the one they found at Jim Cook's house.
Keith revealed the ring he had tied around his neck
with a shoestring and Bruce's eyes went wide
with fear and excitement.
He asked if they were with Myriad.
Keith said yes and put the ring on.
Bruce stared off above their heads
through a curtain of unwashed hair
and began chanting,
Tawil Alakol.
Clark leapt across the desk, tackle punched him,
and knocked a hidden pistol out of his hand,
but Bruce kept chanting.
Keith tried to stomp on his arm to take the ring,
but Robin used the momentum to pull Keith to the ground.
John tried and failed to gag the chanting man
with his own tie.
Bruce threw Clark off of him
and reached the fallen gun chanting the whole time.
Keith instinctively shot the once again armed CEO
to protect Clark, but it only wounded the businessman.
John demanded Bruce stop chanting
and went to check on Winifred.
However, Bruce Robin completed the chant
and promptly shot himself in the head.
Keith took the ring off Bruce's limp finger.
When he stood back up,
he noticed John was writing numbers on the desk in blood.
Clark stopped him, but John strangely wasn't aware
he'd been writing any numbers.
Suddenly, the doors to the office burst open
and the trio realized they no longer stood
in the places they'd had just been standing.
They were stark naked and drenched
in Bruce Robin's blood.
The numbers 218213518152914 were scrawled
in dark red fluid on every surface of the office
and the gang had no recollection of their actions.
When the doors to the office busted open,
three police officers barged in
as John, Clark, and Keith became aware
of their abruptly changed surroundings.
Clark recognized the officer at the back,
an attractive older man with gray hair as Leon Simpson.
Leon dropped two duffel bags on the ground
and expeditiously executed the other two officers
from behind.
He then marched back out into the hallway
and fired a single additional shot.
Clark told the other two this newcomer
was from the circle of knowledge.
Leon came back, donned headphones and gloves,
turned up some outlaw country and began to clean the scene.
Inside one of the duffel bags,
Clark found cleaning supplies
and three clean city PD uniforms.
Clark, John, and Keith cleaned themselves and suited up.
Leon pulled papers from Bruce's desk
and stamped them with a copy of Bruce's signature.
These papers signed Bruce's share of bar corp
over to the mill on the other side of the city.
Among Bruce's things, John found a note.
It read, she broke me open and all new things
have the power to escort change in the future of good
in order to break the cycle and find fulfillment
in an unquestioning goodness
that breaks the relentless tether
holding this lie of a world withstanding itself.
I can smell my past.
I can hear my future.
I am joy.
I am destruction.
I am pure.
Death to Myriad.
811-818-9520-131181119.
They recognized the number from Bruce's house
and finally broke the cipher.
They found the numbers spelled Harriet Marks,
a name they hadn't come across.
Clark received a text on the mysterious burner phone
that read, the book your parents died for
is still hidden in an undisclosed location.
He texted back, what book?
Where?
A quick search for Harriet Marks revealed
she was a pro-union activist
studying at City State University
who committed suicide in her dorm room
just four days before on December 2nd.
Leon said they would go investigate her
after they cleaned up.
The group heard sirens and made a run for Leon's car.
After a destructive chase and a lethal getaway,
Keith noticed Clark and John zoning out
muttering the number sequence.
Keith described to Leon what happened
in Bruce Robin's office
and what they'd worked out about the cipher.
Leon showed Keith a picture of the inside
of Harriet Marks's dorm room.
Spray painted all over the walls was a third sequence.
1522518195518, the code for overseer.
Leon evangelized.
Clark is more than a man.
He's a God.
He's the savior.
A prophecy maintains Clark will go back in time
and found the circle of knowledge.
John and Clark came to in a parking lot on CSU campus
with Leon and Keith staring at them.
Keith informed them they had just been chanting
Bruce Robin's numbers.
Then he handed them the folder Leon had given him.
Inside were pictures of a crime scene in a dorm room.
Numbers were spray painted on every surface.
In the cipher, it read overseer.
Clark bluntly asked Leon if he believed
Clark was the overseer and was met
with an equally blunt yes.
Leon went on.
He believed Clark would eventually go back in time
and found the circle of knowledge.
The contention officers informed Leon
that an old Clark had been poking and prodding
at their lives recently.
Leon seemed curious and asked them to explain further.
They recalled the time old Clark warned Drew
something terrible would happen
before the chief's house exploded
and how old Clark had branded names
into their skin with magic.
Leon proposed the group split up.
John and Keith could head to the dorm room.
He and Clark would go to the administration building.
Leon explained while they're not sure what it is,
it seemed to transfer from person to person.
Bruce Robin got it from Harriet Marks
and Harriet Marks got it from the overseer
based on the numbers in her dorm room.
They needed to know why Clark had done this.
Clark reminded them it's not him
they're talking about exactly,
so maybe they could call old Clark Clarkold
to avoid confusion.
With that, the groups split off.
Leon began to drive away with Clark in the back seat
and Clark noticed Leon reached for a gun
that looked like the tranquilizer gun
he'd given Clark to coerce agent Trent Chad.
Before Leon could fire, Clark kicked the back of his seat
and a tranq dart stuck in the ceiling of the car.
After a short struggle,
Clark wrestled the gun away from Leon.
He held the gun to the back of Leon's head with a strong,
what the fuck?
Leon explained he had hoped to knock Clark out.
He was terrified something would happen to Clark
like a stray bullet.
If Clark died, that could mean the world ends.
Leon felt he needed to protect Clark at all costs,
but Clark argued if he really was the overseer
and he did go back to found the circle of knowledge,
then this must all work out.
In fact, he might be bulletproof now.
In a pretty threatening tone,
Clark reminded Leon he might be the one needing protection
as he didn't recall an old Leon
running around as Clark Old's right-hand man.
Leon replied with a sigh.
He said it was time.
They really needed to go to calm, comfy campground,
but Leon had been coerced.
First, they could put Clark's invincibility theory
to the test and finish out the investigation at CSU.
So Leon Simpson swung the car back around
and headed to the administration building
they'd first set out for
before the failed kidnapping attempt.
John and Keith walked through the holiday decoration
riddled CSU campus to gifts house, Harriet Marks dormitory.
The lobby was dark and vacant.
John hopped on the computer behind the front desk
and the desktop background was a promotional flyer
for the Jingle Ball scheduled for that evening,
December 6th at CSU.
The poster read, follow the scavenger hunt
to make your way to the Jingle Ball.
On the computer, John found the directory
and discovered Harriet Marks and her roommate, Amelia Locke
lived in 328 across the hall from a show dorm
for tours to prospective students.
They called the elevator and the light
that emanated from the open doors
revealed countless unique number sequences
scribbled all over the walls and floor of this building
in materials ranging from spray paint to bodily fluids.
And inside the elevator, the limp corpse of a student
was slumped over itself.
Her face was amorphous, smashed repeatedly
until she was unrecognizable.
Back in the administration building
the campus seemed absolutely empty.
It looked like Christmas itself had thrown up
the decorations that adorned everything in sight.
The lights of the administration building were off
but down the hall stood two figures.
One mumbled a sequence of letters and numbers interrupted
by desperate appeals requesting physical violence.
In their city PD uniforms, the pair approached
under the guise of officers looking for the records office.
In the elevator, John Lee Pettymore began to mumble
and pulled a Sharpie from his pocket.
He put the marker to the elevator wall
and wrote the familiar cipher of Bruce Robin.
The third floor was similarly dark and silent
and the doors to both 328 gifts house
and the show dorm room across the hall were open.
The show dorm room was covered in numbers
like every other surface in this building.
And there was an out of place Casio keyboard
in the middle of the room with a sheet of music
on the stand.
However, instead of notes on the staff
the sheet music is made of little cartoon pictures,
seven eggs, a golf ball, a cat, a demon and another egg.
Keith pushed on a few of the keys
and the electronic piano was set
to make the sound of jingle bells.
Keith put the silly sheet music in his pocket
and continued investigating the display dorm.
A window looked out on the overly festive campus.
In the middle of the quad was a large old bell tower.
Keith ignored that and found a flyer for the jingle ball
and written on the back was a math equation.
The solution to this problem was 330,
the number of the room in which he stood.
Keith ignored that and headed across the hall
to Harriet Marks's room with the mumbling John in tow.
In 328 Gift's house, Keith found trophies
for riddle solving competitions on the desk of Amelia Locke,
a desk which clearly lacked a laptop.
The charging cord and various USB accoutrement
wreathed a rectangular negative space on its surface.
On scrap paper, Keith found a handwritten note from Amelia
that outlined her views on the suicide of her roommate.
She clearly did not believe Harriet was suicidal
and she wrote she had a plan to figure out
what actually happened.
Keith went through Harriet's things
and found a tucked away sticky note
with a two point to do list.
The first, research most unethical corporation in the city.
The second, who is the overseer?
Clark and Leon approached the two figures
in the hall outside the admin office.
A short and slight freshman jumped up
and poked a tall, well-dressed student with perfect hair.
The little one begged to be hit
and the tall one calmly declined.
Defeated, the short dude ran to a wall,
slammed his head against it and yelled
that doing it himself just wasn't the same.
Clark and Leon approached and the tall student
calmly asked for a moment as he stared up
at a banner above the office window that read,
at the end of the 10th day,
my true love had given me blank gifts.
Leon ignored the scene entirely
and entered the unlocked administration office.
The crazed, small student requested pain from Clark
who asked why the kid would wanna be hit so badly.
The student said he would love it
and then suddenly started to spout some numbers off.
Clark asked about the numbers.
The student didn't recall saying any numbers.
Clark hit him and he crumpled the floor in delight
before scampering off into the darkness.
Clark asked if the tall, calm student
was thinking of numbers at all.
He said no.
Leon reiterated the question and flipped on the lights
which revealed countless numbers
covering the walls of the hall.
The tall student affirmed he didn't even know
the numbers were there
and he introduced himself as Donovan West Haven.
Donovan West something explained
he was just trying to work out the riddle on the banner.
After some debate about how to solve
the gift counting riddle,
Clark and Leon agreed to investigate the office instead.
The single computer was password protected.
On the desk sat pictures of a woman in her early 20s
holding trophies for scavenger hunts.
The name on the trophies, Amelia Locke.
There was also a photo of a group of students
holding up a banner that said Best R.A. Gifts House.
Clark suggested their best bet
would be to head to Locke's dorm.
Donovan asked if he could tag along.
He would, after all, need help solving the other riddles.
On the way to Gifts House,
they could hear strange whoops and hollers
from unseen people all over campus.
Inside Gifts House, the lights were out.
Clark motioned for Leon to investigate
the receptionist's computer
while Clark hollered a hello down the empty hall.
Donovan wandered into a smaller hallway
and lights suddenly came on.
Numbers covered everything and from behind a door
at the end of this hall came a desperate no, no, no,
followed by a sequence of numbers.
The door cracked slightly
and a voice very creepily reached out.
Please turn out the lights.
Donovan obliged and slowly backed out of the hallway
and a genuine thank you oozed from the room.
Clark warned Donovan that if he heard numbers like that,
he might want to close his ears.
But Clark still wasn't sure how exactly
this thing spread so he went to ask Leon,
who'd already put on noise canceling headphones.
Clark tapped him on the shoulder
and Leon tapped the computer screen
that showed the room number of Amelia Locke
and her roommate, Harriet Marks.
When asked, Donovan said people
had been shouting numbers at him constantly.
Clark wondered if he'd had any blackouts
or gabs in his memory but Donovan replied no,
he felt pretty good actually.
Clark pondered aloud whether Donovan
might be the thing they were looking for.
It seemed like he could be immune.
The trio headed up to Amelia and Harriet's room
on the third floor.
Clark Bishop, Leon Simpson and Donovan Westerfuck
approached 328 Giff's house
and found John and Keith already there.
John snapped out of a haze as they entered
and mumbled something about being able to do anything.
Keith explained they'd come across a dead body
in the elevator when John went blank
and started writing the Bruce Robin numbers.
Clark asked John if he remembered writing the numbers
and John asked Clark if he had ever felt quote, immense.
Clark introduced Donovan to John and Keith
and revealed there was a chance Donovan was the key
to all this, that he might be immune to the numbers.
John walked directly into a wall
and confessed he was still working out the kinks.
The reconvened team put their heads together
on the riddle from the banner and came up with 330.
The room across the hall where Keith already found
a piece of paper that depicted illustrations
of seven eggs, a golf ball, a cat, a demon
and another egg set upon a music staff
atop a Casio keyboard.
Keith then presented the to-do list from Harriet's desk.
One, research the most unethical corporation in the city.
Two, who is the overseer?
He also had a note from Amelia's desk
where she wrote she didn't believe Harriet
would commit suicide and she was going to get
to the bottom of it.
They hit the first letters of each cartoon
as notes on the Casio keyboard.
It's the melody of Jingle Bells
and out the window of 330 Gift's house
they watched the bell tower in the center
of the CSU campus light up in all its holiday glory.
This not so subtle clue led the party
to a pleasant stroll through campus,
admiring the crisp white snow, festive decorations
and constant screaming on their way
to the lit old bell tower.
They climbed the spiral staircase behind Keith
who warned them to close their eyes
to not look at the corpse of an almost retired security guard
some of them listened.
The interior of the bell tower and the corpse
were also covered in numbers.
At the top of the tower they met an attractive young woman
named ShamWow Chameleon who recited the numbers
for Harriet Marks as she desperately tried
to get onto the roof of the tower.
Keith saw a sleigh lit up across the way
which indicated the Jingle Ball
was in the Accord Student Center.
John accidentally let slip to Leon
that at least some of them might possibly also be ball.
Keith and John helped ShamWow out of the bell tower
and onto the roof and the group headed off across campus
to go to the Jingle Ball.
On the journey a path of colorful string lights
led to a sitting area which contained a ripe corpse
and a frantic dancer who pointed to the student union.
They entered the Accord Student Center
on the middle floor of a three story atrium
filled with the pure chaos
of wholly obsessive students and faculty.
On their level a girl shaved a team of live reindeer
with a blunt knife and glued the fur to herself.
On the floor below a pair of muscular young men
in Santa outfits diligently wrapped a student
in wrapping paper with duct tape and force.
Above an older woman in a bathrobe
and an aviator hat climbed a garland to the top floor.
A huge disco ball and a Santa hat
hung from the middle of the domed ceiling.
On the lower level a naked man used a mop
and bucket full of paint to write out numbers.
An ice skating rink contained three people dressed as elves.
They placed carrots in various locations
on a life size snowman model and laughed hysterically.
A young woman in a t-shirt that identified her
as a gifts house RA threw a laptop in the air
over and over again while spinning around.
A man doing squats on top of Santa's throne
suddenly stopped.
He looked out, wild eyed and screamed,
Tawil alagool, Tawil alagool.
John with the power in his mind
commanded the chanting man to stop.
Unfortunately to no avail.
Keith shot the guy and he collapsed
into the Santa Claus throne.
However, he was not dead and continued to chant.
The gunshot grabbed the attention of the assembly
in the atrium and they changed their behaviors.
The woman with the fur sharpened the reindeer's antlers.
The Santa twins wrapped each other
instead of the other students.
The ascending woman climbed faster.
The elves took off their skates
and the girl with the laptop threw it
even higher than before.
John accidentally shot two reindeer.
Clark ran toward the laptop girl.
Keith shot one of the Santa twins to death.
Leon gave Donovan a gun and escorted him to a safe spot.
Suddenly, the frenzied throng froze
and began the chants.
The man in Santa's chair jumped
and impaled himself on the post of the throne.
The laptop landed on the side of the spinning woman's head
and knocked her out cold.
Clark grabbed the laptop
and checked the unconscious RA's vitals.
As the rest of the deranged chanting party
executed their elaborate and festive suicides,
Emilia Locke took her last breath in Clark's arms.
The atrium of the Accord Student Center
was a suddenly still disgusting mess.
The PA crossfaded out of the classic mashup
of Wonderful Christmastime by Sir Paul McCartney
and Grown Up by Danny Brown,
replaced by a horrifying rendition of Santa Baby
by Tyler the Creator.
John and Clark fell back into their unnatural malaise
and scrawled the numbers for Bruce Robin
all over whatever mess they sat in.
Leon Simpson, for the first time,
fell to the ground to write out a sequence of numbers.
Donovan was still conscious and present,
but absolutely shook.
Keith solved Leon Simpson's new cipher,
the solve Ben Smith,
who Keith recognized after a quick Google search
happened to be the corpse nearest,
the now dazed member of the circle of knowledge.
Still the only team member up in Adam,
Keith opened Emilia Locke's laptop.
He found screenshots
from the CSU Biology Department Twitter account.
The first read,
a few of us who are not infected
are quarantined in the lab.
Please call 911.
Our calls are not going through.
The second was in all caps.
Call 911, CSU campus infected with a virus.
Please help, we are trapped.
Call 911.
And the final tweet pleaded.
We're still quarantined in the lab.
If you are the person or entity scrubbing this page,
please have a heart.
We are running low on supplies.
There were also two videos
and small windows open on the desktop.
One showed Harriet Marks sitting in her dorm room.
The other was a dark and distorted picture
with only a lit candle in frame.
Clark and John snapped back to reality,
but Leon Simpson began dancing
like his life depended on it.
Keith showed Clark the laptop,
but Clark was far more interested
in the glow than the content.
Leon's phone went off and he continued to boogie down
with no concern for his surroundings.
Due to his groove,
the buzzing flip phone popped out of Simpson's trousers.
Clark grabbed it for the glow,
but noticed 25 missed calls
and an interesting text thread.
Responding to, how's it going?
Leon sent, the secretary is stubborn,
looking for another option.
That was the last outgoing message,
but there was a barrage of words from the other side.
In short stabs, they wrote, I don't want excuses, pick up.
Okay, I sent them.
T.O. will be ready for extraction.
Don't forget to get the signatures.
E.T.A., question mark, Jesus Christ, what is going on?
Question mark, question mark, question mark,
before the longer final message.
If he doesn't get here in time, this is all over.
Everything we've worked for, everything that exists,
just gone, for what?
Your fucking conscience?
Morality won't save us.
They all assumed it was Maggie on the other end,
so Clark responded, hey, it's Clark.
Donovan led the group to Glass Hall,
which housed the biology lab.
Clark received a text on his mysterious burner.
He had asked, what book, where?
And this message read, your book.
Calm, comfy campground.
Leon's phone also received a text.
It said, fuck, what did you do?
From both phones, Clark Bishop sent the question,
who is this?
And on both phones, he got the same response.
Destiny.
The walk across campus was soundtracked
by a cacophony of guttural moans,
which danced on the cold December winds.
In the quad, they saw ShamWow Chameleon
as she steadied herself on the sanctified minion blow up
atop the bell tower and screamed about getting even higher.
In the far distance, the chopping of helicopter blades
slowly but surely grew louder and louder.
Given the option between a longer lit path
and a shorter one in darkness,
Clark persuaded the group to stay in the light.
Around a well-lit corner, an old man moaned
and took a citrus peeler to his frail fingers.
Keith saw this horror and lost it again.
The group, sans vigna,
deciphered this old man's number sequence
and learned the name belonged to a coworker
who hanged himself in front of this bloody mad old-timer.
They continued on to Glass Hall Keith came to
and they found a child meticulously sticking syringes
into a somehow unmoving student's eyeballs.
With that, John and Keith
were lost in their numbers once again.
Inside Glass Hall, the sounds of a few deranged folk
bounced and echoed through the halls.
A trail of blood slowly dripped down the stairwell
which had a few bloody screwdrivers scattered about.
On their way down the wet, sticky stairs to the biology lab,
Keith Vigna tripped, fell,
and knocked something loose in his head.
He popped up ecstatic
and grabbed what he thought were handfuls of cash
but were, in reality, handfuls of bloody screwdrivers.
He stuffed them into all of his pockets
and, for good measure, pulled a few out of a woman's corpse
while he smiled and yelled they were rich.
Keith Vigna then crammed his finger deep into his nose
and sniffed with all of his lungs.
Eyes wide, he shoved his finger into Clark Bishop's nose
who did not expect a heaping bump of pure cocaine.
Clark immediately went blank,
but instead of numbers, he chanted,
Ta will alico.
In the basement of Glass Hall,
the team stood just outside of the biology lab.
Keith Vigna collected bloody screwdrivers
he thought were cash.
John Lee Pettymore talked down to everyone
like a god might.
Donovan Wester-something-or-other panicked.
Leon Simpson boogied and Clark Bishop chanted.
The lights went out and the red emergency lights activated.
An ominous glow illuminated the party
as the entrance of Glass Hall burst open.
Orders were shouted.
Crazed voices were silenced.
Clark grabbed one of Keith's dripping screwdrivers.
A small canister was tossed down the stairs
and a thick gas came pouring out of it.
Clark sharpened his screwdriver.
Keith and Donovan rushed into the lab.
Leon danced.
Down the stairs stormed a squad in tactical gear.
They shouted and tossed more gas canisters.
Clark jammed the sharpened screwdriver into his eye
until the handle was flush with his socket.
Blood dripped down his face
and Clark Bishop crumpled to the ground,
limp and lifeless.
John stared at the scene, began chanting
and ran into the lab.
Inside, a man and a woman in lab coats
sat turned away at a desk.
The woman greeted the group and asked
if they knew how to fix the situation.
Back in the hallway, Leon started chanting
and fell to the ground, surrounded by the tactical squad.
John aimed his gun at the door
and waited for the incursion.
Barbara, the woman in the lab coat,
insisted that she and Phillip were just fine,
much like Donovan Whateverhaven.
She asked Phillip to explain, but he didn't move.
Donovan, worried he might be the only sane person
left on Earth, looked to John for help,
but John was turning his firearm on himself.
So, Jonathan fired at John to try to disable him
from committing suicide, but he missed
and sent a bullet right into the CSU biology department's
prized anti-virus machine.
Barbara turned Phillip's chair around
so he could see this madness,
but Phillip held his own eyeballs in his hands
and dried blood covered his face below
his empty eye sockets.
The raid from the tactical squad began.
Smoke filled the lab.
John looked around the room and smiled.
Finally at peace, John Lee Pettymore the third
shot himself in the head.
Keith prepared for a showdown and Donovan went to his knees,
submitted and asked for help.
One of the infiltrating squad members
placed an oxygen mask on Donovan
and he immediately fell asleep,
but high on disillusion and cocaine,
Keith Vigna murdered two of the troops
with bloody screwdrivers
before they eventually ended his life.
Through the haze and red emergency lights,
we see the two casualties of Keith's screwdrivers,
lifeless in pools of their own blood.
The camera leaves the lab,
passes the elderly pile of a corpse in the hallway,
moves up the stairs and out of glass hall.
The CSU campus is humming.
Sirens are constant.
Limp bodies are being transported by teams of two
in full tactical gear
and dragged into prison transport buses.
The sky is littered with unmarked black helicopters.
We see one hovering above the minion atop the bell tower,
a rope ladder allowing ShamWow Chameleon to get even higher.
As we leave the CSU campus,
we see a confluence of black SUVs
heading toward one of the taller buildings
of the city skyline,
a building that is being climbed
by something massive and spherical.
We continue past the business district
and swoop down into the back of a van
heading out toward the pier.
The broken and upgraded and dead and metal corpses
of John Lee Pettymore and Keith Vigna
are jostling around the posterior of this van
that pulls up to a grand old edifice,
alone on the edge of the water
with a well-lit sign outside that reads,
The City Asylum.
Inside the front doors are two familiar guards,
tall and overweight and all black
with prominent facial scarring.
After we move down through the floor,
we are immediately looking through
a long line of the bottoms of feet.
Body after body has been laid out in a row
covered in sheets, feet sticking out.
We stop on the final four soles.
Both right feet are blank.
Both left feet have dead skin
in the shape of the circle of knowledge,
but one left foot has the name Maggie
burned on top of the seven circles.
Our vision moves up through the ceiling
and into a small dark room.
Donovan Westhaven wakes up to the sounds of beeps
and bloops of a machine that you feel yourself connected to
and you're laying in a hospital bed
in a room that is completely dark
except for the lights coming from the machine
on either side of you.
You see that your blood is being drawn
and there is an IV in your other arm
and then a screen turns on,
a freeze frame of like a webcam video
and it's Harriet Marks and she is mid-chant.
Allacle, towel, allacle, towel, allacle, towel, allacle.
Towel, allacle, towel, allacle, towel, allacle.
Towel, allacle, towel, allacle, towel, allacle, towel.
And then you see at the bottom of the screen,
the barrel of a gun comes up and she squeezes the trigger
and then she with a splatter of blood behind her
falls back and out of frame of the camera
and you're just looking at her dorm room
with a paint of blood behind her
on the wall and on the ceiling and then the video stops.
And a man comes out of the darkness
in the back corner of the room
and you can see that he's lit by your machines
and he's wearing a black suit with a black tie
and a white shirt.
I need you to tell me everything that happened.
Okay.
What's up everybody?
I just wanna drop in here real quick
to shout out two absolutely indispensable folks
from over on the Discord who have made this tiresome task
about 10 times less interminable feeling.
First, I Shot Marvin.
I Shot Marvin wrote up recaps for six episodes.
They have earned a shirt.
And second, Here Be Tigers.
Here Be Tigers got a name check last time
because they not only wrote four recaps
but their recaps were super well done.
Well, they added five more episodes this time around
bringing their total to nine fucking recaps.
Thank you so, so, so much.
You have so clearly and obviously earned yourself
an elusive PTBP T-shirt.
As for the fourth and final part
of this Here season one recap project,
I still need your help
and I'm still willing to send you clothes in return.
There's a link in the show notes and on Twitter,
fuck Jack Dorsey and Facebook, fuck Mark Zuckerberg
to a Google doc we can all share.
If you write up a few succinct but thorough paragraphs
recapping an episode of this show,
you will be entered to win a PTBP T-shirt.
If you write up a few succinct but thorough paragraphs
recapping three or more episodes,
you will be entered to win one of five PTBP T-shirts.
And if you really go wolf to the slap, wolf to the slap,
if you write up a few succinct but thorough paragraphs
recapping five or more episodes,
I will guarantee you a PTBP T-shirt.
Leave your handle or email address
commented on the episode numbers
so we know who wrote what and how to contact you
in case we get to ship you a shirt.
Join us, earn a shirt and help finish
this last recap episode so we can deliver you
the final arc of season one of pretending to be people.
I'm so stupid stoked.
We are dumb grateful for all of you sharing
in our absurd story.
In the delicious words of John Raymond Ray Arnold,
chief engineer of Jurassic Park,
hold on to your butts.
How am I the only one trying to pull off
how can you have enough drowning out
of all who knows?
There's no one home.
No one home.
Fly, fly, to the stream you know.