Welcome, my children, to the family reunion that is PTBP.
It's your Auntie Wolf here to talk your ear off
while feeding you some room temp potato salad.
If your potato salad ain't wet and milky,
you're making it wrong.
I'm feeding you live from 694.2.
I think maybe from Ocean City still.
I don't know, man, I ain't looked outside in a minute.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Rob in Atlanta.
Rob writes,
"'Mornin', Wolf, big fan Rob callin' in from the city.
"'In my last year of law school, I gotta tell you,
"'it's wild how often local officers
"'ignore all kinds of laws.
"'Hell, most forensic evidence is based on experience
"'rather than scientific method.
"'Shout out to my good buddy, Sudek,
"'who told me about y'all in the first place.
"'I was hopin' you could play a song
"'I hear people mutter around campus.
"'It goes Shaka, Mr. T, Felicia, all over the sea, yeah.
"'Real ear worm, Wolf.
"'I think it's by the police.
"'Well, hello, big fan Rob from the city.
"'I wonder if you know small fan Rob from contention.
"'I bet y'all would get along together real nice.
"'I have no idea what this song is you speak of,
"'and I know so many songs.
"'I have played so many different tracks,
"'I can hardly keep track of them all.
"'If you wanna write up somethin' for your Aunt Wolf to Hal,
"'please submit your memorandum
"'as a five-star review on Apple Podcasts,
"'and I'll read it here on 694.2 PTBP,
"'Ocean City, New Jersey's wettiest
"'and sweatiest radio station.
"'Ooh, I've got a bad case of the oohs.
"'Doctor, doctor, give me the news.
"'There are two pieces of evidence in this case
"'against Arvin Chilton that just don't add up to this Wolf.
"'First off, Eileen McCarty, the ex-wife
"'who was brutally chopped to pieces on March 21st,
"'was seen by multiple witnesses at a gas station
"'in Upstate New York two days later on March 23rd.
"'And later that same day at that same Shell gas station,
"'the clerk, a 59-year-old man named Quentin Harris,
"'was stabbed repeatedly and disemboweled on camera
"'and very clearly by Arvin Chilton.
"'If that wasn't bizarre enough,
"'this bloody and horrific scene took place
"'out in the parking lot by the gas pumps.
"'During the savage murder, a car pulled in to refuel
"'and did so, all with Chilton and the dying clerk,
"'Quentin Harris, within five feet of him,
"'despite looking around several times,
"'somehow seemingly straight at the seriously shocking scene,
"'the gasoline purchaser got back in their vehicle
"'and drove off as if nothing was amiss.
"'I tell you what, Wolf here might have just done
"'the same thing to avoid having to talk to the cops,
"'but damn, it ain't right.
"'However, it's okay to be wrong every now and then,
"'proving my point with his pleasing pipes.
"'It's Brian Bulger with Bad in a Good Way.'"
["Bad in a Good Way"]
Feels like I'm on the last bend of the deep end,
but the drowning's been just fine.
And when my ears pop and the shell shock
of this pit stop frees my mind,
I'll be all right, I can go there,
now that I've stared death in the face.
["Bad in a Good Way"]
Bing bong, roly jays, do bing bong, roly jays.
Hey, hey!
Bing bong, roly jays, bing bong, roly jays.
Everybody now, bing bong, roly jays, bing bong, roly jays.
So do you guys remember back in,
oh gosh, how long ago was this?
There was a few years ago where suddenly
everyone that Taylor and I knew from college,
Taylor being my wife,
for those of you who are new to listening,
you can see her guest appearing
in certain parts of the podcast
in season one and pretending to be b-ball.
Uh, but-
Was that a reference to season one?
God, no!
You said no references.
Ah, no references to season one.
So when Taylor and I were younger,
we're 29 now, when we were probably 25,
a lot of people here that we knew from college
in Springfield, Missouri started getting married,
and I was supposed to dress for weddings,
and I didn't have any fucking money at all,
and so I was like, basically what would happen
is I didn't have clothes to wear to a wedding,
so every single time I got invited to a wedding,
I would go to Kohl's,
because Kohl's has an insane return policy,
a very, very good lax return policy,
and so I would go and I would get a nice tie
or a nice suit coat or whatever I needed
to go to this wedding.
I actually, I said tie, but I never wear ties,
but I remember specifically for this story,
I got a new suit jacket from Kohl's,
a nice discount suit jacket that looked nice on me,
and then I wore it to this wedding,
and this wedding was actually really fun,
but it was one of Taylor's friends from a long time,
family, friends from an early age.
Zach, I just wanna get one thing clear real quick.
Yeah, hit me with it.
You lied about the tie.
How much of the rest of this is a lie?
Oh, all of it.
Yeah.
I was all set up, and so I went to this wedding,
and I didn't know anyone there,
and Taylor was in this group of four girls.
She was one of the bridesmaids,
and they were just having the time of their life
all reminiscing about when they were growing up together,
and I was pretty lit and did the photo booth by myself.
And did the photo booth by myself.
Well, it.
So there was a photo booth there
that would take four pictures of you
and then spit out a little image there
like you might in a photo booth,
and there were lots of little props there,
so I put on four different hats and just stared ominously
directly into the camera with the saddest face
that I could muster,
and so I had this amazing group of four pictures of me
in this looking fresh in this Kohl's suit,
and I took these pictures, and I was like,
man, I am gonna love these pictures forever,
and I stuck them in the inside pocket of my suit jacket,
and then I returned that jacket to Kohl's,
and as soon as I walked out the door,
I thought, oh no,
there is a picture of me inside of the pocket of that jacket
and not only is it just a weird set of four pictures
of a guy by himself looking sad as possible,
he's wearing that suit jacket.
But he's wearing the jacket that you just bought, yeah.
At least it looks like you're having a bad time
in that jacket.
Right, so if the Kohl's return person found it,
they would be like, oh, well, I see.
I see.
He did not enjoy the jacket.
He had a bad time.
This jacket would only bring forth negative memories
for this saddeman, but if he did,
just like throw it back on the rack,
somebody had the biggest mind fuck.
Yeah, straight up.
Maybe not.
They probably realized immediately what had happened.
That's weird that my suit jacket
is coming with stock photos.
Of a sad man in this jacket?
This kid looks poor.
They would have said,
based on how scraggly my beard probably was.
Yep.
You were a great big fat person back then, right?
Buffalo Bill would have liked you.
Nope, nope.
No, that's just for us.
I am not editing that out.
No, do take out the body shaming.
That's just because we watched Silence of the Lambs.
Literally, then it makes sense for this exact moment.
I know, and you were a great big fat person.
I quit drinking soda
and I quit drinking Tom Collins' every night,
which at the time, for some reason, my mind was like,
I don't understand how every night
when I drink three pint-sized gin and tonics
with extra syrupy lime juice poured on top of it,
I don't understand why I'm getting so fat.
Yep.
So much sugar.
The calories in a drink will get to you, folks.
Yeah, but the calories in a drink
that's also filled with syrupy sugar is also no bueno.
I was literally putting simple syrup and sugary lime juice
in a drink that already had tonic water in it
because at the time, I didn't know that tonic water
already had a bunch of sugar in it.
Like as much as a soda.
That's why it's good.
That's why it's so fucking good.
Ah, so now I just drink beer.
It's honest, you know?
It is what it is.
Beer, for when you're counting calories.
It's fermented.
You can count a whole lot of them.
If you're practicing this well.
Saw a tweet that said I'm Midwest sober,
which means I'm just drinking beer these days.
Holy shit.
There was a, in Mad Men,
there was this guy like peed himself before a meeting
and they're like, you gotta go to rehab.
And one guy was like, yeah, I know,
so and so went to rehab and he only drinks beer now,
so he's doing good.
That actor.
Isn't that Brian Doyle Murphy?
Yeah, he was in God Bless America.
Brian Doyle Murray.
And that movie fucking rules.
Yeah, it does.
It really does.
Right, it does rule.
It's fucked up.
You know what?
I haven't seen it in a long time.
You're right, it might suck.
I don't know, it might suck.
I only recognize that guy from Shameless.
He played like a cuck.
He played William H. Macy in Shameless.
It's Bill Murray's brother.
Yeah, he's Bill Murray's brother.
What?
Yeah, guys, he's pretty famous.
Not Bill Murray famous, but sure.
I don't think it is.
The guy that I'm thinking of?
If you're thinking of Brian Doyle Murray, then it is.
If you're thinking of the guy
who pisses pants in Mad Men, that is.
That's not Brian Doyle Murray, is it?
Yeah, it is.
Yeah, it totally is.
Hold on.
What's his character's name in that?
And that's his whole deal,
is that he's the fun drunk guy, right?
Until it becomes too much of a problem.
Yeah, this guy's not in Mad Men.
The guy you're thinking of?
So that's what I was gonna say.
It's his other brother.
Look up Bill Murray's brothers.
Other brother.
Yeah.
He's another brother, and they eat nutter butters.
Butter, butter.
Dude, nutter butter.
I fuck with a nutter butter.
Yeah, dude.
For some reason, on the outside of a nutter butter.
Joel Murray.
Hold on, I'm talking about nutter butter.
I didn't know that was Bill Murray's brother.
Oh shit, I thought Joel Murray was Brian Doyle Murray.
Oh, this whole time it was Joel, not Brian Doyle?
Yeah, Joel is in Mad Men, and God bless America.
God bless America.
Yes, yeah.
What were you saying, though?
Before I rudely interrupted.
He was waxing poetic about nutter butters.
Oh, nice.
It's the sugar crystals on the outside
that really do it for me, if I'm being completely wrong.
There is nothing more horrifying
than listening to a podcast,
and you know that the hosts are incorrect.
And they keep saying the thing.
If I knew who Joel Murray was in my heart,
I would hate this.
Good, let's give him some negative feels,
because we are dealing with some very
unsettling situations here.
Wait, what are the peanut chocolate peanut butter?
Nutter butters.
Wafer things?
Oh, I know exactly.
Oh.
What are those called?
Fuck.
I like those more than nutter butters,
but I do like nutter butters.
Oh, chocolate.
Are those puffer nutters?
Peanut.
No.
Wafers.
What the fuck?
Are called nutty buddies.
Nutty buddies, yeah.
Or nutty bars.
Yeah, nutty buddies.
What the fuck is a nutter butter?
Nutter butters are shaped like a peanut, aren't they?
Yes, they are, and there's no chocolate.
And a fluffer nutter is marshmallow
and peanut butter sandwich.
Is that exactly what Elvis ate?
No, he liked something with peanut butter jelly
and bananas.
That's right, peanut butter, banana, and honey.
And honey.
And chocolate.
You're just the devil in disguise.
That's a fun Elvis song.
Thank you.
All right, let's get a recap of where we were at last time
because it's been one, I mean, we can let them in.
It's not been one week for us,
but it has been one week for the listener.
So let's give them a nice little recap
to get them in the mod for where we are now.
Shit's fucked up in Ocean City, New Jersey.
Yeah, it really is.
We got freaking, what's his first name?
Arvin Chilton.
We got an ex-Delta Green agent slicing up eyeballs.
That's right, and not slicing through the eyeballs.
Girl, you're so groovy.
I want you to know.
I don't know.
Slicing up eyeballs?
No, I don't know it.
Look, do you know it?
I am on chin and a Lucia.
Pixies, bro.
It's a Pixies song.
That's why I said it.
Cool.
Cool, yeah.
I read Fight Club.
That was, yeah, Frank Black's best book.
What's Kim's deal, though?
All right, so when you guys.
I get it.
Her deal is that she's in a better band.
Yeah.
Things are bad in Ocean City, New Jersey.
We got an ex-Delta Green agent
who's killing people close to him in his life.
Slicing up eyeballs.
Well, he's not slicing them up, though.
He removed them carefully.
He's taking them out real surgically.
We got down there.
We met up with an FBI agent
who pointed us toward his domicile,
and we went and talked to the landlord there.
He was kind of a weird guy,
and then I think it was him who recommended
we go over to a cafe and have a little lunch.
That was actually Mara Kinlan.
Oh, that's right.
We went back and talked to the NYPD who had been on this.
She was, yeah, she was Newark.
Newark.
Newark, yeah.
Did she give us anything good?
She disagreed with Uncle Jimmy
on the fact that Eileen McCarty,
he had this idea that Eileen McCarty was not the body
that was found in her own home
because she was seen by witnesses in two locations.
But she was like, it's definitely her.
Yeah, and then later, Agent Sparrow,
when she was looking over the actual high-res
like digital files from crime scene photos,
came to the same conclusion because Garza,
Uncle Jimmy with the FBI,
was using these like printed out-
Mayonnaise covered.
Mayonnaise covered crime scene photos.
Uncle Jimmy was, he was gross.
Yeah, he was gross.
He was gross.
Yeah, Agent Garza was pretty unprofessional.
We went to Arvin Chilton's apartment duplex,
which was above Alexander Duchesne's apartment.
Well done.
Who did that without notes?
I did.
I don't take notes, folks.
And we looked around.
He had a bunch of Shakespeare in his duplex.
And then we went downstairs and his landlord,
who lives below him,
had a copy of As I Lay Dying.
It was actually the things they carried.
Mother Faulkner and-
He had a copy of That Thing You Do.
He had a copy of There's Something About Mary.
And it was clearly overdue from Blockbuster.
That's right.
Which still existed in 4060.
It was called Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind.
And we all sat down and watched it.
Luke, we literally sat down and had it on
before this started.
What's it called?
What's it start with?
As.
As I Lay Dying.
Band of the Book.
The book.
Or the James Franco adaptation of the novel.
That one.
No, his adaptation was the band of the band.
I didn't watch it for obvious reasons.
James Franco in the band As I Lay Dying.
As the world turns,
as you is mad.
As you imagined it.
Imagine dragging these balls on my face.
As you, I don't know what it was called.
I did look right at the title when we turned it on.
I know, and it's also a really famous Shakespeare play
that you've undoubtedly heard the title of
countless times in your life.
The Wind Flies.
I don't know what it is.
As the Crow Flows.
As You Like It.
As You Like It, as I said.
Do you like that?
I can't believe you made that great As They Lay Dying joke
without knowing what it was called.
I knew it was ads.
He had the ads, yeah.
Anyway, the landlord had a copy of that,
said that it was fitting,
and all of us having read that book play
and watch the college production of it.
We all pegged exactly what that meant, for sure.
Steely Dan was involved.
Pink, come back to me.
Anyway, he had a copy of that.
He said it was fitting,
and we knew that there's disguises involved in that book.
And he smelled like bandages.
What else did we find out?
Here's what's involved in that play,
is people pretending to be things that they're not.
People pretending to be other people.
Which we pointed out.
We already did the joke about our game,
so we're not gonna do that again.
We've done that.
Get over it.
But that is,
but that's the gist of it.
There's also some rural urban class friction themes.
It's pretty good.
I watched 30 minutes of it and then read the synopsis.
What else happened?
That's when we went over to the cafe,
and the waitress said,
man, there's this weird graffiti around the corner.
You should take a peek at it.
And boy, was it some weird graffiti.
Yeah, and we got really lucky with a critical role
that allowed us to season three.
I don't listen to that nerd shit.
I don't either.
That allowed us to recognize
it as a symbol of the Testament of New Flesh,
which is an organization obsessed with magic.
They chant in Aklo, a pre-human language.
Aklo language.
Yeah, and they worship some sort of eternal and elder being.
Oh shit, is this gonna be real Cthulhu?
Are we gonna meet Cthulhu?
Do you wanna meet Cthulhu?
I wanna meet Cthulhu.
We have in a campaign, haven't we?
Yeah, we had Cthulhu end one of our campaigns.
That's true.
Joe's character was on the beach looking out.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was pretty rad.
As Cthulhu just rose up.
Weren't the minions lifting me in the air?
The star spawn were lifting you up into the air
off the beach.
The minions from Despicable Me.
Stuart was there.
Kevin, Bob.
Yeah, all the classics.
I was gonna say,
I would rather have run into the Testament of Nude Flesh.
That's clever.
Cause you horny?
Cause I'm horny.
Everybody out there.
I'm really glad that out of all the different characters
that you guys have made for games that I've run for you,
none of you have ever been like,
and my character is horny.
If you wanna flirt with me,
you can do it out of game.
That's my rule.
Is that where we ended?
No.
What happened next?
We got a rude phone call that ruined our day.
And it was Duchenne saying that he had just gotten
a phone call that ruined his day.
And it was that Arvin had called and said, you're next.
So we sped over there.
How did he say that, Luke?
Oh, I'm gonna kill you.
Yeah.
Slicing up eyeballs.
It sounded like you said slicing up bibles.
Slicing up bibles.
New Testament, gone.
Mickey says eyeballs.
Slicing up eyeballs.
And then we found out that he was in Ocean City.
No, we did not.
What we found out is that the phone call
came from Arvin Chilton's phone, which is in Ocean City.
And specifically, we found out after we went to go
keep watch over Duchenne that night.
We've got uniform PD.
We also had, yeah.
And we arrived ourselves at Duchenne's house.
When we called Chilton's phone,
we heard it vibrating upstairs.
And that's where we ended off.
Someone made an intelligence check about As You Like It.
I believe it was Agent Sparrow.
Which you passed and therefore you were allowed
to watch As You Like It today before we came in.
Right.
Otherwise you wouldn't have let me out of the cage.
I would have said, you cannot get out of this cage, Thomas.
Does it smell like David still?
I got some free time though.
And I watched As You Like It.
Why did we let him go?
I don't know.
It was such a rookie move.
It was so much fun to be a player.
All right, let's dig in.
It's March 25th, 2016.
The three of you are standing
in Arvin Chilton's apartment.
Say your character's names real quick
and your character voices starting with Joe.
Ellen Walling.
Now Luke.
Kevin Gelato.
Now Thomas.
Agent Clarissa Sparrow.
Wow, I loved that.
We should do that more often.
Okay, it's March 25th, 2016.
You're all in Alexander Duchenne's apartment.
It is pouring down rain outside.
It is now dark.
There are four squad cars outside.
You know that there are some ocean city.
Some ocean.
Sorry, I've got to snap.
I've got to take this.
Yeah, of course.
There's some ocean shitty police officers outside
who had their kick the dog moment
when they made fun of Kevin Gelato.
Yeah, he hasn't forgotten that.
He doesn't forget much.
And as the three of you are standing
inside Alexander Duchenne's apartment,
you've asked him to call back Arvin Chilton.
Brring, brring.
And you hear from upstairs,
look at this photograph.
Look at this photograph.
Chad Krager classic photograph by Nickelback,
which is the vibrate thin ring, ring tone.
On Arvin Chilton's phone.
Let's go ahead and move in dexterity order.
So who has the highest dexterity?
60.
I got a 70.
Joe, you were going to kick off in this-
So the phone rings and we're in combat?
Yeah, Joe is looking at me with like, incredulity.
Is it like that we're racing upstairs?
Nope, you can do whatever you want.
Okay, Elwood would not be the first one out the door.
Sure, you don't have to be.
Just because you're acting first
doesn't mean that you need to, you know.
Gotcha.
I thought that's what you were having us talk about,
is marching order kind of thing.
Well, we are talking,
we're talking just about action order.
So not marching order necessarily,
but we're going to start with what do you do?
Make wide eyes at the guys
and do the silence over the mouth thing and point up.
Awesome.
I'm going to roll intelligence real quick.
Pass.
What are you looking for here?
The song is by Nickelback.
Thank you.
I was going to do something if I failed my intelligence roll
but I'm not going to do that.
Always fun when a role player in your group
decides to just voluntarily maybe fuck something up.
Hey man.
Zach's like, it's fun for me.
It's also what you've been a part of forever.
No, no, no, no, no.
We stumble into hilarious farce.
But if you're like, yeah, my guys yells.
He's too dumb.
It wasn't going to be that, but.
Hello?
Because Luke decided that he was thinking
about doing something,
let's just have agent Sparrow is going to go next.
Cool.
Agent Sparrow draws her gun
when she hears the vibrating phone.
And then she looks around to see how Duchenne is reacting.
He is immediately like,
and he's horrified.
And he is like looking for a place to hide.
Okay.
Can I do any kind of examination of him?
Like an ocular pat down and see if this is.
I want to see if he's wearing a human suit.
Okay, ocular pat down to see if he's wearing a human suit.
What do you want to roll for that?
What do you think?
Medicine or?
Search, medicine, intelligence, humans.
I think you would be able to determine.
My intelligence is telling me he's not human.
Three.
Oh, and three on the check.
That was supposed to happen.
It's on a timer.
A light just turned out in the room.
There's a grow light on the plants in the corner.
Cause I don't get enough sun.
He has the bearing of someone who is in public service
who worked for the feds.
Like the way that he reacted was something
that someone with military experience.
Like he's got big claws and fur all over him.
What did I say?
He said.
He has the bearing.
Oh my God.
I was like, I know it was.
I didn't think it was actually going to be relevant.
I thought it was a real big reach.
Like a bear might have.
Like a bear has.
Thomas is forgetting his background.
He was not in any kind of law enforcement or.
All that you know about Alexander Duchene
is that he supposedly played baseball when he was younger.
And you like don't know if that was.
I mean, he said he wasn't very good at it,
but that's all you really got about him.
You don't know a lot about him.
He's old enough to have been retired though.
And landlord is the retirement thing.
Oh, a hundred percent.
He's 79 years old.
Yeah.
Which like, you know, for me, I'll still be working.
That's right.
That's because.
Yeah, everyone listening here will be working
in the water mines until.
But here in 2016, a 79 year old is still
pulling social security.
Right.
Not working for Bezos H2O.
When you say that, does he look like a 79 year old man
who has that background?
Or does this look like Arvin Chilton in the body
or like something controlling his body in an unnatural way?
Go ahead and roll sanity agent Sparrow.
Pass 58 on a current 80.
Yeah, this is just learning something new
about Alexander D. Shane.
Damn it, this is when I should have failed sanity, right?
This is just learning something new
about Alexander D. Shane.
This is an interesting moment of conflict for Thomas.
Yeah, of course.
Because I have a lot of suspicions
about what's going on here.
Why wouldn't you?
However, the main thing is that agent Sparrow
doesn't know she's in a scenario called control copy.
Sure.
I don't know why you keep saying that
because I don't know what that means.
Shut the fuck up.
Don't gaslight me.
I don't know anything about computers.
No, it's your job, but.
It's my job to gaslight you.
That's what a DM does.
In Delta Green, yeah, like half the time for sure.
Yeah.
So without metagaming, what do you do next?
Like my only possible actions
lead me towards a terrible fate.
Right, yeah.
But I guess that's the game we play, so.
It is.
She, passing that sanity test,
she all of a sudden thinks he might be
a little more capable than she estimated.
Sure.
So she says to the uniformed PD,
you stay on him, you protect him.
I'm going upstairs.
Luke, what is Kevin Gelato doing?
He looks up at where the vibration is coming from
and looks down at his hand.
Which is balled up into a fist.
Right.
Sorry, let me say that again without vaping my mouth.
He looks down at his hand, which is balled up into a fist,
but then he sees Sparrow start heading towards the door
and decides to follow her.
I'll go first.
And he heads up the stairs.
No, no, wait.
He waits.
Let me in first.
He lets her in front of him.
Okay, are you approaching the stairs stealthily
or are you gonna run up them?
Stealthily, but quickly.
Which one of the two of you
has the worst stealth of the two?
I don't have any.
I have 10%.
Yeah, same.
Okay, so either one of you can roll.
You should roll.
I got a 91.
She's like running up like FBI.
She's not saying it, but she runs up the stairs,
drawn gone.
And behind her, I mean, behind her, you hear.
Dump, dump, dump.
Wha-choo!
Bless you, but be quiet.
And the door is closed.
Locked?
No, she opens it.
So just like in Silence of the Lambs,
which we watched yesterday,
remember at her Quantico training,
where she gets capped.
Oh, yeah.
From behind the door, she missed the corner.
She didn't check her corners.
She carefully opens the doors, checking her corners.
I love trade craft.
Feels so good when it's well used in a game.
Man, that's excellent.
Okay, so because you checked the corners,
you get to see the same thing you would have seen
if you hadn't, which is absolutely nothing different
in this room except for there is a phone
sitting on the kitchen countertop.
Can we clock that it definitely wasn't there
the last time we were in the apartment?
100% it wasn't, but question for Elwood Boyd.
Are you now upstairs or are you hanging out downstairs?
I am standing behind Kevin like he's a human shield.
Okay, perfect.
Literally peeking out from behind it from time to time.
Yes, and your hands went up to prove it.
Are there any security cameras on the property?
No, none that you're aware of.
What if I rolled electrician to see if there is one?
Yeah, okay, go ahead and roll.
It's my craft.
Okay, fantastic.
I love a craft.
Just four young witches learning how to.
There's not any security cameras.
Thomas showed me the craft.
I'd never seen it until Thomas showed me that movie.
A couple of Halloween's ago.
No, yeah, I remember it,
but I think that was the first time I watched it too.
Oh, nice, it was rad.
What's up?
What about a dating show with witches
called Craft American Singles?
Yeah.
The Craft American Singles, but yeah.
It's always good when a show has sponsorship built into it.
Oh yeah, it's paid for already.
Yeah, wait, forget the witches.
Can this just be a cheese dater show?
What kind of cheese do you like?
I only eat craft.
I failed, so there's not any security cameras.
Oh, you failed, okay, sounds good.
No security cameras around to speak of that you know of.
Everything seems to be in the exact same place
where it was left.
No footprints or anything.
Like bloody footprints obviously right there.
No obvious bloody footprints, no.
Can I get this room and ocular pad down?
Absolutely, roll forensics for me.
Eight.
An eight on a forensics check shows that yes,
someone has absolutely been in this apartment.
You can tell because there's now a phone
in the middle of the table.
There's a path of dirt in between the front door
and the kitchen where the phone is.
If I forensic that and get a critical success,
can I Sherlock it?
You would absolutely Sherlock the entire fucking thing.
This is from.
So yeah, I failed.
She leans down and like picks up some of the dirt
and rubs it between her fingers and smells it.
And this person had stepped in dog shit
and she got some dog shit.
Yeah, a hundred percent.
But you know that that dog shit was fresh.
So like this clearly happened in between the time
where you were here earlier and now.
Kevin sees her doing that and is like,
oh, that's maybe I should do that too.
Maybe I should smell the dog shit.
And he like eats a little bit of it.
Yeah.
He's like.
No, no, yeah.
He just nods his head.
No, I hate this.
Yes, keep doing it.
He nods his head in his mind.
He's like, that's definitely dog shit.
I've had that before.
Sure.
But he just nods his head having no idea
what she's thinking.
She gives him the saddest look.
He thinks she's sad because she can't figure out
where the dog shit came from.
Oh.
Four rolls.
What's up guys?
Zach rolled the dice four times and then didn't say anything.
If Elwood feels like the room is empty, do I?
Yep.
I want to go in and go to the phone.
I want to grab the phone and I want to look through it.
Is this a studio?
Yeah.
Okay.
We're in the only room.
You are in the only room.
The only other thing is the bathroom.
There's two doors, closet and bathroom.
Does that dirt trail lead to the bathroom?
Nope.
Does that dirt trail lead to the closet?
Does that dirt trail lead to the phone
and then back out the door?
Yep.
Okay.
This dirt trail leads out the floor.
This dirt trail leads to the door and out and...
This dirt trail leads to the door after it leads
to the phone, which it led to from the door.
It's actually dog shit, not dirt.
I know.
Me too.
Yeah, I know too.
I saw, yeah.
Maybe he has a...
Does that...
Alvin?
What's his fucking name?
Arvin.
But I thought his name was Alvin last episode too.
Arvin!
Does Arvin have a dog?
I have a feeling it's probably just an environmental hazard.
Okay.
Have you ever stepped in dog shit?
No.
Well, I have.
I was never trying to.
Whoa, what a weird way to answer that question.
I just assumed.
He didn't want to be embarrassed.
Yeah, she's like, who steps in dog shit?
I don't step in dog shit.
It's okay, everybody steps in it sometimes.
You don't know.
A lot.
Some people even say it's good luck.
A lot, I'm lucky.
Yeah, because after you stepped in dog shit,
what's the worst thing that could happen to you that day?
You get it in your mouth.
Yeah, you did that.
You did that.
But that happened before.
You haven't stepped in any of it yet.
No.
So there you go.
Once you've stepped in it,
probably nothing worse will happen
than putting that shit in your mouth.
What kind of phone is it?
Good talk.
I watched a trailer today.
Quick trailer alert.
Trailer alert!
You guys know how we do trailer alerts?
Yeah, classic trailer alert.
Stop trying to make trailer alerts a thing.
Trailer alert!
We watched a trailer for a Netflix Christmas movie today
with the guy from Crazy Rich Asians
and the blonde girl from Game of Thrones.
And-
They, she, a bird shits in her eye.
Nice.
And she fucking dies.
And he tells her it's good luck.
And she's like, what?
That's-
And he's like, do you want to go out with me?
And she's like, no.
Yeah.
Dog shit I get.
If a bird shits in your eye-
A bird shit in her eye and they show it in the trailer
of like the goop hitting, which now, uh oh, side story.
I saw Kings of Leon perform after the-
In a bird shit in your eye?
I think you told this on the pod already.
Have I?
Oh, okay, then I won't tell it again.
But when I saw Kings of Leon,
they played outside in a bird shit in the bassist's mouth.
And they shut down the show after three songs.
I remember that was in the news
when it happened because of that.
Okay, they opened with Closer,
which is the first song off Only By The Night.
And then they played the next song off Only By The Night,
which is Crawl, which is a fucking jam.
And then they played Taper Jean Girl,
which was fucking rad.
And so I heard the only three songs I like
by Kings of Leon and during the third one, a bird strip.
I watched the shit fall down from the rafters
and the bassist looked up at just the wrong time
and it landed directly in his mouth.
He ripped his bass off of himself and walked off stage.
And then they finished the song and left.
That's so lame.
Listen, I don't know how much shit
went how far down his throat.
I can imagine a scenario in which I need to stop the show.
But I think in most scenarios,
if a bird shit in your mouth,
you fucking wash that shit out.
You take a minute.
You take a minute and you go to bed.
You take a minute and then you go play a kick ass rock show.
It was made exponentially better
because Justin Bieber broke his leg on stage
and finished the show.
Justin Bieber just out rockstar'd you.
Yeah, and they're like.
He's a pop star.
They're like, we're southern whiskey drinking boys.
Is that their deal?
Yeah.
I thought that the deal was
that they were vaguely Christian.
Their dad was like a tent preacher or something.
We should get back to the episode.
So there is a phone sitting on the kitchen countertop.
I wanna pick it up and look through it.
Yeah, of course.
It matches all the incoming and outgoing phone calls
that you would recognize from the log
that you got from the FBI.
I wanna check text messages.
Yeah, when you go into text messages,
there are very few and far between.
It seems that Chilton was not much of a texter.
Can I look for correspondence with his ex-wife
before that phone call that she received
a few days before she died?
It had been a long time since he had called her, yeah.
Is there a role I can do
to make sure I'm not missing anything in this phone?
What do you wanna roll for that?
I'll do it too.
That's an eight on SIGINT.
Oh dude, hell yeah.
So, cause you rolled SIGINT and I love that skill
and we never use it,
if you go through the photos
and you start scrolling through,
you're gonna realize that each panel of like nine photos,
the top left, top right, bottom left and bottom right,
remind you strangely of like the points
of that weird pentagram thing.
The flesh pentagram.
The Vitruvian man pentagram.
Yeah, that you saw earlier.
And all the nudes remind us
of the testament of the nude flesh.
Pfft.
Mm-hmm.
That really got me.
It did.
I felt like I stole something.
Like that wasn't that good.
Mm-hmm.
Arvin Chilton, or whoever was using this phone,
is clearly involved with
the testament of the nude flesh.
Thank you.
Maybe we, you should Google the new flesh
and see if we can join in quotation words.
While I'm holding this phone,
can I just Google that, the testament of the new flesh?
When you go to Google the testament of the new flesh
and it autofills.
Autofills, sure.
Autofilled, he's been looking it up himself.
Have you seen these pictures here?
He's even like doing the diagram in his photos.
He knows something.
He's part of this group, I think.
Seeing that pattern that they've seen in the photos,
she asks Elwood, if you go to the call logs,
are there any numbers, new numbers that start appearing
around the same time as that photo pattern?
Let me see here.
It looks like there's, yeah, there's one here
that he hadn't called before, the 20th.
Yeah, it's a new one to him.
When did he last call it?
I wonder when he last called it.
23rd.
Click on the info and it says the 23rd.
That was the day, three days after the deaths?
Two days after the deaths.
Two days after the initial deaths,
but the same day as the gas station death.
Yeah, what time is the call
in relation to the gas station death?
Earlier.
Okay.
And the date of the first phone call?
The day before.
So the day after the McCarty's were murdered
and then the day that the gas station attendant,
Quentin Harris was murdered.
But before the murder occurred.
But before that Quentin Harris murder.
And this is just like a phone number, not a saved contact.
It doesn't say like.
Not a saved contact.
Cool cult number.
It does not say cool cult number.
Is the area code the same like Ocean City?
Great question.
It is, it is not an Ocean City number.
Is it like a New York City number?
It's Newark, baby.
Newark.
No, sorry, shit.
Am I dumb?
Do you not know your nation's area codes?
It's 417 and Zach made the call.
No, I'm sorry, it's Newark.
And is there a duration listed
for how long these calls lasted?
The first one is two and a half minutes
and the second one is 30 seconds.
Oh, okay.
Oh.
Zach's rolling and laughing.
Four times.
Oh my God.
Again for the second time.
Everybody roll alertness.
94.
Four.
I pass with a 14.
It is raining outside.
The highest success was a 14?
Yeah, it's raining outside.
It's like I'm on the last bend of the deep end
but the drowning's been just fine.
And when my ears pop and the shell shock
of this pit stop frees my mind.
I'll be all right.
I can go there now that I stare death in the face.
Doesn't it always seem like the parts that made us laugh
now make us cry?
Doesn't it always seem like the villain
pulling the strings is a regular guy?
You and me have gone bad in a good way, I promise.
Kerosene wipes clean what we couldn't bear to tarnish.
I'll be all right.
I can go there now that I stare death in the face.
There's a conundrum in the wisdom of my spirit.
White washed hymns and the deadliest sins
push me to my limit.
But when you deconstruct
you're shit out of luck for a minute.
After the last bend you can break it all down to rebuild it.
You and me have gone bad in a good way, I promise.
I'll be all right.
I can go there now that I stare death in the face.