This is yet another introduction to a show
that you listen to called, well it's broadcast live
from 694.2 PTBP and I'm your benevolent host
with the gross wolf the dog.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Ash
out of North Carolina who tweeted about the show
and tagged that pretending pod,
which is a nice thing to do.
She writes, hey there, I don't have anything to promote,
just wanna let you know how much this show means to me.
I listen every day while I'm at work
and it passes the time so fast,
my job feels almost inconsequential.
Almost as if the atrocities I've committed don't affect me.
As if I can't hear the violent snapping of tendons
and viscera emanating from my monitor.
A mere taste of the despair that lies
within the nightmare network.
Shout out to my friend Gwen for showing me PTBP
and keep up the great work.
Hmm, nightmare network?
Did you just try to sneak in promotion
for another media channel that isn't my radio station
on my radio station?
Hmm, I shall be contacting my lawyers.
They are definitely real and definitely will do law things
at you, for sure.
If you wanna write up something for your wolf to howl,
tag us on the internet or fuck the zuck,
but preferably write us a five star review
on your podcast listening application.
Whichever way you choose, it's time for the news.
Last time we met Dr. Rusty Hooch,
the never missed scientist.
They insist that she enlist, create an ocean of blue mist.
Her ex was pissed, you get the gist.
Dr. Olivia Miller, the sad single mom surgeon.
Her daughter saw her dissect some sort
of a extra dimensional creature
out of a screaming woman's neck
and it shot into a sir's snot socket
who was promptly shot in the skull
by his sorrowful sidekick, full stop.
Next, Doreen Maureen.
Scroll Pinterest on that iPad, that's a good haiku.
Finally, the step motherfucker himself, the Chuckster.
Coming in at five foot seven,
213 pounds of round muscle that is.
It's ball buster 420, hell yeah.
And he survived the holy suffocating,
holy decapitating tongue from hell.
Well, it's time for the briefing.
Yep, you can hear that creeping.
If your ears aren't leaking, it's Molly Healy with circles.
See ring star, deafening heaps.
You don't know where you found it.
In this state, as your eyes fall short,
you better learn how to keep it.
Welcome to Pretending to Be People.
I am here with the same people who are here
on episode one, part one of this story.
It is now part two.
Let's go around the room as well as the TV.
Eleanor is on a TV on our kitchen countertop here.
We'll take a group photo at the end of this
with us and the TV.
That way we can all have a picture together.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, sorry.
And you can put up a picture of yourself.
Let me know when you want to take the picture
and I'll put up like some glam shots.
Yeah, perfect.
You sell it.
Ellie on the kitchen counter, the nudes.
No, okay.
You guys, that's how you make money in this industry.
I've been trying, Eleanor, but-
Dude, more feet, more feet.
Oh, okay, yeah.
More feet in this audio podcast.
Oh no, they want to see it, they want to see it.
All right, let's go around.
Everyone, if you could just like say your name,
your character's name,
and then the worst thought you've ever had about your mom.
So let's start with Allie.
Ooh, can't wait.
My name's Allie.
My character name is Rusty Hooch, Dr. Hooch.
The worst thought I've ever had about my mom
is that I'm exactly like her.
Way to sidestep the question.
Also, you don't have to answer that, any of you.
Jen, if you're listening, I love you, and she will.
Really?
Probably.
Interesting.
Hi, Jen.
My mom won't listen.
Lindsay, you're up.
I'm Lindsay.
I play Doreen, Maureen, or Chlorine, or Boreen,
or whatever you want to call me.
First name, Doreen.
And the worst thought I've had about my mom
is probably that I based this character off of her.
And she won't be listening.
She will not even know that this exists.
I'm going to, what, Facebook?
I have Facebook here.
It's like, I'll tweet at it.
No, I'm probably not.
Because she definitely has a Facebook.
Pinterest.
You can just DM her on Pinterest.
Slide into her Pinterest DMs.
That's the most definite way to get a hold of her.
Eleanor, who are you playing?
What's up?
Hi, I'm Eleanor DiLorenzo, and I play Dr. Olivia Miller.
And do you want to know the best thoughts
I've had about your mom, Zach?
Yes.
OK, actually, I don't know anything about your mom.
But what's her, never mind.
We're not going to go down this road.
You're going to dox my mom?
I'm not going to dox your mom, no.
I'm sure she's a lovely lady.
Most American ladies I've met are super kind and sweet.
So I'm sure she's great.
My mom, on the other hand, what a, no.
She's the worst thought I've had about my mom is,
oh, shit, yeah, I don't know.
I feel like you can't talk shit about your mom
if you have a good mom, because moms are the best.
So I feel bad about even considering
like the list of awful things.
But so I'm thinking, I'm trying like, hmm, one time
she made like a pretty nasty chicken tikka masala.
So that's.
It sounds like you went through a lot of early life trauma.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
So, yeah, that's the worst mom thought I've had.
And Taylor?
Hi, my name is Taylor.
My character name is Chuck Cheese.
Oh, yeah?
Charles Cheese.
You're going with Charles the Chuckster Cheese?
Charles the Chuckster Cheese.
You can call me Chuck or the Chuckster.
What's your middle name?
Chuckster, Charles Chuckster Cheese.
Charles Chuckster Cheese.
OK, anyway.
My mother-in-law rules, so.
I will say, though, I've had time
to think about this because I was the last one to go.
And when I was a kid, I would walk to and from school
and elementary school.
And if I was mad at my mom, I would intentionally
step on all the cracks to break my mother's back.
Wow, violence.
Did she have back problems?
Yeah, actually, yeah, she had to get a breast reduction
because her boobs are so big it hurt her back.
You're making your mom's boobs bigger
by stepping on the cracks?
Yeah, every time it's like a Pinocchio.
They just grew and grew.
Apparently, my grandma had to do that, the breast reduction.
And I was like, give me those titties.
Literally, it happened in middle school.
And I had a lot of sleepovers as a kid.
And after my mom got the surgery,
any time my friend came over, she was like, look.
And just lift up her shirt and show her smaller scarred boobs.
Do they shape them?
They do.
So they look like perky nice titties, huh?
Yeah, she went from double Fs to perky Cs.
So Zach, are you really happy we're
talking about your mother-in-law's boobs
on your podcast?
Yeah, good.
What are your thoughts, Zach, about your mother-in-law's
boobs?
I was really prepared to answer that question
until you finished.
So my thought about mom's boobs.
You can talk about your own mom's boobs if that's easier.
Tell us about your own mom's boobs.
When I was 17, my birthday landed on Easter Sunday.
And so the whole family came over on my birthday
after church.
I'd been going camping with my friends a lot.
And so my mom got me a camping chair, a really nice one,
because I used to borrow their camping chairs.
This was her really nice way of being like,
stop fucking taking my camping chairs.
So she bought me my own.
And I was so stoked, actually.
I was like, this is rad.
This is great.
It's huge.
It was like a big one.
And she's like, yeah, it's oversized.
So it can actually hold up to 250 pounds,
which was pretty cool of her to say
to her very chunky young boy.
So happy birthday to you.
Self-conscious son.
Yeah, yeah.
It's called a captain's chair, right?
It is a captain's chair, extra large, oversized.
For oversized boys.
For oversized boys who are addicted to Mountain Dew
and White Rum.
All right, so let's dive into it.
Dude, Mountain.
Oh, right, actually.
I was going to tangentally about the topic.
I don't even know how to say tangentally.
You know what I'm talking about.
Tangent.
Yeah.
OK.
One more.
I want to.
One more boob.
No, no, it's not about boobs, but it's about cool women.
I have a cool story about my aunt.
Men in her family would take off their shirts very often
when it was in the summer months in Sweden,
because that's socially acceptable for men
to wear their boobs out.
But even at the dinner table, she's like,
please put on a shirt.
And they're like, fuck off.
Maybe not.
They didn't say that, but maybe something similar to that.
And so one day, she was like, OK.
And she's a 65-year-old woman, and she took off her shirt
and sat down to eat at the table.
And I'm like, that's my goal in life.
I want to take off my shirt.
So we should all take our shirts off?
Yes.
OK, great.
No one will know.
No one will know, guys.
It's an audio drama.
I don't know.
Maybe it will be funnier, just more vulnerable.
Just do sounds with taking your turn off.
Make for better audio.
Vroop.
Skier.
Ding-dong.
Ding-dong-dong-dong-dong.
I get it.
I understand.
All right, let's dive into this episode.
Yeah.
Y'all ready to play some Delta Green?
I think we got a pretty good introduction to your characters
in episode one.
The way in which the game works is now going to change,
because we're going to put you all in the same place
and then send you on a little mission.
OK?
OK.
All right.
Oh, no.
At least a year has passed since each of you
had your unnatural encounters that brought you
into Delta Green.
And here you are again, going into the field
with three strangers sitting in the back of a Sprinter
van turned into a mobile lab in the parking lot of a public park
with no cameras in Shreveport, Mississippi at 2,200
on a cold January night.
Anything to stave off the end of the world, right?
Your handler on this one is a bit dramatic.
Three years ago, this guy's just like talking with his hands.
He's super intense.
He's leaning into all of you as he talks.
Three years ago, Jerome Dyer left his job in Dallas
as an intelligence analyst.
During his second night at the opera, he left.
He abandoned his post.
And he joined a group called Bigfoot Underground Search
and Hunt.
He's been radio silent for three years until tonight.
Dyer made contact with a YouTube account
I run posing as professor and Bigfoot enthusiast Dr. Ann
Falsom.
And this guy looks super proud of himself when he says this.
Agent Dyer is desperately seeking extraction,
but not for him.
For a body, a big body, from an isolated cabin
in the thick, verdant hills of southwest Arkansas
near a small town called Fook.
I've pinned the location on these clean phones.
And he hands you each an older model iPhone
with various used cases on them.
The cases are so that the phone doesn't get shattered, Ali.
Wow.
Called out.
OK, OK, so I've gotten super into Bigfoot Underground
Search and Hunt while portraying this Dr. Ann Falsom.
And the origin story of their ringleader, Carl Lambert,
is fucking tragic.
Check this out.
When he was 14 years old, he went out
camping with his dad and his younger brother Michael,
who was 12 at the time.
So this Bigfoot sneaks into their camp in the night
and abducts the younger brother.
Carl and his dad tried to explain what happened,
but who's going to believe them?
Everyone just assumed the dad killed the boy
and pressured Carl into telling the Bigfoot story.
So dad decides he can't handle being
tried for his son's murder.
So he offs himself, which leaves 14-year-old Carl
with a very singular mission.
Find Bigfoot and kill it.
It's been three decades, but it seems like he finally did it.
So the operation, go to that point, go to the cabin.
Again, GPS marked in those phones.
They have cases on them, don't worry.
Secure the body.
Destroy any evidence.
We can't have, obviously, we can't have this getting out.
Agent Dyer is sabotaging the Wi-Fi and the cell networks
up there.
So Carl and Janice won't be able to post anything
unless they figure out what he's up to.
Oh, Janice Ruth, their third musketeer,
she's a conservation agent, mostly hunts down poachers.
She keeps her identity hidden from most
of the Bigfoot underground search and hunt fan base.
They'd probably deem her untrustworthy, right,
because she works for the man.
Bless you.
He takes another huge rip off of La Croix.
Ruth considers her bachelor's degree in zoology
essentially worthless compared to her countless hours spent
learning everything there is to know about Bigfoot ecology,
behavior, migration on the YouTube channels
of her perceived peers.
Shit.
Sorry, that's so much information.
He looks at his watch and waggles his eyebrows.
Dr. Anne Falsom, with quotes, should be getting on her way.
But that's one of you, obviously.
One of you has to be Dr. Anne Falsom when you get there
to secure the body, right?
Because I've told you that's the whole deal, right?
Real quick, do you guys have any questions?
I have a question.
Yeah.
What the fuck is going on?
We are dealing with a conspiracy theorist, I'm assuming.
Someone who believes in Bigfoot, and we're
here to look into a body.
I don't know what this could possibly be, obviously,
based on this description I was given.
Yeah, it's a Bigfoot.
OK.
Well, how about I make that call when I see what we see?
That's why we hired you guys.
That's why we got two of the smallest.
Oh, yeah.
Are you still going by?
The juxtaposer.
Yeah.
So honored to be in the presence of such righteous ladies.
Fuck.
Very.
So what's your expertise, Chuckster?
Well, you see, I've seen a lot of battle in my day,
fought a lot of not-so-good guys,
and I'm here to keep you ladies safe.
Yikes.
All right.
Dr. Miller taps, absent mindingly,
her revolver she has in her pants,
stuck to the top of the way in her pants because she's like,
guess I will be protecting myself for the rest of the day.
Dope gun.
What's the range on that?
Can I hold it?
Isn't that like sharing a glass of water?
I mean, we just met.
Cool, cool, cool, cool.
I understand.
We all got our weapons.
Dr. Miller has no idea what a range is.
Or is that Ellie, who has no idea what?
I know nothing about guns, but.
I don't either, literally.
OK, good.
All right, 22 miles.
For people who've listened to pretending to be people before,
normally when someone's like, I pull out my M6942K AK-47
silencer laser pointer, I'm like, all right, yeah,
that's a gun.
So roll for shooting a gun.
That's me.
Some Delta Green people are super
into that side of Delta Green.
I'm all for that, but I don't know any of it.
So therefore, I'm not super into it.
So gun, shoot, pew pew.
Doreen is like somewhere in between the Chuckster
and the intelligence of these two doctors.
So she's just kind of taking it all in.
She knows that she, as an agent, has more capability
than the Chuckster, but is not going to say anything.
It's just going to be, you know, she'll let the Chuckster think.
Chuckster is just raw confidence.
That's what he works on.
And that's fine.
That's fine with Doreen.
Doreen can be our audience stand-in for just looking
back and forth between these two groups,
these intelligent doctors.
She's also just constantly looking over her shoulder,
assuming she's going to see children somewhere.
So not that good.
Anyone want a brewski?
I keep them in my refrigerator pack pant pockets.
You see, I invented a mechanism you can put in pants
with their insulated pockets and ice packs
so I can always keep my beers cold.
What's your name again?
I think maybe you'll just want to call me Charles.
All right, Charles, it is 6.30 AM.
If you can please get that.
It's late at night.
It's 2,200.
It is literally 6.30 AM.
It's 10 PM.
Get that brewski away from me.
It is party time.
I understand, I understand.
Doreen takes him up on the offer.
Dr. Miller is very intrigued.
She's like, a wearable fridge.
That could be quite useful, actually, in terms of,
we will, in order to keep certain vaccines cold.
Happy to share my pants with you.
All right.
Well, for now, let's keep the pants on, Chucky.
And maybe I'll take you up on that offer later.
We'll see how tonight goes.
OK, I'm now uncomfortable.
So I'm going to get the fuck out of here.
You guys need to get going.
They expect Ann to be, Dr. Falsom, sorry,
to be up there soon.
So whoever wants it can have it.
And he throws down four IDs on this table.
And you're in a Sprinter van, right?
But it's been transformed into a lab in the back.
So there is almost like an ambulance.
There's going to be a stretcher in the middle.
So you guys are kind of sitting on either side
of this stretcher.
And he slams down four IDs.
They all say, Dr. Ann Falsom, they
have each of your pictures on.
So he's like, your choice.
Whoever wants to take lead on it can do it.
But I got to get out of here.
My number is in those clean cells, right?
So once you have the body, shoot me a call.
The second location that's in those phones,
GPS, is going to be the drop off point.
So I've got a warehouse.
I'll meet you there after the mission is up.
So I have all the faith in you that I should.
You're very intelligent.
You're very capable.
He looks at two different groups when he says those things.
And that'll be it for me.
I'm going to get going.
And he kind of opens up the back doors of this Sprinter van
and walks off into the parking lot, presumably
to be picked up.
He turns back around.
And he's like, oh, yeah, OK, bye, yep, all right.
Bye, bro.
OK, yep.
See you, man.
All right.
And he finally just turns back around.
You hear a truck start on the other side of the parking lot.
And it swings by and picks him up.
And the truck heads out.
You are now, the four of you, alone,
I mean, with three strangers, in the back
of this converted mobile lab slash mobile ambulance
kind of thing that just looks like a standard Sprinter
van on the outside.
So I'm a pretty dank actor.
But I don't know that I'm so much the doctor type.
So maybe someone wants to take lead on being that doctor.
I think, clearly, I need to be the one to do this.
None of y'all can handle it.
You do seem real right smart.
And I like them bangs, girl.
I am a lesbian.
Stay away from me.
All right.
Hey, Ellie, Eleanor, I'm going to ask
Allie to explain something real quick.
What do you even mean, Zach?
Well, I'm just curious about a couple of things.
Do you want to explain kind of your thought process
going into creating a character for being on the show again?
Yes, so this is my third time on the show.
First time I played a straight man.
The second time I played a closeted lesbian.
At the time, I was identifying as straight.
I am now playing an out lesbian and am an out lesbian.
But you're manifesting pilot this time, right?
So I'm going to be a pilot next.
But the funny thing is there was a time in the middle
where I was like, I cannot believe how problematic it is
that I, as a straight woman, played a lesbian on that show.
That's so terrible.
And now it's fine.
It's actually the only reason she became a lesbian.
There's a cover for that.
That's my testimony from being on pretending to be people.
I became gay.
I love it.
What have you guys done for the show?
Anyways.
OK, so back into the Sprinter van, the back of the van.
You guys have this information.
You know that it is called Bigfoot Underground Search
and Hunt.
The ringleader's name is Carl Lambert.
The other two people helping out
with Bigfoot Underground Search and Hunt
are Janice Ruth, who is a conservation agent
and Bigfoot expert,
and an undercover Delta Green agent named Jerome Dyer,
who has been in the field now for three years
working with this group.
So clearly, he saw something early on with him
that showed him, I need to stick with these people
and make sure nothing crazy happens because they
seem to be onto something.
So Dr. Rusty Hooch picks up this ID
that's got her face on it, her bangs,
and the name Dr. Ann Falsom.
So hold on.
Are the rest of us playing pretend characters?
You can be anyone you want.
You can present yourselves as whatever kind of team
you would like.
But this is just a way to get through the front gate,
if you will, a way to get in the door.
So Dr. Ann Falsom's credentials are she is a, sorry,
medical doctor?
And Bigfoot enthusiast, who has been posting she,
quote unquote, this hand letter as Dr. Ann Falsom has been
posting comments and DMing back and forth with the Bigfoot
Underground Search and Hunt YouTube page.
So they're going to trust her immediately.
Yes, because she would be the obvious first choice
to call upon finding an actual body
so that they can have someone who
is respected, quote unquote, in the field
to present their discovery.
What are the skills they would expect from this Dr. Falsom,
whatever her name is?
They want her to come in and be like, yes, this is Bigfoot.
They want her to probably name it scientifically, right?
And then just be there standing, like a product that
is for sale, but no one wants to buy it.
So they have a doctor come on the screen and be like,
I'm a doctor.
So Dr. Miller agrees that a rusty hooch can take on the role
as this pretend doctor and say, I'll
be your second in command then.
I'll support you.
Are we like med students?
Yeah, we're part of the team.
I think to make it more believable,
maybe just say we're med students like first year,
like here to offer hands.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Dr. Hooch is pretty, she's having
a lot of mixed emotions right now
because she grabbed the ID because she's really
feeling like she's surrounded by idiots,
except for Dr. Miller, who she's extremely intimidated by.
And it's pretty clear that Dr. Miller is smarter than me.
So that's why she chose to grab that ID first.
But she is getting a little anxious about it
now because she actually doesn't believe in Bigfoot
and has no idea what she's about to get into.
I wonder if Dr. Miller senses that.
And she's just like, no, show us the way.
I'm sure it will be fine.
And then like, rinse.
She grins and can see like her teeth,
like in a very predatory way, like.
Who's driving?
I'll drive.
Damn straight.
Dr. Miller, may I call you Olivia or Liv
or the Livmeister?
Like what terms are we on here?
Dr. Miller is fine, thank you.
You guys are on a 50-minute drive from Shreveport,
Mississippi, all the way up into the fucking
boonies of Arkansas.
So when you guys are driving through Arkansas,
it is late at night.
You're coming up on, let's see, 2230, 2330.
So it's around 11.15 PM.
You're 15 minutes out from the destination.
And you're driving through the mountains
and you're driving through the mountains
You're 15 minutes out from the destination
and you start hitting windy turns deep into the woods.
You haven't seen a gas station or any business
in 10 minutes or so.
And you're not sure that there's anyone,
any business that is further into these woods.
Every once in a while, you'll see a small house
or a trailer deep kind of hidden in the woods
on either side of the road,
that is it's like a archway of trees and thick branches.
So you can barely even make out the night sky above you.
You're in a part of the country where you'd feel
fairly uncomfortable if this Sprinter van
were to break down.
Yeah, I've been in those parts of Arkansas.
Well, cool, I have not.
Your GPS is getting closer and closer.
And as you get toward it,
you're starting to lose cell signal.
And you remember that your handler mentioned Jerome Dyer,
Agent Dyer was sabotaging the cell signal up here
so that no photos or videos of this body
that they've taken can get out.
So as you're losing signal,
your dot begins to just kind of float
and there are no more roads on the screen,
but you can kind of make out where you are
in relation to where the dot that you're headed toward is.
And eventually you see a mailbox in the darkness,
your headlights lighting it up.
And there's a road that leads off to the left gravel road
with a gate, a red metal gate.
Y'all, I'm so sorry, but we got to go back.
I actually need cell service for another hour.
We got to go back, I'm sorry.
There's something I got to check on.
What do you got to check on?
It doesn't matter, it's my own personal business.
We just got to go back for,
can we just come back in an hour?
I mean, these people have been out here, what, three years?
They can wait another hour.
I think Rusty's keeping secrets from us.
Doreen who is driving does not say anything
and just keeps driving.
It's like solid as a rock.
Oh my God, Doreen is drunk from the beer she drank.
We're letting a drunk driver take us to this gate.
If you want me to drive, I could drive now.
That'd be fine.
Rusty, maybe you and I can have a side adventure.
You and I can walk back together, find that cell service.
If you look at me one more time.
Maybe become best friends.
I swear to God, I will break your neck.
Man, damn.
Fasty lady.
I don't know, I like that.
Dr. Miller is just staring out through our window,
listening to Chucky and Rusty going back and forth
and then she's like, we could be as quick as possible
so we can get back as soon as possible,
but I think we should head on.
I mean, we're here on a mission.
I know they've been out here for three years,
but I've seen some things to worry
that there might be more of an emergency.
I just want to take a look at it
and then I'll make sure that you get back in time
for whatever phone call it is that you have to make.
Dr. Hooch is extremely intimidated
by the doctor and concedes.
Oh, you know, by the end of this,
I think we're going to be best friends.
I sure hope so.
Chuckster, you noticed that there is a file
that is sitting on the counter space,
you know, next to one of the chairs here
in the back of this mobile lab.
And when you pop it open,
it's got a little bit more information about the mission,
including a code for the gate.
Hey, look, I found this file here
and it seems like it's got a bunch of information.
Maybe even has a code to the gate.
Has your voice changed?
It's very possible.
I think you went pretty hard Southern
after going pretty hard, like excited bro.
It's going to wander where it wants.
Don't expect consistency in any manner from me.
I love it so much.
When you got into Mississippi and Arkansas,
you started code switching super hard.
I just want everyone to be comfortable.
Yeah, you're just, you're basically conforming
to where we are a little bit, yeah.
It's also just where every accent goes
when I try to do an accent.
I just have the one.
I snatched the paper from Chuck
because I say, give me this.
You don't, you probably don't even know how to read.
Let me see this.
Yeah, you write after, I'm not very smart man.
I'm not very smart man.
This is the gamer guy who is like,
just stoked to be like, hey, what up, what up?
How you living like?
Just because I'm confident doesn't mean I'm combative.
I respect these ladies, these smart ladies.
Honored to be in their presence.
Dr. Miller is like, I'm going to die.
And so she starts writing down on her cell phone
without cell service.
She's starting to write down a note for her daughter.
So just like, if I don't survive,
you can take like, there's the money in this account.
And then your asshole father has the rest of the money
stashed away somewhere else.
She knows she's not going to survive this.
Doreen asks for the code.
She reaches back and grabs another beer.
She's just stressed.
She grabs another beer out of the pocket of Chuckie's pants
and just chucks the whole thing right there.
As you pull up to this gate,
you see it's an alpha numerical keyboard
that you're looking at.
It literally looks like an old,
like Macintosh keyboard from like 09
that is like the clear blue,
colorful keyboard that is like almost duct taped
to a stick that's been shoved into the ground
and there are wires coming out of it
and then going down toward the ground.
And then you kind of see the wires above ground
going toward this big rusty red gate.
The code is Bush.
Well, it's Bigfoot underground search and hunt.
They call themselves Bush.
Doreen takes a huge sigh
and then leans her whole upper body out of the window.
Do you want to do that?
Boop, boop, boop, boop.
Oh, it took a long time to hit that H, huh?
Doreen is, she might be a little bit above the-
A little faded.
Yeah, she's a little faded.
That's okay, she's capable.
As you type in the H, the gate slowly begins to-
Beeee!
It finally stops.
In an open position.
God damn it.
And then you-
Yeah.
The gate is open.
Let's do this.
Ahead of you is the same kind of thing
where there are trees climbing on either side
and then meeting above the driveway.
It's a long gravel driveway that goes uphill
and then seems to make a slight dogwood left
where you see that there's a clearing
and lights are coming from a small one room
corrugated sheet metal type just room
that has been laid on maybe not even a legit foundation.
So is this like a shack, like a big-
Yeah, it's a big shack.
Okay.
And then it's like shoddily put together
so there's like light coming through cracks.
Yes, that is exactly right.
Yes.
All right.
And there's one streetlight that like,
it looks like they might've literally stolen
a public streetlight and then moved it up by this shack
and the light is shining down on a truck
that is sitting up there.
Were we given anything in the van?
Oh, there's shitloads of stuff in the van.
Okay.
Weapons.
Not so much weapons as just like lab equipment,
anything you might find in an ambulance.
I like to, because you're up against
such insurmountable odds,
I wanna give you everything you need to try to fight back.
So anything that you think of that could be in there
is probably in there and that's just a nice way
to know that you're fucked.
Dr. Mill almost automatically starts scrubbing up
like if there's any protective gear, masks,
anything of just like assuming that they're gonna go
into a fucking shit show of, I don't know.
She's very paranoid at this point.
And she's assuming that all these dumb asses
will do the same but then she realizes maybe
that none of them are doing it
or I don't know what they are doing
but she's just like, oh, perhaps we should,
like she's trying to be polite but then like, oh no.
Yeah, you kind of point at the three other hazmat suits.
I'm just like opening drawers and not closing them
and like opening cabinets, like rifling through.
Like, what's this?
Oh, dope.
Doreen is just like rolling her eyes at Chucky
and like grabbing her weapons that she just of course
has on her as an agent and just putting them
in the back of the van,
getting ready to put the hazmat suit on
and Chucky is just staring with his mouth open
at all of the weapons she has.
And then she just is staring back at him
while she's slowly pulling up her hazmat suit.
Oh, dude, I think you and I are gonna be BFF-les.
We got some fortune comin'!
What's the L?
Liver.
Pretty sure.
It's best friends. Pretty sure.
I think it's liver.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You wanna see my weapons?
I can show you.
I got throwing stars.
I think it's time.
I pull them out and then they're engraved.
I have C.
C.
Oh my God.
What's my last name?
Oh, C.
Cheese.
Cheese!
Okay, change my mind.
Engraved in each of them is just like-
Just cheese.
A cheddar.
It says CCC and then under it there's-
A block of cheddar.
Yeah, chunk of cheddar.
Yeah.
It's very good.
Please just keep those in your pants.
Don't pull those out, please.
All right, all right, I understand.
Dr. Hooch is very preoccupied with Dr. Miller at this point
and she's really fascinated by how professional she's being.
So she is sort of trying to imitate it,
immediately starts putting on a hazmat suit as well,
also starts putting on gloves and things.
And she's still in the backseat,
but she's like kinda leaning forward
so that Dr. Miller will see
that she's like taking it seriously now.
Ooh.
Dr. Miller smiles a little bit to herself
and then she turns around to the other two.
He's just like, whenever you're ready,
we shall have Dr. Hooch lead the way.
Dr.
Dr. Anne Hooch.
Actually- Dr. Anne.
What's your name? Falsom.
What's your name?
Falsom.
Anne Falsom. Falsom.
F-A-L-S-O-M.
Oh, right, no, Dr. Falsom, sorry.
Dr. Falsom, sorry, I forgot.
You're such a famed Nobel Prize winner,
so you did cure happiness, whatever.
I've cured- I've cured-
Mad pal disease.
Which is the cause of sadness.
Very true.
I start putting on my hazmat suit.
I don't know how well it can be one of these doctors,
these medical students,
so maybe you guys could teach me some terms.
I know the word scalpel, and-
Scalpel.
I know the word liver,
and what other doctor terms could I know?
Dorian's like, I think we should just both
keep our mouth shut.
Now that's exactly what I was gonna propose too.
How about Dr. Anne Falser, Falsom?
You do the talking. You look at the ID again.
Dorian helps Chuck put on his hazmat suit
because he gets his hands-
He gets his arms tangled,
since somehow both arms are in one arm hole.
Dorian is starting to find Chuckie a little bit endearing.
She's kind of like, okay, I'll take care of you.
Pat, pat.
Does he remind you of your whippet?
He kind of reminds me of my whippet, yes.
This is pretty useless.
She's like, I don't want my dog on this trip.
I might as well just take care of this kid.
I start mimicking, she's Pavlov to me,
and I start like,
Good God.
Dr. Miller walks up to Chuck.
If there is any weapons, do we have weapons there?
You said you would give us anything, right?
Oh yeah, what do you find?
I would like to find an automatic rifle,
or something that deals a lot of damage
that Chuck would know how to use.
Yeah, absolutely.
I also have my go pack, so I'm ready.
I got my pistol, I got my knuckle busters,
my throwing stars, and my switchblade.
If you want to find something
that has a little bit more firepower,
then there is a rifle in the back.
I think Dr. Miller finds something,
but she is not able to herself use it,
and so she walks over to Chuck, and it's just like,
now listen to me carefully, boy.
If you see something, if you see something,
stop panting, it makes you look dumb.
Sorry, ma'am.
It's okay.
If you see something, I want you to not think,
I want you to shoot, okay?
The door opens.
Oh God.
Not that, don't shoot that.
I look confused.
If you see something that you might find strange,
and might attack, I don't know if the other two
will be able to do it,
but I guess with your quick reactions and presence,
I'm sure that you will be the quickest to act.
Whatever terrible thing we're gonna see in there,
I wanted to not leave this room.
Chuck harkens back to his short-lived military days,
and really likes having a leader tell him what to do,
so he stands in line, mission ready, and says, yes ma'am.
You better be ready, Dr. Miller.
He's gonna piss in your bed.
Yeah.
And she's like, oh God, what have I done?
I start to pull a beer out of my refrigerator pants,
and Dr. Miller slaps it out of my hand.
Maybe, if she wants to.
Oh, hell yeah.
Or she's like, perhaps later, perhaps later.
Yes, yes ma'am, yes ma'am.
Let's go, yes ma'am.
And she taps his shoulder a little harder than necessary,
but I'm thinking like maybe he likes the roughness.
Yeah, and then he does a little burp.
Okay.
You truly are a child, like a young infant child.
Y'all, I got a question real fast before we go inside.
Oh my God, this could just keep happening forever.
The getting ready stage.
Do you think that Dr. Anne Falsom
should have a British accent?
I just wonder if they'll believe me more.
The front door opens.
It's a metal door of this metal corrugated shack,
and walking out backwards is seemingly Carl Lambert.
He is in his early 40s, and he is slightly overweight,
severely balding, wears a dirty tank top,
and as he's walking backwards,
his love handles on either side
are kind of jiggling with each step as he walks backwards,
and as your eyes go up to the top of his head,
he has a makeshift headband, like a t-shirt,
like a ratty old t-shirt that's been ripped,
and is now tied around his head.
He is talking to the camera that is being run
by seemingly Janice Ruth, and then behind her even,
you see a man, you can assume this is Agent Dyer,
and he is kind of a small, thin man
wearing big, thin-rimmed glasses,
and Carl Lambert is talking directly to the camera,
and he's like,
welcome to another Bush product.
Hey, what up, Bushheads out there?
Everybody wants to come on down,
and we got something big for you.
I know we say that a lot,
and if we get a knock on the wood,
or if we get, I mean, the other day,
when we had that knock, I swear to God,
that is what the, I'm getting ahead of myself.
We are going to meet with the one,
the only, Dr. Anne Falsom today.
You've seen her comment on the messaging board,
and you know what she's been up to,
and you know that she is the only one
we would call if we were to,
and then he gets right up into the camera,
and he's like, actually find and kill a big fight.
It happened!
Yes, I am so excited for you.
Smash that like and subscribe,
comment below when you see this thing.
All right, now, let's talk Dr. Anne Falsom here,
and let's get into the thing going.
And he turns around,
camera is still coming towards you guys,
and you can kind of hear from behind his weird growl,
you hear this camerawoman is just kind of like,
hmm, hmm, hmm, just kind of like breathing heavy,
you know, just your normal camera person
who has something like wheezing in her throat constantly.
So if you were to watch Bush videos,
then you would be hearing that in the background
pretty much the whole time.
And she brought her team!
He's looking, Carl is looking back and forth
between all four of you to see kind of who steps forward.
Very frazzled, Rusty quickly decides
to go for a British accent, steps forward.
Chuck steps forward with her, and then she pushes him back.
I shove Chuck back in his place.
Hello, my name is Dr. Anne Falsom.
Aw, yeah, and you can even tell how smart she is
because the way she says words nice.
Hey, Dr. Falsom, it is an absolute pleasure
to finally meet you on camera.
That's correct, it is.
Are you channeling Joe Rogan right now?
I'm sorry, go on.
No!
I've never, I haven't seen him since Fear Factor.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're not a rogue head?
I don't know, is that true?
I'm a Bush boy.
Doctor, doctor, doctor,
I know that I said that I promised you a body,
and what I have is, I guarantee you,
and he looks again at the camera,
the first taken and held and killed corpse
of a Bigfoot that's ever been found, ever,
and we've got it here.
Dr. Falsom, what are your thoughts on the situation?
First of all, I don't want to be on camera.
His eyes turn to pure sadness,
and he kind of pushes the camera away.
But I thought you were a fan.
I prefer to keep my identity private,
and my team as well,
and I will be the judge of whether or not this is a Bigfoot.
Everybody roll alertness.
I got a five.
Oh, what is your alertness?
20%.
Oh, then that is a success.
For rolling rules, if you're new to Delta Green,
if you roll under your skill, then that is a success.
So you want to roll as high as possible without going over.
Price is right rules.
If someone's trying to steal something from you,
like in this instance,
they would want to roll higher than you
in order to succeed.
So what did you roll, Taylor?
A 43.
On a?
On an 80.
Oh, so that is a success as well.
Yeah.
Eleanor, what did you roll?
An 11, alertness 20, so.
And your dice match.
Yep.
And it's under.
All right, so that's our first critical success.
So we have our first critical success.
Yay!
Ooh, all right, nice.
Nice.
Not that it matters, but Lindsay, what did you roll?
Well, I did crit fail.
Oh my God.
Those beers hit her hard.
The beers, yeah.
And I'm also just so paranoid.
I think I just like don't want to be here at all,
but I also really, this is the only thing I'm living for.
There's a lot inside of you.
It's a mixture of me and my mom in real life.
Okay, so with that being said,
let's take a quick pause because Discord is messing up.
You want me to whistle a song?
Yeah, I'd love that.
What was it called?
It's called a little jig.
A jig.
That's beautiful.
A little jig, yes.
A wee little jig.
I shush away, but ever jigging me.
Oh God.
I should have gone with that for my dog accent.
I just want to say,
if ever given the opportunity to have more than one accent,
I will take it.
The last time I got to play a fucking shit.
Zach, you're doing a great job.
I'm losing my mind.
You're doing such a good job.
Thanks guys, I appreciate that.
Quiet on set.
Hello.
Lindsay, during Marine,
because of the critical fail, roll sanity.
Damn it.
Yeah.
Come on, you stupid ass.
Jesus Christ, Doreen is down that ladder.
We have a crazy person in our midst.
Seven.
Oh, success.
While this whole conversation is happening
about whether or not Dr. Anne Folsom
is going to be on camera or not,
you turn around and you see yourself
in the reflection of the driver's side mirror
of this sprinter van and a chill runs down your spine.
And right when you think you're about to hear laughter,
you're almost fucking expecting it at this point.
Nothing happens.
And you're just staring at yourself in this reflection.
And it's honestly probably the first time in a minute
you've been able to just hold eye contact with yourself.
And it kind of feels good to see and be seen individually.
With your critical success, Eleanor,
Dr. Olivia Miller is the only one who notices
that Janice Ruth, oh, she's still filming.
She may have pointed the camera away from Dr. Anne Folsom,
but she did not stop recording.
All right, yeah, no, I understand, I understand.
It's just that I really thought you were a fan.
And I thought that the whole point of you coming out here
was gonna be that you were going to be on camera
talking about the body.
Well, we're talking about science.
So I need to step inside and take a look at the situation
before I allow anyone to record anything.
Okay, so can we try this again?
But it's just me, but then I'll let you see the body.
And then after that, then you'll be on camera.
I don't know, I need to be let inside.
You're wasting our time.
Nice.
Roll persuade.
Please.
I got a 94 on a 20.
I mean, I suppose, can't Dr. Miller step in?
Oh yeah, absolutely.
Especially since Dr. Miller critically succeeded
and notices that Janice Ruth is still recording.
So you can use that kind of maybe as leverage here.
Excuse me, Dr. Anne Folsom did say specifically
that she did not wanna be on camera.
And yet I see that you're still recording.
Is that how we're going to work here?
Is that what we do as friends?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I didn't, I didn't, I didn't notice.
And she's like fumbling her thumb for the record button.
She's like, I really, I didn't know.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Can I roll like a first aid or something
to see what the hell, like see what's going on with her?
Yeah, absolutely.
You can roll a first aid.
First aid or is that, does that make sense?
Maybe not first aid, but like medicine, medicine.
Yeah, medicine works, yeah.
Whichever one you have more of.
52 on a 60, so who?
Ooh, nice.
So you would know that Janice Ruth has health issues,
specifically maybe some untreated asthma.
Okay, so this is not something to be that worried about.
No, she's just very stressed out and excited.
And she's also really worried seemingly
that she did something bad.
You're getting onto her, which she's not used to.
And she's just like, I'm sorry, I didn't know.
It's okay.
I was just trying, I was just trying.
Calm down, just calm down.
So you see her click it off and the camera's off.
All right, all right, yeah, come on in, come on in.
We've just been doing, you know, some photo shoots,
I guess, with the body.
It's actually laying on the pool table.
So come on in.
And you see, as you guys are turning back
and looking at this one door shack,
one room, one door, corrugated metal room.
Jerome Dyer, this small thin man
wearing these large glasses with thin frames
is just kind of leaning up against the corrugated metal
next to the door.
Hello?
Who are you?
Jerome, you can just call me Jerome.
You know me, Bush, Dr. Anfalsom.
Yes, I do know you very well.
You both fucking wink at each other,
like enormous winks, like huge winks.
Oh, I know who you are.
And then I'm like, no, shut up, shut up.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
And then I just put a fist out.
He like taps on it with one finger
and is like testing one, two.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, nice to meet you.
That was so dope.
This guy's funny.
I just walk inside, cause I'm over the bullshit.
I'm coming with her.
Everybody going inside?
Yeah, I wanna see this thing.
Chuckster.
You going inside?
Hell yeah, bro.
There he is, there he is.
Yeah, I'm gonna, I'm gonna waver between country boy and.
It just depends on who's talking to you.
Chuckster, the code switch king.
All right, so you guys all need to roll sanity.
Oh, fuck.
I got a 41 on a 56.
That is a success.
I got a 54 on a 56.
That is also, the doctors have succeeded.
I got a 10 on a 60.
Also a success.
52 on a 40.
Oh no.
And there's the fail, there's the fail.
This is not what you were expecting
and it's also not good.
So even though you passed,
the three of you who rolled under your sanity
still lose one sanity.
Chuckster.
Yep.
No article for you this time.
You.
Serious.
You are going to roll a D4,
which is the pyramid.
And then you are going to add one
and you are going to lose that many sanity.
Four.
Rolled a, rolled a big old four.
So I lose five sanity, I'm now at 35.
Jesus.
There's a thing that happens in this game
when you lose five sanity.
As you guys all know,
and pretending to be people when you lose one sanity,
you have to do a shot of hard liquor
when you lose two to three sanity,
you have to rip a bong,
and then anything past that,
you have to do a fat line.
Ellie, if you'll open the package that we sent you.
I was like, I'm trying to lose some sanity.
Yeah, but also guys,
you have so much money,
like being able to send cocaine.
It's what all the Patreon money.
When you lose five sanity in Delta Green,
what happens is that you have a temporary break from reality
in which you react in an uncontrollable way.
So you are either going to fight, fight.
What did I say first?
Fight.
Or fight.
What I was wanting to do was I'm frozen,
but I'm just going cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
Okay, normally you would roll,
but I think that that's really funny.
So we're going to go with that.
You can kind of like look at the face.
I think the camera is just hitting the face
of Charles Chuck, the Chuck Steer Chuck,
as he's doing cool, cool.
And then the camera kind of slowly pans around
until we can see what all of you are looking at,
which is this corpse that is on the pool table laid out.
This corpse is not the corpse of a Bigfoot, however.
It's a child.
It's a wrinkled corpse of a child,
completely covered in dark purple bruises.
Seems to be a preteen.
This thing is riddled with holes
from 12 gauge shotgun slugs.
Blood has been pouring from these holes onto the pool table,
which has a tarp down that the blood is pooling onto.
And this bruised body just sits lifeless.
For those of you who only lost one sanity,
you see the eyes of Carl Lambert
as they fill up with tears.
Michael, what the fuck?
For a moment.
Oh, that's the end of the episode.
What?
I want to say, hooch is in deep.
Amazing.
Fine, I'll save that joke for later.
Maybe for not this scene.
Dear God.
Wow.
Shit.
That was really cool.
So that's the end of episode two.
That was really cool, thank you.
Thanks for playing.
For, I was not sure if that was what they knew was there
until the Carl Lambert moment.
And then I was like, fuck.
I have theories.
Maybe I'll save it for air,
but I have theories of what's going on.
See rings of deafening people.
You don't know where you found it.
In this state as your eyes fall short,
you better learn how to keep it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Clasp your fist over all the blood.
Water leaks through your fingers.
You're standing in a swirling flood.
And only darkness leads you.
Ooh.
Falling fast into deep abyss.
Till it tears you out again.
Find your feet on your broken bones.
Clear out the edge again.
You're standing in a swirling flood.