Well, how do you do, pupparoos?
It's your grown-ass pup mother, Wolf the dog.
And I am here to provide nourishment for your wittle ears.
It's also live, I'm told.
From 694.2 PTBP, maybe.
The only radio station that can broadcast
in multiple dimensions, probably.
But what I'm rock solid for sure about
is the fact that we got a new Howlin' with Wolf,
everyone named Wolf's favorite segment.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from
Nick with Everything's a Mimic,
who tweeted about the show and tagged that pretending pod,
which is, whoa, something you can do too, dear listener.
So cool of you, wow.
Nick with Everything's a Mimic writes,
hello, Mr. Dog, long-time listener, first-time writer.
Normally, I would take this opportunity
to shout out the actual play podcast, Everything's a Mimic,
and our players, Ryan D, Ryan B, Chris, Cody, and Andy.
Normally, this would also be the perfect time
to shout out our website, Everything's a Mimic dot com.
But now is just not that time,
for I have seen the yellow sign.
Its insignia dances carelessly and purposely
in and out of the black void of our empty vessels
like the ebb and flow of the ocean's embrace.
The pallid mask seeks all who are willing,
and, oh shit, I ran out of characters.
Love you, PTBP boys.
Thanks for the love, Nick with Everything's a Mimic.
Can anyone who knows what the fuck a podcast is
tell me what an actual play is?
Do they actually do things?
Or do they imaginarily do things?
Is an actual play like a real Shakespeare?
I'm so confused by the internet and all it beholds.
One day, when I remember my AOL password,
I'll get to get back on there and see what's poppin'.
If you wanna write up somethin' for your wolf to howl,
tag at PretendingPod on the internets.
Or don't, what do I care?
Though I will say it warms my producer's bones
every time he sees kind words written about pretending
to be people out there on the damn internet.
So if you wanna positively impact my producer's day,
and maybe write some words for wolf to say,
tag at PretendingPod and check out this segue.
One gave me a bruise, the other gave me the blues.
The first part's a segue, and next it's the news.
The boy on the table, Carl Lambert's long-lost brother,
who somehow hasn't aged in three decades,
seems to have been bitten by something
that looks a bit like a tick.
But it's got more than eight legs,
and last I recall, ticks can't normally
phase through matter, like if they wanted
to get into Doreen Morreen's boot
just by pullin' some kind of Hayden Christensen
and Jumper nonsense.
But this here is, indeed, some Jake Gyllenhaal
crawlin' around with Danny DeVito
while chasin' car crashes in his blue kinda stuff.
The Chuckster hollowed for Agent Morreen
to pour some of the potion out of the cauldron
and into her boot, which she promptly did.
Hopefully, luckily, this elixir was exceptionally brewed
by Dr. Rusty Hooch, all while Dr. Olivia Miller
just stared at the rash around the bite
on the unnaturally young boy's bruised and bloodied chest.
The rash rippled like waves from the terrible epicenter,
and the flushed bumps formed a target
on the most recent victim's body.
Unrelated, here's Molly Healy with Circles.
["Circles of Death"]
So I was writing down secret things
that I'm not allowed to see, but it's in my eye line.
That's like when people are like,
"'Don't look at my cards,"
and they're like showing you their cards.
It's like, it's not my decision,
my mental decision to look at your cards,
but physically, my body will turn towards your cards.
Yeah, like guess what, bitch?
God helps those who help themselves, so hide it.
Oh my God, I love God.
["Circles of Death"]
["In the Arms of the Angel"]
You know when you're just like loving God?
Sarah McLachlan.
All right, Ellie.
I, uh.
All right.
You first.
Did you open your email, Zach?
Oh God, what?
I don't know if it's linked to your email, though.
It might not be, nevermind.
Eleanor Tilleranzo just became a patron
of pretending to be people at one of the coolest tiers.
420?
No, 420 a month would be a hell of a Patreon tier.
She's at the $6.66 level.
Yeah, hell yeah.
You can be a patron at the $5 level
at patreon.com slash pretending pod,
and you can get all of our bonus audio content there,
including full episodes of full Delta Green
like home brew campaign that I ran for the boys,
and you can have Taylor's phone call fully sound
as your ringtone.
Ring, ring.
It's on.
But I think Chuck's version of it would be like,
bring, bring, bring, bring, bring, bring, bring.
Bring it, bro.
All right, but Eleanor signed up
at the much cooler $6.66 level,
which is all the exact same rewards.
It's just a cooler number.
Yeah, and I wanna be cool.
So far, so good.
Right, right, right?
No, I was never cool, but I was cold.
My heart is dead.
No, I'm kidding.
What were you like in school?
I was a slut, to be honest.
If you guys haven't figured it out,
but I was totally, at least by American standards.
But I wasn't judged for it, which was great.
Oh, that's great.
That's nice.
I was fondling the D and the P all up in high school,
but no one really judged me for it.
Wait, what's the difference between the D and the P?
One is a hole and one is like a thing
that really shoves things into a hole.
Wait, what are you putting in between the penis
and the vagina to have sex?
I get it.
You shoving something in?
No, no, the P stands for, okay,
the P stands for pussy, pussy.
I thought you were like,
I'm playing with dicks and penises,
and I'm like, I don't wanna discredit your sluttiness,
but that's the same damn thing.
Yeah, you would also be like,
that's when you find out I was lying.
I'm like, I was playing with something called the dick
and I'm the penis with my vagina.
I stuck my vagina inside his penis.
That's how you do it, right?
And then I got pregnant.
No, I didn't.
That was a lot later.
Pretending to be teen pregnant.
You're like, Junie's actually 10 years old.
I know she's just developing a little slower.
Swedish babies take a little longer to cook.
We're like elves, 3,000 years old,
but it's like, oh, or baby Yoda.
Spoilers.
Spoilers, baby Yoda exists.
Yo, are you watching Boba Fett?
So here's the thing, Zach,
when you become a parent,
you have to basically choose your form of entertainment
because you have 10 minutes a day, maybe.
And I've put mine into Yellowstone, great show,
in case you guys haven't checked it out
because I'm super into Western awful people, apparently.
So that's who I like to watch.
Hell yeah, that rules.
I don't know what, I was just gonna talk about
how Thundercat is the cameo in the last episode
of Boba Fett and it made me so happy.
He's a bass player who's fucking awesome.
He's like-
Wait.
Thundercat, like the Thundercats, like the lion?
No, that would be so fucking rad.
No, it's a very cool musician
who Taylor is singing Dragon Ball Durag right now,
which is a bop.
Such a fun song.
Such a good song.
He's such a cool guy.
He like wears like-
It's like kimono print boxers that are like silky.
Dragon Ball Z embroidered logo on them.
It's like, he's a nerd and he's sexy
and he makes dope music and he's in Star Wars now.
So he's my hero.
Wait, Boba Fett is Star Wars?
Oh my God.
Yeah, Boba Fett is the assassin, right?
Like he's a hired, to me, the clone's out of him.
All right, midichlorians, let's dive into the-
The fourth episode of-
Live long and may the peace be on upon you.
Give you peace as you sleep and may you know
that the Lord, your God, loves you very, very much.
That is what my parents said to me every night
before I went to sleep and dreamed about demons.
Let's go.
So much to unpack.
Oh yeah, we all have religious trauma in this house.
Really, I need to know so much because I'm such an atheist.
Oh shit.
Raise your hand if you've spoken in tongues at this table.
What?
Yeah, that's two of us who acted like we were communicating
with the other side and no one thought it was cool.
It was like we were wearing khakis when we did it.
Like it wasn't fucking rad, it was lame and it's also cool.
I don't know, the church should lean into metal imagery
and I'd be way more into it.
All right, let's actually, let's play a game.
I like a bit of chitchat, but I'm very interested
to see what happens next and I have to know.
So let's get into this.
Well, it's like it's your choice.
You're either gonna let my cool ass boot move work
or Doreen, I guess, I don't know, loses a foot.
I don't know what's happening.
I do.
I have a sense, unfortunately, of what's about to happen.
Oh, unfortunately.
You know what, Zach?
I'll just take over from here.
Okay, sounds good.
Okay, so a little bit of meta game,
outside of the game knowledge,
just because it might be good to know this.
Okay, sometimes I just try to talk
and the thing I say is dumb and stupid, so.
Zach, I'm gonna need you to roll sanity for me.
Oh, that happens to me all the time.
I've had a new catchphrase around the house recently
when Taylor's like, what did you just say?
I say, I'm allowed to say stupid things.
He's been saying it so often.
I've been saying a lot of stupid shit recently.
You're not allowed to divorce me
because I say stupid things.
Just because I'm an idiot
doesn't mean you should love me any less.
He blamed COVID quite a bit.
Yeah.
Apparently COVID makes you dumber.
Yeah, I'm a fucking idiot now.
When I was pregnant, I blamed it all the time.
I'm like, guys, it's the pregnancy brain,
you know, it's the mom brain.
And so every time I say something dumb,
it's what I blame.
But one day you realize it's all a lie, Zach.
I know.
You're just stupid.
Well, I'd been doing dry January
and so previously I was like,
it's just cause I'm high all the time.
But apparently, no, it's not.
So I-
Oh wait, for dry January,
you're not allowed to smoke either?
Well, that's what I gave a go.
Zach set rules.
You're doing sober January.
He's doing fully clear mind January.
Until last night and I'm-
All right, but I'll get back.
I'll get back on for the rest of the month.
How about that?
Taylor gave me a look like, really, motherfucker?
Well, last night he's like, I think I'm done.
I think January is over.
It's February negative 11th.
Yep.
Amazing.
February, the shittiest month.
Like it always gets treated so poorly.
It's like you get 28 days
and now minus 11.
The 39 days of February.
All right, let's-
On the negative 10th day of February,
I drink a beer.
God fucking scared.
All right, let us begin.
He can't decide if he's going to let my cool thing happen.
Have faith.
George Michael this situation and let's get into it.
We were in dexterity order.
It was during Marine's turn.
Now it is Dr. Miller's turn.
Oh no, I hate, wait.
Right at the top of the episode.
Yeah, fuck, man.
Okay, so just like a brief little thing,
what was summary of what happened.
Eleanor, that's a really good point.
Let's give a quick rundown of everything that happened
in each of your introductions.
No, I'm just kidding.
So you guys got here,
you got your hazmat suits on ready to go.
They came out with the camera to shoot a Bush video.
You told them, hey, I'm not here to be on camera
until I know this shit is real.
Let's get inside.
As you get inside, you all see not the body of a Bigfoot,
but rather the blues and bruddy body of a 12 year old boy
who is just filled with bullet holes from a 12 gauge.
And there's just blood everywhere pouring onto this tarp
that he's laying on, which is on a pool table.
Carl yells out for his younger brother, Michael,
and he's just begins weeping and weeping.
Michael, his brother who disappeared at age 12,
Carl and his dad both said that Bigfoot had abducted
this boy.
That's what they remember happening in their minds.
That's how they must've explained it to themselves
to try to explain it to other people.
And so now everyone's kind of running around.
Dr. Miller's looking at the body.
Doreen Marine has grabbed this substance, this potion,
if you will, that's in a tiny cauldron
for some goddamn reason.
And then she's pouring it into her boot because Charles,
the Chuckster has screamed that she needs to pour this
into her boot.
Not knowing what's actually in this potion
could just be acid that melts her entire fucking foot off.
I mean, whatever you gotta do.
Dr. Hooch is the one who's created
this pharmaceutical remedy with a critical success
while in the lab.
Janice is on the ground underneath Charles, the Chuckster,
who has just disarmed her and is keeping her.
I feel like you're kind of like on her back a little bit.
Yeah, I've got my knee down kind of over her.
Riding her like a pony.
Absolutely.
That's some genuine Chuckster moves right there.
Jump on it.
I'm doing like a little lasso, fake lasso spin.
Janice.
And Carl and Jerome are kind of in this weird back and forth
where Carl keeps rolling fails on his sanity
to kind of get upset,
but Jerome keeps rolling really well to calm him down
and they're fucking homies.
And you can tell guys, as you're looking at the two of them,
their bond seems to be unshakable.
These two dudes have lived life together
for the past three years.
Honestly, it's cool to see men of this age
being so emotionally full.
Yeah, fucking gay man.
And this is why it's hard for,
yeah, it's hard to be a man in 2018.
Yeah.
Woe is the white man.
Cause Ali's always calling me gay.
I'm such a bully.
Yeah, wait, that's bullying to call me gay, Ali?
Yeah, because being gay is so bad.
Oh no.
Quick reminder for the audience.
Gays suck.
Oh my God.
Double down.
I prefer calling him weak, emotionally weak.
Holy shit.
I'm rubber, you're glue.
You like pussy and I like you.
We talked about that last episode.
What if you guys found out I'm super homophobic
or something awesomely awful?
Right in the middle of the fourth episode,
you're a bigot and we're like, what the fuck?
Yeah, no, but honestly guys.
I can't wait to leave a review on how I was treated
on this podcast.
I think we're now, we stayed very on track
with the rundown of what's happened so far.
And I think that probably gave Dr. Miller enough time
to figure out exactly what she's doing
with this first turn of her round.
What is that?
I've been trying to, I've been trying to catch
this little tick for the past 60 rounds.
So I think if she can see it now, can she see it now?
Can we all see it?
Nope.
Does she know that it went in the boot?
It does not.
Oh, it already went into the boot.
Oh shit.
Then.
Oh, I'm sorry, fuck.
I mean, you should have all assumed
because I had her pour a potion down in her boot.
Yeah, you could maybe yell something in character right now
for just the story to make sense, I guess,
maybe a little bit.
It's the alien bomb.
Bug.
Where is it?
In the boot.
Okay.
I don't know why.
It's the alien bug in the boot, all right.
It's the alien bug in the boot.
It's the alien bug, it's the alien bug,
it's the alien bug in the boot.
So Dr. Miller, she sees Doreen Morin
pouring the liquid into her boot and she's like, oh no.
And so she hurries over and I think tries
to get the boot off of Dr. Morin.
I'm sorry, Dr. Morin.
Morin, Doreen.
You've been upgraded.
You upgraded, yeah.
You're a doctor now, we're all a doctor.
Look at me.
I guess technically we're supposed to all be doctors.
I think we're all.
I'm a doctor, you're a doctor.
Oh right, med students.
We are all supposed to be.
Oh, that's right.
She says, doctor.
Yes, doctor.
Get your boot off, doctor.
Take your clothes off.
Okay, doctor.
I strip naked.
Yeah, not those clothes.
Okay, down to her boots.
Hey, quick question, Zach.
How does it get in the boot if she has a hazmat suit on?
You don't know that it went in the boot.
The thing that I told you when no one else was listening.
Wow, you are the Luke of this group.
Jesus Christ.
Do we need to take our?
Oh yeah.
I remember how it got in the boot.
If it even is in the boot, you know.
That's a good point.
Okay, Dr. Miller runs forward to Maureen
and tries to like, is it in the boot?
Is it in the boot?
And then she's panically trying to get the boot off
and try to find this thing.
I like to think that Doreen Maureen loves her military boots
so goddamn much that she took them off
to put on the hazmat suit and then put the boots on
over the bottoms of the hazmat suit,
which is how she was able to pour this liquid
down into the boots while still wearing the hazmat suit.
Done, he's in the hazmat suit.
It's still over my foot.
Let's be clear about that.
Yeah, oh, it's definitely still over your foot.
And so Dr. Miller helps you remove the boot.
Okay.
Yeah, you take the boot off, you look inside,
you don't see anything.
Sick, where the fuck is it?
Yes.
You scream and Janice Ruth looks up
and she's like, what, where's what?
As she's being straddled by the truckster.
Where's what, what are you guys talking about?
And Jerome is like, wait, you said alien bug?
The fuck is going on?
What do you know?
They're cool, it's cool, they're cool, you can tell them.
All right, based on the stretch marks
on this poor boy over here,
I have reason to believe that it used to be something
that it's not anymore.
And what we saw was a tick running away from it.
And I can only assume tick tend to be only feeding off
organic live material.
If this boy has been dead for a while,
as I understand, several decades,
this doesn't make any sense.
So we need to find this tick.
So basically Dr. Miller reveals everything
she heard in private.
And then Chuck yells,
where, ticker, where, where, where.
Sorry, that's how I get into character.
Totally.
This isn't no normal tick though, bro.
This tick is like jumpy in time and space
and like versus there and then it's there
and then it's there and then guess what, what?
Where is it?
Is that true?
Then we can all be infected right now.
All I'm saying is that's what I saw, dude.
Everybody roll sanity, helplessness.
This is called helplessness.
Jesus.
You feel helpless and it's a ness.
Super fail.
11.
Not Loch Ness, it's just Bigfoot.
What?
78 on a 34.
A fail, lose one sanity.
I also failed 91 on a 54.
Lose one sanity.
11 on a 59.
Nice, critical success.
You gain sanity.
I gain sanity and I don't even know
if this tick is in my hazmat suit right now.
Critical success.
You're able to keep your head very much on your shoulders
and we'll go to Eleanor real quick for her sanity.
39 on a 55.
Congratulations, zero sanity lost in this situation.
You too will be able to act with a cutting edge movement.
You too, the edge.
All right, so shit.
Lindsay, because you critically succeeded
on your sanity check,
I am going to give you some information
that nobody else can hear.
So take off your headphones, wiggle your ears.
Hey, Ally, maybe don't fucking put your fingers
in your ears this time.
They can go on the outside.
Guys, it's been a joke from the beginning.
We don't do bits on this podcast, Ally.
Lindsay.
Yes, that's Doreen.
Doreen feels a bite on her foot.
Because you're clear and present in this situation,
it's very, very apparent to you
that underneath the hazmat suit, you've been bitten.
You know the feeling when you like see a bug
and then your skin starts to fucking crawl,
like you think that they're on you?
You feel that feeling all over your entire body.
Because you critically succeeded on your sanity,
I'm not gonna have your sanity again.
So you're gonna be able to have your wits about you
in this situation.
Stay calm, take care of it.
Can I just cut, just chop?
Can I just chop that bad boy off?
You can do whatever you would like to do.
I'm gonna get them back.
If that's your first instinct,
there's definitely a hatchet on the wall.
Like this is a barn slash camping, hunting.
And we have equipment to sew me back up.
Definitely.
Okay.
I mean, the mobile lab is probably a better option
for cutting off your foot than the hatchet
that you see on the wall.
You would only know that
because you critically succeed on the sanity.
Otherwise that hatchet's the best thing in the world.
All right, so I'm gonna bring them back
and then you can act.
Yes?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hello, come on back please.
Is this, okay.
Doreen just screams fuck
and just runs outside to the mobile lab.
Runs outside?
Runs outside.
Do you leave the door open?
She left us.
No, I closed the door behind me.
To the cabin.
You just slam it behind you as you run out?
Yeah.
She left us.
Dr. Hooch, you're up.
All right.
Fuck.
Did I see the tick going towards Doreen?
I don't know.
Did I tell you that you saw a tick going towards Doreen?
No, I don't think so.
I don't think you saw a tick going towards Doreen.
Okay, so all I know is that my potion
has been poured on a foot
instead of where I intended for it to go.
Uh-huh.
Hey, quick question.
Doreen, did you leave the rest of the vial,
the rest of the cauldron on the ground next to you?
And did you pour all of it?
No, remember at the end of the last episode
I said not all of it.
Not all of it.
Okay, okay, so there's a little bit left.
Okay, so I forget my British character.
Of course, yeah.
Fuck, God, God damn it.
Oh my God, my potion.
I jump for the cauldron.
I dive for the cauldron and grab it
and I scoop the rest of it up in it
and I'm on the ground scooping up
the rest of the potion into the cauldron.
Carl's going.
Is Carl near me?
No, he's on the other side of the pool table.
So yeah, I mean, he's just across
the pool table from you, I suppose.
Still elbows, staring at the corpse
of his younger brother who he fucking killed
and having a hard time getting over it.
It becomes clear to me pretty quickly
that Carl's emotions are gonna hinder us
in this process so I just throw
the rest of the cauldron on his face.
Holy shit, okay.
Yeah, go ahead and roll athletics just to,
I mean, I'll give you a plus 20
because he is completely still
and this seems pretty easy but in order
to get it enough of it.
And not on Jerome.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
49, or 46 on a 50.
Oh, nice, yeah.
So it splashes all over the face
of Carl Lambert and he's like,
whoa, what the, you're not British?
British?
As he like slowly slumps onto the ground
and Jerome is like, is that gonna knock him out
or kill him, what did you just do?
It'll just knock him out,
he'll just sleep real good for a bit.
Okay, okay, what's next?
What's next?
Fuck, fuck, where'd she go?
What is she doing?
It's Chuckster's turn.
I pull out my burner phone.
Well, I got this, guys.
And then I Google why this Bigfoot be a tick now though.
And then if you could just tell me
what my Google search results are.
Pull up your phone, grab your phone.
Yep.
Google why this Bigfoot be tick now.
Though.
Are you spelling though out
or is it just a THS situation?
Tick now though.
Stupid.
It says six steps what to do
when you find a tick on yourself.
Okay, this is great information.
Let's read off at least the first one.
Oh, wait, hold on.
The third result is a song by big homie G called Tick.
All right, Chuckster gets distracted by a song
instead of looking up what to do with a tick bite
which might've actually helped you in this situation.
It is Carl's turn.
He is asleep on the ground.
On a drink so I can't speak up,
bitch sucking my dick up.
If she bites, she gonna beat up.
I won't take no disrespect from no ho.
I'm a crazy bitch, I'm psycho.
Not a tip like a light show.
Gee, where you been?
Hell if I know.
Smoking runts, head in the sky, ho.
She says she's sick of me, bye ho.
I fucking hope.
Pull up that skirt, skirt.
Watching bitches stalk my bio.
I can't go nowhere without my money or my iron.
Okay, this is literally Chuckster's clicked on it
and this is just playing from his phone
and he's just looking at it now.
You fucking monster.
Janice's turn and Janice is still under him.
He is literally straddling Janice Ruth,
an asthmatic older woman,
and playing the song over his phone.
It is fucking-
Okay, honestly though, it's so relevant
because it says Johnny did these teeth.
Whole lotta cheese for these VV's.
I don't hardly be smiling but my shit big
when I say cheese like Carl's teeth.
Oh my God.
The truth comes out, I am big homie G.
This just turned into an episode
of Righteous Gems.
Oh my God, okay, it is Doreen Marine's turn.
Wait, so I wasn't helpful?
Oh no, I think you were extremely helpful.
I thought it was fucking, hey, I love you
and I loved that.
Oh my God.
Thank you, so I'm helping the mission
is what they all think?
I mean, unless there's like something in the wave,
like it would not be out of the realm
of Delta Green possibilities for the wavelengths
like underneath a song played by a certain Google search
would like pull up some sort of like spell like ability
in the air of the situation
but this is not one of those times.
Can I roll, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can I roll military science?
Cause hear me out.
The military has been studying how to use music
to brainwash people into telling the truth.
Did you learn that in your one week at basic?
I spent two months there bitch.
And also, I'm sorry.
And also, so anyway, I think that I was
on the special forces team of basic training.
Oh my God.
I passed, so anyway, do with that what you will.
Your military science would tell you
that the action that you've just taken is not helpful.
Doreen, it's your turn.
What can I say here?
Is there anything off limits to say?
Let's have them take their headphones off.
Yeah, and let's just get this over with.
Wow.
Oh my God.
I mean, for your sake dude.
Okay, because I mean.
You're doing this alone?
Well, my actual brain wants to,
I'm trying to channel Doreen,
but I'm thinking like if I have full sanity during this,
my first thought would be I'm gonna run out
and grab tools to do this and come back.
And come back, okay.
And ask for help.
Right, okay.
Because if they know what's going on, it will help me.
And if I'm fully sane.
Totally.
Yeah.
The excruciating pain in your foot is growing
as you feel the bones in your foot begin to shatter.
I'm ready to get it off.
All of the bones in your foot just shattered
and your muscles are beginning to rip apart and reform.
All the tendons are stretching out in your foot.
You've never felt this much pain in your entire life.
Roll sanity.
Am I like hopping back into the?
Ugh.
No.
What did you roll?
99.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Fucking 99.
Are you serious?
Those dice are fucking cursed, dude.
These dice suck, I'm mad.
Hey, that's a critical failure.
I know.
On you realizing that you're about to turn
into a goddamn Bigfoot.
And you're by yourself.
I'm by myself.
I'm trying to get back, I tried to get back.
I tried.
Okay, so I'm gonna have you roll fight, flight or freeze
in this situation.
So I want you to rank them.
You're gonna roll a D six,
which is just the normal standard six sided dice
that you would use in normal games.
I say normal games like they're not lame.
Okay, so here's what I want you to do.
I want you to rank from most likely to least likely,
fight, flight or freeze.
So what is the most likely?
So fight.
Sorry, fight.
Allie and Taylor are being fucking wild,
rubbing their ears.
They have no clue what's going on.
You're making too much noise.
That's fair.
Oh, you can hear that?
No, I really can't hear anything.
I can't, I can't.
Okay, so I would definitely, my number one go to
as Dorian would be fight.
Okay, so that's four, five and six.
And then flight.
Okay, so that's two and three.
And then freeze.
Is one, so roll a D six.
Seven.
What the fuck?
I said, it's only got six sides Lindsay.
I read it wrong, I read it wrong.
It's a fancy dice, I couldn't see the thing.
Four, five, six is fight.
Hey Lindsay, Dorian Marine sees
a set of tools next to her.
She grabs a saw.
She's smart enough in this moment to strap her leg down
on this stretcher that is meant for the Bigfoot corpse.
And she cuts.
The first one is not the hardest actually.
Well, I'm feeling this other pain that seems worse.
It does seem worse until you hit a nerve.
And that's just this.
Just like running through the back of your head.
I mean, you just begin almost like violently coughing
and choking and your stomach hurts.
And if you have any food in your stomach, it's coming up
and you're just sawing and sawing and you start crying.
Tears are running down your face.
Just like hit the bone and then boom, you're just sawing.
Saw, saw, saw, saw, saw, saw, saw, saw, saw, saw
until finally crack.
This feeling is growing as it goes up into your ankle.
And as those bones begin to shatter
and the muscles begin to break,
it helps you cut the rest of your foot off.
Your entire foot is only hanging on by the skin
that is on the back of your calf,
attached to the skin on the back of your ankle
as you finally have cut through your Achilles tendon.
Just for listeners right now, I'm literally crying.
Yeah.
I mean, you start bleeding out almost immediately.
And so I need you to roll a D six and then add two
for how much hit points you lose.
One.
Wow, okay.
So one plus two is three, you lose three hit points
and Lindsey, you're gonna lose one D four to blood loss
every round until this is fixed.
What's your highest skill of medicine first aid?
Whoa, hang on.
I have zero in both.
Oh, you're fucked, dude.
Until someone comes out here,
you're bleeding out one D four per round.
Can I like scream as loud as possible for help?
Yes.
Yes, and I'll have them roll alertness.
Okay.
Do you need me to like scream?
That was absolutely miserable.
No, that was good.
I'm leaving the room from now on for those.
Yeah, sorry.
I thought that that wouldn't take as long,
but then some crazy fucking shit happened.
So Mabi, oh, Ellie.
She's scrolling this.
She's on Pinterest.
You on Pinterest, girl.
I was, I'm looking at pre-ordering the Elden Ring.
It looks so funny.
Oh, fuck yeah.
I need Dr. Miller, Rusty Hooch and the Chuckster
all to roll alertness real quick for me just to kick off.
Yes.
That's a big ass fail.
Big fail for me too.
Okay, Chuckster, you're the only one who hears
just the slightest faintest, just like blood curling scream.
Very, very muffled, but coming from outside.
Dr. Miller, it's your turn.
My D dog.
What's going on with my D dog?
Okay.
Seeing that she said like,
don't leave this house because we're all gonna die.
She's very disappointed in her colleague, Dr. Marine.
So she is going to take out a firearm from her hazmat suit
and actually follow Doreen ready to threaten her
to not leave and get back into the house.
And so she's gonna run after Doreen.
Yeah, you're gonna be able to make it
to the back of the van.
So you can start off the next turn, opening up that door.
It's gonna move on to Dr. Hooch.
Not Carl or Janice or anyone.
I mean, I want Dr. Hooch to have some power.
I just thought you were skipping.
Oh no, I'm actually skipping Jerome in this moment.
That's my bad.
Jerome, where'd she go?
Alien bug.
Someone tell me what the fuck is going on here.
I didn't know this shit was happening either.
You've knocked him out.
Do we need to...
Janice, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I think I'm gonna be okay.
I just need you to stay calm.
Okay, do you need to be on her right now?
I was just getting comfortable, but I mean, I guess not.
Hey, Janice, you gonna be cool?
Janice, be cool, please.
She trusts Jerome dire enough to where she's like,
okay, okay.
And she's just gonna walk back over
and go sit on the couch that's in the corner of the room.
And she's just sitting there
and she's just got her head in her hands
and she starts weeping uncontrollably.
Dr. Falsom, what do we do?
What is the plan?
What is happening?
You've got two people gone already.
I'm losing trust in Jerome Dyer.
I'm becoming suspicious of him.
Okay, I pull out a gun, I point it right at Jerome
and I say, show me your fucking ID right now.
What the fuck, dude?
Are you kidding me?
I'm the one who brought you here.
I don't trust you for shit.
You have no, you clearly have no fucking clue
what's going on. What would my ID do?
Show it to me.
Can she roll like an alertness or something
to see if she trusts him
or like to see if he's doing anything that might be.
Roll human.
Okay.
Human intelligence.
It's reading people.
Hugh Mint.
Is it 10?
Mr. Mint, Hugh Mint.
48 on a 10.
Yeah, unaware you continue your shitty line
and questioning piece of shit.
And he's like, I don't know what this will prove,
but he reaches back in his back pocket.
Okay, as he's reaching down, I just fucking tackle him.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, roll unarmed combat.
35 on a 40.
98.
Yeah, you take him right to the ground.
I mean, he's a small little nerd man.
And so fucking bang having banging black turtleneck
wearing Dr. Hootch just like lunges over the pool table,
over the corpse and just spears this dude into the ground.
Tight tackle, bro.
I'm saying, what do you know?
What do you know?
I know you know something.
I don't know shit.
What the fuck?
We're just trying to stop.
There's an alien bug apparently
and you're not doing anything to stop it.
And it's Chuckster's turn.
I'm still like humming the tune of my big homie G song.
And it's Carl's turn.
No, I'm still humming it under my breath.
And then I kind of like come to and I'm like,
what are we doing?
We can't be fighting ourselves, bros.
We gotta be helping each other take down this alien dick.
Now I say we all go out there and check on our friend.
Come on.
I am trying to keep control of this situation clearly
because nobody else is.
Everyone's just letting sheer chaos happen.
So I'll just hold down the Fort in here.
I'm still on top of Carl or Jerome, sorry.
You're on top of the sleepy, sleepy Carl.
I'm keeping control of this situation.
Okay, so you leave?
Yeah, I'm gonna run after Dr. Miller.
Yeah, I think that makes sense.
So Carl's still asleep.
Janice Ruth is crying on the couch.
And Doreen, you've got a D4 to roll please.
A D4.
It's a pyramid.
It's a little pyramid.
This guy?
Yeah.
Three.
You know what to do.
Like in yellow, back in yellow, back in yellow.
Dr. Miller, you run out into the darkness.
The street lamp is shining down.
It's the only thing.
Snow begins falling.
I think that's nice.
Snow begins falling down through the street light.
It's actually really, really beautiful.
And as you-
It's the most wonderful time.
Starts playing as you open up the back doors
of this sprinter van.
And Lindsay, can you describe what she sees?
I'm still just screaming and like growling
and trying to put pressure on this nub of a leg.
Could you demonstrate the screaming and the growling?
Ugh.
Something like that.
Like big, nevermind.
Like big what?
Big poop sounds.
Yeah.
I understand.
I didn't understand before, but now I get the sound.
You know when someone cuts off their foot
and they make sounds like-
Big poop sounds.
Poop, poop, poop.
Wait, wait, wait.
She's putting pressure on a fucking nub.
On a nub.
And you see her foot and ankle standing up
on the stretcher next to her.
She's like strapped her leg down onto the stretcher.
Blood is pouring out between her fingers.
She has no idea what to do.
She is at less than half of her hit points.
And so she is turning white in the face
as she's crying and screaming and gurgling.
And literally the foot that is next to her is transforming.
So I need you to roll sanity real quick.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Bigfoot foot.
Bigfoot foot, but only the foot so far.
Point of a Bigfoot.
Yeah, that's a big old 91 on 55 sanity.
This is extremely unnatural.
And so I'm going to have you roll a D4 and add one.
Four.
Four plus one?
Three plus one.
So four.
Oh, just one shy of that temporary insanity.
You lose your fucking shit because this foot,
you would know as a medical doctor
that you can see the bones,
part of which is sticking out of this foot
that's just sitting on this stretcher next to Doreen Marine.
The bones are shattering
and then seem to be reforming themselves
as the tendon, the Achilles tendon that she's severed
begins to stretch and grow out.
Like all of these things are trying to grow.
As they're shattering, you see the blood that's spreading out
and all the blood is coming up to the surface in this foot.
It's rapidly turning purple,
as well as the blood that's hitting the air up top
is finally oxidizing.
So red is starting to pour over the top
of all of these bruised and bloody foot
and Doreen is bleeding the fuck out
and with your sanity failure,
you're not able to attempt to stop the bleeding this round.
The Chuckster is running up behind you in this moment.
I think Dr. Miller turns around and throws up.
And you see the exact same thing
and I need you to roll a sanity as well.
Okay.
Really low odds of me.
Ah, 23 on a 33.
It's the first time I passed a sanity check.
You run up, you see Dr. Miller has turned towards you
and begins throwing up.
You nimbly dodge out of the way of this vomit
and you peek your head around and see Doreen Marine
and this foot, her bloody situation, what do you do?
So one thing about Chuck that you guys don't know
is he's very astute
and he puts things together really quickly as, yeah.
Oh, really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Did not know that about Chuck at all.
Yeah.
Yeah, so he doesn't talk about it that often.
He's a real humble boy.
But anyway, so he puts together
that the tick must have gone inside
and that if he shoots the leg,
it's just gonna leave again
and maybe infect something else.
So he wants that tick to stay inside the foot
and he notices a deep freeze.
So he's gonna throw the foot in the deep freeze
and lock it.
Smart.
And then he says, not today Bigfoot foot.
Yeah.
And then he fist bumps himself.
Extremely excellent work.
Thank you so much.
And Doreen, you continue to bleed out.
Roll a D4.
Yeah, sorry, Doreen.
I'm gonna die.
Oh shit.
Three.
How many hit points do you have?
Five.
Bummer town.
All right, you are down to two hit points now.
What happens when you run out of hit points?
You die.
Death.
There's no death saving throws.
There's no negative hit points.
It's not like-
No potions can save me.
You fall unconscious at one or two hit points
if you do not fail a constitution check.
So Doreen has two hit points.
She is going into shock from blood loss.
You have to pass a constitution check
or you will fall unconscious
and you will still lose a D4 from blood next round.
I think I was lost.
Let's see.
She's like shaking.
28 on a 55.
That is a success.
Doreen Marine can keep her eyes open
for a little bit longer.
You know, before she fucking dies.
It's Dr. Miller's turn.
Wouldn't it be Hooch's turn?
Hooch, you're on top of Jerome Dyer
whose actual turn it is
and he is not trying to fight you.
He is just laying there and he lets his body go limp.
He looks up at you and he says,
do you think you're doing a good job?
Wow, he got you so good.
I don't even acknowledge him.
I do get off of him,
but I'm just still kind of like pointing my gun
in the general
or are all three of them kind of in the same area
at this point?
You are on top of Jerome
and you're literally next to a face down,
like Carl is now snoring and he's face down,
which is impressive.
Like that he's still snoring face down.
This guy, wow, what a body.
And you can hear Janice is sniffling over in the corner.
What a goddamn mess.
My team is outside.
There's a fucking kid on the fucking table.
I gotta destroy some of this evidence.
Yeah, that's what I'm here to help you do.
So I'm still just kind of pointing a gun over in that area.
I walk over to the cameras
and can I roll computer science
to just wipe all the cameras?
Yeah.
But we have to look at the footage.
Nope, I'm wiping them.
Oh my God.
Wow, fucking rebel scientist.
83.
83, Jerome notices what you're doing
and I don't mean to, you seem very,
do you want, I'm, this is, I'm good at,
I'm good at this stuff.
You're gonna have to prove it
because you've done jack shit since we've gotten here.
Before you finish the sentence,
he's already finished clearing one camera,
which literally meant like,
he took out the SD card from it and like steps on it.
And then he's like, staples.
That was easy.
I don't like you.
That seems clear.
Do you want to help me with the rest of these?
Janice looks up and is like, who are you?
What, how do you, why are you?
And he turns around and he's like,
well, obviously it wasn't Bigfoot Janice.
I just point my gun back at her.
I just say, shut the fuck up Janice.
I liked Jerome.
Dr. Miller, you've already lost your sanity.
You can pull your shit together here.
You have to save this woman.
If you can pass a first aid check,
you will stop the bleeding and give her one D4 hit points.
Dr. Miller is going to turn around to Chuck and say,
you guard that thing with your life.
Pointing towards the ice bag that he put the foot in.
And then she's going hurriedly trying to stop the bleeding.
And Chuck's just like sitting on top of this deep freeze.
I'm doing the like surfer sign where you stick your thumb
and your pinky out and you shake it.
And you shake it.
And Dr. Miller says, tubular bra.
Righteous.
And rolls a 90 fucking five.
Oh my God.
Sorry, Doreen.
Bye Doreen.
Bye.
Holy shit.
Dr. Miller starts fumbling with her things.
And she's like, you're going to be all right.
You're going to be all right.
Okay. You have to survive.
Just trust me.
Trust me.
And you just can't find the exact shit you're looking for.
I don't know.
Like you're looking for gauze.
You're looking for anything to like,
to maybe burn the, you know,
singe the flesh at the bottom
to try to cauterize the wound, anything.
But you just can't find what you're looking for.
Why can't I find anything in this fucking car?
Yeah. She starts panicking.
And then continues to look at Doreen
trying to be like, you're going to be fine, all right?
You're going to be fine.
Just trust me.
Give me one moment.
As she continues to look for things,
fumbling like a fucking idiot.
Like the fucking idiot she is.
I didn't mean that, Dr. Miller.
I heard that, Chuck.
I just like sadly put my surfer hand down.
Back inside, Jerome and Dr. Hooch are wrapping up
and Jerome is like, okay.
And I think we'd uploaded on this laptop here.
So Dr. Hooch, you actually see on this laptop,
you see some of the pictures that they took
and it's the strangest thing.
They're all blurry.
It'll be like a picture of the two of them
throwing up peace signs on either side of the pool table.
Like, ah, we got it.
There's this like incomprehensible blurry thing
on the table.
It's almost like there's some sort of cloaking
that this creature might have that would make it
so that no one could get like a clear picture of it,
no matter how good the equipment was,
no matter how hard they tried.
It's almost like the pictures you've seen
of Bigfoot in real life.
Why can't anyone get a good picture of Bigfoot?
Maybe that's why.
Roll sanity.
48 on a 53, baby.
Success.
You're like, damn, I figured out Bigfoot.
Okay, are you finished up there?
Fuck.
Y'all can't hire a fucking photographer
that knows how to take a good damn picture?
Look, it's like it auto-focused on my face and Carl's face,
but it didn't, Jesus.
It just seems like no one here knows what y'all are doing.
I start like just scrubbing through the photos,
frantically trying to see if there's one that's in focus.
Not a single one.
I just throw my hands up in the air.
I'm so frustrated.
Where's my fucking team?
They all just ran outside.
And I open up the front door and just look outside.
Yeah, you can smell death.
And Chuckster, it's your turn.
I'm gonna valiantly take my shirt off.
Nice.
Hell yeah.
But like I could easily just pull it over,
you know, and it would come off easily.
But instead I like rip it from the collar down.
So it like still has like part of it.
Like one sleeve is still on, but yeah,
there's got a big patch in the front that's off.
And I wrap that around her nub.
Okay, go ahead and roll first aid to save her life.
Not good odds, but.
I pass!
36 on a 40.
I save her.
Oh my gosh, the Chuckster is so tight.
Doreen reaches up and gives him a little pat on the head.
Hold on, let's go back.
I mean, you're patting him on the head
as he's wrapping this around.
And you see Dr. Miller is still just frantically going out.
I mean, just like throwing shit out of the cabinets
all over behind her, trying to figure this out.
You guys are almost like dodging shit
that she's throwing out, being like,
why can't I find it?
Why can't I find it?
And you're just like calmly wrapping your torn t-shirt
around the nub at the bottom.
And I'm giving her little eyebrows, like while I do it.
Oh, this is the patch up the soldier moment.
Okay, one of you guys.
As you're patting his, I mean, roll a D4 please to see.
You're able to stop the bleeding,
which is the most important thing.
And with three hit points back in your system,
that takes you back up to five.
And you're able to kind of stabilize your breathing.
You're still extremely panicked.
You're on the verge of throwing up at any moment.
You're extremely pale.
You've lost a lot of blood.
You do not feel well, but you at least have someone
who is your fucking savior now.
I knew there was a reason I loved you, kid.
You do remind me of my whippet.
Ha ha ha.
This might be too forward,
but do you want to celebrate Christmas together?
Ha ha ha.
It's January.
Doreen is so happy to have something wrapped around her.
She was like, absolutely.
Yes.
Searing star, deafening heat.
You don't know where you found it.
In this heat, as your eyes fall short,
you better learn how to keep it.
Clasp your fist over all the blood.
Water leaks through your fingers.
You're standing in a swirling flood.
And only darkness leaves.
Falling fast into a deep abyss
till it's reaching out again.
Find your theme on your broken bones.
Be your outlaw or he is your king.
He is your king.