Greetings, friends.
It's your BFF, WTD.
BFF means beefy, funny friend.
And a WTD means wet-tongued doggy.
You're welcome.
TTYL, time to yell loudly.
There is a new howlin' with Wolf,
and that makes my nasty old heart always burst with love.
This howlin' with Wolf is from Distant Egg Song,
location, Houston, they write.
Thanks much to the trash slurpin' host with the most.
Always glad to hear your voice on the airwaves.
This goes out to Tamantha in St. Louis.
Hey, Vinnie, glad you turned me on to this podcast.
It made my 2020 better.
Regarding your question, I checked in Ma's recipe book.
The way to render the sacrificial,
purulent goo from a gamer's flesh
is to go low and slow for a minimum of eight hours.
Glad to see you and Vinnie and Galina.
Let's do it again soon.
Your brother from the Venuccia mother, Vinnie.
Mmm, damn, that recipe sounds
abso-fuckin'-lutely tasty, scrumptious, unctuous.
I must visit this all-mother
and exchange my forbidden recipes with them.
If you wanna write up somethin'
for your BFF forever, Wolf to Hal,
you can go fuck yourself.
Ha ha ha, I'm just kiddin'.
Fuck Mark Zuckerberg, I got some hot news.
I have it on good authority
that this here is the second of two Q&A sessions
to wrap up season one of somethin'.
And I have it on even better authority
that next Friday on November 5th, ha ha, shucks, for real,
am I gonna have to say some corny, stankin',
remember, remember nonsense?
V might be for vendetta to some folks,
but to me, V is for volumizing shampoo and conditioners.
And beginning next Friday, November 5th,
we will have a guest seated at the head of the table.
You might know him as the rules lawyer
on the Glass Cannon Network star finder program
Androids and Aliens.
And if you don't, you'll get to know David Winters
as the handler of pretending to be people
for the next five weeks
as he runs Joe, Luke, Thomas, and some idiot named Zack
through a classic Delta Green scenario.
Get ready for an absolute mess, y'all.
And finally, get ready for ol' Wolfie
to be an absolute mess.
It's time to say goodbye to a brand new song.
This premiere will be the last time I play it here
on the main feed of 694.2 PTBP.
So if you want to hear this infant baby
of a banger ever again,
you actually have tons of options.
One of which is just Google cuts you with no backbone.
Luke, you have a question for Justin?
Oh yeah, did you see the article came out today
or just the story of Chokin'?
No.
Yeah, Chokin' on Deez Nuts.
Got him!
He didn't get him.
He didn't say Chokin'.
He didn't say it.
Yeah, but I did.
I got you.
Yeah, he got you.
He got you to say Chokin' on Deez Nuts.
Yeah, I got you to say it.
And then I wasn't a participant.
Reverse got him!
Reverse got him.
I got got.
Thanks, Joe.
Someone in the UX industry, user experience industry
was telling me that like a lot of people she works with
no longer use Photoshop.
They use a program called Figma.
And I just had to like, be like, yeah, wow, interesting.
Because it's not a person I could say Figma balls to.
You know what?
We fucked around pretty hard last time.
And then it took us a long time to get into the questions.
And this time took a long time for y'all to find out.
I have a bad story first.
You want to hear it?
I do want to hear it.
Let's fuck around.
So whenever we were clapping,
I forgot that I had stabbed my hand with a steak knife
earlier this week.
Why did you do that?
Oh, wow.
I have a hole in my hand.
Shit.
Wait, I didn't see it.
So that first clap, I clapped and like almost went.
Yeah, show us your hand hole again, please.
It's hard to see.
Hold it over to the screen.
It's like, Zach doesn't know how to use Windows.
Yeah, oh.
How'd you do that?
It doesn't look that bad.
It's deep.
I was trying to split two hash browns apart
that were frozen with a steak knife.
And I was holding them in my hand
where the knife, when it pierced through, would stab me.
And I literally went, I shouldn't be doing this.
And as I said that, it's spiraling.
Nice.
Like without much pressure at all.
And I just like stabbed into my hand
and I just was like, oh man.
The fact that you were sober when you did this.
Oh, it was an afternoon, yeah.
So you were drinking for a few hours at that point.
I'd been gone for hours, you know, a Tuesday afternoon.
Yeah, Tuesday afternoon.
So this is, you woke up and this was like
a midnight snack, almost.
And yeah, and luckily I was okay,
but I did see some hand chicken meat, as I like to call it.
Cause if you've ever like sliced chicken,
where it like kind of the muscle kind of split,
I did a little bit of that,
which was very fun to look at.
And I was like, oh man, that's bad.
You guys make chicken different than I do.
You ever split your chicken meat, bro?
You might not have seen the inside of your hand.
It's chickeny.
Oh.
Have you ever seen the inside of your body?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I've had some x-rays done.
I suppose I've seen the inside of my body.
Technically, yeah.
Yeah.
I go with Zach to his colonoscopy and take a gander.
Yeah, I do want it.
I'm Zach's second opinion.
I'm like, nah, I think there's something wrong.
That looks, doesn't look normal.
Pollip.
It's a pollip.
That's a pollip. Is that a Pokemon?
That's so cute.
Yeah.
Sir, it's, we try to get the patients as clean as possible,
but it's clearly shit.
You can see the corn.
Yeah, that's a pollip.
Wake him up, tell him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You gotta wake him up because they put you in a daze.
It's a real a pollip of daisy.
Oh my God.
Pollip of daisy.
What?
Do we have any questions?
All of them.
The bollard asks, what the fuck?
Fuck you too.
I think what the fuck is an appropriate question.
Yeah, that was my first question to you.
To what we've done.
When you stop the recording, it's the last episode.
Oh yeah.
I think that's what I said.
I think that is what you said at the end of season one.
The fuck?
I mean, it's just a small town mystery.
Just a small town mystery.
They also asked, will we ever find out the backstory
of Wolf the dog?
I mean, we've had at least a-
There's a little bit.
We learned a little bit.
If you can, if you're, you know.
If you're smart.
Pretty clever, but yeah, you can,
all of Wolf the dog is in there.
So go back, re-listen, get those numbers up.
Definitely re-listen and get those numbers up.
Actually, at the Patreon $100 tier,
I will call you on Discord and tell you.
You have to be subscribed for two years.
It's patreon.com slash Justin wants money.
Yeah, alternatively, you can Venmo Justin $200.
If you listen to the 694.2 PTBP Pledge Drive episode,
you can see at least the story of Wolf the dog.
Yeah, there's some slight origin story in there.
That's how he comes into the studio.
He's a great DJ who loves eating trash
and I don't know why it needs to be any more than that.
Yup.
Celery Top asks, to do hakenu.
To do hakenu to you as well, son.
Nerds, cling as they cling on.
To do hakenu are true words of power,
but how did you come up with vis-a-girl
and shuck-a-tee-felicia?
Asked and answered.
We went over this one last time,
but hey, Celery Top, we like what you do.
You've done some sick art.
Exactly, pasted it again in the Google document.
I think Celery Top did the Contention Trucks artwork,
which is fucking rad, yeah.
Abadfeeling asks, question,
what was up with the feet eating?
I'm curious about that too.
No, I was gonna ask you, Joe, if you had an idea.
My only theory,
and I don't know if these guys know this yet,
that was how I was introduced to that light plane world
with the jibugabuntubus, and-
You can say it.
It was a jagant umbropithecus.
It was a xenonimatoh that they attached to my foot
to send me there.
And so I assume it's maybe covering up evidence
of those scars on,
he kept mentioning that scar on my foot.
I assume it was maybe covering that up in some way,
but I wasn't sure why they needed to consume it.
I didn't know what was up with that.
They had to do it.
All right.
And I mean, did you have a reason at the time
beyond it's real spooky?
Yes, it was simply what Joe said,
that it is a thing that shows
that you have been at the circle of knowledge.
And if you were a Delta Green agent
and you were like cleaning up
after like a mission or something,
and one of the parts of the mission
was that certain people had this crazy scar
on the bottom of their left foot,
then yeah, you'd cut it off and-
Feed it to them.
Like you do.
Okay, but Chief Maggie Cook had some serious issues
with James the Mill Worker specifically,
because James the Mill Worker
clearly had issues with Chief Maggie Cook
and his own blood,
if you would have tested the blood at his house
that spelled out stop her,
that was James the Mill Worker's blood
because he knew that Chief Maggie Cook
was going down this dark path.
Hold on, tested with the Advanced Crime Lab
at the contention police station?
Yeah.
Drew Andrews is a-
Vampire.
He's a vampire and you just give him a little blood.
I forgot about it.
He licks it.
He laps it up.
And then he goes,
and his head vibrates and shakes around
and then he blows blood.
James the Mill Worker's blood.
And then he tells you who's blood it was.
We kept forgetting to take advantage of that.
You guys are idiots.
Compliment and question from a bad feeling,
the various theme songs for the show's various arcs
strike me as something very cool this show does
that other TTRPG podcasts don't do.
Will this continue in season two?
Yes.
Any bangers picked out yet?
No bangers.
No bangers picked out.
Circling some?
We're circling.
How did you pick the songs and where did you find them?
We chose the song so far from bands
that either we know or have seen live.
Yeah, Springfield bands for the most part.
Springfield bands that we're into, yeah.
Connected to the region at the least, yeah.
For sure.
Justin and I were in a band
and we played with Blue False Indigo
and that's kind of how we met them
and who else was on the show?
We played with Dream Girl and Kudzu before too.
That's right, yeah.
And Kudzu, who you might know from a song
that we've used a couple of times on the show
called No Backbone, the lead singer of that band
is a very good promoter in Springfield
who always makes sure that bands coming through
are well taken care of,
that they have a good place to sleep
and that they get paid.
So we were happy to promote Kudzu, yeah,
which No Backbone's a fucking banger.
The rest of the songs, I mean,
we've got Someone Still Loves You, Boris Yeltsin,
who's just a fucking staple of the Springfield scene.
We've all seen them countless times, I would imagine.
More than any other band.
Joe and I's band have played with them a couple of times,
not to dunk on y'all's bands.
And then who else do we have?
Grady P. Drug, who is just an excellent musician.
We saw him a couple of weekends ago actually
and he was phenomenal.
A Dragon in Three, which is an offshoot
of Someone Still Loves You, Boris Yeltsin, yeah.
And they are an incredible little outfit
who I am always stoked to throw them on.
And I'm looking forward to new music from them, hopefully.
Creek Rocks are some friends of mine
and they've got a residency right now
down in Silver Dollar City.
Oh, no shit.
Go check them out.
That's super rad.
That's probably coming to an end soon
as the weather changes.
I think they play in an outdoor amphitheater, but yeah.
Creek Rocks, that song rules.
We've been really happy, I think,
with all the songs that we've been able to play.
Do they have any pants left?
To throw on the show.
Wow, that is a deep cut from Luke talking about...
There's a ride at Silver Dollar City
called Fire in the Hole.
Oh, yes, I should have got it.
God dang it.
And as you go through this ride,
Luke, do you want to describe?
Yeah, it's called, did you say what it's called?
It's called Fire in the Hole.
And you ride through and basically
you just see a bunch of stuff.
Like you see, is that the same one
with like a prison escape or something?
Oh, yeah.
It's a town on fire.
And the town is lit on fire by the...
Bald Knobbers. Bald Knobbers.
But they don't just light towns on fire, no.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
At a certain...
Yeah, I just hope you don't have any pants lying around.
Why is that, Luke?
Oh, because at one point in the ride you see a home.
A home that is on fire.
That's on fire and one of the guys
is getting out of the home.
He's hanging out the window.
And she says...
And he's wearing his long underwear.
His nighttime clothes.
And she says, whatever your name is,
it's whatever his name is.
Whatever your name is, get back in here
and put on your pants.
And he goes...
And he says...
I can't put on my pants.
I ain't got no pants no more.
The dang Bald Knobbers stole them.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
So that's just some local humor.
We're trying to get local work.
And blank a patch, shout out to blank a patch
from NerdPoker.
All right, so what was the fucking question?
How do you pick the songs?
Oh yeah, that was it.
We answered it, good.
Moving on.
Black Moxa asks, congratulations.
Oh, that's, thanks.
Congratulations on excellent work across two continents.
Thank you.
It was across three at one point,
which I was super proud of
when we had Scott Dorward playing with us.
I bragged about that to people in my life
that we were playing a game across three continents.
That was cool.
That was dope.
That was rad.
We're cool as fuck.
So were the time loops and resets
always part of your story?
We're the coolest people who do this.
No.
Or did you have to introduce them
after the characters got into impossible situations?
Yes.
Also, how...
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Did the characters get into impossible situations
or did little Zachy get into an impossible situation?
Yes, also yes.
Very much yes.
It was my doing that I had opened up the story
to too many avenues.
And I thought to myself,
how will I take them down these avenues?
And then I thought, well...
Time travel, the greatest cop out of them all.
And the easiest to handle.
Exactly, famously.
I have this future version of one of Joe's characters
that I can play with who might be able to do some stuff.
Yeah, fucking nightmare, honestly.
Never gonna do it again.
And also, how is the create-a-campaign
this community contributed to going?
Fantastic question.
Yeah, it's a great question.
It's going really well.
Frankie and, no, no, no, no, no, no, hang on,
have compiled everything that everyone has written
and voted on up into one document
and it is slowly being whittled down into a playable game.
And it'll be out in, oh, what, 2031.
Yeah.
It'll be playable.
Let's not put it that close.
Okay, yeah.
We were shooting for the 10th anniversary of the finale.
Yeah, let's push that right now, actually.
2053.
Yeah, no, that campaign is dope.
And if these guys have forgotten enough
of what they might've read
from what people wrote about that campaign,
I would definitely be interested
in running some form of that.
I purposely didn't read a lot of it
because I thought we played it at some point.
Hey, guys, it's really fucking scary and cool.
So I would be interested in using,
maybe even just using parts of it to create a one-shot.
What's up, Thomas?
This is the first time I've even heard of it.
Oh, right, perfect.
The modest light.
I've read as much as Thomas has.
I knew about it.
The modest light says,
thanks for doing such great work.
Hey, thanks.
Honestly, it's been great
just listening to you guys improv together.
I felt like I've learned a lot
about how to keep the jokes rolling in my own life
just by analyzing how you all do it.
Sit you on a bad path.
Dangerous ground.
Yeah, you're on thin ice, my friend.
And let me tell you,
you better walk back right now
for the sake of your relationships.
Yeah.
You don't want this.
And your career.
And a future podcast editor.
We don't do this.
Right.
Yeah, all six of us have,
or there's five of us, I have no, no.
You okay?
All five of us have four friends, so maybe two of them.
My dude, I literally was answering that question.
Like, I was like, well, wait,
let's talk about what we mean by friends
because I have four friends.
I have tons of people that I like
and that I'll talk to in public.
It's the people on the pod, yeah.
How did you guys know it was a good idea to start a podcast?
And did you have any fears going in?
These are the two questions.
I was the one who brought it up, right?
Probably, for sure.
Yeah, you've been wanting to do it for a while
and I don't know if that just stemmed out of the idea
of recording the games themselves to listen back to.
But we also, we were all listening
to a bunch of role-playing podcasts.
We were.
And when I listened to a lot of music,
I thought I could play music.
And when I listened to a lot of actual play podcasts,
I thought I could do that too, so.
The thing about the actual play podcast
is that we were getting together every week
and being as funny or funnier than them.
We're like, why not record it?
At least enough that we thought we could do this.
Yeah, it was enough to where when I brought it up,
no one balked at the idea, except for Taylor,
who was like, all right, this is my cue to bail.
Yeah.
We felt good.
We all felt good playing together
and we thought it might translate.
We honestly didn't expect this.
No, not at all.
Thomas is shaking his head like I did.
I did.
He was shaking his head, no,
don't put a nod in his mouth.
Ooh.
These nuts.
Did you guys, you guys didn't have any fears?
No, I didn't.
Going in, I definitely did.
But like after the first session, I was fine.
Do you guys have any fears now?
Oh yeah, there's so much more to lose.
One fear.
Yeah, my fear, my biggest fear is success.
When we first hit record and when we slipped into it
and we finally found that we were just playing
at a table together, my fears were allayed.
I remember that we have fun doing it either way.
That's right.
Exactly.
And it helps we didn't release it for so long.
Yes.
We kind of touched a bit.
So that was on that stream the other night.
The stream the other night, yeah, yeah.
But we, yeah, because we did record so many episodes
before releasing them, it really did allow us
to just put the game we were playing on the air.
We were very comfortable with what we were doing
at that point because it was just the same thing
we'd always done, kind of.
Yeah.
I think that's a smart way to do any creative thing
like that is to build up a little bit
and then start releasing it so you're not scared
immediately from poor results after one thing.
It's like edging.
How do you feel about edging, Justin?
It's the only way.
Brenner Nunez says, what was the balloon shirt?
To quote the great Nicole Byer, I don't want to edge.
If you start fucking me, you better make me cum.
She went on Punch Up the Jam and she punched up the jam.
She was on it.
Bruno Nunez asks, what was the balloon shaped head kid
from the JLP the Third Flashback?
I mentioned a balloon shaped headed kid multiple times.
He had very dark eyes.
Who was it, Joe?
It was Pastor Adam Kane.
It was Pastor Adam Kane as a child.
When we were listening to the episodes in real time
and I got to my flashback, I had already
played at that point a scene with Pastor Adam Kane
and he described him exactly the same way.
And I texted Zach, you son of a bitch.
I know who the balloon head kid is.
Yeah, that was a fun one.
I thought you were just dunking on that poor kid.
This balloon headed mommy stuck kid.
So there's this balloon headed idiot next year.
Did you have a flashback with him
or was that just a mistake on their part?
That is from the flashback of his father,
John Lee Pettymore the Third, burning down the Kane home.
When you put on the watch.
Yeah, when John put on the watch,
he saw his dad rescue him is one way of saying it.
Steal him and burn down the house of his family
is another way of saying it.
The gherkin at Merlin's Merkin says,
he says, will sweet boy Justin be a regular for season two
or will he be banished back into the pit
from whence he came until another uncle PC is introduced?
The pit, the pit.
Zach said I can't come out of the pit.
Yeah, he's going to be, he's an uncle.
He's an uncle forever.
No, but we talked about that and it's just
my schedule is going to be so freaking wacky with grad school
crap, especially when we're going to start recording it.
He already does side characters.
He already makes all the music.
You guys asked too much from him.
And he's trying to escape from that pit.
I'm trying, please.
And Zach keeps putting, like digging,
Zach's down there with me digging it.
He keeps sending more grad school assignments down there
and he's like, ah, you want to finish, don't you?
No, but I think being a regular on top of all the extra stuff
would for me right now would be just a little bit too much.
Even though I've had a blast.
If you do all my assignments, you'll
finally earn your Zachster's degree one of these days.
What'd you say?
Alexia says, I love this format where I can just immediately
move on to something else.
Alexia says, thank you for making this amazing show.
Thanks.
It's been such a light these months.
You're welcome.
Question, how do you manage to find so many amazing bands
local to you?
Well, it all dates back to the Ozarks Jubilee.
You see?
That's not, that's kind of a joke.
That's also true.
It's also true.
It has a really cool musical history.
And it's just been full of musical talent.
We've had a burgeoning musical scene forever.
And exactly, it does go back to the Jubilee.
I saw this question earlier on.
And I wanted to plug, there's a documentary out there
right now.
You can find it on thecenterofnowhere.com.
And it's kind of about the history of Springfield music.
It used to be on Amazon.
But I think they had some weird thing where
they took a bunch of documentaries down.
But you can find it on that website.
They're trying to hide the truth.
They want to silence the truth of the Springfield music scene.
Well, I also think, I don't know.
Zach, did your parents also take you to a bunch of musical stuff?
Because your parents do music stuff.
And mine do.
And Joe's do also.
Yeah.
My parents tried to make it.
They put out a cassette.
And they moved to Nashville before they had kids.
And put out a Christian cassette tape.
And opened up for some notable acts.
But neither one of them have Grammys.
Switchfoot.
Oh, yeah.
Does anybody's dad here have a Grammy?
Yeah.
He's like, my dad's a good old.
I was like, you have to explain.
He's a good, good piano player.
He's a really good piano player.
He's on an album that won Grammy.
Or it was a folk album of the year, I believe it was.
We should make our dads do a battle of the pianos
against each other.
My dad would kick your dad's ass.
Yeah, I'm sorry, Justin.
But my dad's a really nice guy.
He has a degree in composition.
Music composition.
What has he composed?
Yeah.
A cassette tape?
He put out a one hit, not so much of a one-two.
Have you heard it?
He's a great dad, though.
So good on him.
Moving on, we found so many amazing local bands
because there's so many amazing local bands around.
We've got an embarrassment of riches around us.
We really do.
And also, throw yourself into the music scene
in whatever town you're in.
Because it's probably got good music.
Yeah, I'm sure you're going to find something that you like.
Also, it's really easy for people
to record music these days.
And so more people are making it.
And there's a lot of garbage out there that you can step through.
Want to go somewhere says question.
Every time the boys woke up back in the cemetery,
was there another group of them running around
in the same city?
Yes.
Or was that an alternate timeline?
Alternate universe.
Yes kind of thing.
So A, yes, there was an alternate version of them
in that scenario.
But in, for instance, the iteration
where you guys went to the Glass Family Compound,
that world continues on and keeps doing its own thing.
The next time you come back, you're
in a different iteration of that same plane.
But you've done what you did previously before.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, I do get that sort of, so our guys are doing it?
Yeah, so in the first one that you were in,
there's only one of you.
In the second one that you woke up in,
there's two of you in that world.
In the third one you woke up in, there's three of you
in that world.
Three collective yous.
Yeah.
And then in the last one, there's
four of you in that collective universe.
Well, there's not because you died in the CSU arc.
But yeah, that was my idea with all that.
We got another question here.
What up with the names branded into their skin
when they wake up at the cemetery?
Was it an overseer hint on where they need to go next?
Yes.
Or was it something more than that?
It was also a little bit more than that, but barely.
It was simply that when you interact
with the person who is branded on your body as a whole,
your group will have that name crossed out.
The next time you wake up and you only
have until all your names are crossed out,
then you have one last time to go through it.
So first time you had one name crossed out.
Second time you had the second name crossed out.
Third time you ran into both Tildy B. Mitchell
because Keith ran into Tildy B. Mitchell, Andrew Andrews,
and therefore crossed out both of those names,
giving you only one more chance at life.
Thank goodness.
Yeah, it worked out really fucking well, actually.
So it was just the overseer saying, hey,
you need to talk to these guys.
But he was just hoping that you would figure out
what you needed from him.
Yes.
Yeah, that was his.
Again, that's what I intended for sure.
Good, good, good, good.
That's what I was hoping.
Punk-ass book jockey, that's a great name, Compliments.
I love the way, this is long.
I love the way you created horror
by constantly throwing new mysteries and problems
and gross shit into the plot.
Instead of being scary because of slowly built tension,
it was scary from being completely overwhelming,
like it was a mental breakdown.
It was.
Yeah, very cool inversion.
I love that you wrote a time travel plot
and still held characters and plot elements
so loosely and let unexpected things happen.
Yeah, that was really fucking hard.
I loved how great everyone was
at instantly bringing each new character to life.
That's just good for you guys.
Thank you.
I love the way the players play
like they are horror movie characters.
Yes, again, thank you that I agree with that.
Thank you for doing it.
I thought it was great
that no matter how tangled everything got,
it always felt like there was an explanation for everything.
If we could just understand.
That's the amazing illusion Zach creates.
I mean, your trust means everything to me.
I love that when the players were given complete freedom
in the final episodes, they kept topping,
lol, lol,
each unbelievably cool thing they did
with another unbelievably cool thing.
Thanks.
Thank you, yeah.
It felt cool at the end there, man.
We all kind of felt like our power is unlocked.
We're all just topping.
And for you guys,
what one thing do you wish you had done different?
So they're saying, having done such cool stuff,
what was the one thing you wish you had done differently
as your character?
I don't know if I would have changed this,
but I would have been super curious
how the whole thing would have gone if I'd gone with Leon.
That really was a fork in the road
that could have drastically changed
the way this whole thing went.
Yep, I have no idea what would have happened.
If I wouldn't have jumped out of the bus,
I would want to see what happened then.
Ah, yes.
Ooh, nice.
Yeah, that bus was on its way to the mill.
So you would have-
Oh, you would have been right on it.
I don't know what decisions I would make differently
with Jon, probably a lot,
but Jon does know as a character
that he should have shot Keith like a long time ago.
Oh my God.
Who was your favorite interlude character that you made?
So any of the small Mark characters?
Yeah, Martin Cupertino.
Oh, okay.
So we got one from Calm Comfy Campground there.
Everett Pace for me, I loved him.
He was really fun.
All three of those were really good.
Justin, what about you?
Like all of my beautiful children that I've created.
Yeah, you got Don, you got Jack Pearlman.
Don and Donovan, the two Donnies.
Yeah, the Donnies.
I really like Donovan because I love-
Shut the fuck up.
Who are you telling to shut the fuck up?
Shut the fuck up, Donnie.
Donnie.
Oh, oh yeah.
That old chestnut.
It's a movie.
No, I really enjoyed being Donovan
because he felt so opposite of like all the characters.
He was good.
He was really good.
And then his turn at the end, wow,
you made some really dark decisions there.
Yeah, I definitely wasn't forced upon it
by some unknown entity.
I messaged you and was like,
hey, you want to get fucking wild?
And you were like, anything to give Donovan more power
is literally what you responded with.
I would literally,
you want me to kill all those members of contention?
They also said for Zach,
what do you need from the community
to release the campaign notes in some form?
Money.
Which actions from the players did you most expect
and which was the furthest from what you expected?
Good question.
I expected some things here and there,
but most of the time I just,
honestly guys, I set up scenarios
with the hope that you will surprise me.
I don't plan the ending of any of this stuff.
And so everything, like fucking everything constantly.
Yeah, but like, I mean,
we touched on this in another question.
I think the most surprising thing
has to be the myriad Keith.
Yeah, the myriad Keith name.
I didn't plan it.
No, yeah, that was the great thing.
You could see that like by the twinkle in your eye,
you had thought of it almost as you said it.
That's the way to role play by my book.
It just says, do what you want.
What's the most squeamest thing
you've seen in real life?
Snake.
A snake probably.
A snake, yeah.
I saw a really big giant black snake in Arkansas
when I was a little kid.
It was so cool.
Oh, that's rad.
It was so big that we heard it dragging itself
across the concrete of the carport
and we thought it was a plastic bag rustling in the wind.
It's just loud.
Do you ever feel like a fat snake?
Like a fat snake.
The snap, like I saw a snap, like a-
Kimono dragon.
I saw a huge turtle one time.
I was like, that's cool.
And it was wet.
It was a big wet turtle.
Edgeworth08 asks, what was the editing process like?
How much did you cut and did it become less and easier?
As time went on.
Editing is-
Difficult.
I cut out anything that seems repetitive
or unnecessary or dead air or me saying um,
like with a long space on either side of it.
That's mostly what I edit out.
I don't edit out a lot of content.
There's not like role-playing scenes
that I have to cut ever.
And as you all know from listening,
when someone says like, hey, let's cut that out.
That's typically like a cue to leave everything in.
So you really hear pretty much everything that we do.
Those of you in the Den of Sin just know
that I edit out dead air.
Not even a lot, just enough to keep it all going.
I just want listening to this show
to be a nonstop fucking ride.
And that's kind of been my goal
is that it just pushes, pushes, pushes constantly.
For sure.
TD underscore Woogie says,
is Wolf the dog going to still be around in season two?
I hope so.
And there's a follow up from Sensory13 that says,
and or Justin as a full-time character.
Second chance to give us the right answer, Justin.
What do you think?
Yeah, you still busy?
Say it.
Fish.
I don't know, Zach.
Is Wolf the dog going to be in season two?
Find out on the first episode of season two, but also.
But maybe not.
Yes.
Oh, Justin said, maybe not.
TBD apparently.
I hope so too, TD underscore Woogie.
I hope that Wolf is still around in season two as well.
He might be busy, guys.
Like underscore Larry says,
this is a question for Zach.
Were the story arcs inspired by the intro songs at all?
Or were you able to find songs
that the lyrics oddly tied up with the story arcs?
Either way, it's very impressive.
I found songs that matched what I was doing so far
is my answer to this question.
However, No Backbone was chosen
before I decided that the balls would rip out your spine.
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
So the plot of the balls definitely came from No Backbone,
but then for the rest of the stuff,
anything that was coincidental.
Actually, you know what?
I definitely listened to the lyrics
and just like threw stuff in every once in a while.
There's a really fun thing in Pretty Sexual
that's like, I swore I knew you before this.
Yeah.
It was good.
When I like heard that lyric,
yeah, that probably definitely influenced
even though that was gonna be probably part of the plot.
Honestly, I don't know.
Moving on.
It was a lot of back and forth there, I think.
Brofos, brofos, brofos, brofos, brofos, brofos, brofos.
What about Brofose?
Brofose.
What was up with all the hand sanitizer
in the Cabin in the Woods arc?
The hand sanitizer specifically was being used
by Mary, M-A-R-Y, Ball,
who was Old Madge hanging out in the woods.
Old Madge was M-A-R-Y, the ball,
and she had concocted this gel
that could be put on human skin
and then would- And it killed bacteria.
Would.
Whoa.
It was amazing.
I hope that answers your question.
Denny Cready asks the functions
of all the different key devices.
Well, you know, I wanna know.
Basically, if you used the hand sanitizer,
it allowed me as the handler to pull you out of reality
and get you, quote, lost.
So anytime someone used hand sanitizer,
I took the initiative to anytime they were moving
from one place to another,
they got lost on the way to their destination.
So that is what the hand sanitizer did.
It allowed me to put the PCs into situations
that they were not expecting.
Cool. Yeah, that was really fun.
Denny Cready says the functions
of all the different goo devices is clear
apart from the helmet.
What exactly does the helmet do?
You say that the functions
of all the different goo devices is clear.
Oh, they also say it seems it's either illusory
or allows the user to benefit from other dimensions.
The goo devices, let's go over them real quick.
First ones, the camera.
The camera takes pictures
when it has been a certain amount of time in between uses.
It was all based on time for these devices,
or as we saw Pastor Adam Kane use,
you could slam some goo up toward the,
the goo was able to travel through glass,
and so it could move into any of these devices
and then charge them and make that green light lit.
The camera was taking pictures of the dark place,
the plane that you guys ended up in,
and that was all just random
and based on plot, how I wanted to do that.
It wasn't based on location or time
of what you guys were getting in those pictures.
The gun, okay, this is the weird one.
The gun had a bullet that was in the trunk
that John Peters pulled from the green box.
The bullet was to take the user to the Old West,
specifically made by Keith Beans as Silas Cole
to eventually get back there.
However, that bullet was used by Tildi B. Mitchell, right?
So she slams the bullet in.
The person who used the gun previous was Jermaine Glass,
who used it before the podcast started.
So what happened was John Peters pulls the trunk
out of the green box, goes home.
He owes the Glass family mob a lot of money.
The two brothers show up at John Peters' house
to get the money.
John Peters grabs the gun to try to defend himself,
pulls the trigger, and inside the barrel of this gun,
inside the chamber of this gun is, what is it?
Not the bullet from the Old West.
Therefore, the ooze goes in and fills up the chamber,
sending him to the ooze plane of existence.
The next time it's used, Tildi B. Mitchell grabs the bullet
that was with it, slams it into the cylinder,
and then fires, which sends her to the Old West.
Then the gun is used once more, finally, by Rose M-A-R-Y
after the ball takes over Rosemary's body,
but M-A-R-Y knows how to use this gun.
So she blew snot into her hand,
which would have filled her hand with ooze,
and then she loads the gun with ooze
so that she can get to that plane, and that is the gun.
Straightforward.
Very straightforward.
The radio is obvious, it switches, you know.
It's not obvious, I thought the illusory thing,
but he brought up the different dimensions.
Oh, the radio, the radio is obvious.
Radio is obvious.
The radio just switches bodies, but yes, the helmet.
You are correct, though, it is illusory.
So when the person who is wielding the helmet
passes a power contest against someone,
then they can change the reality of the person
who they are contesting with by using the helmet.
But is it an illusion, or is it actual dimensions?
It is an illusion.
Yeah, it is all illusory.
So when you guys were all seeing different stuff
at Bean's Pond, you were still interacting
with what you thought was real,
but as some of you saw,
like the repercussions of your decisions
came about in a different way.
So it wasn't an alternate plane, it was simply illusory.
Al-G-Rhythm, oh no.
I haven't even seen the new Space Jam,
and I know that that's the bad guy's name.
It's so cool to know that Don Cheadle listens.
He says, hello, I love your show.
I have a couple questions.
Originally, was the officer whose name changes
throughout the show supposed to be the gaslight that it was?
No.
Or did Zach, oh yes, or did Zach Wright forget
to write it down in his notes?
No.
Was it originally going to be memory manipulation,
or was it always time fuckery?
It was never either of those things, really,
because it was just split dimensions.
The whole thing is based off of the Mandela Effect,
the Mandela Effect, which I'm a huge fan of.
That's a concept that fascinates idiots.
Exactly.
When I heard about it in college or whatever,
I immediately called my mom and was like,
who wrote the books with the bears?
What were they?
The bears.
That's the thing that was wrong, is who wrote the books?
Who wrote the books?
I always thought it was Emily B. Bear.
It was Jan.
Anyway, so when I was finally able to have Sinbad
on the podcast, that's actually one of my crowning
and achievements in my mind.
Probably against the terms of service for-
I looked it up a few times and I didn't find anything
that said that it wasn't able to be used.
PTBP, I didn't say anything about it.
If you want to cut this, it does specifically have,
there's categories of people who are doing promotion
and not promotion, and you have to make sure that you do.
But it's not promotion, it's art, baby.
Cool.
Luke, that's the name of our Detroiters firm,
or that's our logo, at least.
It's not promotion, it's art, baby.
It's art.
Gonna give us $50.
All right, yeah, so it was just the time splitting off
into different iterations of the same world,
but infinite versions of that same world.
What a great final question.
The final question is-
Zach looked up the definition of squamous,
the ooze and the worms and all that.
Are they goopy or are they squamous?
Good question, Zach, what does squamous mean?
Scaly, and I-
Did you know that when you called the ooze squamous?
I've always pictured the ooze as being squamous.
I don't believe it.
Scaly ooze.
Like an old wet turtle.
I don't think you've seen the ooze,
this word or a turtle.
Guys, it's Delta Green.
Of course it's squamous.
It's a scaly, horrible ooze.
It's very goopy and very squamous.
See, it's just that those are nearly,
it's not that they're quite-
No, they're not antithetical,
but they're close. They don't quite
cancel each other out, but they almost do.
Which makes it so creepy.
Exactly, it's the conundrum that makes it so scary.
The conundrum is that you didn't-
Non-Newtonian liquid.
Thank you, so a non-Newtonian liquid
as both solid and liquid at the same time,
and in my mind, that is essentially what this ooze was,
that it's this horribly, if you look,
if this thing-
Yeah, but which part of that is scaly?
Dude, if it reached out to you,
and you looked at it, and you thought
that you would poke your finger up to it,
it would be hard, but it's still gooping
and oozing toward you at all at the same time.
But in a repeated scale pattern?
A repeated scale pattern.
Scaly?
Yeah, squamous.
Any questions?
No, Zach didn't know what that word meant.
Who would you cast as the ooze?
Andy Serkis.
Nice.
It's all that mocap.
Maybe the guy who did Jar Jar, since he's the OG.
Nice.
First one, first one in the biz to do that.
Is the ooze a Sith?
From the ooze's perspective,
contention PD is evil, so it's like.
Justin, I have a question for you.
As you've been making music for the show,
have you changed your goal or perspective
of each time you sit down to make a track?
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah, I actually have been thinking about that
revving up for season two.
I was actually messaging you,
because I was like,
here's the points I think we should hit,
because I can't just make any old random song.
I mean, I can, but then it would be like,
okay, this is only useful for one really particular moment.
So yeah, when I'm thinking about the music,
I'm thinking about how it interplays with the,
I don't know what the correct term is,
the moment to moment of the sound, yes.
I'm thinking of how the audio exists.
No, I'm thinking of how the music interacts with
the different tones.
What was that?
The feeling, the mood.
Oh yeah, the mood, the feel, the vibe, the aura.
But yeah, so I...
Aria.
God damn it.
The start of it all.
I, what do you get, oh God,
you guys keep mumbling, interrupting, I can't.
So you try to make it good now, right?
So I'm gonna hit you, I'm gonna hit you.
Aria.
Yeah, I try to make it good.
I wanna compliment you on that you do make tracks
that fit these moods, but the Western one,
the one that has that kind of tinkly guitar or piano riff,
maybe it is, that is so perfectly creepy and old timey.
It's one of my favorites, it's so good.
Thank you.
I liked the, it was fun to know ahead of time
that there was gonna be the old West arc
and be like, all right, let's do some...
Basically I took what I would have done,
like a weird arpeggiated synth thing or other,
or just nasty synth stuff and converted it over
to like Western instruments and stylings and stuff.
And so that was very fun.
The name that Justin gave the track
that Joe brought up there, The Urgent Wind.
Nice, yeah.
The Urgent Wind was the time rewind.
That one wasn't in the old Western arc, was it?
That one's called A Road,
then it just got uploaded to YouTube
cause someone on the subreddit.
A Road or A Road?
A Road.
A Rod.
I love it.
It's a good one.
I thought you were talking about the one that's like...
Waaah.
No, I also love that one.
That's my favorite track.
The one that has the big strings.
It's just me on a microphone going waaah.
Zach never uses it,
and it's Zach's, it's Joe's fucking favorite song.
Put it in the show, coward.
It's all right, I fall asleep to it at night anyway.
Yeah, it's four hours long, so I get it.
He's like, hey.
Hey folks, thanks for listening.
You're welcome.
Wait, no, you, the listener, not me.
No, we really appreciate you listening, Justin.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks, Justin.
You're welcome.
Do you have any questions for us?
Yeah.
As a matter of fact.
Unfurls a scroll.
What the fuck?
Hey, Zach.
Good question.
What the fuck, bro?
Hey, Justin, I've been meaning to tell you,
our friendship means a whole bunch to me,
and I'm really proud of you,
that you're taking the shot at grad school
and really focusing on it.
And while doing that,
we've created the artistic collaboration
that I've been most proud of in my entire life.
And we've collaborated on a lot of artistic stuff together
from music to short films to this.
And this is like really fun to make.
And I'm really glad that you're on the team.
Thank you.
Me too.
I agree.
We weren't talking to the rest of you.
This is me and Zach's time.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, I love creative group collaboration is fucking rips.
Everyone should try it sometime.
Seriously.
When you first started this,
did you think our characters were gonna die
and we would make new ones or were you?
Yeah.
Yep.
And I thought you'd have new ones.
We're gonna do that in season two, by the way.
I'm gonna pull out the rug from some of those
Pulp Cthulhu rules that we're using.
And we're gonna go a little bit harder on Delta Green
to get some nice, satisfying character death.
Is this a regular street like feed episode?
This is.
If you want to hear me play a minion,
subscribe to the Patreon.
Nope.
That is also gonna be on the main feed.
That is?
Yeah.
Do it anyway.
He's talking about his own thing he's gonna put out.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Luke, are you gonna run a RPG where we all play minions
and you play guru?
Yes.
Yes, we will be doing that before season two.
Why did you conjure that into existence?
I don't even.
I quit if you don't edit that out.
I'm writing it right now as soon as I.
Do minions say anything except banana?
Would we all just be yelling banana at Luke?
What else do they say?
Pudding and other kind of like desserts and fruits.
Pudding.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Yeah, so thanks for listening.
We're gonna be back next week, actually.
We're gonna be back next week.
If you follow along on Instagram or Twitter or Facebook,
Reddit or Discord or any of the places
where you can find out information from us
outside of just listening to our voices speak,
then you know that on November 5th,
the first episode will be out of a short five episode run
that we're doing with a guest handler
running us through the Delta Green scenario,
Convergence that is being updated by Delta Green
and Arc Dream publishing right now
and our handler was able to get his hands on
straight from the source of Shane Ivy,
a copy of the updated version of Convergence
for the new Delta Green role playing game
to run for us.
And then after that, on the main feed,
I will be running Control Copy,
another Delta Green scenario,
this one written by Dennis Detwiller,
which the patrons voted on over on patreon.com
slash pretending pod.
They chose Control Copy for me to run for this crew
and that'll be out after Convergence.
And so that's what we've got ready now
and more on the horizon.
And we're all really, really looking forward to it.
I can't wait to play.
Yeah, we got so much good gaming ahead of us.
Oh yeah.
There's a lot of gaming left in these old bones, Joe.
So let us tickle your ear holes
with our Deez Nuts and Deez Nuts signing off.
This has been Luke from NPR.
Pweloo, how can you have enough
Drowning out all the notes