Hello friends, strangers, bits of biological matter, and hitchhikers from all over the
galaxy.
I am your guide Wolf the Dog, here to disseminate information and tips to help better your life
in the vast emptiness of space.
Get your towels ready, cause it's gonna be a wet one here at 694.2 PTBP, the galaxy's
only holistic radio station.
I hope y'all are ready to buy some of my supplements, cause we got a new Howlin' with Wolf this
week.
This one comes from Man's Best Friend's Best Friend on Twitter, and Zach's friend Jack
in real life.
Note here says, your wedding reception this weekend made Zach real fuckin' happy.
You two compliment each other so beautifully.
He has a personal request for Wolfie.
He writes, at some point in the show Zach was having a drink with 1800 and some type
of seltzer or soda water I think.
Problem is, I'm too lazy to go back and find the episode slash recipe lol, so I'd like
to request a formalization of the drink recipe, with measurements included, read by Mr. Dog.
Ooh baby, Mr. Dog, I love the ring of that.
Well best friend, I'm in the delightful position of being able to deliver exactly what you
request.
I have here the recipe for Zach's Roleplay and Juice.
It is two ounces 1800 silver tequila and one ounce Grand Marnier in a rocks filled glass
with crushed ice, topped with grapefruit spindrift sparkling water, served with a lime wedge
that should be promptly squeezed and muddled into the drink with dirty fingers.
Enjoy the blessing and curse of being the Luis Mendoza of your roleplaying group.
He's the kid from D2, The Mighty Ducks, and D3, The Mighty Ducks, who could skate real
fast but could not stop.
You know, people call Wolf the Luis Mendoza of radio, I uh, I don't know what it means
but people keep saying it.
Remember, if you want to write up something for your wolf to how, tag at Pretending Pod
on Instagram or Twitter, tag Pretending To Be People on Facebook, or write a 5 star review
and email us at pretendingpod at gmail dot com.
Also get up on the contest happening over on the subreddit, r slash pretending to be
people, all entries have a shot at winning a D&D 5e starter set.
If anything, go check out all the brilliant entries on the thread so far, including a
work of staggeringly beautiful non-fiction that depicts love between Joe Terry and his
character Clark Bishop.
Seriously y'all, it's there, and it's delicious.
Speaking of facts, it is the news.
Last time, Kathy Piston, Doug Jacobs, and the body of Agent Trent Chad, Keith Vigna,
Clark Bishop, and John Lee Kevinmore did their best to survive what seemed to be an
imminent demise.
After a lethal contest with a human man that is also somehow seemingly part fish and a
monstrous giant version of the same abomination, Keith Vigna fell asleep due to blood loss,
taking us now to the darkness inside his unconscious mind.
It is kudzu with no backbone.
Keith, yes.
In the darkness, you see a woman wearing old-timey clothing.
She looks very normal, except for the hole in the middle of her head.
Regardless of how she turns to look either way, you can see right through the middle
of her head, and she is walking toward you.
As she walks, her clothes change multiple times, as if she's in an unnatural fashion
show that is moving forward in time, decade by decade.
She pulls out a Zippo lighter, and as it hits the ground, you see the House of Chief Maggie
Cook go up in flames.
You saw this happen in the front yard, but this time, right now, you see it from the
backyard.
The fire spreads and explodes toward you, over you, through you, and you turn around
to see these flames ignite the pond, Bean's Pond, and immediately, the water evaporates.
Looking down into a dry basin filled with fish flopping their final flops, you see your
brother Ferguson Beans, crouched over a hatch in the ground, wearing a cowboy hat and spurs,
and the watch your father, William, gave him.
You look down on your wrist, and the watch is there.
You look up, and the pond is filled with water and animals, and Tildy B. Mitchell comes walking
up out of the water toward you, and darkness fills your vision once more.
Clark Bishop, Keith Vigna is out cold, and it is your turn to act.
Nice.
I'm going to move over there by Kathy, and I'm going to take a shot at that one nearest.
Go ahead and roll firearms for me.
This is just one of the regular old fish men.
Just a regular fish man.
I rolled 24 again.
Wow.
On different dice also.
That's weird.
So strange.
This room absolutely loves you.
Go ahead and roll damage for me.
1d10.
Oh, there we go.
That's a nine.
Nine.
All right.
Hell yeah.
And that one actually goes down as well.
You are dropping these things.
Fuck yeah.
Like flies.
Hook, line, and sinker.
And as it dies, it says, barely knew her.
Oh, that one was so chill.
Super chill fish man.
John Lee Pettymore.
It's your turn.
I don't know what stat this would be, and I'm hoping you would agree with the American
government during World War II that every American boy can throw a baseball.
I want to roll a flashbang just right on top of Keith Vigna basically, like in the middle
of the monster and the other guy who's right on top of him.
And there was another guy that killed him because he's a bad ass.
So yeah, I want to do that.
Okay.
That is going to be an athletics roll.
Who do I have that?
Kind of 50.
50%.
That's a pretty good chance.
Yes.
41.
Yeah.
Describe what happens there.
So yeah, I just kind of like from my position on the catwalk, pull the pin on the splash
bang and I just chuck it underhanded and it sails in an arc and just lands right on
Keith Vigna's chest.
He's unconscious and it explodes.
Would that burn his skin?
A little, maybe.
Not like two hit points worth or anything.
You know what?
It might go down to the armor, the metal beneath his skin veneer, but it's not going to do
any real damage.
He's going to look so cool after this.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, he will.
Oh my gosh.
You're welcome.
The scars on his shoulder and back and then it's like, kind of like a cartoonish like
soot.
Yes.
Explosions.
No eyebrows.
Blown his shirt off.
And yeah, and so this like a ball of light and sound just like emerges in the face of
this giant fish monster and the other fish monster.
And hopefully disorients him for a turn or so.
They both immediately dive into the water.
That could be good or bad.
nearby.
Doug, go see if they're around.
So sorry, before they do that, Kathy Piston is up next and she moves past Clark on the
other side.
Oh, actually I'm in my mind, you kind of bend over and she does a roll over your back.
Yeah, she does.
Rush hour two style.
Super cool.
And on one knee gets in position and nobody understand the words that are coming out of
your mouth, Kathy Piston.
And she fucking rolls a success again.
She's a goddamn assassin.
Kathy Piston has not rolled over 40.
Fucking John Wick.
And she rolled a nine.
Yeah, Kathy.
That a girl.
So she fires into the smaller of the two fishmen, the humanoid one, and it takes an absurd amount
of damage.
You can see blood and acres just like leaking out of this thing.
It is now its turn as well as its fish friend in the very back of the room that you can
see on the other side of this giant beast thing.
And they both dive into the water nearest them.
It is the giant creatures turn and it looks down where it had just had its meal ready
and you could tell it smelled and it knew this, this would be a meal that I've already
had and it was taken away from me from the inside and I must feast once more.
But the flashbang confused it and it swipes down into the water near it thinking that
it's where the catwalk is and it falls face first directly into the water.
What an idiot.
It's a stupid thing.
Fucking fish dick.
I love fish dicks.
Clark Bishop, it's your turn.
And this is the, uh, who, who pressed the button?
Was that John?
John Lee Pennymore?
All right.
So when it's your turn, it'll have been one round.
Is that right?
I did that at the end of my first turn and I had the turn where I threw a flash grenade.
So that would have been one round.
Absolutely.
So it'll be two rounds.
Coming up on two full rounds.
Clark Bishop, it is your turn.
The elevator door is not moving.
What's the numbers above it say?
Oh, that's an interesting question.
666.
Why?
Uh, I'm going to, is that, is my distance to Keith two movements or one?
Looks like two to me.
I will.
I got to take it.
So I'm going to do it.
That's real scary, but I'm going to have to just be there with the plan of picking them
up next round.
You're right there.
John Lee Pennymore.
It's been two rounds since you pressed the elevator button.
What do you want to do this round?
I want to run out as far as I can towards Clark.
All right.
You run to the end of the catwalk at the point where the room begins and it is now, it would
be Luke's terms.
Oh, rip.
It is now the Fishman is the turn of the Fishman gotcha.
And the Fishman turn of the Fishman, the turn of the Fishman.
One of them, the one you would assume maybe that was in the back of the room pops up quite
nearby.
And the one that was nearer Keith and it's giant compatriot busts up out of the water
and then it's going to roll a crit success.
So it jumped real good.
I mean, who cares?
So the other side of Doug is at the elevator door at the elevator door time to waste that
on the other side in between Doug Jacobs and the elevator door.
And it critically succeeded.
Basically what it did is it hopped up out and it is swinging its scythe at Doug Jacobs
in the air.
Doug Jacobs.
Oh, wow.
Doug Jacobs was not full of health as one might say.
And with this critical success, while the fish person is in the air, it swings its scythe
all the way through the neck of Doug Jacobs and the body of agent Trent Chad and lands
standing in between you all and the elevator as the body and head fall separately into
the two opposite sides of water on either side of the catwalk.
He was a good boy.
Poor agent Doug Chad.
So at that exact moment that the song hits its climax, claws grab onto the catwalk just
on either side, just next to Clark Bishop and Keith Vigna.
And it starts pulling and pulling and trying to rip this catwalk down into the water.
Oh no.
He rolls an op too.
Of course he does.
It slows.
It's not very much.
Yeah, it fits contested in any way.
Oh yeah.
Clark gets pulling up against it.
He's like re-riveting it as it comes like popping out.
Clark Bishop needs to make an extremely important strength roll in order to, I assume, hold
on to Keith Vigna and keep the two of you on dry catwalk.
I'm going to have you roll that now against this ought to.
Oh yeah.
Hell yeah.
It's a 54 on a 65.
Congratulations.
Clark, I love that roll.
Do you say anything to his unconscious body?
To Keith's unconscious body?
Yeah, as you're pulling him.
I got you my child.
My baby boy.
Go ahead and roll sanity.
Fuck you too.
That's a fail.
That's a fail over my power.
Oh, all right.
Well go ahead and play that up and remember that you're God and lose one's sanity.
I forgot about that.
Luke's dead ass could make himself useful and bring us some beers.
It's going to depend on how you want to do this mechanically, but what Clark would do
now is he would throw Keith down onto the catwalk, turn around, and he wants to walk
up to the giant fish thing and throw a grenade down its gullet, the frag grenade.
Okay, so you would have to put yourself into the water to do that.
This thing is pulled down successfully and it is in the water now with the catwalk as
you are up on the catwalk.
He's about five feet below you.
I can't.
He can't just toss it down.
Oh, you want to toss a grenade?
I thought you wanted to place it gently inside of its mouth.
Do you assume we're idiots?
Yeah, baseline.
No, of course not.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it, baby.
Only many times.
Joe, go ahead and roll an athletics check here.
We're going willy-nilly here.
Is there any kind of advantage for being right over it?
Yeah.
So you actually get, because you'll be rolling athletics, to drop it in.
Maybe a nice beer pong shot this grenade into the mouth of this being.
Because it's right there next to you, I'll give you a plus 20% on your athletics.
That's really handy because I don't have any, so I got the baseline 30.
Alright.
And then you add 20.
I got a 50 on this.
50% chance here.
Here we go.
I pass a 37 on a 50.
Alright.
Roll 4d6.
Ooh, baby.
Baby, baby.
You got a couple of d6s over there?
Yes, sir.
Actually, I got some here.
Never mind.
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11.
11 points of damage with that grenade down inside of its belly.
The grenade explodes and you hear the same screeching roar that you heard when the flashbang
went off.
It's like...
Sorry, I was yawning into the mic just then.
What was the sound it made?
It was actually really similar to what you just did.
Could you just...
I'm so sorry, I didn't get much sleep last night.
We can take a break if you need a Red Bull or something.
Yeah, I'm gonna run down to the gas station.
And it is John Lee Pettymore's turn.
I want to move one space forward and do the same thing.
Drop a grenade right on top of it.
Roll athletics for me with a plus 20%, putting your athletics at 70% if I'm not mistaken.
You are not mistaken.
Oh, 70!
70 on a 70.
Roll 4d6 for damage for me.
10.
10 total?
Yeah.
Or did you roll 10 on 1d6?
This thing makes the same horrifying noise, but even louder this time.
And it starts to kind of gargle.
It's like...
As it moves into the water.
Down below.
And it is Kathy Piston's turn.
That was the end of my turn.
Any change in the elevator?
Oh, go ahead and roll alertness for me.
7.
No.
Damn.
You know my alertness is 60 and not 6, right?
Yes and no.
Kathy Piston moves up at the end of the catwalk leading to the elevator door
and lines up her shot on the fish man that just took down, decapitated,
and smiled at the death of Doug Jacobs.
And she rolls another success.
Yes!
Yes, my murder queen.
This girl!
Joe, these dice you got me are great.
Hell yeah!
But she only rolls a 4 on damage.
And it doesn't look like it took very much damage at all as she shoots it
in its kind of plate amphibious lining there.
And some of the sharper parts catch some of the bullets and make it so
I don't know why I'm explaining armor on a fish creature to you, but
that's what's going on there.
The fish man will retaliate.
And the fish man that is closest to Kathy Piston rolls a 10 and succeeds
and hits her for 7 damage with the scythe and just digs the scythe
into her leg and she starts screaming out and she's gonna try to like
grab on to the end of the scythe and kind of battle back and forth
but as she's battling it's just digging in further and further and
it finally hits a nerve in her leg and she just can't take it anymore
and falls backwards.
Kathy Piston is now bleeding into the water as well.
Isn't that good?
There's also a fish man that is right next to Clark Bishop and Keith
Vigna and he is going to try to pin Clark Bishop to the ground
so we are going to roll an opposed test of unarmed combat.
Okay.
I rolled a 30 succeeding.
I rolled a 15 succeeding but lower.
So this fish man uses its scythe to pin you to the ground and it
puts the long end of the stick up against your throat and it's knee
down on the thing and as it's bearing down on you its teeth are gritted
and you see this mucusy wet slime form and it's big thick lips and
it kind of drips down directly onto your face and just splats.
The giant creature jumps out of the water and you can see that it
has not taken enough damage to be considered what one might call
bloody in a game called D&D and it's coming for you John Lee
Pettymore.
It's coming for you real fucking hard with one of its claws.
It reaches back all the way to get as much momentum as possible and
it claws at you and it misses.
Kevin Lee Pettymore ducks agilely and doesn't hit its
microphone and he flips two birds at the fish.
Oh very very very cool.
Very cool indeed Clark Bishop.
It is your turn.
You are pinned currently.
The only thing you can do unless you're more creative than I is an
unarmed contest to become unpinned.
Or unarmed combat.
Yeah, I'm going to do that.
Get creative.
Try to persuade it.
Those are the two options.
Yeah, I kiss it on the lips.
I do things your wife would never do to you.
Yeah, I'm going to use the unarmed combat to try and break free.
It rolls a 16 succeeding.
I failed.
74 on a 70.
It's actually going to take a shot at you here.
Can it do that?
It's my turn.
Oh, it is your turn.
I'll wait until it's its turn.
It keeps you pinned though.
That's for damn sure.
Thomas, it's John Lee Pettymore's turn.
Guys, if I don't move do I get two attacks?
No.
Okay, but you can move and attack?
Yeah.
Let me pitch you this.
I want to move one step backwards while tossing a grenade forward
and then shoot a shotgun.
I just got mad deja vu.
Have you done that move before?
No.
I sure like it.
So I toss my last frag grenade at it while I'm right in front of it
and stepping backwards.
Okay, I'll give you a plus 20%.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
Yes.
Okay, 61 on a 70 modified.
Nice.
It's going to be another 46 of damage.
Listeners, we're not saying 46 like the number.
Four six-sided die.
Indeed.
Four D six.
Four dicks six.
Which is the alternative name of our podcast,
but the size is...
We found out the math didn't quite work out.
Joe throws things on.
The weight.
Dropped one of my D six and crushed my balls
trying to catch it with my legs.
The dangers of real playing.
So I'm actually going to count that one
that's a four right now on the floor.
Fucking good because I sacrificed for it.
You know what?
We've never made rules about squishing your balls
while you roll, so let's keep that four.
Okay, so four, four, two, and three,
which is...
Thirteen.
Which is...
Wow.
You do thirteen damage
and you actually hear a whimper
from this giant creature in front of you.
It swallowed a kid!
It's like...
I don't know if you quite agreed to my pitch
but I do want to shoot my shotgun as I...
Oh, I did not agree to that.
You didn't disagree.
I'll let you do what you did. How about that?
Well, you would take it away from me if I pressed the point.
John Lee Pennymore's dead.
John Lee Pennymore, go home, John Lee.
John Lee Pennymore falls over heart attack.
Dead. Get out of here.
You said you trusted me. Trust me now.
Good lord.
No, I think moving and throwing a grenade seems...
seems perfectly reasonable for a turn.
And it is going to be Kathy Piston's turn
and she just got mucked up in the leg by a scythe.
You can say fuck.
We've all been doing it.
For sure.
For real?
Yeah.
You can even say crap.
No, with my mouth?
Yeah.
Alright.
But you can't say beep.
Kathy Piston just got...
I can't do it.
Mucked in the leg by a scythe
and she's bleeding all over the place
and she looks up with this determination in her eyes
and a barrel in her hand.
But the gun part, not just the barrel.
Yeah, I was like, where'd she get that barrel?
I don't know. I don't know. She's good with it.
And she is going to once again
fire at a fish man
succeeding once again on her roll.
MVP.
She cannot stop. She will not stop.
However, she just once again
does not roll enough damage
to actually damage the creature
and therefore, she's like
my leg, your leg
and she shoots it in the foot
and it starts bleeding out
and hopping up and down on one foot
while still chanting
photography, photography
Very cool. Very cool fish.
Very cool fish person.
However, it's now that fish person's turn.
And it doesn't like being shot in the foot.
And so, it's going to come
for Kathy Piston.
This fish creature takes its scythe out
raises it above its head
and slams down the scythe
into the top of Kathy Piston's skull.
No!
I need you both to roll sanity
for witnessing this horrible event.
For some reason that one hurts the most.
A fail above my power.
I fail 24 on a 17.
Alright. I need you both
to lose just one sanity.
Kathy Piston was a human
trafficking asshole.
And just because her death was gruesome
does not mean
that it may not have been deserved.
I don't know if deserved was the right word there
but she dead now.
Her tank is down.
Or no, she was DPS.
She's the glass cannon.
You hear chants from underwater.
MVP! MVP!
It's pretty unsettling but also pretty cool.
I wonder how Luke's doing.
The other fishman
is standing on top
of Clark Bishop's throat
with its scythe pressed down
and according to the rules of Delta Green
it gets a free shot.
It contested me.
I can't contest it.
Dad!
With an automatic success.
Now we're worried
about the rules of Delta Green
and all of a sudden
all of a sudden
Zach's an expert.
I read the rules today finally.
You read a Chuckling Boy post?
Quick shout out to user ChucklingBoy
on Reddit who is doing
incredible work on the subreddit
for r slash pretending to be people
and it is so cool.
He posts these posts
on Monday and Thursday called
Mythos Monday and Technique Thursday
and they are
just phenomenal.
Awesome reference guide for running
a Delta Green game.
They are so good you should go and check them out.
It's absurd.
He has been such a huge supporter
of us and we really
can't thank him enough for all he's doing.
Thanks man.
It's really fun to read all those posts.
I don't read all of your posts because I'm worried
that I'll learn too much and I like
being the one who doesn't know a lot about the game.
Also he can't read.
I just skim him for the stuff
that looks neat.
That's a pretty letter.
Clark this thing
just headbutts you for one
damage.
Breaking your nose just a little bit.
You feel an
intense rush of pain
throughout but it doesn't
kill you that's for sure.
That puts me at 15.
It is the massive
creature's turn and it is going
to rush
John Lee Pettymore who just threw
another grenade directly
at its face
and it rolls a success
with the claw.
The claw.
Oh actually what did you do with your turn?
Tossed a grenade at it and took a step backwards.
And he pulled out his shield.
That is going to be 7 damage
and it has a chance
to grab you.
It failed the grab attempt.
But its claw just like
swipes at you scratching the
shit out of your body
in the front part of it
ripping your cool clothes that Kevin had
all the black tactical gear
less tactical now
that it's been shredded up by a
big fucking claw.
It takes me down to 6 hit points.
Oh my god.
We are fucked.
With that I have to teach you.
How's that elevator?
Roll alertness for me.
It's not that turn yet. Never mind.
Oh we didn't do it though.
It's my last turn.
So Clark at the top of this round go ahead and roll
an alertness check for me.
I fail.
An 82 on a 70.
That would make sense. I'm on the ground being
strangled by a fish man.
I wouldn't know what's going on with the elevator.
Yeah.
I first saw a thing where you just
lifted up enough.
Just to have something happen
maybe.
And it's your turn. What would you like to do?
You are still being pinned currently.
Would you allow
can I reach
into my boot to grab my other gun
and use it to fire up at the
creature? No.
Then I'm just going to unarmed back at him.
So that's the thing with being pinned.
It's supposed to completely
immobilize you.
So he just has to bust out of it with strength.
Exactly.
Which I should be able to do and I'm having trouble.
He'll get it.
I succeeded with a 12.
I succeeded with a 29.
Fuck yeah.
He punched this fish bitch in the face.
Fish fish.
I don't know how the unpinning rules
work but can I fling him so hard
that he gets away from me?
He'll be enough away from you to where you can
act naturally or however
you want on your next turn but so will he.
And or it or
whatever a fish person
that's you know. Does it do any damage
to him? It just unpicks me. No.
It just gets him off.
Crickets. Yeah it does.
Thomas. It's John Lee Pettymore's turn.
Okay. Low on health.
Yeah. Low on grenades.
High in spirit.
I'm going to walk up to the big fish creature and
blast my shotgun at it.
Cool. Point blank.
Very cool.
Did I get any
modifiers for point blank?
Right at the fish eye.
It definitely seems like you should with a shotgun
at close range. Well there's a damage
modifier. Oh gotcha.
Yeah. I'll give you a plus 20.
It's going to be hard to miss. Doesn't matter
because I rolled a 53 on a 60.
Nice. So yeah. Point blank
range. That is
3d6. It is indeed.
It would be 4 if it was a crit.
5, 3, and 2.
So 10 again. 10 again.
Just like give us a visual of what's
going on here. Well John Lee Pettymore
he looks like
Nick Cage at the end of Mandy.
He's just completely covered
in blood. You can see
this giant just like these
gashes down his chest
revealing bits of like bone and
metal and he kind of staggers
towards this thing one space
and then just brings his shotgun
up to his hip and just blast
it right into its fish face.
And doing so blows
a massive chunk
of the fish's teeth
these massive human
like teeth. This is like a mouth
that you could climb up into for
fun and it
like a quarter of this
fish's mouth just
dissipates into like blood
and dust and slime
as the creature
just moans and
spins away
from you as it takes this
massive amount of damage.
But it is still conscious and it is
still moving. I don't know if
I'll get a chance so I'd like to say something cool now
having heard it so much. So
John Lee Kevin Moore
he
kind of groans
looks like tonight McDonald's is serving
filet of you.
No but for real.
And it's so
offended and taken aback it dies.
MVP.
So good Kathy.
John one of the
other fishmen is the one that
just murdered the shit out of
Kathy Piston and really
fucked her up good comes up
behind you and is going
to swing at you
with its scythe.
He rolled a 43
on
a 25 percent.
Nice.
And it swings right
above your head and you feel
the wind brush atop.
You see little wisps of hair
get shaved right off.
Exactly. And the camera
immediately whip pans over to
one fish man standing
near Clark and Keith
and it is going to attempt
the same thing at
Clark Bishop and fucking fails.
Oh thank God. Missing wildly
after being thrown off
of Clark Bishop it doesn't know
quite what to do.
However
what does know what to do
is this giant giant beast
that is just
reeling from the attack
sent to it by John Lee
Kevin Moore. I need you to
roll an unarmed combat
contest.
18 on a 40.
19.
Oh my God.
Fuck.
With
claws akimbo on either side
of you it grabs on
to the catwalk
below it and it uses
its giant arms to
launch itself toward
John Lee Pettymore with its mouth
wide open and it swallows
you whole.
Oh.
Well
Keith got out of this and he's an idiot so
this is arguably
the safest place I could be right now.
With that
you take six damage.
Oh. Well that's uh
that puts me at zero.
That puts you at zero zero? Yeah
I had six points.
Oh shit. John Lee Pettymore
the darkness closes in on you
as the light above
you leaves
as this giant creatures mouth
closes
but you can still feel
all of this wet
gunk
inside and you can feel
water
and just. I want to spend
ten like to avoid major damage.
You still
feel this water
rushing in.
Okay we'll put that on pause.
My super cool monologuing
about the water that you feel
as you fucking die. I was
I was frantically scanning
the little luck thing.
The sheep of how to spend luck.
Yeah for ten points I can
spend uh. You know the last couple
episodes could have used some luck spins maybe.
I don't know. Anyway where are we at here?
I'm at twenty luck.
Oh shit. So I can spend ten points to
roll a d6
to reduce damage on that last attack.
Incredible.
Five. Fuck yeah. Holy shit.
Very well done.
So you're at five hit points and you feel
this water touching your skin
and all this fish guts
and blood and
viscera that is inside
of this fish and I need you to
roll an intelligence check for me.
Ooh.
He has a seventy five intelligence
and he rolls a thirty one. You remember
that the hole that Keith
blew into this giant
creature is on its
right side.
And you think by the way
that you were eaten
and then went down
Jude!
No!
That's gonna be on your
left side. That big hole
there. I pressed forward
into the fish.
And we will
make my way to that hole.
It's a badass scene in my head if you had known
that that's what was gonna happen
that you just go charging at its open mouth
and dive straight in.
That's exactly what happened listeners.
It was my plan all along.
It is the fishman's
turn. I feel like I haven't gone in a while.
Is that maybe the case?
You struggled with the uh...
By the fishman I meant Clark Bishop. It's Clark
Bishop's turn. Big Daddy just went
and swallowed John. Also his name is
Big Daddy. Big Dad!
You don't play video
games so. Oh I don't. What's that?
Bioshock. Oh cool.
You're in the aquatic realm though.
We're close. Sure.
He doesn't know it's a rip off.
I'll take it.
And so Clark Bishop
it is your turn indeed.
How does the action
economy work with picking up Keith?
Is it a whole action to do that?
We'll say yes.
But then you can still move with him.
But only one spot? Only one spot.
And the
fishman that's nearest me how's he looking
health wise? Have we touched him even?
A little bit but he looks pretty fresh.
Oh but you're free of him right? I'm free of him.
I can move now. I just worry about how fast
he can move. He can get all up
on us real quick. I'm gonna have to
I think look at the elevator.
How's it looking?
That's interesting because
the elevator
roll alertness.
I do not pass
a 72 on a 70.
You do not see anything or hear anything.
Alright I'm going to
pick up Keith and fire
the fishman. Alright. No movement.
If you're gonna pick up Keith on this one
I'm gonna give you a negative 20 on the firearms.
Okay. Alright go ahead and roll
firearms for me. So I
normally have 80 I'll be rolling on a 60.
Fuck! It's a 76
I would have passed but I don't pass.
You could roll you could spend 16
luck. I'm not gonna. I think you mean
luck.
John Lee Pettymore.
Holding his breath
and swimming downward into the
beast he John Lee Pettymore
is going to
release his remaining flash bang
and one of the smoke grenades
down into these guts as he like
swims out the hole. I'm gonna need
an athletics check in order
to properly
do this whole maneuver.
on a 50. Nice. Which I think is
exactly what I rolled last time on my
athletics check. You gave me
haunted dice Jeff.
We're bumping rolling doubles. It's weird.
It's real creepy I don't like it at all. Yeah I rolled
two eights in a row before the game even started
because I was rolling like a dumb ass.
Those would have come in handy Thomas.
Anyway
Anyway I passed.
Congratulations.
Thank you. You drop off
this flash and this
smoke and flash.
So the flash grenade is hopefully gonna
I mean it's a big concussive thing.
Hopefully that's gonna fuck up his
insides and while he's in
the water and then
if it doesn't
I hope the smoke grenade makes his tummy real
upset. Yeah no doubt.
Like if you swallowed a cherry bomb.
That would be so gross. I can't even
imagine what that would feel like.
Just like
like dry smoke
billowing through your soft insides.
What you have to do is implant
one into your guts and leave the fuse
sticking out of your belly button and then you can
light it. That's what the belly button is for.
That's what the pros do.
Yeah what do I do
to this fish man? Well I think you swim
out of it but you are now being
birthed out of the side
of this massive creature out of
the same hole
that Keith Vigna
came out of. Was once birthed from.
Previously and as you
as you
I think you're gonna have to get birthed from this fish thing.
To get on our
spiritual level. Otherwise
we're just gonna leave you in the dust.
Like on the astral plane.
As you
come out of it you feel this
other body follow you through
the hole and you begin to swim
out of the creature.
I hope it's just the corpse of that dude.
It doesn't sound like it's corpse. I guess it could have
just floated out.
Clark you got a fish man on you man.
Right now in this room.
There's one still
standing guard at the elevator and
the other one is standing right in front of
Clark Bishop and he is going
to attack you.
And he fucking
fails. Oh thank god. This is absurd.
This is absurd.
This is positively absurd. As soon as it
like pulls the scythe into position
to swing at you it kind of loses
grip of the thing and just kind of grabs
it on the end with one hand and then just
kind of swings it down at you and
the stick part just kind of hits you in the arm.
Yep.
That's it.
That's all that happens.
And the other one is going to
move closer
to the elevator door. With that it's
Clark Bishop's turn. Really?
Nope. I didn't
make an initiative tracker for
myself. I was like oh I can totally
do this by memory.
Nope. Thomas you
you hear a noise
as you come out of
this creature.
And as
you're swimming away
you feel something grip
one of your legs.
Nevermind Zach it was
my turn.
Thomas you're in this water
you just swam away from this
creature that you were birthed
out of and you feel
something grab your leg.
You turn around. No I
kick as hard as I can. You kick as hard
as you can. Go ahead and roll
unarmed combat.
80 on
a 40.
You kick as hard as you can and you feel
the restraint that your
leg has as if you
cannot move it at
all. I didn't sign up for no
water zombies.
Do you try to continue swimming or do
you turn and look? I turn
and look. When you turn and look
you can only see
the murky water that is
around you. You can't make out
where your leg is
in the water. The water
is too opaque
in its nastiness.
Okay so I grab back on whatever's
grabbing to me and try to pull myself
it. Okay like if it's a hand or something
I grab that wrist and yank myself
to it so I can see. Awesome.
Go ahead and roll unarmed combat again.
94.
Got another success.
You actually can use
your ankle as a steady point
a held point in this
water and you can move
your like doing a crunch
to grab at what is underneath
and you feel
nothing
on your legs, on your
feet but something unseen
is holding you in
place. I need you to roll a sanity
check.
90. Fail. You lose
and failed over my power. You lose
control of your
body and
you lose control
of your mind. You're gonna
lose one sanity and your
mind is splitting itself
away from your body. The John
Lee Pettymore part of you
and the physical Kevin
that you embody are at
odds. No this isn't right.
Where am I? What's going on
down here? That's happening in my mind.
John is starting to
wake up a little bit inside of Kevin
and he's forgotten a little bit. Yeah.
I need you to roll 4d6 for the
damage that you left
inside of this creature.
Good thing we just played tiny d6 for the Patreon.
Plenty of d6's to go around.
4 he said? 4.
3 6's
and a 2. Holy shit.
So you see this
absolute explosion.
It's like water shockwave
like wooo. Exactly.
And it actually it lights up
the murky water that you're in.
Looking down there is absolutely
nothing holding on to you but
swimming away
you do see there is a
little fish head about
the size of a softball
that is on a human
body the size of a Barbie
doll and it is
awkwardly swimming. Don't like
anything about that. I need you
to make a constitution
check because you've been in the
water for some time
and I looked up the rules
for suffocation.
Now you look up the rules.
36 on a
50. Alrighty.
So you only take 1 hit point of damage.
Okay that brings me down to 4. Oof.
Now I need you to roll a power
check.
Fail.
89 on a 60.
That hand that you felt
on your leg rips you
downward.
And you feel water just
rushing up your nose.
And I need you to roll another
constitution check.
36 pass.
Lose 1 more hit point of
damage. As we
roll for power again this
unseen force continues
to try to drag you to the bottom
of this tank. Maybe it wants to
take me someplace safe. Maybe it should just go with it.
It wants to take you someplace safe.
12 I pass.
21 I pass.
I need you to roll another
constitution check.
52 on a 60 I pass.
Lose another hit point of damage.
2.
2? Yeah that's what I meant.
Because you're down at 2 hit points we need to roll
constitution to see if you can stay
conscious.
No. 71 on
a 50. This unseen
force drags you and
drags you down to the bottom
and slams your body
up against
a hard surface.
Your eyes
open up
and in front of you on the
other side of this
glass
you see
Marvin staring
straight back at you.
You've been in his office before
and that is where he is standing.
And he
has his hand up
and the orifice on his face
tries its
hardest to make a smile
as your lungs
fill with water.
Glub.
So ends
John Lee Pettymore.
The only one
trying to
pull over
How can you
have enough
drowning out
of the noise
Cause nobody
knows
nobody
dies