what's good my 26 years in the past babies it's crazy that y'all will be 26
years older in the modern times the era from which my voice vibrates to y'all's
ear hairs I am hitting you live from the future in the the past from 694.2 PTBP
y'all know who it is wolf the damn dog here to stick my metaphorical tongue in
your very real ears that's real nasty right there but it's true y'all need to
keep that volume dial cranked up because I'm about to crank out some community
love to me wolf the dog now that's some real self-love y'all this week's how
them with wolf is from Dave Bruno over at the mythos mystery society who
tweeted about the show and tagged that pretending pod which is we all know is a
very cool thing to do he writes dear mr. wolf we here at the mythos mystery
society have been listening to your show and applaud your efforts for presenting
the horrifying truths of cosmic entities to the common folk our methods of
shouting from our headquarters rooftops at any passers-by has been largely
unsuccessful in comparison we would like to let you know that if the good boys of
contention PD need assistance the MMS has a no case too strange policy and are
happy to help spread the word cordially Dave Bruno y'all never give up when it
comes to shouting at strangers from unseen positions if I may give some tips
to get the attention of the masses beneath you throw some giblets on them
y'all got a slop bucket better get a slop bucket what kind of juices do y'all
secrete get on that I'd let the contention PD know but uh we aren't on
speaking terms right now but thanks Dave if you want to be cool like Dave and
write up something for old wolfy to how you know the deal Instagram Twitter
Facebook a five-star review on Apple podcast perhaps if you want to talk
about the show with other listeners you can find them on the subreddit and the
discord if you want to support the show with money you can get bonus episodes
and other rewards at patreon.com slash pretending pod if you want to get a
quick recap of what's going on don't touch that uncle fucking dial because
right now is the most perfect time for the news
Charles Digby Roger and Angela Fairfield Walter and Alan Grimes and Bradley Cooper
met with James the executive director of calm comfy campground during
orientation a game of two truths and a lie got a little out of hand the group
was then led to the boathouse to meet Jack Russell the boatman he was an odd
guy who warned the group to never go out alone in a canoe on the brackish water
of Lake calm the past doesn't seem nearly as fucked as the present I bet it
definitely stays that way no way things get weirder and weirder and spin out of
control nope so stay calm friends stay comfy turn yourselves down but turn up
that radio it's dream girl with pretty sexual
Oh
hey Thomas Isaac so Bradley Cooper is standing with a key in hand it's just us
you can call him Martin Cooper you're so right Martin Cupertino is standing
key in hand to cottage number five and you're standing right in front of this
beautiful little cottage you've walked down those same kind of a cobblestone
path to get to your cottage and it is by itself secluded by all these trees and
bushes and stuff and it's in a little opening space it's quite lovely and
there's a front door with a window to the side and you are home for the
weekend he eyes it all up and kind of huffs and says cozy and goes in yeah and
when you walk in it is equally cozy inside there is a fireplace and it's
fully decorated in a sort of like not quite lake house kind of decorations a
little bit higher level but it's still rust yeah yeah and so your bags are up
in your room which is on the second level and it's a loft by itself up a
staircase and there's a bathroom attached and then downstairs there's
like a living room there's a little study and there's a kitchen I prepare a
small meal of fresh fruits and vegetables that I bought at a local
market before I came here and while those are simmering I'm meditating on
the floor but not very well because I'm paying attention to the cooking
vegetables what is your mind keep wandering to when you're trying to
meditate I told him I told him it had to be white but I think it should be ivory
it's got to be ivory god damn it that and the smell of the cooking vegetables
but he's trying to just focus on breathe just breathe Martin breathe in and out
just focus on your breathing ivory would be revolutionary and after he eats the
meal he's going to take out a biography of Hannibal Barca the general across the
Alps to invade Rome and he's gonna read that for a while and after some time
he's gonna kind of look around and see if it doesn't look like things have
quieted down outside and if they have he's gonna make his way down to the
boathouse and take a canoe out to the middle of the lake cool so as you're
walking around the cottage you come down the stairs after doing a little bit of
reading and as you're making your way out to the front door you step on this
wood panel beneath you and it is extremely loose to the point to where it
almost slides out completely god damn I almost slipped on this slidey and loose
panel I could sue anyway I guess I'll take a look at it though what's
underneath the panel what's underneath the panel who knows but it is definitely
a gym bag there's a gym bag hidden underneath this panel you have to grab
another panel and move it to the side in order to get the bag up out of there I
get the bag up out of there when you get the bag up out of there you open it up
and inside it is filled with cash money there's also a passport there are many
cassette tapes and there is a map it's a map of the calm comfy campground with
Lake calm and then all of the wilderness around it and the map leads to a spot
far away from here in the wilderness and it is circled and it says the door
there's also bottled water snacks and a syringe that is filled with a clear
substance I am going to pocket the map and with a quick visual estimation how
much money do I think is in here at least 10 grand okay I look at the
passport the passport is for a man named Jack Russell and you'd recognize the
picture as the man who is the boat man I'd recognize those fuzzy cheeks anyway
fuzzy cheeks fluffy bags mmm full eyes clear heart of the eyes can't lose looks
like Jack was ready to get out of here in a hurry do the tapes the cassettes
have any kind of markings on them any like side a of Jack explains the
mystery they're all labeled with like Jack Russell number 532 Jack Russell
number 533 Jack Russell 534 Jack Russell 535 was there a stereo a cassette
player in my room there's not hmm how many tapes are there how many did I just
say it's 64 for four okay pocketable amount yeah I pocket them okay I guess I
take the passport to have leverage he doesn't care about the money he just
covers that back up there's also the bottled water snacks and syringe filled
with a clear substance what kind of snacks rollos combos bugles and a bunch
of nuts and some hard meat okay he takes the nuts and starts snacking on them as
he considers his next move yeah they're pistachios without the shell it's kind
of thing that's gonna make our country lazy Zach loves pistachios without the
show it hurts my hands X lazy Zach's the kind of thing that's gonna make our
country is that is accurate is there an employee parking lot you've seen no cars
how did I get here roll sanity uh-huh I figured it was something like that 51
huck on a 50 god damn it oh okay yeah so go ahead and lose one sanity okay as
you cannot for the life of you remember getting here you can like vaguely
remember being in your car but then like you don't even remember taking a boat to
get on the island you were just standing there at six o'clock not the time the
position and you don't have any memory of coming to this island if I say gaze
out at the far shore of the lake say it this is maybe look like we're moving oh
interesting role some sort of science or survival or anything that you can think
of that would be helpful to produce this just intelligence yeah you can roll
intelligence okay 31 on a 70 the island does not seem to be moving okay okay
there was I didn't notice any stereo or anything at the boathouse no and you
didn't see anything when you're in the lobby or in the meeting room either but
you also haven't been up to Jack Russell's apartment and you haven't been
in the rest of the main house hmm I think I need to go find that Metallica
kid maybe he had a Walkman hell yeah do you remember where he was staying no
absolutely not no he got his room assignment and left went straight there
okay what would you like to do I put everything back well I take the tapes
out I keep the tapes in the map but I put everything else back in the hiding
spot okay I go and unlock my luggage and lock the tapes back up inside it and
then he's gonna go back down to the boathouse and take his canoe okay sounds
good he's still like he's like this place is weird but I've really got a
focus for the launch of cube so I'm sorry for the what the launch of cube
voice in my head cube cube cube it's gonna be huge I've got a launch cube
cube Martin Cupertino as you make your way out to the boathouse you are
unmolested I'm gonna say something else you do not see anyone on your way out
and about and you get to the boathouse and it seems that Jack Russell is up in
his apartment and these six canoes are all looking you dead in the face I look
I'm dead back what are you looking at and I grab a life vest and a paddle and
I go out on a canoe and you just hear this echo and your back of your head
that's why we always sticked it to you in a canoe he actually doesn't hear that
echo the the listener might but as soon as he actually heard that the first time
he was like very specifically just thinking about like how it did not apply
to him are you comfortable on the water he is actually he was a high school
swimmer he grew up in California and did did some nature things he really grew up
with an appreciation of California's natural spaces and so yeah you know he
knows his way around a canoe all right sounds good so you go out on the water
oh god I should have asked for a joint from that girl anyway all I want to do
now is row out there's not necessarily a middle of this ring like lake but I'm
gonna go it's a lifesaver it's a lifesaver donut I'm gonna go to the
middle part of the ring okay you know the thick of the lifesaver yeah as far
from either shore as I can get and I'm gonna paddle out there lean back in my
canoe and meditate on cube do you come up with anything I'm starting to second
guess the whole ivory thing I don't know well I'm coming back to cream bone is
also an option but that's really close to ivory roll alertness for me yes okay
that's not that's a d20 36 39 on a I think I gave myself a little bit here
45 oh nice so when you're out there you decide on cream and at that exact moment
you hear and looking over you see the tail end of something dip down into the
inky black water of Lake calm and you see ripples slowly moving toward you he
assumes a karate stance he stands up in the boat which is it's it's kind of
feasible because he's only like five foot seven so yeah it doesn't move it
around too much when he stands up there but he's yeah any I'd like to have you
rolling athletics yeah honestly it looks like he knows what he's doing what is
your athletics I think it's pretty if it's good enough you don't after all 65
oh yeah then you are good okay he gets into like an Elvis karate pose and he's
like what is this industrial espionage and the lake does not reply he keeps an
eye out for a while and then anything nothing cream won't do any respect you
get back there and it's still quiet on all fronts so you can put everything
back in peace and he does do I see a light on in any of the other cabin we
can't really I was like you don't see anyone I hope
well and if I leave right after this I hope no one sees me go ahead and roll
stealth for me if you're trying to be sneaky that way I have it for oh he's
not honestly he's not no no no he's paying a lot to be here that is yes and
it's a goddamn lake trip and he is very confident it's gonna use the lake he
knows how to canoe he knows karate he's fine yeah he's gonna go back to the
cabin and I'm gonna study that map a little bit does it look like what I
think this place should look like it looks exactly like what you think this
place should look like and you see that the trail that was pointed out to you
earlier by Jack Russell if you took that trail you would only need to dip off
about halfway through the trail to go off trail to get to where it is marked
the door okay what are the odds that I brought a Walkman I want to say zero
so I'm gonna okay you have a CD player but you don't have any you know that's
that player so true yeah yeah you do have a walk with yeah but not the kind I
want he gets really annoyed at other people for not being early enough
adapters it's 26 years ago give up the times that was a terrible laugh I'd
liked it I was really scared fine I'm kind of getting invested in this
mystery I guess I do have to find the Metallica kid but but not tonight and
right as he says that a little beeper goes off on his on his watch on a
digital watch and he's like ooh bedtime and to sleep you go yep he gets into
some some really nice pajamas oh hell yeah it's a little incongruous with what
he's been wearing the rest of the day sure but this is this is some good
sleepwear high thread count mm-hmm hell yeah
hello Joe hello Zach what's up man what's up man what's up dude what's up
dude how you live how you live in large as hell large as hell all right so fuck
I can't do that you got me Roger and Angela Fairfield are standing in front
of cottage number nine you've got the key in your hand with the little keychain
hanging down that says number nine right on it and you're staring at this
beautiful little cozy little cottage it's in its own little clearing so
there's trees all over but yeah there there's an opening for this cottage to
be and you've got a front door and a window in the front seems to be a
two-story with loft as the second story from what you can tell outside you said
just a window it's not like a nice glass or anything like that it's a nice glass
little bay window sure okay I got you I'm getting a picture yeah yeah it's got
a chimney brick chimney and when you go in it's equally as like rustic and
charming and modern as the main big house was and you see that there is a
living room there's a study and there's a kitchen and then when you go up the
stairs there's the lofted bedroom with a bathroom attached is the kitchen a fully
fully equipped kitchen it is fully stocked and as you guys are in there
actually Angela starts cooking like immediately she's like I'm just like a
little hungry and you notice that as she's moving around the kitchen she
seems to know where everything is she's just like opening up drawers and
grabbing what she needs honey have you ever have you ever stayed here before
have you been to the common comfy campground without me no you seem to know
your way around that kitchen pretty dang well oh yeah well it's like this kitchen
is set up so intuitively it's like everything is where you expect it to be
that's that's handy yeah yeah it's wild what do you want what do they got well
I'm making just like an omelet with some bacon and I figured maybe maybe some
biscuits make it too all right we'll do I'm gonna go and put on my pajamas and
you head off and she continues cooking you can hear kind of humming to herself
from upstairs and looking around the bedroom it's just nicely decorated
everything is there for you there's I was gonna say there's phone chargers
like ready to go but that's silly I was like what's the nicest amenity I can
think it's just a phone charger already waiting for you USB outlets everywhere
it's fucking sick man and yeah there's a nice big bathroom up there that's
attached Roger is changing into some really nice silk pajamas oh hell yeah
what color are they gold tight you take your time changing and when you come
down she's finishing up cooking I sit at the table okay so I did your eggs in an
omelet like I said I was going to even though like they kind of split like
halfway and so I was like I scramble should I omelet I just didn't know so
whatever it's a it's fine and you look down it's a beautiful omelet I was about
to ask is she a good cook yeah I'm excited for it says Joe can I get that
omelet I'll be right back thanks thanks Angie this looks great you deserve it I
mean thanks I don't I don't know that I did anything in particular but I just
thought that you were just so open and ready for the experience and that just
means so much to me you know you've talked a lot about me being open and
receptive and and as I'm saying this I'm kind of holding my hand out I'm gonna
hold her hand in mine it's am I doing the right thing is this is this exactly
what you want me to do I'm willing to work on whatever you need me to work on
it's just like communication and being being available to talk about anything
like I just feel like with your work and everything you just keep everything so
bottled up I don't want that for us I understand you you want you want you
want open lines of communication which maybe I can I can work on I can do that
are you willing to maybe meet me halfway halfway I'm going full way baby I pull
my hand that I'm holding her hands I pulled the sleeve up and I I'm showing
the track marks to the room to us can you tell me about these I haven't seen
those before roll human I don't think I have any I got they got the baseline 10%
all right it was close but no cigar it's a 26 she immediately is like well you
know I had to get all those shots for when we go overseas next time when I'm
going to visit you on your trip over on the new dig site did Roger have these
does Roger know about these shots are they a real thing they are a real thing
oh the vaccinations they they did that to your yeah it doesn't it look crazy I
sure my arm where I got those two and it's nothing there now it doesn't yeah
no this is this is what mine looks like this is oh my lucky oh my big strong man
are you sure those aren't infected should we maybe see a doctor oh shit I
didn't even think about that does it does it hurt today doesn't really hurt
and she like presses on it it's like no it's it's fine I honestly didn't even
really think about it otherwise I would have said something I'm so sorry yours
you were scared oh did you think I was a drug addict I thought maybe something
had happened that you were afraid to tell me and this whole time if I would
have just been shooting up in the bathroom that's crazy I tell you what I
am embarrassed to have even brought it up on oh my god you Roger does feel
embarrassed good he's buying he's buying the story your wife claiming she's like
into heroin or some shit I get it's 26 years ago and that might be popular but
damn Angie I got it I gotta tell you it's honestly a relief that that's not
what I thought it was of course it's not you know me so much better than that I
have my vices but they're not that also I do have pot sorry about that I should
have told you I I was a little thrown off by that but I figured you know this
is part of the being open thing we're not gonna get in trouble out here I
don't think no I don't think so with these big skies and everything too I
thought we could just like smoke and look up at the stars will you make me a
promise though that you won't go out in those canoes while you're high I just
Jack made it sound like there's always a danger out there and I don't want you
babe if we're out on those canoes it'll just be with me and you clear hell if
I'm getting high all right yeah I feel better about all this all that this is
nice this is really nice I'm glad you thought to bring us out here and you
guys continue conversing while you finish up eating and then she's like I
actually I do not feel good something maybe in those eggs I I don't know I'm
I'm feeling fine it's just that oh oh god yeah no sorry I I'm gonna call it a
night I understand I'll do I'll clean up down here and I'll meet you up there do
you want me to bring you a mug of tea or something glass of water by my bed
please alrighty oh I guess we do that she goes upstairs and you are left alone
in the cottage you doing anything before you turn in you know what I will do is I
will do what I just said I'll clean the dishes and I'll bring up her up a glass
and as I set it down on the nightstand I'm gonna see what they have to read
maybe maybe just sit in the den for a minute and I'll be up here and hour so
how's that sound oh she's asleep oh okay yeah honey you said that I wake up
honey I'm going to read for a while Jim you're not even shouldn't be here it's
Jim honey and she's asleep holy shit Roger is wondering about that but he's
gonna let her let the sick sick wife sleep maybe talk about that later
fucking boom dear but I do want to go downstairs and see if they like you said
there was a study right there's a study what kind of what kind of literature
that they have in on the bookshelves there's a vast array of different styles
of literature in this study and you can find really maybe anything that you're
looking for if it's vague enough I would like the history of the calm comfy
campground that's for sure not there yeah no no so Roger audience if you
haven't been able to tell by my actions so far he wasn't exactly the one who
decided to go on this trip but now that he's here and he really wants to work on
this with his wife he's gonna start to embrace this forestry lifestyle like
half of it is self-help well right well yeah I was gonna say that he gets he
wants to pull down like a local flora and fauna like textbook you can start
reading about the trees and the plants all around this neck of the woods and
he's he's kind of settling into an armchair and trying to put himself in
the mindset of a guy who's at a campground and he's reading about trees
and you're 15 pages in before you fucking falls there's a chance Roger
would be really into it he gets 30 pages in and then with that you nod off with
the book just kind of slumping onto your belly as you're sitting in this nice
comfy chair I like it
hey Luke Kingson oh god thank you that's what yeah I'm sure yes so Walter Grimes
is standing outside of cottage number three with his father Alan Grimes who is
standing right behind you and the two of you are in this clearing where your
cottage is surrounded by all this lush forest green and yeah Alan grabs the key
up out of his pocket and is like okay let's go on in and probably call it a
night walking in you see a living room there's a study on this floor and
there's a kitchen and then there's stairs that go up to a lofted bedroom
that has two queen-size beds and a bathroom attached but where does Alan
go Alan immediately heads to the kitchen and just grabs some tea and puts on a
kettle I walk over to the refrigerator and I open it up is there anything it is
fully stocked as I open the refrigerator I look at Alan and I go father would you
like me to prepare you any food that would be fantastic what would you like
there's pretty much everything you could ask for in here breakfast eggs and bacon
yeah sounds good to me so I pull out three eggs some bacon
pour them a glass of milk make an omelet and cook up some bacon yeah and he's
gonna go into the other room and you hear him flick on the TV and start
changing channels with his tea while you do that curiously I break off a little
piece of the bacon very crisp by the way I was curious yeah I break off a little
piece of the bacon and I put it in my mouth and I chew it I masticate yuck and
I attempt to swallow sure and when I swallow it is immediately rejected out
of my body not puke but like just sent back into my mouth and I spit it out and
in my mind I I think I wish that I could enjoy this like he does and then I bring
him his breakfast for dinner as you walk into the room you see that the channels
are flipping from channel to channel to channel to channel at a rapid pace at
one point Wheel of Fortune comes up sure I see the clue is just things and there's
no letters on the board and I immediately guess beer battered rock
shrimp and then they spin the wheel and they guess B oh my oh my god that was
incredible I wish that this was fun for me as well here you go and he flips to
another channel and when it flips to the next channel the picture is a square
instead of a rectangle like is the shape of the TV and the square picture is in
black and white and it is the living room entryway of a cottage that looks
identical to the cottage that you are in so it looks like like video like
surveillance surveillance videos what what what is going on I stand there and
I just continue looking at the video you see that Bradley Cooper makes his
way into frame and seems to step on something on his way to the front door
so in the entryway in between the stairs in the front door Bradley Cooper steps
on something and immediately looks down and then you see him get down on his
knees and he pulls a wooden plank off of the floor looks into it and then he
grabs another wood plank and moves it and then he grabs a black duffel bag
out of the floorboards and when he opens it you can't quite see what is inside
but then he pulls out this piece of paper that is folded up that he kind of
looks at for a second refolds it and puts it back and then he grabs four
cassette tapes while he does that make me roll something for this but I zoom
and enhance with my eyeballs well you get my eyeballs in quotation marks my
cameras okay go ahead and roll search
seven whole shit okay roll a d10 for okay so add four to that skill so take
the time right now to explain to the listeners what the deal is with Walter
Grimes I gave Walter Grimes 30 skill points on almost everything almost every
skill except everything except like unnatural firearms and unarmed combat
yeah and like heavy artillery and shit like that the yeah but besides that has
got 30% and everything and I've told you that every time you roll whether you
succeed or fail you learn something and you gain a d10 so right now I've got 30
on everything except search I now have 34 and surgery I have a 33 fantastic
surgery of all things I think when I was like oh I've got a 30 in surgery they
were like yeah Thomas was looking at your character she like what the fuck
and then I think he saw that you have 30 on everything yeah that's not right
because I don't want to give away I'm a freaking robot I leaned into it a little
bit but I'm hoping that they haven't I did say something along the lines of
like I have the same hit hips that I was made yeah you definitely made and Joe
gave me a look of like God like kind of like oh interest and I was like damn it
well we'll see if you wrote it down yeah so you zoom in with your eyes onto this
TV screen and somehow the picture clears up enough and where you're looking for
you to see that the map that he pulled out is of calm comfy campground and he
kind of ran his face the island over the island and the the greenery around the
island of the lake and he kind of pointed at a point at the top there can
I make a mental note for my character of where he pointed to yeah sure it's in
the northeast quadrant of the map you also see him pull out four cassettes and
you just see a name on all of them and then a number afterward and it says Jack
Russell number three hundred and and then something now all four of them are
three hundred and something Alan looks at you and he's like we got up I guess
we should look around to see if there's cameras like that and and this in this
cottage I think you might need to look for cameras and I'm going to look
underneath the floorboards by the entrance smart so go ahead and roll
search 16 oh you pry up some of the floorboards they're not easy to get up
but you well I shove my fingers there's like I find one little spot that the
floorboards aren't completely touching each other and I shove my entire hand
down into it some of my silicone skin rips a bit and blood comes out but then
I have enough grip underneath the floorboard and I pull it up and looking
down there you see absolutely nothing and Alan comes up behind you and he's
like okay thankfully there are no cameras in this cottage it must just be
in that one band-aid oh god oh yes of course and he goes and grabs a band-aid
throws it on you and then it's like okay enough of all this nonsense I'm going to
bed for the night you did a great job today Walter and I think that you'll do
even better moving forward I think we're definitely I think you've convinced them
so far and if you can make it through this thing we're on to the next step do
you need me to tuck you in yes please I follow Alan to the bedroom he lays in
bed and I very mechanically like tuck him in to bed and I place my hand on his
forehead good night father I will discontinue soon good night Walter you
can just say you're going to sleep I will go to sleep soon and he is out like
a light pretty quick Walter stands there watching him until he goes to
sleep he walks out of the bedroom he takes up the floorboard that he had
ripped out earlier places it back where it came from kind of like stomps on it
to like put it in place yeah and then does a little tour of the house just
walking around looking at every little piece of each room he goes next to the
door where Alan is sleeping he looks down at his shoes he reaches behind his
head and presses on a pressure point shirt on his head the matrix spot and
his piercing blue eyes turn to completely black and he's out perfect
hey Justin hello so Charles Digby is standing outside of cottage number seven
he's got the key in hand with the nice little keychain rubber with the number
seven on it says calm comfy campground and looking at this cottage it's quaint
cute it's got a little brick chimney and a front door with a window right next to
it and the front door is painted red because that's nice how calm is it oh
dude it's calm as shit you can't hear anything the only thing that you hear is
the wind and looking up you see the beautiful stars above you mildly
off-putting there's no sounds out here pretty weird to be honest can you hear
crickets no you cannot unsettled so when you go into the cottage you are going to
find a living room and that's in the entryway and then back there's a study
and there's also a kitchen on the main floor and then up the stairs there's a
lofted bedroom with a bathroom attached I'm gonna go to the kitchen and make
myself a little cup of coffee for sure anything in it no just black absolutely
sad coffee sad coffee my favorite kind personally sad coffee for a sad boy
what's Charles thinking about as he's going through here Charles is thinking
about just how how he got here he's wondering if this is all a mistake he's
not used to opening up to anybody he's thinking about his past relationship and
how she would have enjoyed being at this kind of outdoorsy place and how he being
from the city does not particularly enjoy it although he's trying his best
with your cup of coffee are you going straight to bed are you the type to take
caffeine right before sleep yes this is this is like kind of his nightly ritual
gotcha he does the whole like slug down some coffee and then lay down and try to
fall asleep let your brain just go yeah it's weird so as you're laying there
staring up at the ceiling ceiling fan going around and round and round five
blades on the ceiling fan you kind of like focus your eye on one of them as it
goes and then you hear from underneath the bed hello is it like someone the
floor below me it does not sound like it's on the floor below you it sounds
like it is under the bed I like immediately like like I just like get
out of bed like freak out cover like fling covers off like like you know how
sometimes you waking dream where a spider is coming down onto your face I
don't know if I'm the only person who has this all the time you could ask Joe
he fucking hate spiders I have that where I literally will have like a right
before I wake up it looks like a spider is like from its web like coming down
onto my face and I will spring out of my bed and throw my covers off the bed holy
shit I've literally never sprung out of bed it's bad sometimes I get sprung in
bed just like like a knee-jerk reaction of like what the fuck and like look
under under look under the bed immediately yeah under the bed there is
a little walkie-talkie down there and it goes hello oh fuck okay and then he
grabs it relieved that it is not yeah a little creepy person or something yeah
that would be worse activates it and like hi oh oh hello sir who is this oh
you know is this Charles Digby this is he who are you oh I just wanted to know
if you figured it out yet what what am I supposed to be figuring out the reason
why you're here I mean that's it's kind of private why I'm here okay sleep well
we'll talk later Charles gets like a shiver up his spine and it's like what
the fuck wait wait and tries to talk again this is a walkie-talkie so you can
talk all you want who are you what's going on here how did you know I was
gonna be here and there's nothing but he puts it on the nightstand next to him
anyway nice and lays back down but he's like staring fucking just dead eyes
staring at it just waiting kind of you don't turn it off you leave it on yes
yeah I'm just gonna leave it on for a while at least until nothing happens and
then maybe I'll turn it off to try and get some sleepies eventually but he's
very perturbed yeah seemingly was this a young girl's voice maybe it was a young
girl's voice interesting is there anything else I could it you can ask
anything you want baby welcome to the show did I hear the girl's voice earlier
you did not whenever I was okay I assumed I didn't and did I see her with
a walkie-talkie earlier which we did not sing with okay say I might I would I
would assume that this is that I also take my notebook out of the night drawer
absolutely take a couple notes of some spooks and then put that back in lay
back down even though I'm like kind of adrenal adrenal eyes adrenaline filled
with adrenaline got sorry you should say that more when you scare people with
your spooky stuff you're right and then just got fucking scared bro and while
the creep spines down your neck you good motherfucker or fatherfucker yeah yeah I
would I would lay back down kind of just wondering to myself what the fuck was
that and just like stare back at the thing but then I think he would be
restless get out of bed look out the window oh and try and look out see if he
can see anything some go ahead and roll search for me
fail okay bad today I am sorry that you don't learn the information that I would
have given you you're like here's everything if you just would've rolled
right yeah I always make my scenarios where if you just succeed on a single
search role you'll learn everything you keep searching you get fucking tuckered
out staring out this window there's something about the deadness of the
night is just wearing you thin and that coffee is not enough to keep you
standing like conk back out lay back down no covers this time though just
like laying staring directly up back sleeper what the fuck what the fuck
indeed
Oh
you