Hey there y'all, it's your little ol' Wolfie boy again here on 694.2 PTBP
Now I know y'all have been missing me even though my last broadcast was only about a half hour ago
It is currently 11 a.m. on December the 6th
Today on Howlin' with Wolf we got ourselves an announcement from user totorosebangbus over on the subreddit
Who posted about the show and tagged at pretending pod on Instagram
If you want to write a message for Wolf to read on air, follow in their extremely helpful footsteps
Tag us on Instagram or Twitter at pretending pod
Or write us a 5 star review on apple podcast and email us at pretendingpod at gmail.com
Totorosebangbus writes
Hello folks, Patreon here and I just want to say that I don't understand why you keep mentioning me
But I would like to thank you for the influx of money that has come my way recently due to this show
Thanks to you all, I am one step closer to getting my mushroom restaurant shiitake on me up and going in the city
I'd like to offer everyone a 15% coupon off for when we do open
Man, I can't wait to use that 15% off coupon to get me a steaming bowl of some of that dirt fungus
My favorite part of the mushroom is all that nasty mud
I hope they don't wash them off too much
My producer has a note here
Apparently a vast and overwhelming number of wolf pups are android users
This makes it all the more necessary to steal the iPhones from your parents' nightstands, your co-workers' desks, your children's hands
And write a 5 star review for pretending to be people on Tim Cook's bondage fetish machine
Man, I can't stop thinking about all those delicious funky mud babies that I'm gonna get at that mushroom diner
The fungus that dwells as a morel
Give me that mushroom stew, baby, and give it some extra stank
Speaking of blasphemous smells like rot and greed and cirrhosis piss, it's the hemorrhoids of truth, it's the news
John Lee Pettymore or Kevin Lee Pettymore or whatever he's called himself now had a vision and is now convinced he has the second sight
Keith Vigna desperately wanted to call the number left to them by Agent Kennedy
Agent McKinley and Billy Harrison
Oh shit, Kennedy, McKinley, Billy William Harrison?
I definitely get it now
Clark Bishop was called out by a strange humanoid figure that just appeared on top of a nearby crypt
And taking us to that scene now, using the unnatural power to roll back time
It is kudzu with no backbone
And now
You hear this massive noise erupt from behind you
You see standing and materializing all at once on top of this crypt that is overlooking the clearing that you are standing in for the funeral of Ari Manstein
There is this figure, this large, like six and a half foot tall humanoid figure with translucent skin
It's got giant gaunt features wearing a black suit and it looks at Clark Bishop directly in the eyes and says
Hello subject 15225181955018 please give me the book
How scared am I of this thing just by appearance?
Go ahead and first off, everyone roll sanity for me
It's like a man in black kind of thing, like a grey man
Exactly
What are we doing? Sorry?
Everyone roll sanity for me
Oh hell yeah, I got a 53
I fail
I have 14 so I fail
I fail, 34 on a 20
Everyone lose one sanity and did any of you roll over your power?
No
I did
Yeah, I rolled a 90
I've rolled a 53 on a 50
Also I need to borrow a pencil
Yeah, same
Shit
Fuck
Why did you have to get this nice soft desk? I can't write anything on it
This is like a test in Men in Black
There's no proper surface on which to write
What just happened? We lost one sanity?
You each lost one sanity
And you and I both rolled over our power
That is correct, so keep that in mind
Okay, very close
I've got a 19 with a breaking point of 18
Oh boy, and Thomas?
A 21 with a breaking point of 20
Oh boy
Luke, where's Keith at?
I'm at 13 with a breaking point of 8
Alright, we are down to the end
I want it that way
That was tight
For $50 a month on our Patreon you can get the
The acapella
It's the PTBP acapella
Yeah, that's hard to say, Justin has to say it like every week
PTBP, PTBP
Anyway, we recorded a 45 track album
Covering every boy band
Well, we just do a lot of interpretations of Tell Me Why
Tell Me Why
We've got Dixieland, we've got hip-hop
It took us a lot of takes, but we put them all on there
There's the Bread Street Boys
Tell Me Why
Oh my goodness
Oh, we even have parodies
Well, you have to get into parodies when you do that many versions
Okay, so you each lose one sanity
And the figure, the towering gaunt figure
Is just staring at you and it slowly begins to hold out
One of its overtly long hands
Clark is going for his gun, but as he's doing it
He's yelling at the thing
What, what, what book, what are you?
And as I finish that, what are you, my gun is pointed at him
Okie dokie
Kevin John has very little left to live
And he just reaches out a hand
In greeting
You're about 20 yards, 20 feet away
You're gonna try to shake its hand
I mean, it's got a long arm, but I don't know if it's that long
How long is the arm?
I would say the arm itself is 5 feet long
Too long
What is Keith doing?
Keith runs behind a
Anything
What do you call the above ground
A mausoleum?
A mausoleum
I run behind the closest mausoleum, pull my gun out and hide
Alrighty
You hold out your gun pointed at it
I need you to roll power for me
I pass a 50 on a 60
Alright
You feel internal struggle within yourself
But overcome it in your ability to continue pointing this gun
And the creature says
Please, I would not like to ask again
Please give me the book
I don't know what book you're talking about, evil thing
It turns its attention to Kevin John Lee Pettymore standing next
And it says
What is your name?
Roll power
Pass, 20 on a 60
You have the ability to do whatever you would like to do here
As it asks you your name
Well I'm Kevin John, that's a long story
What's your name?
43629 and I am here for the book
Well, we don't know what book you want but
I can feel the book is nearby
Clark is looking for Keith
Keith is hiding behind the closest mausoleum
I peek around the corner
Aim my gun at the guy and take a shot
Oh shit
Roll firearms
It's a 32 on a 70
Alrighty, roll a 2d10 for damage as you fire your small powerful pistol at this creature
That is a 4 and a 2, 6
4 and a 2, 6
You fire this gun and you wing it in the arm
And you see as the bullet flies through
This arm just kind of like dissipates and then begins to slowly reform
And before you have even smelled the smoke off of your firearm
This creature is standing next to you with its hand on your throat
And it lifts you up against the mausoleum
And it says, what is your name?
Roll power
That's cocked
59 on a 50
Keeping them honest
You immediately respond with your name
Keith Vigna, what are you doing here?
I was here for the funeral
Why are you shooting?
I'm just scared
It slowly places you back down on the ground and says
Do not be scared
And you are not
Oh dope
This guy's cool
When it was not on the mausoleum and was then at Keith
Did we see it do anything or did it just blink?
It's as if you stood completely still while it moved there in a normal fashion
But it was all sped up
This is likely what you think
The other perspective was
Like what the audience saw
Super duper cool
I am only here for the book
And then I will go
Subject 1522518195518
There will be no trouble
Give him the book man
I don't
John I don't know what book it wants
I don't have a book
I came here with the clothes on my back and a gun
Oh shit I'm not near you sorry
Keith you got a book?
What?
Give him a book
I don't read
I don't have any books
Clark is trying to address the thing
Is it looking at me when I do?
Immediately
We do not possess a book
A book
This creature walks up to you
And begins tilting its head
To the side
Back and forth like a dog
When you say squirrel
And it says
No book
No no book
What you do
It is here you are
Subject
And it's kind of like
Freaking out it's getting really upset
It doesn't understand
Why you don't have this book
And especially why you're not just
Giving it to it
Where are you?
I'm here
I'm at a cemetery in the city
The city cemetery
I am where the book is
You should be here with
The book
I walk over to
Ari's coffin and open it up
And see if there's a book in there
Roll search
84 on a 40
You've merely horrified her
Few remaining relatives
If anyone else is here from their funeral
They are fucked up
There's one old lady who has been sitting there
She can't leave
She's in a wheelchair and she just
On top of all this she sees you open her granddaddy's
She can barely see
And she's completely deaf
She's just like where did everybody go?
Clark is kind of not
He's holding his gun up
To be not threatening now
Can you describe
The book?
What book is it?
The book is necessary
For me to take
Away from you
You are not to be in
Possession of the book
Your time with it
Has come to an end
Now and
We do not want you
Using it any further
I guess good news we don't have it anymore
That is not good news
I need to bring it
What do you mean by
You're where it is but we're not where it is
The book is here
When?
I take another shot at this thing
Damn it
Keith
Roll firearms
10 on a 70
Roll damage 2d10
Oh no
2 nines
Ok
As you fire
Through this thing
Oh right
Sorry you mentioned earlier that it went through
Like dissipated so maybe you're not hurting it but anyway
The blasts
Go through its body
And it falls
Never mind
Every single part of its body
Dissipates into smoke as it hits the ground
Including its suit
And it is no longer
Standing or existing
In front of you I need all three of you
To roll sanity
Fail
Oh I pass
A fucking 14 on a 19
Congratulations
98 on a 13
Is that over your power?
You each lose one sanity
And Luke I need you to dive deep
Ok so that's my breaking point
The next time that you
Go unconscious you will wake up
With a new
Disorder
I run over to Clark
And I tackle him
And I want to pin him down
And ask him
What fucking book was he talking about?
Alright I need you both to roll
Unarmed combat
Just to see who
See what happens here
Keith
You're fucking fucked
I rolled a 40
On a 40
I rolled an 11
A crit success
But we're not contested
Crit beats a 40
Automatically
Crit beats a regular success
So as Keith comes running at Clark
Clark you can describe what you want to do with his body
As he is yelling
At you about the book
What do you want to do with his body?
If you're diving at me I'm just gonna try to spin you past me
You just whiff on me
Maybe I'll throw you to the ground
Fuck Keith
I'm looking up at you from the ground
Eyes wide
Probably pupils
Dilated and I'm
Shaking in like fear
Don't hurt me, don't hurt me
Keith, Keith it's alright
What's going on?
I just
I start to approach him hands up
Kind of like a calm down kind of gesture
I approach him from behind
And slap him twice on both cheeks
To try to calm him down
I've calmed down a little bit but I get up
And I just start backing away from the both of you
Keith it's gone, it's gone
It looks like you got it
I don't
Did you summon that thing here?
Summon that thing?
How did you?
I don't know Keith I don't think I did
I keep walking back
And my back gets up
Into one of the mausoleums and I kind of bump into it
And I still like looking back between
The both of you and I just
I just faint
Oh shit
Keith
John he's out, he's out cold
Let me slap him
A few times to make sure
Slap, slap Keith wakes up
Let me slap him, I don't think he's quite awake
Let me slap him two more times
Slap, slap Here I'll give it a shot, slap
So I'm slapped awake and then
Slap, slap five times
While I'm awake and I
Keith you alright? I'm so sorry
Did we slap you out of it?
You know what?
Came over me
I'm sorry
I didn't
My heart is beating like a thousand miles a minute
I'm sitting down
I look up at both of them
I'm really sorry
Something in my brain just triggered
I don't
I'm really sorry I didn't mean to
Attack you or accuse you but
That thing just fucked me up
What you did?
Oh
I don't know
The alien thing yeah the
The gray man Was he gray?
Translucent He's a
He's a man in black right?
Did that
Did that thing not remind you
A little bit of marfing glass?
Translucent skin
Too big and small
At the same time Not enough lipstick
What the fuck are we dealing with?
Do you have
Any idea what book he was talking about?
Fellas I mean I don't have
Any book
I did find a bunch
Of papers and documents and books
At Jim Cook's house
Maggie's father
Maggie's father Maggie's father was part
Of the circle of knowledge Did you find anything
Books that
You think he might have been talking about
Maybe Do you have them on you? No
No they're back at his house I just
Left them there where I found them
Maggie walked in on me so
You didn't pick up any way Maggie walked in on you
That's where she found me
At Jim's house
So it turns out that
Maggie's dad was in the circle of knowledge
As I was raveling through his papers I did find a leather
Bound book that
Boy it was
It was freaky deaky Like a grimoire
Was there anything on the front of it?
It was extremely grimoire-ish
It was leather bound
It was just the circle of knowledge
You didn't think that one super weird book
You found was the book that fellow was talking about?
I mean I didn't have it he kept asking for it
I was racking my brain for books
That's the one that just now came up
Are you sure you don't have it? I don't have it
Clark I know where it is
Is it on your person right now?
No but we can go get it
Clark
Alright you got me Do you have it?
No I don't have it
Well so
After I shot this thing
Did it dissipate too? Yes
Did you flip through that book?
Did you see what was in it?
The thing was that book it was freaky deaky
I could only open it to the last page
And I mean I could only
Open it Was it like
Magnets almost?
That's what it felt like
Magnets you nailed it What did the last thing say?
The last page was
It had this drawing
This hooded figure with light
Coming out of its mouth but it wasn't actual light
It was just drawn
And written over the top of that
Over and over and over the entire page
It said
It is only through death that he may rise again
That's all I could see
So the drawing
What did it look like?
It was like black
Like if you were to draw black scribbles
In the shape of a hooded figure
And then leave the middle of it
Emanating light out of its mouth
I used an eraser there
In that part
Clark's an artist
Whoever drew this picture
Clearly had some skill
They knew how to use negative space
They had a command of negative space
That is unrivaled in contention
I saw the contention
High school art programs
Fucking yearly fucking exhibition
There's no motherfucking kids in that class
Who can do that shit?
None of them have command of negative space
Fucking balance, color palettes
Point of view
Perspective
As much as I love talking about artwork right now
I think we should get the fuck out of this cemetery
That's my whole point is that it's fucking terrible
If we take it as fact that that's the book it was looking for
I might need to tell you a little more about it
Yeah, tell us about this
I'd love to hear about it
This grimoire
It's some kind of
Word text of some sort for the circle of knowledge
And uh
It has to do with the revelation
Of the overseer
What does that mean?
Yeah, expand on that
From what I've gathered
Essentially the circle of knowledge
Is hoping to
The overseer's maybe a good guy
Who lays peace on the world
Or something like that
Anyway, it's not the big thing I saw
The big thing I saw was a scary thing
That maybe combats it or something
There's some reason they want the overseer
Is this the creature you were talking about?
It's not, that's what I mean
The overseer is maybe the good guy
And the thing I saw is the bad guy
I don't know, I'm piecing it together as I go
Well so, where is this book right now?
It's at Jim Cook's house
Can I take him there? Do I remember how to get there?
Would I remember?
I could bring you guys there if you wanted to see it
Is that in contention?
It's in the city
John, I'm remembering something about what I saw
When I was John
Keith, you got dragged off by those fish men
But
Clark
Old you looked a lot like the fellow you described in that book
Robed and with light coming out of the mouth
Oh shit
Old Clark?
Yeah, old Clark made this Clark come back to life
Wait, I've been meaning to ask you
Where did you get them old fashioned contention PD digs?
The circle had them
The circle had a beautiful rim that gave me anything I wanted
I think that was more mechanical than me
They gave you retro like off
Keith is looking at both of them
I have no fucking idea what you're talking about right now
Oh
What do you mean by old Clark?
I believe Keith Vigna was
Fingers deep into boiling water
Fishing for crawdads when you guys were discussing this one on one
I don't know what you mean by old Clark
I was trying to figure out how the hell I'm around since
Kevin seemed to know that you were around
I asked him
How am I alive?
And Kevin let me know that he thinks he saw
Old me is what he said
Old you? What does that mean?
Did you say plural?
It was an older Clark
And he was wearing them ropes
And his mouth lit up
Just like the figure he was just talking about
In the grimoire
Like a future version of Clark?
Or like a non-bubblegum tree Clark?
Old Clark
Aged
Aged Clark
Clark in the future
Old Clark
I know what old Clark means but is it a future Clark or is it a
This is the first I'm hearing about this I'm super confused
I'm looking for definitive answers in the middle of this horrifying circumstance
Well it seems like both of you know
Have heard of this before
We just know
I mean I don't know about Kevin but I just know that
That apparently old Clark
Dragged me into a room or something like that
Drug me away
An older version of you drug you away?
Now what happened is
An older version of you
Showed up, that light came out of his mouth
And he reached into you
And then you both disappeared
Oh
Well that makes total sense
I get it
So we can move on
Well thank you for clarifying
That does jive
I mean if the circle of knowledge
Has something to do with the light mouth in the book
And then I woke up and then
Maggie found me and took me into the circle of knowledge
It sounds like they orchestrated it in some way
To bring me into the fold
I'll accept that for now
If you said I blipped out of existence
Maybe old me blipped into existence
Well if you blipped out of existence
Don't you think maybe
Is that something like Stan Manstein did?
Kinda similar yeah
Oh nice
Did you see them blip out?
Was it the same way that Stan Manstein blipped out?
Not quite
Did you see where old me came from?
No you was
You was just approaching
Your dead body
Old you was
And then you did the thing and then you guys were gone
Hey well you look good buddy
You're looking good yeah
Thanks John
If none of us know really
Let's turn back to the task at hand
Somebody's trying to get this book
Do you think we should try to go
Find that book?
I mean
We can drive there
We can certainly go and get it
I don't understand its significance is the only thing
It was asking for it
That's the book that it wanted
I mean we can grab it just to make sure it's in our possession
It's in the city
Let's get it and then let's go deal with Marvin Glass
We ought to drive over there get the book
On the way we can call the
Quote unquote FBI
Oh good idea
On the way over there and then we get the book and then
You think we go to Glass?
Yeah I think we settle business in the city
I think so too
So we head toward the book we call the FBI
And then after that we do the Chewbacca plan with me
We take care of business
I like it
And break
Joe roll alertness for me is
Clark has the highest
Alertness in the group
Damn
What's a DM4 but for wrecking plans
Fuck you Seth
Oh that's a hella fail
What was I rolling on?
Anyway alertness
It's a 96 on a 70
Well that is a fail indeed
Well that was fun with your plans
That will certainly happen right now
We're already out of the cemetery goodbye
So wait how did
Both of you arrive here
I drove the police car that we took
To Glass
Oh nice the circle provided me a car
Silver Honda Accord
Cool okay
I came with Rosemary
Well do you guys want to take the two cars
Or do you just want to hop in the police cruiser
Hold on real quick
I haven't checked on where Rosemary
Is this whole time
Are you with Rosemary?
I was she was on Overwatch
On one of these mausoleums
You see her anywhere? She was here
Who's got the best search between the three of you
I have 40
50 I think Clark has the best search
No I don't have the best search
It's under S
I have the baseline I have the 20%
Oh shit I have the best search
Alright Thomas go ahead and roll
Top's bad at searching
Okay you look up exactly where she
Was and you don't see her
Looking around you might even
Put your fingers on top of one of these mausoleums
And lift yourself up and looking around
I do that
You see that she's not on any of them
But what you do see
Is two city police officers
Heading straight your way
Hey boys
Rosemary's not up here but
Two city PDR
They're hoofing it our way
We might want to fucking skedaddle
Okay guys follow me back to the police cruiser
Let's get the fuck out of here
Take the same car? Yeah
I think my police cruiser is a little better than your civic
So let's get the fuck out of here
I wait for John Lee Pettymore
To get down from the mausoleum
And I start booking it towards
Where I parked the police cruiser
Okay are you guys just going out the same way you came in
Through the normal route
That one would take to get from the parking lot
To this clearing?
Taking directly the route away from the cops
Like straight away from them
Even if we have to double back
We're taking the route that will get us out of sight
Of the fuzz
Okay I'm going to go ahead and roll real quick
As you guys begin to recollect yourselves
And head out through the back way
You hear
Freeze! City PD!
We are now in combat order
Thank you
I turn around
Everything's fine fellas
I think you have a gun in your hand still?
I mean
I don't know if I would have had that still in my hand
Everything's fine here fellas
Contention PD
We're getting out of your hair
Your jurisdiction is far away from here sir
Keep your hands in the air
Where we can see them
I was gesturing to the coffin
Which is open
Because I had opened it up
We lost a good one in the contention ranks
I'm kind of frankly disappointed that you're crashing it like this
They both have their guns up
And they say
Yeah we heard there were some shots
That went off during the funeral here
I got it under control
It was the 21 gun salute you mother fuckers
I need you to roll persuade for me Clark
Oh I pass
I fucking pass a 16 on a 40
Alright the police officers
Put their guns down and they say
I'm glad to see that you got everything under control
And they look at
Keith who's wearing just these absurd
Clothes
Is he the one who did it?
Nope he's with us he's a member of the Contention PD as well
Traditional Contention PD morning clothes
I pull my
Contention police badge out and I say
When I hung out with Ari
We always like to go boating
These officers
They want to know more
They start walking up toward you guys
And they're like alright well uh
Let's get this down here
And they pull out a notepad
And they're like we need to take statements from all of you
I want to move up to intercept him
Okay you do so
Does Kevin have any kind of identifying information on him
Anything that ties him to Marvin Glass
You would probably have
Yeah you would probably have
Like a dirty dog keypad
Something like that
Okay I pull the dirty dog grooming keypad
Out of my chain and I'm like boys
I don't think we need to have this conversation
I'm with Mr. Glass
Oh and they kind of look at each other
Oh oh oh
And then they start whispering to each other
And
We are certainly sorry
Please give our deepest apologies
To Mr. Glass and
Actually they cover up their names
And badge numbers
And they turn
And they're like we are so sorry to bother you
Also Rip your fallen
Police officer sorry to hear about that
Sir again
Deepest apologies please don't say anything
To Mr. Glass we weren't even here
That's god damn right
And they turn around and they
Hoof it
Kevin I thought that would work
What's the keychain do
Oh that's a fun one so the keychain
The dirty dog grooming keychains
They like open up the door to the fucking
Den of Sin and maybe some other
Places in his things
The Den of Sin?
Oh the Den of Sin you know where we were
Held as cage fighters
I saw a whole rowdy
Bunch of degenerates
Open up a door on the floor
Just in the fucking street
Dirty dog grooming keychains
That's what John Peters had on him right
Yeah that's exactly what John Peters had on him
And John Peters we know hung out
In the Den of Sin
Well he was a dirty degenerate that couldn't
Bet for shit
Am I the only one who heard that?
The Den of Sin is a name I don't know but I do
Oh that's where we were
The Den of Sin was the name of the place we were at
Yeah
We found those bedding stubs at John Peters house
That tied him to the place
And John Peters he was telling a big story
He was saying he was all important
There wasn't really happening for him
There's more to that than I remember
Well as these police officers
Walk away I look
Back at both of my
I would say former co-workers
And now I think we're
Co-workers now again but in a different
Capacity and I say
Hey well I'm parked over here
As you guys begin leaving the
Funeral do you want to do anything
Here in the clearing before
You head out there are three
Corpses of basically androids
That are laying out
And then also the body of Ari
Manstein is in her coffin
But not in a tomb
I believe the funeral might have ended with
Placing the coffin in the tomb
I want to pay my respects to the androids
And
And then we probably
Need to get on that crank and lower Ari
Down
Keith walks over to the corral fish boil again
And grabs three four more
Lose a hit point
I think it's cooled down by this point
Whoever was manning the fire
Has been gone for a minute
These are all above ground mausoleums
Around us right? Is there one that's obviously
The one she was heading toward?
There is one with an open door
Tomb doors to the mausoleum
That is right nearby
I grab one of the things that the pallbearers hold
The bars on the side of the coffin
Let's get her rested
Go ahead and grab the other side
You pick up the coffin
Of Ari Manstein
And you begin walking her
Into her crypt
That she will stay in
For the rest of her time
Hold on, hold on, hold on
Before we take her in here
Let's look through this coffin
I think Keith
I saw Keith run over there earlier
We've done this twice already
I looked for the book
And then I also opened it up earlier
To see if she was even in there
She was? She is in there
And there is no book in there
Oh good, okay let's bury her
I grab one of the bars
And I close the coffin
And I think the three of us
Start walking into the mausoleum
The mausoleum is
Completely dark
And as you walk in
You hear a voice
Clark, it's a voice
You might recognize
Maybe a little bit quicker
Than the other two
Because it sounds
So much like you
And looking up
You see these little sparks
Of light as a voice
Rings out chanting
In the darkness
You see these flashes and sparks
Ignited seemingly by this
Steady chant
It emanates a piece of parchment
Held by an old Clark
Bishop wearing a dark cloak
That is covering almost all of his
Face as light begins
Emanating from his mouth
And the words he's chanting
Begin to ignite
And the fire lifts off the page
And begins to dance in a circle
Around you
Looking up
You all see his lifted hands
Are cut open
Pouring onto the ground
And actually go ahead and roll
Sanity for me
Fail
Over my power
Or constitution
I fail a 76 on a 19
I got a 1
Baby
Alrighty, so
Luke, Keith, he loses
No sanity whatsoever
He rolled a 1, correct?
And then Thomas, John
Loses one sanity
Clark, you also lose one sanity
So this blood is
Pooling on the ground
Clark and John, both failing their sanity
Checks, both drop their load
Of the coffin, leaving Keith
As the sole support
And the coffin hits the ground
Ari's corpse, limply plopping
Into the muddy blood puddle
In this dusty
Cold crypt
Alternatively, this
Logically sashaying fire
Surrounds you and bathes
All three of you
In a comforting, warm
Light that feels familiar
But the look on Joe's face says
Otherwise
I am diving directly at old Clark
Trying to get him to the ground
And as you do so, you grab
On to an empty cloak
And hit your face directly
On the back of this
Mausoleum
And you just hear his
Clark, that's the guy I was talking about
How can you
Have enough
Drowning out
All I know
Is
There's no
I don't know