Greetings, my great greasy grandchildren.
It's your grease keeper god, Wolf the Dog,
and I'm here to recycle the grease.
I will turn old, dead grease into new, alive grease
once again by using the purifying properties
of my fur hairs.
I am the Greasier.
I am born unto the grease,
and I will return the world to grease once more.
Also, I'm a radio host for 694.2 PTBP.
Grease bless this mess.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf was a bit strange.
When I finally stopped greasin' up the joint
and got behind the mic,
I noticed an unfamiliar package on my desk,
shaped like a cassette tape,
and inside was a cassette tape,
and that was titled in rainbow-colored marker,
each letter a rotating, vibrant hue of Roy G. Biv,
and it read,
Something has been happenin' to you at night lately,
by a lie remains a lie,
and or at countless bats on Twitter.
There is an eight-foot, hunchbacked, wolf-muscled man
who opens your window quite gently at night,
and he climbs in and crouches beside you
in bed there to watch you.
He touches your face with his thick-knuckled hands,
and he opens your mouth,
and he works out your teeth one by one
to inspect them, replace them with new ones
he's lovingly crafted with thick-knuckled hands.
Terribly, slowly, his face is a factless intent,
and you ask me why you don't remember this happening,
and I tell you, you do.
Oh, you do.
Heh heh, uh heh heh, uh heh heh.
Well, uh, thanks from whoever sent that.
I definitely will be sleepin' just as soundly
as I had previous to listenin'
to that nice little piece of audio.
It definitely didn't scare the piss out of me
from sheer terror.
It's a good thing I have my dog, Wolf, the dog,
to keep me company and keeping the terror at bay
for yet another night.
If you wanna send in a strange package
for Wolf to play on these slick airwaves,
tag at PretendinPod on the internet,
or write up a five-star review on the Apple Podcasts.
I'm going to start readin' five-star reviews
live on air here and there,
so make them snappy, sloppy, and sweet, y'all.
Now listen to me.
I will click the links in the show notes.
Man, if we got old, wouldn't I know
that we're with me today,
Gigantumbropithecus.
A Gigantumpropithecanth.
An Umbagumgarbregrath.
Whatever that thing was, it lost its balance
when a clerk bishop blinded the big fucker
with a bright flash of face light.
And then the Don Jon AT-ST
casted a wand-focused Devil Hands,
which, overclocked by the sacrifice of Wheeler Fortjohn,
demolished the large shadow ape.
Planet Juggernaut gracefully turned
and whipped itself up into the air
like jumpin' out of a swing,
if the swing warped and dissolved into nothingness
as the booty achieved liftoff.
And the overwhelmingly enormous champion of the scrap pit
landed directly on top of M-A-R-Y,
crushin' both her and her hopes
to open this portal to Tildy B. Mitchell,
where Silas Cole had trapped her,
deep below Bean's pond.
Taking us now to the sultry dulcet tones
of Mick and Nick Nickles,
is Draggin' In 3 with What Kinda World Are You Livin' In?
["What Kinda World Are You Livin' In"]
Praise be to Planet Juggernaut,
the lord and savior of all who have gathered here today,
as well as those that exist in other variations
of this plane of contention.
Praise be, Nick Nickles!
Praise be, my brother from the exactly same mother.
Planet Juggernaut is here,
for he is our savior no matter the time or place or space.
Praise him!
Praise him all!
Hail Planet Juggernaut, born a virgin and very round.
Rotund Planet Juggernaut is celibate, and that's okay.
Hail him!
Hail him now, you weak idiots!
I personally will weep at the feet of Planet Juggernaut
and clean his shiny metal foundation.
I am already crying so many of my tears
for our round mound of chrome.
Let us use our tears to wipe away the blood
of all of his enemies off his shiny shoes.
I want his holiness, Planet Juggernaut, to come inside me.
I have sinned so many times in this life,
but Planet Juggernaut has forgiven all of them
and cleansed the many dimensions.
My sins are no longer an issue.
Please do not look at my sins.
Look at Planet Juggernaut.
Let's get him now!
Let's give him a quick talking to a post-game conference
here with Planet Juggernaut.
Planet Juggernaut, how are you feeling after today?
No need to thank me, Mick and Nick.
Just doing what I do best.
That's being a fighter.
Mick, I like your enthusiasm,
but obviously I won't come in you.
Planet Juggernaut, after a performance like today,
what do you think is gonna happen next?
What's next for Planet Juggernaut?
I haven't really thought about it, Mick and Nick.
Might just go for a little spin.
Wow, what a humble hero.
Hey, it's you guys who are the real heroes,
you know what I mean?
Catch you later.
It's like he's the size and shape of an Earth
and he's down to one.
That's just incredible.
I'm glad he finally pointed out
that we're the true heroes here.
This Planet Juggernaut, our Messiah,
has delivered us from both the chaos of the Scrap Pit
and the horrible, unsplikable monsters here in this,
oh, nope, oh gosh, oh Mick.
Oh, Planet Juggernaut.
What's going on, my beautiful brother?
Everybody needs to look up right now
and see this ocean of motion of wormy worm times
coming on down towards us slowly but surely.
Oh, I do not wanna be squished by those bugs.
I don't like looking at the worms, brother.
I don't like looking at them either.
Let's hold each other with our eyes closed.
I'm giving you a big hug.
I'm doing a hug.
Make that sound Justin made, both of you together,
like you're quivering and hugging.
And from below, everyone can see the top half
of Keith Beans up in the sky,
continuing to wriggle as the worms make their way
through his skull and attach themselves to his brain.
Luke, I would like to speak to you.
Alone?
I think that seeing as how we're at the end here,
they can sit in on it. Yeah, that's fine.
Keith Vigna, you are standing at six o'clock
on the face of a watch.
It's a massive, massive watch face,
surrounded on all sides
by an unnaturally wriggling ocean of darkness.
And as these worms begin to consume your brain,
you are somehow unable to die
and therefore your synapses are firing off
and connecting simultaneously to the worms
and across from this massive watch face
that you're standing on at noon,
floating in this endless void,
you see Ferguson Beans, your brother.
He's wearing a white suit.
It fits him like a glove.
It's got a red rose on his lapel.
He looks dapper as he's ever looked.
Aside from the bullet holes in his chest,
blood pouring down,
matching his flowery lapel,
his corsage with the blood
that is now leaking through his white suit.
And when he sees you,
he begins walking slowly
across this massive watch face toward you.
How close is he to me?
Suddenly he's standing right before you
and he falls to his knees, weeping.
Keith.
Keith, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, why, what?
Why are you sorry?
They made me, they made me into who I am
and I'm so sorry of the way I treated you.
Who did?
Bob and Dad.
You were always kind of mean.
They turned me against you at such a young age.
Why did they?
They were trying to make me into something,
something that could handle what was going for all of us.
Well, I'm sorry, but they chose the wrong son.
I'm, I think I saved something.
I'm sorry you had to die for it.
You're kind of like a savior in your own right.
Well, I feel,
I feel like a martyr.
Do martyrs know that they've done something wrong?
Do they all deserve it?
Yes.
I don't know a lot.
So is that the answer you wanted?
And he's just crying.
Keith doesn't know what martyr means.
A murderer, you say?
Is that the one that is half goat?
I just, I never wanted to turn you against,
I didn't know exactly what I was doing.
Our relationship and how important I think it would be
later in life to actually get to know you.
I was just always jealous of you.
And I still loved you.
I do still love you.
I was, I think about you.
Why did you do it?
To be completely honest, I don't know.
There was some kind of hate in me from a young age
that just lived there.
And I, you know, I didn't realize how much was in me
until an opportunity arose.
Did you get it out?
Did you at least, did you get it all out of your system?
Are you okay now?
I've been better.
Did Fergie just ask him
if he got his hatred out by killing him?
Yeah.
What a guy.
Keith embraces Ferguson and weeps with him.
As we turn away from that scene,
here's what's about to happen.
I am going to set the scene of what's all going on
here in the aftermath of the defeat
of the Gigantum Burpithecus and M-A-R-Y,
as well as the closure of the portal,
which removed the additional threat
and all around rough time of dealing with Tildy B. Mitchell.
And then after I describe what's going on
with the NPCs that are here,
you'll have one D-12 plus four minutes.
I have a handy dandy timer here on the screen
next to Justin's handsome little mug.
Why did I say that?
And when the one D-12 plus four minutes run out,
this ocean made of unimaginably slippery
little pulsating membranes with two sets of sharp teeth
inside each adorable circular mouth
will come crashing down.
And these little guys will latch on
to every last one of you.
So you'll need to figure out how to deal with that
in your allotted time.
But also some people might feel the need to catch up.
And if there's anything else you wanna do or grab or use,
maybe the phone or the broken radio
up at the top of the shadowy building,
the grabbing or using would presumably need to happen
before you each go into your own tiny worm dream hole
for the foreseeable forever of your character.
So let's roll a D-12.
Who wants to do it?
Joe. Joe.
Joe.
All right, sure.
One D-12 plus four.
Don't fuck this up, Joe.
It's a 12.
No, I don't think so.
It's a three.
Oh.
So we got seven minutes.
Fuck.
Seven minutes.
Thomas, did you just roll a one?
Yeah, but I sure did.
You're like, don't worry, I'll save us.
Oh, I thought it was a D-12 plus a D-4.
It's just one D-12 plus four.
Yep.
Thank, okay, cool.
Thank you.
What a kind DM.
Seven minutes is a good amount of time.
Well, let's just pair up and go into the closet.
Oh.
Nice.
I got it.
Time to go to heaven.
Slowly.
A room full of people who are not invited
to play that game.
Hey, yeah, same.
So like, what happens in there?
All right, I'm setting the timer now at seven minutes.
I will click start when I tell you that I'm clicking start.
Click pause really quick.
No timer has happened yet.
So I was a little confused about the order of events here.
We can do whatever we want right now,
and then the seven minutes starts.
No, we can do whatever we want for seven minutes.
Yep, I thought it was gonna be longer,
but we'll have seven minutes out of character
and in character, just seven minutes total
before the worms come down.
So, okay, you're like,
there's a radio at the top of the tower.
Did any of our characters discover that yet?
Keith saw it.
Keith saw it, okay.
I saw what?
Yeah, so, no.
I didn't hear what you said.
Oh, Don saw it.
Yeah, Don saw it too.
Yeah, what did I see?
The radio.
Oh yeah, I saw the radio and I used the phone,
so I know it's there too.
And I have been positively reinforced by the phone
because I gotta make flurry.
I'm back.
Back in the New York groove.
Now Thomas is gone.
Back in the Maybound town.
Pissing my pants downtown.
Pissing fast, pants are down.
Peeing in my little pants.
Doo, doo, doo, pee in my little pants.
Doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo.
I wanna piss my pants.
Pants.
Oh, I tell you something.
I wanna piss your pants.
Lie.
All I want is, I wanna piss your pants.
I wanna piss your pants.
Are you peeing on someone else's pants in this?
No, pissing in them.
You don't wanna hold my pants.
And when you piss them, I feel happy.
Doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo.
A warm feeling, let that stain.
It can't hurt.
What about Dave Matthews band, Piss?
Piss into me.
Hey, we do something with making my way downtown yet?
Yeah.
Are you ready?
Oh, are you ready?
Absolutely not, this is crazy.
Yeah, I definitely thought this was happening
tomorrow night.
The Luminous Land Liturgy,
which includes Drew Andrews, Councilwoman Carrie Pages,
Gary Daley, Mildred Mitchell, Clara Blankenship,
Casey Kristoff, Everett Pace, Jack Perlman,
Greer Hilfintop, Kermonkernau, the saloon bartender
and piano player, as well as a gambler named Thomas,
along with myriad animals,
either held, perched, or healing.
Keith, you see, Bean is running happily, tongue akimbo,
and this entire group continues to bob and weave
in a ceaseless musical number
at the unnatural direction of the overseer,
though their voices quiet down to an eerie whisper
as they dart around uncontrollably.
Sha-ka-tee-fa-leet-ah, all for the overseer.
The myriad begin to speak in unison.
We appreciate the efforts of subject 1522518195518,
your attempt to destroy the countless alternative timelines.
It garners our respect.
However, plane 1620216 still has far too many variants.
It is unstable.
We have decided it is best to just shut it down
and try again.
For your own safety, please stay here.
We will repeat ourselves one more time,
fearing you either did not listen or did not hear.
For your own safety, please stay here.
And with that, this myriad of lanky skin,
thin, thin-skinned, thin-skinned creatures
in black suits just pops out of this existence.
You have seven minutes until the horrible ocean
of little mouths and huge worms drowns everyone
in the endless isolation of their own unsound minds,
starting with the last one.
Starting now.
What was the number that the overseer,
that the myriad referred to this plane as?
I've translated it before, he's given it to us before.
It's PTBP.
Nice.
Glad I didn't spend seven minutes on that.
Overseer wants to yell to the masses,
I think I can send you back.
You don't have to stay here,
but I can get you back to your own places.
And he wants to try that.
He wants to look at Clark, make eye contact with him
and the plan is to create portals
that send them back to their timelines, not to ours.
The overseer.
Okay.
When you say theirs, not ours.
Can you pause the time while you think?
Those creatures just said that they can't stay in here
because there's too many vectors.
They can't stay in the PTBP plane or whatever.
So I was gonna send them to other,
where they got plucked from.
So the Old West guys go back to the Old West.
Go ahead and roll a natural real quick for the overseer.
69.
It's a 69.
Wow.
Fuck.
It's a straight 69.
That's the best 69 I could've rolled.
Holy shit, really?
I could've rolled.
Amazing.
It just keeps happening.
Okay, so in this moment,
you know that the plane 1620216
that Myriad is talking about
is the entire existence of your world.
And so there are many different infinite variations
on that world that are all considered
to be plane 1620216.
However, with a 69,
I am going to change the entire idea
that I had and allow the overseer
who has dedicated his entire life
to jumping between these little planes
that exist all over 1620216.
He has the ability now to send
each of these Luminous Land Liturgy members
to their respective existences
wherever they happen to come from.
However, based on what Myriad has told you,
they plan to shut down that entire plane.
So you can send those people
to go end their lives wherever they belong,
but that is essentially what you will be doing.
I wish we hadn't started the seven minutes yet.
We're like halfway.
I could send everybody back
and then take the fight to Myriad.
Keith feels himself dying above him somehow.
And he realizes he's like,
I'm gonna die again.
I'm gonna die here.
And he looks around and he sees the people
that he's gotten into this mess with
and he just yells,
Drew, Drew, Drew.
Where's Drew at?
He's chanting, he's whispering,
Sha-ka-tay.
But in the voice of Councilwoman Carrie Pages.
Keith goes up and grabs Drew.
Is the Councilwoman here too?
The body of Councilwoman Carrie Pages
has Drew Andrews inside of it
and the body of Drew Pages,
Drew Andrews has Councilwoman Carrie Pages inside of it.
I could just go grab both of them.
Follow me.
They are very much,
I grab them by the ears and pull them
and run towards the castle thing.
Okay.
They are still chanting
and desperately want to get away from you,
but in that moment,
the overseer has the option to release them
from their bind.
Clark.
He drops,
he knows that for them to get anywhere,
we have to drop this spell.
So yeah, he drops it.
Okay, completely for everyone?
Uh, no, just those two for now.
He needs the power that he can keep.
Yeah, okay.
So then immediately you're getting like a,
oh my God, oh my gosh.
Why, what is going,
what is going on here?
Drew, Drew.
No, I'm Carrie.
Carrie, Drew and Carrie.
Yes.
We're gonna die.
Drew here.
Yes.
And if I'm gonna die,
I wanna die with Drew and Drew's body.
Let's get you switched.
Okay.
Follow me.
Come on, run.
And they run after you.
We have 90 seconds left.
So they're running.
What are you, the other two doing?
Can Clark, by time,
can he try and do a spell that pushes the ceiling back?
Yes.
Go ahead and roll a natural.
60.
Passes both Clark and the Overseer.
Give me some sort of a magical chance here.
Both Clarks look up in the sky
and because they're kind of linked now,
they both know what's going on
and they put both their hands up
and they start chanting.
R-S-T-L-N-E.
Fuck yeah.
And I am clicking pause on the timer at 30 seconds.
They love goosebumps.
Why aren't we paused?
Because of the spell.
You would be seeing how much we bought
or is it just pause paused?
Go ahead and roll another d12 by itself.
Four.
Four more.
Beautiful.
Well now we have, it just seems like almost too much time.
And with four minutes and 30 seconds left.
Oh shit.
So we've got a John and a Planet Juggernaut still in play.
That is correct.
So Planet Juggernaut just shoots up into the air
and opens its giant Pac-Man mouth
and starts eating Xenonibatodes like the fucking krill.
And John is gonna pitch in and try to help the Overseer
and he might even start throwing chunks of the muck world
up as like flak pieces towards the Xenonibatodes
trying to blast maybe even a hole
just above us in the circle.
Cool.
Super dope.
If it's not bottomless and endless forever and ever.
Worms.
Amen.
Thomas, go ahead and roll a d100.
91.
Well, that's not gonna do it.
He eats 91 Xenonibatodes.
That's a good number.
You do what?
You gotta tell me what I'm rolling for
so I can tent the dice.
Yeah, he can pray.
Go ahead and roll a natural for John.
John Ball.
That's a failure.
That's an 85 on a 67.
Oh no.
Okay, unable.
So cutting to the top of the tower, we've got a dark room.
It is pitch black.
Keith Vigna is running in with Councilwoman Kerry Pages
and Drew Andrews and he makes it to this very,
very dark room at the top of the shadowy tower.
He starts to feel really calm.
And he's getting real sleepy and warm.
Yep.
And he realizes what's happening to him
and he looks at Drew.
You gotta do it, buddy.
And then he lays down on the ground.
I gotta do what?
Bubblegum tree, bubblegum tree, what am I supposed to do?
The radio, that's how the cat switched.
I can't see anything.
Yeah, I can't see anything in here either.
Who do you think is at fault?
That's super nice.
And Drew Andrews and Kerry Pages
are just arguing back and forth and confused.
They begin to start feeling all over the room,
trying to find anything in the room.
And Drew immediately finds the radio.
Kerry can't find anything, but Drew's like,
I think I have it.
I'm almost positive that I have it, sir.
Do it.
Do what?
Press some buttons on it and get it working.
I don't, I'm feeling around.
The goo, get some goo or something.
Get some goo?
Or just lay down and chill.
30 seconds.
Okay, Keith, I roll a D100.
If you can roll under 30,
I'll let Drew get out of this room with this thing.
32.
Fuck.
We just need to get out of here before the sea falls.
So Overseer's just doing a giant portal
under the ground of all of us
and just dropping us into wherever.
If that doesn't work,
John asks the nematodes politely to stop.
Okay.
Okay, so I've paused it at one second left on this timer.
He did hit it exactly when there was one second left
on the timer.
Which was right after Joe said he opened the portal,
which was pretty dope.
So let's go ahead and get that roll off time
of dropping this world down.
It's a pass, 52.
Okay, roll a D12.
Two.
No!
Two minutes starting, meow.
And so the whole entire floor,
this lit land all over everywhere that you can see just,
oh, would it be cooler if,
yeah, it'd be cooler if there were walls.
It'd be cool if the two minutes start after
you say all this shit. Shut the fuck up, dude.
I hate it when you're right, it's stupid.
You're like, hold on, give me a couple minutes
to come up with a cool description.
Hold on, guys, it's gonna be cooler.
Two minutes.
Do you want to describe what happens?
I was just picturing that he encompassed
every piece of land that is occupied by people now.
So it includes the tower, I think.
And then my chanters and wherever Juggernaut is
and John Ball and Don.
And it's a perfect circle around all of that
that just drops down, leaving giant white walls
all around us in a giant circle.
It's so bright in here.
Yeah, it's very bright in here.
Is it bright in the room now?
Yes.
That's what I meant to do, for sure.
Wake you up.
And the timer starts now.
Drew Andrews grabs onto the radio
and the rest of you outside see him
running out the front door.
Councilwoman Carrie pages his body,
sprinting out across the land toward you,
holding this broken radio.
And Keith, I'm following behind, running after him.
And I'm going, fuck!
I wanted to die in peace!
Don.
Don starts chanting,
Vis-a-girl, Vis-a-girl, Vis-a-girl.
And he's hoping to rewind some fucking time.
Roll Unnatural for me, please.
Oh no, I thought since it was cool,
you'd just let me do it.
52 on 70.
Yeah.
Yes, you look over and what do you see?
You look over and where you had expected
to maybe see your brother, nephew chanting with you
and aiding you once again,
you see a cartoonishly crisp black skeleton
where this John Lee Kevin Moore used to be.
And you can tell all of them went into that last spell
that you cast against the Gigantopyrthicus.
There is a charred one inch in diameter sphere
sitting on the ground in between you
and your brother and nephew.
And you have all of the strength in this moment to just.
Just purr-gossive, purr-gossive, purr-gossive.
Push back time.
I think you see tears coming down from Don's face
whenever he sees the charred corpse.
And then they start like, before they hit the ground,
they start coming back into his tear ducts.
That's so cool.
That's fucking awesome.
I'm gonna put seven minutes back on the clock.
The original time that you had
immediately after Myria disappeared.
And you are reset exactly where you were.
Everything moves in reverse.
The floor moves all the way back up
and becomes level with the ground around it.
The tower is dark once again,
but Keith runs backwards.
Drew Andrews and Carrie.
The chief leacher for the overseer.
And begin whispering once again.
And the seven minutes starts right now.
Kevin Lee John Moore sees you guys
back in your original places.
He shouts, he shouts, overseer, floor, Keith, radio.
And then he shouts, juggernaut, get him.
And juggernaut wants to try to do it again.
Yeah, while this is happening,
Keith gets his phone out of his pocket,
turns the light on and runs to the tower.
And overseer's dropping the floor again.
Just give us some light in this area.
Okay.
And more time again.
Oh yeah, and I'll do the spell.
I'll do both.
Okay, go ahead and roll.
Back to back on natural rolls.
One of them doesn't work.
Okay.
The other one does.
32, so I'm gonna do the floor.
Okay, so you're able to drop the floor down.
Go ahead and roll a D12.
10.
Oh!
Nice!
That's some juicy time!
All right, and 16 minutes begins.
Boom, the floor drops down once again,
illuminating the entirety of this cylinder
that you've trapped yourselves in,
much like the cylinder that the Gigantum Rapithecus
was trapped in when you arrived.
The difference in the time that we just did,
he drops it so much further down than he did last time.
Yeah, oh my god.
Literal tower of terror shit.
Yeah.
He created an elevator.
Planet Juggernaut, please go ahead and roll
some form of athletics or dexterity,
which we'll call a 70%.
93.
Damn!
93 worms down.
Planet Juggernaut jumps up.
That's two worse than the last time.
Once again, and just like biting for the sky.
The ground drops out from under your feet
as you're trying to jump,
and you just can't quite reach.
And then you fall so far down into this long cylinder
into the bottom, much like a can of beans
that you're now one of these many, many baked fellas
down at the bottom of this saucy, saucy barrel.
Keith Vigna.
He runs to the radio,
and he wants to go grab the phone as well,
and then run back to the Drew crowd.
Okay, go ahead and roll strength or dexterity
or athletics.
Carrying a large old radio and a rotary phone
is difficult business.
I dropped the radio.
You hold onto the phone?
Yeah.
Okay, you can choose.
Well, I've got both in my hands,
and as I like take off,
I have the receiver of the phone in my hand,
but like the base of it is still just sitting there,
and I run and the cord jerks me,
and I drop the radio,
and it's like sitting busted on the ground,
and I grab the base of the phone and start running
and seeing if I can hear anything in the receiver.
Hello, hello, hello.
Shabababee, shabadoo, shababee.
Go ahead and roll a natural.
You have absolutely no idea.
Oh, damn.
How'd it connect?
He rolled really high.
89 or 89?
I have a 79, so that sucks.
Oh, damn.
Yeah, I'm still running back to the crowd,
just gibberishing into the...
You have time to go back for the radio.
We've got so much time now.
Like, we could take real life poop breaks.
Like...
Shabababee, shabababee.
And I'm, yeah, I'm just standing there,
looking at the radio, talking gibberish into the phone,
trying to think, what the fuck am I gonna do?
Young Clark remembers that he had a vision a long time ago
about the Overseer in a dark room lit by a candle,
and he looks back at that tower
and sees that that's what that was.
And he yells up, do you know anything about the phone?
Can we use that?
And as you talk to yourself,
you know that you've used the phone once or twice.
However, each time that you've used it,
they have found you on your next time
going into a myriad different forms of existence
that you're popping in to try to save
each of these towns of contention.
And an impossible task the Overseer has placed upon himself,
but he does not like being chased,
and every single time he is going
and fucking with time and existence,
he is being chased by these tall, gaunt men.
I mean, I don't know, in character or out of character,
the point is we have to get out of here.
Once we get out of here,
we might have more time out wherever we end up, right?
It's just the sea that's collapsing on us
that's giving this time requirement, right?
Yeah, and just the words of myriad ring in your head,
for your own safety, please stay here.
And you know, in Clark's mind and the Overseer's mind,
the Overseer has been able to make jumps
into plane 1620216,
a plane that he is from and familiar with.
He has been unable or scared to jump to a different plane.
Can I, quote unquote, Clark Young,
help him and convince him?
We gotta try, we gotta get somewhere else.
You got more juice here than you've ever had before, right?
This hasn't happened before.
This has to be all new to you, and I'm here now.
We can go to another one.
We don't have to be in this one.
Hey, could he send them to another one?
And John points up.
Clark, young Clark, wide-eyed, just looking at Overseer.
Yeah, yeah, we already stopped him for a minute.
We can do something to him.
We can send them not here.
The Overseer's wide-eyed begins nodding.
Is it as easy as using that telephone?
Wait, hang on though.
The reason we were gonna get out of this plane
was because they were gonna destroy it.
They were saying it's gonna be purged
or whatever they said.
That's every existence that you have ever known
in all of the different forms of you that have ever known.
It's that whole plane.
On PTBP plane.
But that's, so my original thing was,
let's go to a new plane.
Yep, 100%.
So let's get us out of here instead of the nematodes.
Sure, yeah.
Thought it would be nice to save our world.
It's all homey.
Yeah.
But I guess it's better to save the 13 people here
instead of our entire plane of existence.
I mean, that's 100% a good point.
Wait, but Myriad now is gonna destroy it.
Anyway, this whole plane, everybody in it, not just us.
All that.
Keith, didn't you make Myriad?
I can't hear you, I'm too far away.
Keith is on the phone, he's like, fuck.
And he just throws the phone down, grabs the radio
and starts running back.
Did he want to be say my name?
Yeah, didn't you make Myriad?
Probably.
Well then make Myriad not do this.
Stop!
Just screaming futilely at the heavens.
The wormy wormy heavens.
I'm your dad.
I made you.
Stop!
I get it Myriad, he is a shit father, a terrible creator.
I hate him, I hate that he's my god and daddy,
but he made me too.
Why don't you just stop with all this foolishness
and just come on back down to this plane here.
Go to your room.
And we've got roughly six minutes to talk about it
before you have to destroy the place.
Last time you were here, I think,
actually we had a lot less time maybe
and you just like, you were boogying,
but we've got more time now.
Brother, Myriad?
Roll Persuade.
47 on a 60.
A single, tall, gaunt, translucent skinned creature
appears in between you, Keith,
and the phone that has fallen on the ground.
I knew they'd listen to me.
And which one are you?
Hello, we are Myriad.
What's your name though?
You.
I am Myriad.
Myriad, could you not blow up, what was it?
1620216.
Plane 1020216 still has far too many variants.
It is unstable.
We'll take care of that, just give us some time.
We can fix that.
We're working on it.
We're getting rid of some of the variants.
You've been working against me all this time.
We finally did what I needed to do,
now we can work together.
And if you destroy this plane, I would have never made you,
and so you'll stop existing too.
But then this plane will have never ceased to exist,
and then you'll just have to do this all over again.
It's gonna hurt to think about, so just don't do it.
It's all timey-wimey, unless you don't destroy this shit.
These are compelling arguments.
And I'm your dad.
And I'm your brother, ball.
I guess I'm like an uncle, maybe?
I don't know how it works for me, but.
I think of you as an uncle.
He's a very close family friend,
and we've raised you to call him uncle.
Keith is like talking with his hands,
and he is slapping the radio
while he was screaming at his sons.
Yeah, and you see the ooze that's dripping
from the John ball, and you think,
oh, if I could get some of that,
I could probably get this thing going.
Oh shit, does that just need some ooze?
Well, I need some radio juice.
Some just shoots out of John's index finger
straight into the.
I'm so glad you said index finger.
Which is what he calls his penis.
And Keith has a bright idea,
puts his hand on the shoulder of the myriad thing,
and flips the switch on the radio.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
You gonna pause that, Zach?
Pause.
An energy erupts as the brightest flash of light,
it makes the surrounding bright walls
of this cylinder that you've fallen into look dark,
because the light that is flashing
from this radio in this moment is so bright,
you are all completely engulfed.
And when the world kind of comes back
and you can see what's happened,
Keith Vigna has switched bodies with this creature.
And Keith, you have this crazy fucking sense in your head,
like you are tied into an entire network of individuals,
creatures that all work on the same sort of.
My dude, not individuals, not creatures, Keiths.
Keiths.
Fuck you, fuck me, fuck.
It's a whole thing of Keiths.
We're all fucked.
I mean, the body of Keith Vigna is looking around
and touching its skin.
Yeah, a high find has just been thrown
into the body of Keith.
It's trying to understand its own singularity.
It's like playing co-op.
It's like walking like that.
Keith, with the entire hive mind that watches over time
and the universe at your disposal.
The Keithers of the universe.
The Keithers.
Keiths shut their eyes and think real hard.
Keiths shut eyes, think real hard.
Fuck, I don't know what to do.
I can do pretty much anything,
cause I'm a myriad, right?
Just like I expected.
Let me read this long thing that I wrote.
Or when you did this.
Yeah, Keiths, he shuts their eyes for a second.
Oh, I just won't do it.
I just won't destroy the plane.
What do you mean you won't?
I just won't do what they were gonna do.
You're, hold on.
I'm probably, are you?
It's Keith.
What?
We are Keith.
Keiths just start popping up everywhere
and just kind of waddling,
like wandering over to me, Keith.
And they're all talking at the same time.
Yeah, I just won't destroy our existence.
That was easy.
Old Clark and young Clark are just looking back and forth
between each other and this Keith creature talking.
As the Keiths are popping in,
one of the Keiths grabs the phone
and brings it over to me, Keith.
And I listen to it.
You hear your internal thoughts.
Okay, Ty, just making sure I was in control of this.
How do we get out of here?
So John has, like the ball has been speaking,
just like Planet Juggernaut and the other balls
seem to have this weird capability to speak,
just as John.
And he, when he kind of realizes
that they have a moment to breathe
and he is just this ball,
he just starts like making a mud man of himself
out of the muck, slapping it on himself,
like a kid playing in a pile of mud.
Every time you're reaching in
and grabbing more of this luminous land below,
it like turns into like this oozy muck
as it's forming on you.
But pretty soon it's not just this like clay creature thing.
It's assumed the shape of the John you knew kinda,
although it is entirely the black,
like shiny, continually shifting colors.
It's metal Mario, but it's...
Yeah.
And as a final touch,
he gets a little handful of the muck
and you see him rolling it and he throws it on top
and he's wearing a fucking sick cowboy hat.
Yeah.
Hell yes.
In the meantime, you can see some of the myriad,
Keith's like playing patty cake with each other
and doing stuff like that.
They're like looking at each other like...
Some are fighting,
some are very sensually looking at each other.
Do I know you?
And then laughing.
Doing the Spider-Man point here and there.
Doing the Spider-Man Mary Jane kiss with each other.
During this whole time,
are the worms still just slowly descending
all this jovial stuff we're doing?
We got it paused when myriad...
Oh, that didn't have anything to do with the nematode.
No, it didn't.
But I paused it in this moment to just like
let the gravitas hit of everything that's been happening.
But I will go ahead and click start.
Thank you, Justin.
Thank you for reminding the teacher that there was a quiz.
There was a quiz today.
Thank you for reminding me.
Timer has started.
My favorite student.
Two minutes, 50 seconds.
As more myriad continue to pop into this plane,
I close my eyes and think again
and everybody just stops and closes their eyes.
Okay.
Like I unlock the part of the know-how
of destroying the plane.
And I'm like,
maybe if I just condense it into just like a little bit
and not the whole plane and just do it right above me,
I'll do that.
Roll a natural.
Pass.
Describe what happens as Myriad wipes
this entire oceanous ceiling out of this world.
Above everybody is just nothing.
Pure nothing.
Darkness.
And all of Myriad lays down
and starts like,
oh yeah.
So the ground is dark as well?
There's like barely any light in this plane anymore.
And they're just like,
but it's like hundreds of voices saying that
all at the same time.
Nice.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Nice.
I'm going to pause the timer
as the current threat of the xenonimitotion
has been dispelled.
Like a handful of little solitary nematodes
are falling down onto the...
In pure darkness?
That's horrifying.
Yeah.
Just like a couple here and there.
Cause I, you know,
there's an inch or two that I didn't get.
And you guys just hear this like,
squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak.
You just hear a few Keith saying,
ouchie, ouchie.
Ouchie.
So, yeah.
What now guys?
You can just chill with me.
It's pretty nice.
In the total darkness,
you see two lights blink on
and it's Overseer and Young Clark's faces.
They've got this light thing down
and they're illuminating the area around them.
Amazing.
But they are also looking bewildered.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Oh, the Overseer's like,
I fought those guys for centuries.
I don't know.
I've lost track of time doing what I've been doing
and Keith just switched bodies with them.
That was all it took.
That's all I ever needed.
Son of a bitch.
Yeah, we could have done that from the start.
Well, you know, I made them so...
Of course you knew just what to do.
Well, all's well that ends well.
Let's go back home, boys.
Oh, God.
Bad girls on top of the water
Mary and Caroline, I'm on the borderline
Leaving my mind at your altar
Crossing the double line, doing it every time
Tell me what kind of world are you living in
What kind of world are you living in