what's up my babies it's your stepdad's stepson wolf wolf the dog's dog taking over the airwaves
here on 694.2 PTBP due to a frankly terrifying display of holiday cheer aka wolf the dog
gargled down more steaming mollusks swapped than the rest of family combined in our semi-annual
chowder challenge oh wolf is in the dumpster and he's breathing but it's real high-pitched
now it is something to do called howling with wolf so how does the man who drives the snow plow get
to work in the morning next is a non-sequitur transition into fucking Mark Zuckerberg but for
real help my fake dad out talk about app pretending part on the internet and give them money on
patreon sometimes people write five star reviews on the apple podcast app and he gets so happy
because he feels validated and understood and that means a lot to dogs like wolf
now put down the booze and listen for clues it's time for the news last time
Leon told Clark that he would become the overseer go back in time and start the circle of knowledge
Leon split the party tried to shoot Clark with a dart gun got fucked by Joel's uncanny ability
to quit and then Leon Clark came to an understanding fulfilling their original plan
the two headed over to the administration building where they heard numbers coming from a voice
at the end of a dark hallway Keith and John went to Harriet Mox's dorm John last touched again and
focused on the Bruce Robin numbers while Keith scoured Harriet's room for clues turns out
Harriet's roommate Amelia thinks the suicide story is fishy and Harriet was on search for two
things the most corrupt corporation in the city and the overseer and now to the middle of a party
timed holiday themed storyline even when Clark is being a dick it's a track that makes my
ball drop welcome to 2020 motherfuckers it's kazoo with no back
boom
girth knife baby girth knife she's so girthy girth knife baby girth
no she's so girthy girthy so joe clark bishop is walking down this hallway i actually decided
to go the other way yep that makes a lot of sense so when you turn back the other way
you find Cthulhu ah dang it i'll go the other way okay yeah that makes sense
so as you're walking down toward the office you see these two figures in the distance and as you
come up on them you see that one is very short and very slight in stature and also slender
and the small one is uh jumping up and poking at the other figure who is played by Justin
hi yeah what is he what does your character look like Justin six one six two kind of tall dark nice
hair he's a he you can tell he takes care of his appearance he's dressed up quite nicely all right
and this little fella is just like jumping up and poking you in the chest over and over and
he's just like oh come on please hit me god please just hit me in the face i'm gonna i'm gonna need
you to stop right now please oh gosh i would love to four if you just any mumble some other words
and is like please just hit me hit me hit me oh god if you don't i'll have to do it to myself
i i grab him and i shake him and i go i'm not yeah just like that no yeah i'm not gonna touch
your skin with my skin you're doing it right now no okay oh and then he like uh he runs over to
one of the walls nearby and just starts like slamming his head into the wall oh jesus and
he starts hollering he's like it's not the same it's not the same when i do it and clark bishop
and uh leon simpson walk up into that can i get a uh sense of age from of these two people are
they students can i tell yeah they seem to be students uh the shorter ones looks to be a young
looking freshman in college and i look to be in my early 20s let's say let's say and then it's true
once you say that's how role-playing works yeah i walk up to you the well-dressed one who's not
slamming his head against the wall it's not as good sir can you what what's happening hold on
give me one moment sir and he's looking up at this banner outside the administration office and it's
like hanging over uh these windows looking into the office and the banner says at the end of the
10th day my true love had given me blank gifts and it's uh capital g i f f s and leon looks up
at it and he's like oh the administration office it's right there is the banner handwritten no no
it is well made and it is in a very uh festive font it's uh is it uh it's not the same when i
do it myself oh hi there sir and he this little guy walks up to you and he's like will you please
hit me oh god just please just like punch me punch me punch me punch me punch me i don't i
don't want to do that to you what about you and he looks at leon leon's like i don't do you know
is this door i'm just gonna check and walks over and the administration office is unlocked so leon
just like opens the door and turns back and he's like oh come on come on please just like one good
punch why do you want me to hit you god love it but why with my with my body like every single
inch of me just wants and needs you to hit me please four three oh god just hit me please
why are you saying those those numbers numbers i punch him hey
yay as this kid falls to the ground he's just like yeah
thank you thank you for that i can get back to these puzzles i'm trying to solve why was your
friend acting so it's crazy like that i just stare back at the sign again completely ignoring
i look up at the sign it was received tim gifts at the end of the 10th day my true love had given
me blank gifts oh um i can i can do that oh shit i can't do that because i don't remember how high
it goes 13 is it 13 days of christmas sir will you please that one was really good but if you could
just send me right over the top leon looks at you and is like ah should i he was saying numbers
that's why yeah i'll punch him too and just like fucking slams him in the face and the kid falls
to the ground is like yeah oh yeah oh thank you sir and just like scrambles off and dips into
the darkness of the corridor and runs away oh shit how did he look after the both of those hits do we
like bloody him ecstatic and also yeah bloody yeah yeah a trail of uh this little boy's 18
year old boy's blood is that bad we established college age everyone's 18 on this podcast from
here on out leaves a trail of his boy blood i look i look back at the well-dressed one like
what the hell why did he want us to hit him i honestly have no idea he would not stop asking
me did you know him before just i have no idea who this person was well all right but i thank you
from the bottom of my heart for striking him multiple times you're not thinking of
numbers right now are you what are you talking about okay just just checking you're not thinking
of numbers at all and you guys look down and you see like leon had flipped on the lights in the
office when the lights come on you see that the walls of the hallway and the office are just
covered in numbers oh shit the entire inner workings of this building have just been like
chalk sharpie pen blood semen everything just like yeah semen and then everything
have been used to write numbers all over these walls and the floor and the ceiling
i uh look a little scared at the well-dressed guy you didn't write any of these did you i
didn't even know these were here until that guy flipped the lights on what are you doing here son
what's your name what are you doing here my name is donovan west haven oh hey donovan i'm leon nice
to meet you what are you doing here oh i'm trying to uh i'm trying to solve this riddle you can see
it up on this uh banner up here why it's the christmas i don't remember it's the christmas
i don't remember huh and then he like literally looks to the bottom right of the banner and there
is a logo for the jingle ball hosted by csu the jingle ball it's a holiday episode at pretending
to be people where the tinkling music comes in justin it's whatever i'll figure whatever our
normal logo is now has christmas lights hanging off of each letter oh that's adorable and all
the scary music is now um it all has like nice little bells and yes honestly just only sleigh
bells that's the only difference just got this constant jingling in the background which might
be more horrifying we're trading out carpenter for williams the jingling never stops clark looks up
at that banner that's just uh that's just the number plus them all so if it's the 10th day
it's 10 gifts and the day before that they would have gotten nine just add them all up i think it's
carry the one is 55 i think i think it's 55 i don't know yeah you have to do what now you're
the first day your lover gave you a partridge in a pear tree sure second day gave you two something
two french hens two turtle doves and a partridge in a pear tree what is this from oh does she give
you the all the gifts again and then on the third day it's three something or others and then two
turtle doves and a partridge in a pear tree right am i singing the song right you're singing the
song right i just figured that each day she was given the extra new gift she wasn't repeating the
previous day's gifts every time if that's the case the math's a lot higher i mean i it could be higher
i i don't know i'm i'm more should we go in the office yeah i just i think that's the answer to
the question on the banner yeah let's go in the office i turned to the well-dressed guy uh you
have a you have a pleasant pleasant day sir can you tell me what that number was again i've
forgotten already i think it's 55 but if leon's right this is leon by the way hi leon hey donovan
hi if leon's correct the number would be a lot higher and i don't have the time to do the math
right now on it which seems like an outrageous number of presence and i thought the first number
was an outrageous number that lady loves that guy clark you're not doing christmas right
and he walks into the office uh with the lights on you see that the everything in this office is
covered in numbers uh the desks the chairs like anything that people could possibly write on
are covered in these numbers and he walks over to a computer weirdly enough there's just one main
computer in this office space and there is a monitor and keyboard normal computer stuff
leon looks at it and is like all right well i guess let's boot it up and there's a passcode
to get in any ideas leon i mean and he starts rifling through the desk looking around the area
you see that there are pictures sitting at this desk of a woman she seems to be in her early
20s same as donovan what was that last name donovan west haven all right similar age of
donovan west haven and you see that the pictures are with trophies from scavenger hunt championships
with this person holding trophies up and you see the name engraved on the trophies
is amelia lock l o c k e with an e and then there's also a group photo of a lot of girls
who seem to be 18 19 years old as well as this nice and uh the frame on this picture says best
r a ever and they're all holding up a sign that says third floor gifts house which is g i f f s
space house let me let me try something here leon and i'm gonna try lock l o c k e as a password
it does not work i'm gonna try amelia it does not work i'm gonna try amelia lock
it does not work okay well we've exhausted all of our options yep we're done here
so
clark i think what we we might need to just find this amelia lock and then convince her to
unlock this computer no no no we're gonna we're just gonna sit here and guess until we get it
okay sounds good what's your next guess uh zero zero zero one okay that one didn't work zero zero
zero two i tried that one as well zero zero zero three okay i think we're on to something you're
locked out for the next uh hour ah shit should have should have thought of that oh we didn't
even try password oh we definitely should have tried password it was password
it was either password or guest admin you really fucked up admin one two three
go ahead and roll alertness for me
okay
i pass a 21 on a 70 you notice that on the opposite side from where you were standing
outside with donovan in the hallway from the vantage of inside the office you see that there's
actually some stuff printed on the back of the banner is a map of campus and the four dorm
have their names listed and the dorms are called maymay house tinder's house redight house and
gifs house uh will you go ahead and just spell those for my own sanity yeah maymay is m-a-y-m-a-y
tinder's is t-y-n-e-d-e-r-s redight is r-e-e-d-i-g-h-t and gifs is g-i-f-f-s those are hella some names
yeah those are some hells of some names
uh hey uh leon this uh this this picture here with amelia it looks like it's the
the gifs the gifs house that's if you want to find amelia i think there's a red spot are we
sure there aren't any paper records in here though i mean we might just be able to thumb through the
files yeah we absolutely could and you look and see that all of the file cabinets have locks on
them well i know dag nab i mean we could like blow them up or i don't know like we shoot the
locks on them or how pressed for time do you feel we are leon do you want to go on a scavenger hunt
like amelia here likes and find amelia or should we donna our business here oh yeah yeah how hard
are these scavenger hunts usually i mean for me extremely hard but i uh i don't know everyone
else seems to be a genius at this university i don't know do you want to go to the jingle
ball any any help i could get to do this i need i need this win guys i need it i mean yeah we can
uh we can go on a scavenger hunt i guess you know people's lives are in the balance here right leon
i mean that's people's lives are always in the balance clark sometimes you just got to do a
scavenger hunt for a holiday episode if i don't solve if if i don't solve this scavenger hunt
i will literally die emotionally not physically oh donovan the stakes you just raised them to the
right level for old clark to get involved i'm gonna need you to take it down a notch
clark i'm sorry i'm sorry i just got excited that you needed help and i'm here to help you and we're
gonna we're gonna solve this uh scavenger hunt then okay calm down clark you just see important
leon's eyes are big and he looks at you and he's like look at you saving people sometimes it feels
like it's what i was meant to do all right well let's go to either 55 or 330 gifts house yeah i
mean i think mine's correct but if you think that she's giving all those presents every day let's go
to yours so when you guys walking across campus it is again a ghost campus there's nobody out
and about you hear some like
just like for you know just like normal noises from across campus just like some creepy noises
not to dissuade your foley work because that was wonderful thank you but was it all obviously
emitted by a human or is there some of those that are actual animal noises at least one of those was
an owl okay it wasn't the one that sounded like an owl that was a person and you guys make it over
to gifts house unobstructed and when you get in there you see there's a little secretary desk on
the right and the sitting area on the left with a baby grand piano and then ahead of you there is a
glass wall with a door there and all the lights are out by the way nobody's sitting at that
nobody is sitting at the receptionist desk the uh the lonely glow of the computer there is shining
onto an empty chair behind it clark is just going to point at the computer and i'm motioning for
leon hey leon you want to check on that and clark is going to go like to is there a staircase in
here so when you walk forward past the desk you would see there's hallways on either side of you
and there are doors with like the little stairwell markings on both sides right or left well i just
kind of clark just wants to yell down if there's nobody around hello anybody anybody here roll an
alertness for me justin you want to roll some dice yeah roll an alertness for me i bet you
have like a 60 in an alertness uh yeah i rolled two d-10s they aren't he doesn't even know which
dice to roll hey joe hey joe shut your fucking mouth
it's so dark in here i failed failed oh wait wait wait is a double a uh crit fail
that's beautiful i i failed also not a crit though perfect well uh as you're just like
stumbling around in the darkness donovan walks over into a hallway that is an offshoot from the
bigger hallway that leads to the stairwell and the light comes on you see that the walls on either
side of you are just covered in these numbers and like there's some sigils posted up now and
it's just some sigils sigils yeah and it's all written in the same just like varying materials
as soon as the lights come on you just hear from a door in this hallway there are three
doors in this hallway and from inside one of them you hear no no no five six four five five five
six no no the door cracks open and you just hear please turn out the lights
oh my god donovan slowly shuts the lights backs away
thank you and the door shuts real quick there's silence you're you're welcome hey donovan come
back this way this let's stay away from that uh that area there real fast i think that's a good
idea donovan i i know you didn't ask for this but there's a chance that we're wrapped up in
something real bad here and those numbers might be infectious so if you hear numbers you might
close your ears or maybe don't look at them i'm not sure how it works hey leon you know how this
thing transfers he doesn't respond and when you look over at him he's actually wearing his noise
canceling headphones ah fuck i tap him on the shoulder oh he startled looks over at you and
he points at the computer screen and he's pulled up the room number for amelia lock amelia lock
she lives in 328 gifts house and her roommate is harriet marks ah it's all coming together
you notice when you turn back around the glass panel of windows looking into a separate room
uh the glint of the uh computer screen kind of shines over there enough for you to make out a
pool table in that room you assume it's some sort of entertainment or games room there's probably
nothing fucked up in there hey leon leon he takes the headphones off and he's like yeah i'm
just trying to you know protection from the numbers right yeah you got a couple extra pairs
of those well you seem already fucked and this one's a dumb dumb so should be fine you think
i'm already fucked well that's why we're here right to fix what happened to you i mean i feel
like we snapped out of it didn't we we're not we're i'm not saying numbers now am i you're not
right now we'll see about that i don't know maybe i've been inoculated maybe that's what happened
here maybe maybe since i've already done the numbers thing and you snapped me out of it you
snapped all of us out of it maybe i don't have numbers in me anymore i hope that that's true
all right boy it seems like you don't know as much as i thought you might have known about
all this donovan how many numbers have you been privy to yeah there's been uh people keep uh
shouting numbers at me constantly it's really annoying actually i don't do you have blackouts
or gaps in your memory in the last few days or no no feeling pretty good actually a little hungry
peckish i look at leon i mean maybe he's the thing we're looking for he's sounds like you
might be immune to it or something i don't i'm a man not a thing joe clark joe clark
i'm sorry donnie i uh i accept your apology this time just don't do it again i did mean to
dehumanize you because you might be an antidote of some sort that we need your blood or oh my god
yes that's that's fucking brilliant what's happening nothing uh you'll just want to stay
with us we have to protect him sure i was already doing that were you not oh shit leon i just mean
like it's a priority now gotcha yeah i sure i definitely was protecting him before donovan is
staring at his phone like swiping through whatever social media exists in this universe completely
oblivious to you talking about him right next to him what's going on dude yeah i think we're gonna
we're gonna go up to amelia's room now i think is the yeah that works for me yeah stairs yeah
whatever will get me to the prize i own the prize that's right donny you got a real tiger spirit
i'm gonna need you to not call me donny again mr westworth yeah no yeah no you can call me donovan
that's what everyone calls me even my mom all right donovan thank you did he sound like your
mom when he said that let's go and he uh he starts walking towards the stairs when you get
into the stairwell it's also pitch black and it is lit up a little red with the exit sign right
across from you as you walk in there's an there's a door outside from here as well and when you walk
into the third floor we'll find out what you see later oh shit this is where we where we stop being
here and boys do other things other where we'll see what happens other where other where's the
things are about to happen you guys don't exist to me anymore blip out yeah you do you do you do
everyone exists
thomas i have good news and bad news just give me the good news then okay the good news is it's
almost christmas yeah i'm looking forward to um i mean it's it's always nice this time of year when
the podcast gets around to the gameplay sure and i'm really looking forward to three or four years
from now when we get to december 25th in an actual game world yeah so we've been recording for two
years releasing for a year and we've made it all the way from december 1st to december 6th what a
week and way back in the past and then way back in the future past yeah i bet we'll make it by the
end of tonight all the way to christmas to christmas all the way to christmas spoilers hey i have to
tell you the bad news okay john lee pettimore is gaining a new mania and it is going to completely
engross him oh he didn't reach his breaking point i know he didn't but it's a part of a mechanic for
this arc that this mania will absolutely dominate every other mania that you've had before and every
role-playing decision that you make so it's going to be kind of important and i hope you roll well
so you're going to roll three d 100s and we'll look at the list and see what you got
94 okay keep rolling 89 oh that's a good one i bet sounds like it yeah it's high
99 whoa jesus all right so 94 is theomania belief that he or she is a god
i think maybe we've got a winner right off the bat yeah if you can get me back in a room with joe
oh we've got another really good one 89 is scribbleomania an obsession with scribbling
or doodling interesting that's really really appropriate and then 99 is xenomania which is
an obsession with foreign things i'm gonna choose theo philia or thea what was it theomania you
love god i love god what was it theomania theomania belief that he or she is a god
there's two gods in this role-playing game now and that's not counting any of the elders uh
something older than me older than john lee pettymore himself
as far as we know i'm ageless i came out of a spine as a little ball i can do anything i am
planet juggernaut and i am your god hell yeah it's important in delta green to really give people a
sense of hero worship over their own character yeah let's get into it
so i know we're past christmas but we still have a lot of holiday traditions that take place around
the end of december and the beginning of january or mostly the in between therefore of the two
situations with which we call calendar months within a year into the next one but i was
wondering what your guys's favorite family traditions are from the holiday season no i
don't want to tell you you're gonna make it something scary i'm gonna make it something
so scary yeah i don't trust like that
justin i've always said that you should trust more yeah i just don't though and that hurts
how can zack manipulate you it's really fucking hard to gaslight you when you don't trust the
words i say justin i'm sorry zack when i was a kid we used to listen to a song uh when we were
hanging out the ornaments on the tree we'd always listen to christmas music and one of
our favorites was a muppet christmas carol soundtrack to that movie it was great but
my personal favorite growing up was a song by john denver this isn't a joke this is just true
it he has a song called merry christmas little zachary oh that's you and it made my heart warm
did you know he died yes yeah he's dead we made it scary for you
and now every time i hear it i can only so when i when i heard the song as a child i could always
immediately visualize john denver's face wherever he was in the world but now i just see his rotting
corpse which is cool and festive but it's not you know what i'm looking for so i had to stop
listening to that song you just think of this instead luke is just handed oh my god dude stop
it it's a it's a picture of john denver's plane crash that's not his it's just a plane crash
it's wildly inappropriate merry christmas everybody
other than the normal like christmas morning stuff that i absolutely love we have a weird
tradition in the family that christmas eve we do a frozen pizza and oyster soup that is interesting
very weird so the frozen pizzas i think comes from my mom and they've just chalked it up as
like not wanting to cook the night before christmas okay and then i think my dad maybe
brought the oysters no that might have been hers also but the oyster soup is like a really great
fancy oyster soup that my dad makes and it's great great great and it's really weird to have them
together and i love it yeah it doesn't sound good it's weird and it's i don't know if i could
recommend it but i it's a christmas memory yeah what do you guys do while you're having this like
weird dichotomous meal it's with family friends instead of family it's the it i i i do sunday
suppers with a bunch of people that i've done since i was a voice changer when you said that
because it's so wholesome and sweet he's a little he's a little child and it's that group i get
together with that group for that christmas eve that's fun yeah i like that justin what's your
family do on uh my family is weird because we don't do jack shit on christmas we do everything
on christmas eve and we do an all like homemade italian meal oh hell yeah this is my grandparents
who immigrated from argentina in argentina it's like a ton of italian food so they just uh
we just wonder why that is because there's a lot of italian stuff
luke do you need anything for christmas uh we uh christmas lunch and it's like a bunch of
appetizers like little smokies and meatballs oh nice yeah and also
so uh my family for christmas um my stepmom will always make uh fresh cinnamon rolls
oh and then we drink mimosas
yeah it's justin hasn't been on mike in a while
you know you learned to not sneeze
oh god have you seen that video of trump getting pissed off with the guy who sneezes anyway we
don't need to talk about monsters on this show it's it's christmas it's time to think about
pleasant things not real horror yeah um and then uh my step sister who like uh is a chef she went
to culinary school and everything oh credentials she makes us these dope eggs benedict damn hell
yeah it's a lot of fun that's awesome we get sloshed and we eat cinnamon rolls and eggs benedict
dude that's how this wins that's incredible we're all coming over okay done all right so
you guys are all standing in different places so clark bishop and donovan westerfuck are walking
down the hallway of the third floor of the gifts building gifts house as you're walking down that
hallway you see that the light is on in one of the rooms down the hallway and looking at the
numbers you would see like oh that that might actually be the one that we're looking for the
328 number and when you arrive there you find keith vigna and john lee pettymore standing in
room 328 of diff's house uh is leon with us oh yeah i'm here for sure always been here never not
clark just knocks on the door jam fell fellas oh hey uh hey clark john like turns with a start
and sees you and sees where he is and he's like it is true i can anything i want i'm right there
what hello hey i'm glad you snapped out of it snap snapped out of it what more like snapped
into it uh did you guys take the elevator up here uh i believe we took the stairs didn't we uh well
there's a dead body in the elevator and he saw it and he started uh he just kind of
blanked out and started writing uh bruce robbins the the code for bruce robbins numbers again
yeah maybe that's what it seemed like i dragged him along with me corporeal form dead but yeah
well john were you writing were you writing numbers did you ever feel did you ever feel
immense
period period question mark immense i mean i've been working out some but you are looking a
little camille right now topical weeks from now of course you wouldn't understand um
welcome to the to the room everyone you guys i think i brought you all here you guys would
notice that they are with a third person so keith vigna and john lee pennymore you are seeing
donovan for the first time and he looks like what justin's about to say donovan west haven is about
six foot one six foot two somewhere in between those two inches dark nice hair done up really
nice and he has like a let's see he's like a button-up buttoned all the way up tucked in
he's a handsome boy who are you an adult boy just to be make sure we all know that he's an adult
who's this clark guys this is this is donovan donovan this is the fellas that's john over there
and that's uh keith there i shake your hand i'm like donovan i've known you all your life
donovan doesn't shake he nods at you and's like hi what's up we ran into this guy like nod and smile
over in the uh the administration building me and leon think there's a chance he's immune to these
numbers he's been here on campus in the middle of what you're saying john lee pettymore walks
straight into a wall like slams into it yeah john john no i'm still working up the kinks don't worry
i've got it all in my hands oh god okay keith what were you saying though sorry has he been
like this for a while i mean he was no longer than you know he was normal until we saw that body then
he started writing on the walls and now i don't know what the fuck he's doing do you do you keith
have any missing time in your no okay who's this guy his name's donovan we ran into him we think
that he might be immune to the the infection of the numbers he said he's been having people
yelling at him numbers all for the last few days a few days yeah and he seems to have no ill effects
he doesn't he doesn't affect other people i mean it affected us have any other do you know any
other students it's been affecting oh like um all of them except me okay we actually ran into him he
had another fellow with him who was asking to be punched in the face and then he started saying
numbers so i obliged well we found a we found a body in the elevator uh dead um i didn't
investigate too much on it but uh nearly moved on to the next phase i kind of look at john and
eyebrows high john smiles benevolently at you i didn't investigate it too much but uh it could
have been self-inflicted i'm not really sure were there were there numbers on or around the body
i mean there's numbers all in this you look around the room and the room itself is also
covered in these numbers as was the hallway on the way down the floor the ceiling all over the desk
the chair all over the place in here from what i'm gathering from leon here he's not even 100 sure
the uh method of infection but he puts on headphones every now and then just to maybe
combat the that's not not a bad idea so the only thing i've found obviously you know we're in
harriet's room uh we found out her her roommate's name is amelia amelia lock amelia lock yeah
have you seen this and i hold up the flyer for the ball yeah do you uh do you know about the
scavenger hunt yeah but i haven't really found anything out about it but uh if you look over
there and i point to amelia's desk take a look at those trophies i do you would see that they
are trophies for being an elite riddle master and a scavenger hunt champion oh yeah so we we found
i found her desk at the administration's office oh yeah and uh i saw some pictures of her holding
these trophies here um there was also a clue back at those offices i assume maybe the first
clue what was it it uh basically asked how many presents does a person get on the 10th day of
christmas and me and leon have differing opinions on that number but either way it's just a number
i don't know if it well well i would say 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 and 1 thank you thank you keith
thank you john exactly leon uh i'm just saying i just can take my answer on this is fairly
authoritative i don't understand are you really good at math amongst other things you there what
was his name donovan what was his last name west haven west fucker west mr wet fucker why do you
think mr wet fucker you there child your voice got weird mr char mr west fucker are you do you
hear yeah what's up why do you think the numbers had no effect on you i couldn't tell you honestly
i don't know tell me i'm just maybe you know it just like i know it tell me maybe i'm maybe i'm
special after all ah yes i can see it in you
you are special you are very special more than you know child is john speaking with an accent
have you noticed i don't know i mean he wasn't acting like this before your friends are weird
and they're freaking me out so leon here thinks that every day she's repeating the
presents from the previous day i don't no i don't think that i think it'd be 110 the only the only
leg he has to stand on is that she does say on the fifth day christmas my true love
hey out of character think about who made this puzzle and then and then who do you think has the
right but i also i agree with that you get all the presents each day right you get all the presents
the true love is a real true love well if that's the case then look at this
also 330 is the room right next to us it's the room right across the hall and keith vigno holds
up a sheet and on the back of the sheet is all the math of like one plus three plus you know
essentially uh fibonacci sequence but not right for this thing and it leads to 330 which is the
room across the hall which keith vigno would then say i found this in there
and i hold up another piece of paper you guys fucking nailed it we got there i hold up a piece
of paper that has a picture like in cartoon form a picture of seven eggs a golf ball a cat a demon
and another egg yep uh yeah there was nothing in there beside it was just a normal it's like
we found out it's a like a staging dorm room that nobody lives in it's just to show prospective
students what a dorm room looks like i found this in there and there's a casio keyboard in there
too does that mean anything to you casio keyboard it doesn't mean anything no no it doesn't mean
anything to me either but i can tell you whoever made this riddle seems very cool
you a puzzle fan leon oh huge puzzle fan i'm glad you're here with us then do these look
like emojis from the movie yeah exactly are these emojis from the emoji movie i don't know if there
are yeah essentially they're this of similar ilk in style but they're not emojis i don't think so
right no i'm not there i just mean like they're not like it's not made out of emojis they're
like cartoons they're like cartoons they're uh illustrations cool like pictogram they could be
small enough to be sent in text form though does that make it an emoji no man oh okay then no
definitively no it was seven eggs a golf ball a cat i saw seven eggs a demon and an egg when you
say demon can you describe that demon is it like the demon emoji yeah it looks like the demon
like is it horns is that what it has yep okay purple with horns baby and a little toothy smile
that one's an emoji uh just a couple other things before i don't know if i mean we ought
to probably go check that room out but uh in harriet's desk she has a to-do list
number one research the most unethical corporation in the city and number two
just said who is the overseer and then uh in in uh i know amelia's desk uh she had a little note
i found and basically says she didn't think that harriet would have committed suicide and that
she's going to try to get to the bottom of it and that's what i found in here so far so previously
we were thinking that maybe it was a uh a leaping disease that went from one person to the next and
he wrote down their names and yada yada if harriet killed herself first then amelia
would have maybe gotten it or gotten it in investigating her death that could be have
we seen amelia's name written anywhere in these numbers and i do a quick look around
at the actual numbers and see if i can find her name in the numbers nice roll search
i pass an eight 20 you find a couple numbers that start with one but none of them move to
whatever m is next what about her last name just lock can't find it anywhere okay yeah i'm just
not sure if our if our theory is wrong or something else happened in the sequence of
events here but donovan what do you think i gotta get that jingle ball i need it you
mean you have to get to the jingle ball yeah whatever i just want to win whatever donovan
do they give out an actual jingle ball at the jingle ball if you make it there last maybe
that was really rude of you yeah sick burn leon yeah what what the hell he's not children children
i look at both of you like with a right smile but like paternal love i am unsettled as long
as you're quiet young man holy shit and quiet he is
jesus you see john lee pettymore is beaming at you with fraternal pride do you think we ought
to go back into 330 see if you guys might find something i didn't so yeah i'd like to so
beautiful put my eyes on that room for sure i'll head across the hall so when you guys go across
the hall into 330 you would find this dorm room set up to be the pinnacle of what all dorm rooms
could look like here at csu come on down become one of the fighting plant things can't remember
it what's it called fly trap and well what if it was the fighting for cithias
oh i like that a lot feed me see more and there's a lot of things that we can offer you here at csu
much like this dorm room that is very well equipped with lots of blankets and pillows and
athleisure which is what the college kids wearing these days bad commercial for csu but uh you would
see that all over this room there are numbers thickly written i mean to the point where it's
hard to make out the sequences just like everywhere else however in the middle of this room there is
just a casio keyboard sitting there it's turned on and there's a music stand that is now empty
i'd like to play the keyboard cat riff oh you do it can you do it
it just kind of goes on right john does it though does the pictogram symbols do they end
with a single egg yes i picked this up off that music stand and the symbols are on a staff on a
music staff yes oh is it in the form of e g c d e it's written just across the music staff it's
no up or down okay but we might assume one might assume a guess might be it's the guess that was
clearly being made there i want to hit those notes that are the first letters of the words
of the pictures e justin can you take that live for us wow she is majestic wait does that keyboard
that keyboard does not have an outboard audio on it but we could pause and go to the piano
real quick i'd like to hear it let's take a pause and go to the upright piano real quick
joe hammered down those notes that he got and keep in mind my dad is a professional piano player
so it only took us about 45 minutes to practice one it's four in the morning we're all dying but
assuming the first letter of egg golf ball cat demon and egg represents musical notes it might
sound a little bit something like this and as g vigna or clark bishop are all of you with your
hands all together just doing it like the cat did on the keyboard as you play the jingle bells tune
you all the camera like pans through you none of us thought to not do this
and no it's nice you look through the window and you see right out the window of 330
gifts house you see the bell tower on the csu campus lit up in all its holiday festive glory
are there wreaths dude you have no idea how many wreaths there are you can't count them are there
lights because you can only see two sides of it and there are so many lights but you don't know
how many lights is there a minion inflatable there's a minion inflatable right on top it's
actually using it like a butt plug and trees and trees cool we got it all baby here at csu
come on down and join us for your next semester of fun and fall festivities that can take you
all the way from the jingle ball to a new hall of your new office which is where you work now
because you've got a college degree and it's america which is all you need to work in the
system that is in place to keep you down csu come on down get kept down i just graduated today
so
go
streaming