Skip a bop, a skibbity bop, a wee dee dee dee dee dee, a skip skibbity skip skip, it's
Scatman Wolf, y'all, hittin' you from bleeba deeba 694.2 PTBP, my jazzy babies, and I am
hittin' you live from the past and the present, and maybe even the future.
Time is weird, time is like jazz.
It's all made up, and no one fuckin' understands it.
Speaking of things I don't understand and I'm forced to do, this week's Howlin'
with Wolf is from Brittany Roxanne, who tweeted about the show and tagged that pretending
pod.
Seriously, what a pleasant thing to do, they write, I have an urgent message for Hurt Ork.
Your message is simple, infiltrate the enemy, gather intel, and report back what you find.
If your cover's blown, do not, under any circumstances, contact us.
Good luck, Agent.
Uh, this seems like a weird avenue to deliver super secret urgent messages to people.
I hope Hurt Ork accomplishes whatever the mission was, unless that mission is to infiltrate
my home and gather intel on little ol' me?
Hey, producer, beef up the security around here, you salty salt dog.
If you see some Ork who was hurt, you know what to do.
Hey, do you like this show?
Do you wanna help this show?
Do you even think we deserve it?
Patreon.com slash PretendingPod, at PretendingPod on Twitter and Instagram, Reddit.com slash
all slash PretendingToBePeople, write a review on Apple Podcasts, why don't ya?
Let the congregation say amen, an elf, a dwarf, and a wizard.
Blessed are the measures that light the fuse, let's erupt the oppressors and we'll write
the news.
The PCs all woke up feeling strange and finding they'd been pricked in their veins right in
the pit of their elbows.
Hmm, elbows, the knees of the arms.
Zack fucked up Justin's reaction to failing his constitution check, and I'll bet it never
comes up again.
Seriously, he just thought Justin succeeded that check for some reason.
Hmm, he must've been all nervous and shit.
What a dumb motherfucker.
Anyway, Martin twisted his ankle in the go bag hiding place he had previously covered
up and he found the go bag was missing.
He also cannot remember arriving here at calm, comfy campground.
Walter and Alan discussed who to trust, deciding they could only trust each other.
However, Walter no longer trusts Alan due to his memory of Alan trying to sell him.
Charles Digby had a knock at the door.
The bellboy Leon was looking for Jack Russell and Jack Russell was hiding under the floor.
They talked about an inoculation and Digby promised he wouldn't snitch.
Roger Fairfield realized he'd been drugged and found a hair tie near the open window
that was locked and closed when he had gone to sleep.
The hair seemed to match a young girl named Maggie who ran from James to Angela while
calling her Ann.
Hmm, nothing suspicious there.
In the meeting room, Angela was called out into the hallway by James.
Inside tensions rose.
Walter tried to turn himself off after Martin violated his personal space.
Walter came back with a throat punch that gave Thomas permission to do whatever he's
doing.
This week I got exactly what your soul desires.
A brand new song, a premiere, a future classic, a modern myth, a song that makes you feel
the right kind of wrong.
It's Dream Girl, my babies, with Pretty Sexual.
This is real, I dream I knew I'd make you be foolish
Thomas Martin Cupertino just got fucking rocked in the throat by Walter Grimes.
And all of a sudden you're sitting in a chair in a room, it's a pretty small room but it's
made to feel even smaller because it is filled with flowers.
So many flowers of all different varieties, shades and shapes that you've never seen before.
Sitting right in front of you is James, the executive director of Calm Comfy Campground
sitting behind a desk and he has a folder in front of him and he looks up at you.
Martin, go ahead and tell me a little bit more about Cube, I'm curious.
Because of the state that your brain is in currently, go ahead and roll Constitution
at a negative 40.
Well 80, so I failed that, but I also didn't have much chance, I have a 55, so.
Oh shit, yeah, that would have been rough.
So you, maybe for the first time in your life, maybe for the first time in a long time you
feel docile almost, you feel so pliant.
Well I mean, I'm not supposed to talk about Cube, but I'll let you in on a little secret,
yeah, you can know about Cube before the rest of the world, basically Cube is just a really
expensive personal computer, looks like a jellybean, obviously modeled pretty heavily
on the iMac, which was the thing in the late 90s.
Really it's just all marketing baby, that's all Cube is.
And how much money projected do you think that Cube is going to net?
If a sucker's born every minute then quite a bit, my calculations seem to show it's more
like 48.5 seconds, that's of course rising exponentially with global population, but
once we reach the crest of that, really you need to get in now within 30 years when the
population of western nations are plummeting and the markets aren't there yet in the developing
nations, there's just not going to be as many fools per capita to sell to, you really want
to get in right now.
Well consider-
On the verge of this new gilded age.
Me sold.
Sold.
You want to buy a Cube?
He flips open the folder and there's a thick stack of documents in there.
Please.
What do you get, what's that, what do you have there?
And he holds a pen out to you and you see on the folder it's titled Operation Hole Puncher.
And inside there's document after document after document and he hands you a pen and
he needs you to sign at the bottom of every page.
It's like, yeah, I'll sign whatever.
Is this ASMR?
Do you like that?
Man sits next to you and clicks pen, obnoxious.
I'm clicking my pen right now for you.
This is the worst.
It's the worst.
You're going to have to go to the Patreon to get that content, our ASMR Patreon feed.
Oh no.
Zach DM's you to sleep with.
Oh my god.
You're going to have to roll sanity for me.
For me.
You always say roll for me, which is like, seems a little bit like self-aggrandizing.
Roll it for me.
All right, Justin.
You were in the meeting room a second ago, wait, you're sitting in this room.
It's small.
It's made to feel even smaller by the overwhelming amount of flowers in this room.
Sitting across from you at a desk is James, the executive director of Calm Comfy Campground.
He's looking through a folder and he looks up at you and these flowers that are all around
you are the same flowers that you've seen all over the island.
What color are they?
All different kinds of colors, all different kinds of shapes, varied in many different
ways.
Charles, you take pictures, right?
Part of your job?
Yeah, pretty much.
That's almost all I do these days.
And you've got some pretty damning pictures of some fairly important people.
Is that correct?
Yeah, I can't quite say who, but yeah.
We know who.
And he's flipping through this folder.
Charles, you feel, go ahead and roll a constitution at a negative 40.
Oh, that's going to be hard.
What's your constitution?
55.
Oh boy.
Oh, I crit failed, 55.
It would have been a great success if you wouldn't have fucked me like that, Zach.
It wasn't me that fucked you.
You immediately list the people.
There was the mayor, there was this actor guy that people around here know, there was
a radio DJ, there was a city council member.
All right, all right.
Calm down.
I know.
Charles Digby's like, wait, why did I?
It's okay, Charles.
Why?
You're working with us now.
I need you to sign these here documents.
We're working together now as a team and we're going to need those pictures.
Yeah, whatever you need.
And you walk up to the desk and he's got this folder that says Operation Hole Puncher on
it.
And then he flips it open and there is a thick stack of documents there.
All right.
If you'll just sign and initial all these.
I'm doing it.
I'm getting in there very quickly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
Oh no.
I don't like where the-
Roger, you were in that meeting room.
Walter just like goes to punch, wait, no, you're sitting in this room.
It's a small room and you're surrounded by flowers of every shape and shade.
They're the exact same flowers you've been seeing all over this island, but you're not
sure if this is a memory.
It feels like a memory.
It's a small room, but it's even smaller because of how many flowers are just surrounding you
in every direction.
And in front of you, there's a desk and behind that desk is James, executive director of
the calm comfy campground.
I need you to roll constitution at a negative 40.
Oof.
Dang.
43 on what would be a 30.
Roger, you were an archeologist.
Is that right?
Yeah.
And you're single, right?
And what is this dig site you're working on right now?
I mean, we don't exactly know it, but we're just calling it the nameless city right now.
We don't know exactly what civilization it belonged to.
We just found it.
Interesting.
All right.
Cool.
Well, basically today we're just here to sign some paperwork so that our partnership can
continue.
Yeah.
That sound good?
Sure.
Yeah, of course.
And you approached the desk where he's got a folder that he opens up and the folder on
the front says operation hole puncher.
Oh, damn.
I got to pull out my other notebooks, Zach.
And inside there's a document after document that he has you sign an initial.
Okay.
I do.
And he looks up and he's like, look forward to working more with you.
And you too.
What the fuck?
Walter, you reach out and just like slam Martin Cupertino in the throat.
And then all of a sudden you're just standing in this room.
Next to you is Alan Grimes, who you know as your handler.
And in front of him is a desk.
Behind that desk is James, executive director at Calm Comfy Campground.
This room is filled with flowers of all different shade and shape.
It's the exact same flowers that are covering the Island where calm comfy campground sits
and you are completely docile.
So Alan, you're saying that you've got more of these.
Yes.
I've got, we have warehouses in Washington.
We have warehouses in Chicago, new Orleans, Las Vegas.
We have access to as many as you need.
Well, that is, that is something else and they'll just do whatever they'll just do whatever
you want.
Yes.
Yes, absolutely.
Hey, uh, Hey kid, touch your nose.
Walter touches his nose.
Luke touches his nose immediately, but Walter touches his nose.
Oh damn.
That shit's wild.
Slap your face.
Oh, it looks like it hurt.
Yeah.
I liked it.
He slaps his face.
Man.
All right.
Well, uh, shit.
Let's go ahead and take this partnership to the next level.
Let's sign some paperwork and Alan Grimes approaches the desk where James has a folder
that's labeled operation hole puncher.
And inside there's a bunch of paperwork.
Alan just signs and signs and initials and signs.
Alan turns back to you, salutes.
Thank you for your service.
Thank you.
Bad rolls out of the way.
It's like warming up at the free throw line before the game.
Let's clank a couple.
Visualize the failure.
That's what my mom tells me.
It's a real fucking bummer.
I'm sorry, man.
It's okay.
So in our last alone session, was the minotaur speaking English?
Yeah.
Okay.
Just kidding.
I remember that.
Y'all looked at me.
What the fuck happened to Joe?
Bradley Cooper, you like step back.
Like you just got punched in the throat and everyone's eyes just kind of cross each other.
Walter.
I'm sorry.
Just reflexes I guess.
You little bastard.
I didn't.
Cool.
And it's silent.
All right.
Now you're just milking it.
Somebody punch him again.
Walter, you didn't need to punch him.
That was.
What?
I mean, he was a reflex.
He touched me.
He did.
He did touch you.
That's true.
Are you okay, Brad?
I like walk over to him.
I kind of.
No.
Fuck you kid.
I hate this fucking kid.
I hate this calm, cozy campground.
I'm leaving immediately.
I'm gone.
I want a refund.
Where's James?
Did anyone else just see James somewhere?
I just had a, was it a memory?
I'm having these weird flashbacks like we had last night.
That happened to you guys?
Was that a flashback or a dream?
I don't know, but I am so sorry.
I am so sorry, Walter.
I don't know what that was.
Walter kind of like squints at his dad and just kind of looks ahead and doesn't say anything else.
I was in a room full of flowers with him.
Were you guys in that room?
It was the flowers all around the island.
That's kind of an old trick.
We'd do it in the waiting room when we had to renegotiate contracts.
You fill it all with flowers so it looks like people really care about you and are thinking about you.
And it just makes the other person feel small.
I pegged it right away.
I definitely felt small in there.
They were.
Like you'd never been sent that many flowers in your life.
They were all around.
It made the room feel smaller.
Boy, whoever got these flowers must be important.
That's really the play there.
At least it was with us.
I think we need to find James.
If my recollection of the memory is correct, then I absolutely need to find James.
I think last we left off, I was kind of heading toward the door to get Angela back from him.
So I'm probably heading toward that door anyway.
Yeah, and when the door opens up, there are two people wearing staff clothing,
which you haven't seen before, but it is the calm, comfy campground staff uniform.
And it is like a one-piece jumpsuit with a collar that goes all the way up buttoned to the top.
It is a tall broad woman and a short scrawny man.
And they both have spray bottles in their hands.
Who the fuck are these boners?
What the fuck is that in their hands?
They immediately go to spray the two who are heading straight for the door,
which is Roger Fairfield and Bradley Cooper.
Can I athletics away?
Yeah, you can absolutely try.
Do you want to try to get out of the spray range there, Roger?
Yeah.
I fail.
They both fail miserably on their attempt to spray,
but something about seeing these bottles...
I got an eight on my attempt to help away.
Oh, hell yeah.
How do you get out of the way?
I just straight up like Neo.
The Matrix hasn't come out yet, so it's really innovative and revolutionary and shockingly cinematic.
But yeah, I just lean back away from the spray, duck behind the guy,
and I want to try to grab the spray out of his hands.
You do grab the spray bottle out of his hands.
Bradley Cooper, Charles Digby, Walter and Ellen Grimes, and Roger Fairfield,
you are all standing together in a cottage.
It is familiar because the setup is the same as the cottage each of you have been staying in.
However, this cottage is filled with surveillance equipment.
Screens line the walls, and you can see the grounds of Calm Comfy Campground,
the insides of Cottages 3, 5, 7, and 9,
as well as, it seems, the forests that surround Lake Calm.
Do I still have the bottle in my hand?
No.
Where are we?
Where the fuck are we?
Everybody roll alertness.
Fail.
69.
Fuck, I fail also.
Ooh, great success.
Ooh, nice.
Success.
Walter, nice.
Walter immediately looks down at his arm and sees that there is not a puncture,
like a mark of blood where there was.
Can I see if anybody else still has that?
If they'll show you their arms under their sleeves.
Do you guys still have, look, do you still have your mark?
Let me check.
No one has the mark.
Does it always seem to be the same time of year at Calm Comfy Campground?
It does.
And because you Chris Exceed, you actually will see on the surveillance footage.
What surveillance footage?
So the screens in front of you are showing all of Calm Comfy Campground essentially,
and you see there is a tall, broad woman and a short, scrawny man, both with a bottle
in their hand, heading toward a cottage, which you innately feel is this cottage.
We can set an ambush for him, boys.
Was the cottage, there was one that had like a tent, like a spray tent or whatever.
Sure.
Do we see that on the surveillance?
No.
Looking out the window, do I see it draped in a tent?
Oh.
Which cottage do you think we're in?
Probably the one that was tinted.
What did you say, three, five, seven, nine?
Those are the ones you can see on the footage, yeah.
Which one was tinted?
Five was me, right?
Yes.
I was in nine.
I was in three, I believe.
And seven.
Yeah.
Those are the four that you guys are in, yeah.
Yeah, I think we're in that tinted cottage.
So is it before it was tinted or after it was tinted and then taken down?
No way to know yet, but it looks like we've got the jump on these fools.
We can see them coming.
What do you think they're doing with those bottles?
They're going to subdue us.
When you grabbed it, could you tell what was in it?
No, it's like some kind of controlling force sped us away from that moment before I could
investigate any further on that awesome roll I got.
It was a success.
What do you suggest that we do?
Well, I think you should go out to greet them.
Okay.
Wait.
Don't just greet them.
Run to the door.
Tell them to get in quick.
Tell them there's an emergency.
We'll wait in the hallways in the crevices.
We're going to, we're going to jump these fools.
Okay.
How far away?
Roger real quick wants to look around this room for anything that he can use to, uh,
uh, if we do subdue them to be able to tie them up.
So like cording or roping.
Hold towels in front of yourself so they can't spray you.
Yeah, you can, you can find ties.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
What are those called?
Like zip ties?
Is that what you mean?
Okay.
I was hoping to be able to use my knot skill.
He's like, well, okay, if you've got to use cheaters knots.
Are there any big, uh, calm, cozy comforters like on the couch, like big knit, uh, there's
actually no, there's nothing in here except for surveillance equipment.
So there's not like a bed or any grab a monitor boys and we're just going to chuck it at their
heads.
Everybody grabs a monitor.
How heavy are the monitors?
They're like nineties action movie, little security camera monitors, right?
Yeah.
They're just all over the place.
And like stacked on top of each other and shit.
I just toss one to each of them.
How far away are the sprayers?
Uh, they're approaching right now.
I look at Martin.
Do I go now?
Do it.
I run out the front door.
How far away are they?
Can I see them?
They're, they're literally right in front of you.
There's, I like shut the door behind me so they can't see.
There's something is wrong in there.
Yeah.
In the face.
Like immediately.
As soon as they walk up to you.
What do we see happen as we're holding our monitors?
Yeah.
You guys are watching from, from inside and you just see, as soon as he gets sprayed immediately,
his chin goes down to his chest and he just stops moving.
Okay.
They turned him off.
Does the door open in or out?
In.
Well, yeah.
I just want to wait for them to come through the door and then we all check our monitors
at them, at their head.
After, after they've sprayed him, do they do anything with him or do they walk past
him?
They walk right past him.
Yeah.
They just keep moving.
And, uh, everyone roll humid.
Me too or?
No.
Shouldn't listen to.
Pass.
37 on a 60.
Tell you what I'm told.
So you guys noticed that there is no emotion or anything on these two's faces.
There is just a blank expression.
Look, they're drone people.
If you accidentally clobber them too hard, you know, they go down for good.
You don't have to feel bad about it because clearly they're already dead inside.
So what's the plan from the inside?
Clobber.
Just as soon as they open the door, three monitors smashing down on their heads before
they can even fucking like see.
I'll try.
Martin.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not a fighter.
I'm not a fighter.
Hey, hey, hey.
Pull yourself to fucking gather, man.
He's going to go kind of toward the back of the room, but be ready to throw.
While they were also searching, is there like a gun on any of the desks nearby or anything
like that?
No.
But you guys can, if you're all doing the monitor gig, I'd like to do a wield monitors.
You can roll athletics or strength and I'll give you guys an advantage of a Thomas.
You would take no advantage, but the other two can have a plus 20.
The reason you don't have an advantage is because you're using two.
I absolutely fail even with all the advantage.
Yeah.
Same.
Okay.
I rolled an 11 and a 100, but these are, are these contested?
Yeah.
Okay.
So you're fucked either way.
Well, what did you roll?
I rolled a 57 and my skill is 65.
So if we're doing highest without going over, I completely smashed two monitors on both
your fucking heads.
The 11 was a crit success, right?
But it's still for, but that doesn't count a contested rules, does it?
Yes, absolutely.
It trumps everything.
If it's a crit.
You've played this game, right?
Yeah, but this, these rules are weird.
Always have been, always will be, I suppose.
Only when you lose though, do they seem to be weird.
You just keep inventing conditions in which I can lose.
I turn back on and attack them.
No, you absolutely smashed one of them.
We'll say the tall woman who is extremely bright.
You were rolling for them.
These aren't my rules.
What game is this?
So you describe how one of them goes down.
Well, the first one through the door just gets like, I just straight up lob this monitor
right in their face.
They don't even see it coming, just like full fucking glass to the face.
They go down.
Oh, immediately, literally laying back on the ground with a TV on their head.
But that was my right hand and I'm not as good with my left hand.
And so the person immediately behind them has a little time to like see it and duck
and it's not as like strong or good a throw.
Roger, what did you roll?
A fail, a 97.
Okay.
And then we got a successor fail over here.
Fail 93.
Okay, fantastic.
All right.
So the other one is going to...
Can we just throw our monitors up into the air?
Yikes!
Immediately horrified, the little scrawny guy was not expecting this and he, still,
no scream, no holler, no anything.
And he just holds up his spray bottle and begins spraying and running toward you guys.
Is it like a squirty spray or like a misty spray?
It's a misty spray.
Luckily.
Yeah.
Can I do something to avoid that now?
Yeah, absolutely.
So this will be another contested roll.
Wait, is he going after the both of us?
He's coming after the room.
You guys are all like right there in the front.
What are we rolling?
Athletics or dexterity.
Okay, let me try rolling again.
Or dodge.
And you roll the...
83.
Not a good fail.
Oh, okay.
Oh my God.
Do I get any bonuses to this one?
No, you do not.
I got a 53 on a 50.
I got a four on a 65.
He actually also failed.
So does he spray himself?
Not a crypto.
He does.
He sprays himself.
However, there seems to be no ill effect.
Okay.
I want to just fucking punch him in the face.
So literally what happened is he's spraying as he's walking and you guys all just like
walk into rooms and he's just like walking down the hallway with his arm out flat just
spraying it forward and then he's going to turn around and he's going to change the bottle
into his other hand and then spray and just walk down the hallway the other way.
Back out the door.
He's heading back through the hallway.
He's basically just trying to...
Corner us.
Yeah.
Whatever room I've ended up in now, can I see if there's a window that I could break
out?
Oh yeah, for sure.
What do I do?
You see a window.
I want to break it out.
Or open it.
I got to get out of here.
I'm going to slam my head through it.
It's bleeding all over everything.
The glass hurts so bad.
It's all worth it.
Open it.
Can I open it?
Yeah.
You open the window.
Okay.
I'm going to crawl out.
Sounds good.
Justin, what are you doing?
Can I see if there's something I can use to bludgeon like something with some reach like
a bat or another monitor or something.
Yeah.
There's actually a...
Help me out here guys.
A tripod.
What would...
A tripod would be pretty good.
What could he use?
No, something far more.
There's like a...
Like an empty bed frame?
No, there's a...
A keyboard.
Fuck.
Tennis racket.
We're giving you golden things that can be in a cabin.
Loose wood panel on the floor.
There's a snowshoe.
There's a big hairy mean dog.
An old fishing pole.
An old fisher man.
A samurai sword.
I got a collection of samurai swords and bazookas in here.
Bazookas and grenades and land mines.
It's one of those things on the wall with the pinned insects on it.
There's a bigger spray bottle.
There's a spray bottle that says anti-spray bottles guy.
There's a taxidermied frog holding a banjo.
Ooh, that one.
That one, yeah.
That one.
There's a taxidermied frog holding a banjo.
I pick it up for violence.
Don't destroy that art.
God damn, now I want a taxidermied frog holding a banjo.
That's some quality folk art.
I want to hide around the corner if there's a nook of some kind where I can get a jump
on him.
Yeah, absolutely.
You got it.
Okay.
I'm just going to wait.
Does the door open in or out of this room?
There's no door.
Oh.
Well, there goes my plan to wang him on the head with a door.
What kind of taxidermy is in my room?
Ooh, a raccoon with a straw hat.
Yes.
And a reed.
Yeah, absolutely.
A long reed.
The reed is actually longer than the raccoon is tall.
I pluck the reed and I start chewing on it.
And I, yeah, it tastes like old glue.
And I hold this thing like a baseball bat and I'm also behind my corner just waiting
for him to come in.
When you say hold it like a baseball bat, are you holding it by the head and its feet
are standing up?
Or are you holding it by-
I'm holding it by the feet and its head is the club end.
And I imagine its arms are doing kind of cute things.
So those are kind of like little spikes coming out from it.
Yeah, that's like a D12 weapon at least.
At least.
He won't see either one of these attacks coming, so you guys can both roll with a plus 20 and
it won't be opposed.
Wang him.
Who goes first?
Both of you at the same time.
Is this athletics or?
You can roll-
Oh, this would be not-
This would be melee combat.
Oh, no.
Are you sure?
Oh, hell yeah.
Plus 20?
Yeah.
Okay, I have a 50.
I rolled a 52, but I have a plus 20, so limo.
Yeah, I failed big time.
97.
Okay, so thankfully the frog stays intact.
Oh, thank God.
That's all I cared for.
You swing right over this.
He's a very short fella and you were expecting the tall broad woman, right?
And so you swing right over his head, but thankfully-
Yeah, I see his shadow come through the doorway and I just wind up and fucking Sammy Sosa
this motherfucker right in his face with the raccoon teeth pointed out.
If I could catch those on an eyeball or something, I'm really trying to do maximum damage.
Yeah, you catch the teeth on an eyeball and his eye, as he hits the ground completely
unconscious, you see that there is the string essentially holding the eyeball in place,
is actually stretched fully out and you still are holding on to the other end and if you
kind of like-
Yeah, I try to get my raccoon loose.
Yeah, and his head is just like pop, pop, pop, like hitting against the ground.
When I finally give it the pull that rips the eye out with the raccoon and his head
flunks down to the ground, I bow and I say, Namaste and I walk out.
I also collect his spray bottle and I think I want to change into his clothes and I come
out into the room to do all that, so Justin just sees me in the process of becoming fully
nude.
There's no time to waste.
Oh, okay.
Can I go find the woman's clothes and change into them?
Yeah.
Okay, so I want to investigate this bottle.
It is just a spray bottle, there's absolutely nothing on it and you're looking at it and
you're standing in the meeting room for where you had orientation and you're looking over
the spray bottle that you have in your hand.
Dope.
Bradley Cooper is looking down at the spray bottle and when you do, you-
I think you can call me my real name now.
Oh, Martin Cupertino.
Who?
Oh.
A billionaire?
What a billionaire.
Looking down at this spray bottle and as you're holding it-
I was really proud of that word and then I Googled it and it's definitely a thing.
Oh, yeah.
It makes sense.
Cupertino?
Yeah.
Garden?
Billionaire.
Oh.
Cupertino was a very intentional choice.
I just like came up with that and it was wild.
That's what I thought you were saying.
I was like, yeah, man.
No, no, no.
Billionaire.
Uh, well, you know what they say.
There was a...
Uh, no.
Oh, well.
Who?
Um, stop it.
So when you look down at this bottle, you see that there is a piece of tape on it and
written on the piece of tape is the word Sanfera Blom, S-A-N-F-E-R-R-A space B-L-O-M.
Sanfera Blom.
Yes.
And as you're holding it, real quick, Roger Fairfield, roll an intelligence check for
me.
I pass a 43 on a 75.
You would recognize that name from the book that you're reading of the flora in the area.
Nice.
I remember it as a plant.
Yes.
And Martin Cupertino, you smell this bottle like it is pungent and you can smell.
It's the exact same smell of the flowers that are all over this island.
Cool.
Can I remember details about what I read about it?
Guys, guys, guys, everybody shut up.
Shut up.
Remember all the flowers blooming in the city.
Oh, I don't.
That's a different character.
I remember though.
Yeah.
Nice.
Interesting.
You get five luck points for not this character, but maybe in the future when we're using
luck.
Right.
Write it down.
I'm just going to...
Yeah.
Zach owes me a debit of five luck.
That's exactly right.
So Bradley Cooper, Charles Digby, Walter and Alan Grimes and Angela and Roger Fairfield,
you are all in this meeting room with the walls that round off at all the corners.
And there is these two people, this tall broad woman and this short scrawny man are both
on the ground and you're holding one of the bottles and the other bottle is across the
floor and it's been opened and it is just like in the corner.
It's spilling out of the room.
I want to spray the guy next to me in the face and fucking book it out of the room.
Okay.
What's everybody else doing?
Is Angela being there a thing?
Yeah.
We'll see.
I pass.
No.
It's not a thing.
Okay.
Hey, Angela.
Hey, Raj.
This is crazy.
We need to get the fuck out of this room.
I feel like I was just coming to see you.
That's weird.
Yeah.
I think we got to get out of here.
Right?
You're looking at me, but Martin Cupertino has fled.
Yes.
Real quick.
What are the Grimes doing and what is Charles Digby doing?
I look at Alan.
What is he doing?
He's shaking his head back and forth and his jowls are just flopping about, little bits
of spittle are going everywhere as he's just very confused about what's going on.
I'm going to just wait there for a second.
You're going to what?
Just wait there for a second.
Okay.
Charles Digby.
I think I'm going to book it with Martin.
As soon as you guys get to the door, the door opens and Jack Russell is standing there,
short stout man, and he's like, we need to get the fuck out of here immediately.
Are you kidding me?
What?
I think you got him.
You got him.
I'm glad he said that because I was about to spray him in the face.
What happened when-
You hold the bottle up and I'm like, if you're with, that's actually hilarious.
If you're with them, I'm going to spray your ass down right now.
His hands go straight up in the air and he's like, no, Mike, there's no way that I'm with
him.
I'm trying to-
I believe you.
I found your go hole.
You didn't have a bag, really.
You didn't have a go bag, but you had a hole full of supplies underneath my floorboards.
I put my hand in the hole.
Do you have the syringe?
No, I forgot about that the first time.
Check your pockets.
See what you brought with you.
I check my pockets.
You have the syringe.
It pokes you and you die.
Oh, yep, there it is.
Ow!
I do.
Did that peak horribly?
Probably.
Say ow again.
I check my pockets.
Ow!
Yeah, I have it.
No, I probably didn't peak the first time.
What happened when he sprayed the guy?
Literally nothing.
Those people are blank, and when they fell, they just kind of stayed down.
But when you look over at them now, they're slowly getting back up with just a look of
nothing on their faces.
Are they getting up like people get up, or are they getting up in-
They're getting up like people get up.
I don't recognize these people at all, do I?
You would just recognize them from this weird out of place memory that you have of being
in cottage number 11.
These aren't the same attendants who we've seen before?
They were the same attendants that you saw in cottage 11 who sprayed Walter Grimes.
Are they getting up kind of like on their hands and knees?
I'll describe how they get up just to really put it down there.
So they're both on the ground, and they both put their palms on the ground-
In a weird way?
Like people do?
And then slowly move their feet up toward their palms.
Oh, okay.
So just like a normal person would.
Exactly.
And then once their feet and palms are both like next to each other, then they slowly
remove their palms and release towards the sky while exhaling.
Listener Zach is on the floor doing all this.
Doing yoga in front of us.
And it looks exactly like how a human looks.
I got a lot of mic for this one.
So as they're doing that, I want to go over to the guy, and while he's like still hands
on the ground, I want to get behind him and put my hand under his jaw and try to rip.
Good call.
As if maybe it's a removable face.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, I get it.
Exactly.
We all got where you're going with that.
Okay, roll unarmed combat.
Unfaced combat.
Fail.
90 on a 49.
Yeah, as you put your hand underneath his jaw, he grabs onto your hand and begins to
slowly move it away from his face.
And he turns around to face you.
And he holds up his hand like he has a spray bottle in it, but he doesn't.
And he's trying to like moving his fingers like he's spraying you in the face.
Okay, I'm going to run away.
Hey, real quick, how do you have a 49?
I have a 55 now.
Whoa.
I don't...
Okay.
Zach gave you some fun mechanics.
Luke asks, and I like to say yes.
All right, so...
Can I get better at beating people up every time I don't beat someone up?
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
Zach, I would like that too.
This story won't go that long, probably.
All right, so what does everyone know?
I mean, these two aren't going to be an issue, right?
And so, and then he looks up and his eyes cross Angela's and his eyes get really big
and he's like...
I'm so sorry.
I just noticed the bottle of hand sanitizer that we have in front of us as a very sassy
like font.
And it says, what did you touch?
Oh my God.
What did you touch?
Which is exactly what Jack Russell says to Angela Fairfield.
What did you touch, honey?
What did you touch?
Honey, what did you touch?
And she begins backing away slowly from everyone.
Honey, you all right, Angie?
Yeah, no, I'm fine.
I'm confused though.
Is everyone cool here?
What has happened?
Are you guys good?
Yeah, we're cool.
Are you cool?
Do you have any weed?
I feel like we never got to the bottom of that.
Oh, we got to the bottom of it.
Do you have anything on your hand?
I brought weed.
Yeah, it's no big deal.
Will you pass me a J?
Is this the time?
Yeah, canonically, I just kind of want to get this done.
Okay.
And she just reaches into her little clutch and throws you a joint.
Okay, I'm going to add a syringe and a joint to my inventory.
The classics.
Yep.
Woof.
Can I roll human to see if something's fucky with her?
Yes.
Can I do that too?
Do we all even see her?
Yes.
Okay.
I passed my human troll.
I failed.
Charles Digby, you know that she is extremely nervous and confused.
Okay.
Honey, you seem nervous and confused.
Why don't you come with us?
Yeah.
Yeah, no, I'll come with you guys.
Do you guys remember if she was with us the last time?
What are you talking about?
Of course.
In the cabin?
She wasn't with us in the cabin.
Out of character.
Yeah, she was not.
No, I was asking in character.
Yeah, in character.
What the fuck is going on?
What are you guys talking about when you're in the cab?
We've just been waiting for James.
Waiting for James.
Is that all you think you've done here?
Well, I do remember James came in, and then I thought that you left with him, and then
I was going to come and get you, and then you...
No, we were all just waiting for him to come in because we're having another meeting.
I think we need to run now and talk about this later.
Yeah, we're going to run.
You can come with us if you want.
We're going with Jack Russell.
Roger, come with us.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, but you said we were waiting for James to come in.
Yeah, we were waiting for James.
So he hasn't come in yet.
That means that maybe he's coming.
Why don't you stay here and find out?
Roger, come.
We need to go now.
And I grab him.
I pat him on the shoulder, like, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's
go.
Honey, come on.
We should follow them.
Yeah, okay, but what are we doing?
Why are we leaving?
There's something wrong.
They're spray bottles, and they're...
Zuhur Ilknei, Zuhur Ilknei, Zuhur Ilknei, Bradley Cooper, Charles Jacobi, Walter and
Alan Grimes, and Roger Fairfield, you are all sitting in a half circle facing a single
empty chair in the meeting room where you had orientation.
Everyone roll Constitution.
Except for Bradley, who crit.
Oh, well, he just passed again.
59 on a 60.
Nice.
Fail.
I pass a 14 on a 70.
Okay, everyone take your headphones off except for Justin.
Yay.
Don't hurt me too bad, Zai.
Okay, Justin, I need you to play on this one like you don't remember like anything from
all of these confusing plot points like you just got here and everything's normal.
Cool.
You ready for that?
So like I just first arrived?
Yeah, like you're fresh and ready to go.
Right, okay.
Okay, everybody back.
It's weird.
It's weird how well that works.
The listener can't see us, but usually we go out of the room when it's short, Zach just
has us take our headphones off and then we just like press our ears.
Ear flap?
What do you call that part?
Yeah, right.
It has a name.
Tragus.
I'm sorry, whoa, what is it?
A tragus.
Ear anatomy.
If you just slam your tragus on both sides, you get a roar in your ear.
Oh, okay.
Can you guys?
Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
Ear rumble?
Oh, the ear rumble, yeah.
I didn't know everybody couldn't do that.
I think most people can because- It's called the tragus.
Yep, that's what I said.
You're acting like Luke.
Good job, Luke.
We both are right all the time.
Thanks.
I've got both my mind pierced, so that's how I know.
Oh.
You can't tell because I have headphones on.
Did you actually in the past get your tragus?
No, I've never had anything pierced.
Anything?
My PA, I've got a Prince Albert, but that's it.
You would look really good with some piercings.
I thought you were going to say it with a Prince Albert.
You would look so hot.
Obviously, everybody would look great with a Prince Albert.
I just think Luke could really rock some funky tragus piercings.
I don't think if I got anything pierced, it wouldn't-
It would be your dingus.
I don't know what I would get.
Your dingus.
We'll think about it later.
I'll let you know at the end of the episode.
So you guys are sitting in this room.
It's just you guys.
The spray bottles aren't in here, the two people aren't in here.
Angela's not in here.
How's our memory working right now?
Do we remember spray bottle guys in the room?
You do, but they're not here.
This place sucks.
Why did you guys come here if it sucks?
Aren't we all coming here to get better?
Angela wanted us to get better, yeah.
That's good.
Yeah, I-
What?
Wait a minute.
What are you so-
What?
Why are you so protective of this place and its agenda?
What agenda are you guys talking about?
I'm not talking about an agenda.
I thought we were just here for therapy.
You've seen what's happened here.
Don't you remember?
Charles Digby's getting scared.
What's going on?
Do you not remember?
We were all just here.
But it was different.
Right?
Am I fucking losing my mind here?
I remember that.
Yeah.
I remember.
No, this is my- I just got here.
And this is like our orientation, isn't it?
Or-
Oh, damn it, Digby.
Did they spray you?
Who are you?
I'm Martin Cupertino.
I'm a Silicon Valley billionaire.
Oh, I read about you.
Yeah.
Definitely not taking pictures of people like you before.
I want to go over to-
I am a paparazzo.
And put my hand on his jaw and rip.
You?
On Charles.
See if he's-
Okay.
Well, this young kid-
I contest.
And a Metallica shirt walks up to you.
Hey, what are you doing?
Do we need to do it?
Yeah.
I mean, if he's going for it.
Unarmed combat.
38 on a 55.
Oh, shit.
Uh-oh.
Fuck.
41 on a 60.
Oh, wait.
No, let me do it.
I thought it was below.
You rip his face off.
Yeah.
I kill him.
I kill the boy.
All right, Luke, describe the beginning of what you do, and then we'll let Justin describe
how he combats that.
Like, after he is saying all that, I just kind of look at him weird, and I just stand
straight up, walk right over to him, and with just my pointer finger and thumb right behind
his cheek, just try to-
Yeah.
So at this point in time, what's Charles Digby doing?
I just grab the hand and pull the finger back.
Not break it, but pull it back to be like, what are you doing?
Yes.
Walter, get away from this man.
I don't think we can trust him.
Why can't you guys trust me?
Charles, what's going ... You don't remember anything?
I've never met you guys until today.
Have we already done the true truths and a lie in this room?
Yes.
Well, yeah.
Of course we have, but we've also done a lot of other ... Do you remember when there
were spray bottles?
The spray bottle thing?
No, I don't know what you guys are talking about.
I'm a little ... Maybe I need to go talk to James.
No, no, no, no, no.
I kind of start getting up and walking towards the door.
Father, I'm confused.
Sorry.
We all just made eye contact.
I say, sorry.
I'm trying to tackle you now.
Awesome.
27, not great for a contested unarmed combat role.
He's trying to tackle you.
I don't think I'd notice because I'm walking ... I'm assuming you're tackling me from behind
or something.
Yeah.
So it just happens.
Didn't say how you tackle me.
Yeah.
What's his body feel like on your body?
What's your body look like?
Average.
It feels like an average.
Average sort of tackle.
It doesn't feel like the NFL or anything.
That's good.
It's small compared to that because he's average.
As this is happening, I look at Roger.
What was your wife saying?
Oh yeah.
She was saying ... Can I remember what she was saying?
Role intelligence.
Oh fuck, I fail.
A 78 on a 75.
No, you can't quite remember.
Fuck, neither can Joe.
It was something weird.
It was weird.
It was like a chanting kind of thing.
Have you ever heard that before?
No, never.
Is that the correct answer?
Have I never heard her do that before?
I have no idea.
I don't know you.
Walter, tell me.
Have I heard it before?
You've definitely heard it.
Do you remember Tuesday?
No, you have never heard that before from Angela.
There has to be something in this room that gets us somewhere else.
It was the spray bottle once and then when she chanted that, we came here.
Oh God, no.
It was something strange and I don't ... But now she's not even here and everything-
Yeah.
Hey, buddy, you know your wife's in on this, right?
And she's probably not your wife.
Is she not here with us right now?
No.
Is Martin on top of me while this is happening?
That keeps happening.
Yeah, I'm on top.
I turn around.
Am I like struggling or like ... You didn't say you were, so I just thought
you were lying flat.
He's just admitted.
I'm sorry.
I was just like, I give up.
You got comfy.
I'm sad.
You're like actually the weight of another human being for the first time in a while.
Yeah, it's really nice on my back.
Oh, yeah.
I like getting sat on.
That's why I'm here.
Can I do a search to see if there's anything out of place in this room?
You can.
10 on a 43.
Nothing is out of place in this room except for maybe that Angela Fairfield isn't here.
Is anything two in place?
I don't know what that means.
You actually looked at me like you were going to let me roll?
Yeah.
So maybe that's exactly what it is.
You can roll.
64.
No.
Oh, then you don't learn the cool thing.
Can I struggle to get up or am I like, did you tackle me from behind or are you just
like-
Yeah, I've got you pinned, I think.
I've got you.
Yeah.
Can I try and, is there like a struggle mechanic?
I mean, it's unarmed combat.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Do I have advantage because I've pinned him?
You do.
You have a plus 20.
Fuck.
Oh, I didn't pass.
I did pass.
I'm like-
How do you keep him down?
46 on a modified 90.
Yeah.
No, like with no apparent effort.
I've just got him pinned.
Comfortably in a pressure lock.
And I'm still just turned around like, you know your wife's not real, right?
Half the time she's not even here.
I'm doing the thing where the only thing that's moving is my neck and I'm like, but no part
of my muscles are moving.
One of my arms is pinning you down, but another one is gently rubbing your back, just trying
to calm you down like a pig or something.
Now I'm more confused.
I'm like, what?
I don't-
I'm just trying to temple grand in you.
I'll just squeeze you.
Calm me down.
While this is happening, I'm just going around touching everything in the room.
Okay.
I feel you just like touch my chin.
I'm like, what the fuck?
Roger, when Martin is on top of Charles Digby and he's looking at you saying that your wife
isn't real, how are you responding?
Of course she's real.
She's my wife.
I don't understand.
I don't understand how she wouldn't be-
I feel like we've seen you go through this before.
The door opens and Angela is standing there.
See there.
Hey guys.
Hey Angela, are you really his wife?
Her eyes get really big.
Yeah.
Why?
I'd like to humant that.
Roll humant.
Oh shit.
Uh, fail.
Yeah.
85 on a 60.
I don't understand the line of questioning, honey.
I don't either, Angie.
Where's this going, Martin?
Come on, man.
She's never here.
I mean, sometimes she is, but like when shit goes down.
Why are you on top of-
Martin?
I thought you were Brad Lee Cooper.
Brad Lee Cooper.
That's right.
Angela, help.
Go get James and get me out of here.
What's happening right now?
I didn't come here to be treated like this.
This is supposed to be a nice calm-
Oh, that's right.
That's why I'm on you because you wanted to get James.
Yeah, actually-
Angela.
She takes one step back and shuts the door and she's on the other side of it.
Angie?
Yeah.
I'm tired of coming.
I think that you could fall.
I knew I'd make you believe.
Cooler than you could lose me.
Yeah.
Now I think you could swallow me.
Corner room in at least right.
Corner in at least right.
Yeah.