Happy Friday, babies!
It's December 6th in PTBP time,
but it's Friday time in yo' time.
My producer wanted to let y'all know
that we are on a Friday release schedule now.
I'm sure it's so they can get up
to all sorts of debauchery on the weekends
without having to worry about producing this fine program,
or something like that.
I don't know, the producer never speaks to me anymore.
They just kind of ominously glare at me
while emitting white noise frequencies to frighten me.
Last week was regrettable.
I ate so much chowder
that I vomited continuously for a week straight.
I was empty, so very empty.
My stomach became an endless void
devoid of all hope and sustenance.
But y'all know what that means.
Just more room for clam gravy.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Lady Betavir,
who tweeted about the show and tagged that pretending pod.
She writes,
"'Dear Wolf, as my favorite time-traveling pirate radio host,
"'I was hoping that you could settle a debate
"'I've been having with some of my friends.
"'Recently, we got into a highly theoretical
"'and not at all realistic discussion
"'of whether it was impolite
"'to decline food offered to you on a visit,
"'particularly when your host was an elderly man
"'who may or may not be involved in a grisly murder,
"'and the food is a bladder
"'of incredibly questionable cold cuts,
"'olives, and warm baby vegetables.
"'My friend Ellery and I both agreed
"'that it was better not to eat anything
"'than to risk vomiting in front of your host,
"'but our friend Brew insisted
"'that it would be too rude to decline,
"'even if the olives seem to be looking at you
"'and the carrots have fingernails,
"'so we could just not all agree.
"'Now, I usually ask my handler,
"'er, my good fishing buddy, Lord Bonk,
"'about this kind of etiquette,
"'but when I brought it up,
"'he began mumbling under his breath
"'in some language with too many damn consonants,
"'like Welsh, maybe,
"'and rolling his eyes into the back of his head,
"'so I suspect he's not entirely sure either.
"'Do you have any insight to share
"'on the proper behavior for this oddly specific
"'and completely made-up scenario
"'that certainly has not happened to any of us?
"'Thanks from another loyal listener, Lady Bettevere.
"'P.S., if you ever get a hold of anyone
"'from the contention police department again,
"'please give them our kind regards.
"'We'd love to bring them
"'some completely unquestionable cookies,
"'but we haven't seen anyone at the station for two days,
"'or six months.
"'I'm actually not sure which it is,
"'but we miss them all the same.
"'Greetings, loyal listener Lady Bettevere.
"'In this house, we always eat whatever is given to us,
"'for the meat of man is still meat nonetheless,
"'and all meat is good.
"'And though you might vomit, worry not, children,
"'as that is but a sign of respect in the House of Wolf.
"'So I'm on Baby Brew's side,
"'and ask your old fishing buddy
"'to quit being a fucking weirdo.
"'Also, drop them unquestionable cookies off at my address.
"'Just smell around, I'm sure you'll find my abode.
"'To grow this show, send a memo to all that you know,
"'even your foe, to say hello to our fine audio.
"'And if you got dough, a Patreon subscription
"'would blow Wolf to and fro,
"'hitting falsetto while dancing flamenco on a rainbow.
"'From high in the sky to low and slow,
"'I'm on a booze cruise to soothe the news.
"'On the last episode, holiday hijinks
"'led Clark Bishop and Leon Simpson,
"'along with their new friend, Donovan something,
"'to the dorm room of Harriet Marks and Amelia Locke,
"'where Keith had information and John had changed.
"'In the room across the hall,
"'the group banged out the melody of Jingle Bells,
"'turned and saw the bell tower in the middle of the campus,
"'dressed in lights, wreaths,
"'and topped with a giant minion inflatable.
"'Just a reminder that it is December 6th here in the city,
"'so the whole holiday cheer thing is appropriate.
"'Kazoo with no backbone.'"
["The
And we're back in the groove, boys."
Ready to click record.
As you finish hammering out the tune to Jingle Bells
on this Casio keyboard, you hear the bell tower
in the center of campus ring out as well.
You see through the window of this dorm room,
the bell tower lights up in a congratulatory glow,
and snow begins to fall.
I think we need to go to there.
But that's just a weather thing.
That's just a John thing.
I turn away from the camera and I kind of like
smile and wink to myself.
Another camera gets it and you totally Jim the camera.
It's all about making moments in my line of work.
So is the plan to go to the Jingle Ball or,
I mean, we can assume that if this Alicia Locke,
what was her name?
Amelia.
Amelia Clark is down there,
then we can only assume that she's got more information
at least that we can talk to her.
So I guess we need to.
Yeah, I think she's probably the first one to get there.
So let's finish these clues and go talk to her.
We'll head to the bell tower.
Should we take the stairs or the elevator?
Not the elevator, it sounds like.
Yeah, probably not.
I'll just walk to not embarrass you.
As opposed to what?
He says that and John like rapidly rolls on all fours,
like out of the room.
What?
Rolls?
Yeah, he gets down and like,
he gets down into a ball and he rolls out of the room.
And then he turns around and he like winks at Donovan.
And he's like, roll sanity, Donovan.
I look at Clark and I'm like,
I'm thinking that body fucked him up a little bit.
Yeah, no shit, Keith, what the fuck?
But yeah, let's take the stairs to avoid
maybe that happening to you.
And away we go.
Walking across the campus, you see that the-
Walking and rolling.
I'm so sorry.
I'm walking next to you.
I was rolling to demonstrate how much more quickly
I would get places using my preferred method
of transportation.
Jesus Christ.
You guys are walking and not rolling,
rolling mentally maybe?
You guys are walking to the bell tower,
which is nearby on campus.
And you pass many a holiday accoutrement on your way there.
And the snow falling has made it a really delightful evening
even though it is quite quiet on this campus,
except for the distant noises of holiday cheer and screaming.
Other than that, it's quiet though.
Besides the cheer and the screaming.
Have you fellas noticed how much screaming
is happening around us?
No, not until just now.
When we were first entered that gifts hall,
that gifts house-
Is that a dinosaur?
Donovan walked into a room, flipped on the light,
and a real creepy little dude said,
turn off that light.
And we did and got the hell out of there.
What?
You didn't investigate it?
It scared us.
What?
We'll have to go back to that.
You remember that Donovan?
Yeah, I don't actually remember if it was a boy or a girl
so much as a shadowy entity.
And I just wasn't done with it.
I didn't really want to deal with that.
I just figured that all these screams
were coming from people in dark rooms and it scared us.
So we turned off the light real quick.
Well, that would have been nice to know,
but we'll get back to that, I guess.
And I continue walking towards the bell tower.
You guys make your way to an old stone bell tower
with a large gated entrance that is built into the rock
and stone formation that is forming this quite small,
cylindrical, phallic shape that it reaches
into the night December sky.
And the door has a gate right there.
There's a gate on the door, there's a door on the gate.
It's just a gate, it's not a door, and it's open.
I walk on in.
I follow.
So this is a dark stairwell.
It is open all the way up like a silo in the middle,
but there are these stone stairs that go in a spiral upward
to the very top.
Thomas is just drawing circles in his notes.
It's really horrifying.
Who's first?
Who's going first?
Keith Vigna's going first.
I'm going to go first.
And Keith Vigna, you about halfway up,
you see that there is a corpse on the stairwell.
I look back, I'm like, close your eyes, guys.
You're not going to want to see this.
Close our eyes?
Just trust me.
Looking past Keith Vigna.
Technically, I don't have eyes, but I'll humor you.
At this point, Keith is kind of like worried about Jon,
but also like, okay, whatever.
The world worries for me and I worry for the world
and neither of us can do a thing to help the other.
The corpse is wearing a security guard uniform.
And it's dead.
Guys, just close your eyes and keep going up the stairs.
And I stand by the corpse to kind of guide them past it.
I want to stop at Keith standing by the corpse.
I grab him by the shoulders.
Worry not about this vessel.
I'm not about you?
It is as much here as it ever was.
And it is not here.
Like it always wasn't.
Come up the stairs.
Let's go, Keith.
Same as it ever was.
There is water at the bottom of the ocean.
Keith is like just-
Pretty weirded out.
All right, Clark, come on.
Get past this and let's keep going.
I go past.
Okay.
I'm keeping my eyes open.
Nothing happens to me?
Nope.
Keith, I can look at the body, it seems like.
Okay, good.
I just didn't want-
It's face down.
You don't see any like blood or anything.
It's just a face down body.
So yeah, I mean, you could assume it's sleeping
if you want to rationalize it that way,
but you know based on the world that you've been living in
for the past however many, you know, whatevers.
It's probably dead.
Are there numbers and stuff all in this place too?
Any on the body?
Oh yeah, there's some on the body.
Anything that we've seen before?
Is it all-
Oh baby, we're in the wild west of numbers.
I turn back to Donovan.
Hey Donovan, you might, Keith's warning here,
you might want to shut them eyes.
Donovan is staring directly at the body.
But he's not like super phased by it
and he just like steps over it.
Oh, that was Jerry.
Didn't much care for him.
You actually see he's got a,
there is a notepad in Jerry's hand.
Who me?
Yeah.
Oh, couldn't be.
Do some investigating.
Hey, what is this?
Picks it up.
It's just a to-do list for tomorrow and it says retire.
Poor bastard.
It was wise of you to look closer.
I set up all kinds of jokes like these.
I continue up the stairs.
Clark, your friend's freaking me out.
John, you set this up?
Did you?
Keith, did he ever leave your sight?
He never did, no.
I laugh as they try to understand.
I don't know what's going on with him.
I think he might've had a break.
You don't say.
Holy shit.
Let's keep going.
As you approach the top of the tower,
you hear a voice that is mumbling.
And that's just right, I just,
42 can't find it, you know?
If we can't get higher from this perspective,
then we gotta figure it out later.
Hello?
Oh, yes.
Oh my goodness.
Yes, peoples.
Yes, come on over.
Come on over to the top of the tower, please.
Can I see this person?
Yeah, as you approach,
it is an attractive girl who is in college age,
early twenties.
And she has two boobies.
God damn it.
No.
She has two buns on the back of her head, on her hair.
It's like grade A, grade A content.
And uh.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
Oh, thank you.
Luke cams on it.
I just want you to hear.
Oh, we're gonna make so much money.
On the Luke cam.
Would you guys please help me get to the top of the tower?
And she's like got her hands on her head
and her eyes are wide and she's looking at all of you like,
oh my God, if you could just please take me to the two forts.
I can't take you to the top of the tower,
that'd be, that would just be fucking tits.
I look at her and I close my eyes and nod my head.
And is she still there when I open my eyes?
Everyone pull out your headphones
and then cover your ears real quick.
Hey Thomas, when John closes his eyes,
he just sees a mass of numbers flash before them.
And then he sees the visage of Clark Bishop age rapidly
and then age and reverse Benjamin Button style back down.
And then you see your own face take over for his face,
age in the same way and then age in reverse.
The beautiful topography of time.
As you open your eyes, she's still there.
And she's like, I don't think it,
can anyone get me to the top physically
with their bodies and hands and stuff?
What's your name?
Oh, my name is Sham Wow.
That's unfortunate.
No, it's Sham Wow Chameleon.
You didn't hear the whole thing.
Fucking millennials.
What's at the top?
Higher than this.
I'm just trying to get higher, baby.
Gotta take me higher.
Four, three, two, six.
Well, why do you need somebody to take you up there?
Well, because it's harder for me to do it
because I can't climb this rope.
And she points at the rope that the giant bell is on.
I'm afraid if I jump onto the bell by myself,
I won't be able to climb all the way and I'll fall and die.
I don't wanna fall and die.
So I wanna get to the top of the tower.
I wanna get higher tippy top.
If you had to think of any numbers in the universe,
what would they be?
Clark is getting his punching hand ready?
Immediately Leon Simpson puts on
his noise canceling headphones.
Are we at the top of this other than like climbing
up the rope to the bell?
Are we at the top of the tower?
Yes.
Cool.
There's lots of names.
There's numbers.
There's so many numbers.
They're inside my brain
and they keep coming out all over the place.
And you would not believe the week ahead,
but I guess like if I had to think about the ones
that speak to me most truly,
it would be 811-818-9520-1318-1119.
And all the rest of them are also in here,
but they're all over the place sideways
and on top of each other.
And it's just constant and it's all inside,
but I gotta get higher.
Was that Harriet?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure it was.
Harriet.
Oh, you know Harriet.
Did you?
I know Harriet.
I know you.
I know everyone on your campus.
I know your mother, your father.
That's wild.
You know, the chameleons.
John, thanks for a minute.
And it's like, they're not coming to mind right now,
but yes, of course.
Wow.
Did you know Harriet?
Marks?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, not too many people
are named Harriet these days.
Can you get me higher?
What do you need up there for?
I just gotta get higher.
Number one.
Number one, I gotta get higher.
Are you working on the scavenger hunt?
Yes, for sure.
But most importantly, gotta get higher than I am here.
This is the highest spot I've been
and the highest spot I can be,
but I could get higher with you guys' help
if you wanna help me get higher.
Do you know what would happen if you got higher?
Feel good.
I wanna look around and see if I can find like a clue
that would have led us here.
She grabs onto Donovan's like shirt
and is like, take me higher.
I don't, no, I don't wanna talk to you.
Roll search for me.
What are you looking for?
Just like another clue, like why we came up here.
Sure.
35 on a 40.
Yeah, so looking out from the bell tower,
you very clearly see across the way,
there is a sleigh that is completely lit up in lights
that is on top of a building across campus,
which Donovan, you would know is the Accord Student Center.
We drove here in an Accord.
You think there's any connection?
Donovan, what's that sleigh?
That's the Accord Student Center.
That's where a lot of people meet up.
Perhaps a ball could be there?
In the sleigh is a brightly lit sign
that points to a light up chimney.
And the sign says in all caps, the jingle ball is this way.
You guys, I think that might be where we need to go next.
Are you telling me we did a scavenger hunt
to be told that the jingle ball was at the student union?
And that we're all balls are held?
Yeah, what's the problem is a really hard rule to solve.
Hey, y'all remember how we might all be balls?
You think there's something to do that?
Jingle balls, balls.
I'm not convinced I'm ball.
Let's go back to that.
You said that you're all balls?
No, my child.
Can you take me higher?
You're all balls though?
Would you just do the top of the thing?
I'm sorry, you said that you all were balls.
You'd like to be.
I just need to get on top of this bell tower
as fast as possible.
I wouldn't listen to John right now.
You can hear how he's been talking some gibberish.
I just, he's just out of it right now.
Well, persuade.
I'd like to confess his rule.
Oh, okay.
You can roll persuade.
Profits are never appreciated in their own time.
No, they die.
I keep sending them though.
81.
Yeah, okay.
That's fair.
I guess balls.
So if you could just take me
to the very top of this bell tower,
it's just right around.
So you see how it's open right here?
I think if you two of you stand right on the edge,
you can hold my feet with your hands on your knees,
maybe thigh, maybe I could get some upper thigh
and then I could work my way up
with my sleek rock climbing abilities
to get even on top of the tower even more.
I'm kind of ignoring this person
and I look at, we don't need to help.
Well, I was thinking we might as well just help her
and then get over the ball.
Oh yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'll see you there.
I have a feeling she's gonna follow us
and annoy us if we don't do this for her.
Plus I just wanna see what happens.
You guys could take me higher
and that's who I wanna be.
If you could take me to the Christmas sky,
I could feel it with all of my might.
I get down to like in the position she told us to get
and I just kind of look over.
I look over at Clark and kind of shrug my shoulders.
I just feel like we're leading this person to their death.
They're gonna fall off that rope.
I look over at Donovan and I'm pointing in front of me
and I shrug my shoulder.
I have an idea.
Clark, will you strike this woman down
as you did the others?
I'm not too bright, Clark,
but I think it would solve all our problems
if you struck this woman.
Clark cracks his knuckles.
It's like, well, that's true.
I could just knock her out.
John moves in front of her.
If you're gonna knock her out,
we might as well help her keep her dreams.
My savior, take me higher.
John holds his hands up in front of him
and he's like, Clark.
Our John is an awesome John.
He reigns from heaven above with hands.
I keep one hand pointed out to John,
but I put one hand behind me and I put it on her forehead.
Your John.
With her hand on my forehead, take me higher, Satan.
Is anybody gonna help me out here?
Honestly, I have no idea what's happening anymore.
I just feel like if we help her onto this rope,
that's a death sentence for her.
Well, you're gonna punch her, so.
It'd just knock her out though.
That wouldn't kill her.
Just so many potential complications.
We could also just leave.
We don't have to.
No, no, you don't have to leave.
Come on, God.
You're gonna make me leave with your hand upon my skin?
I will help you, my child.
And Keith Vigner, are you gonna help us out?
Yeah, I'm gonna help too.
Sick.
All right, so between the two of you,
who has the better luck?
I have 35 him.
I'll have you roll it.
A three.
Oh!
You help her out the little opening
that's looking out onto the campus,
and she is starting to climb up,
clearly misses with one of her hands and begins to fall,
but you catch her legs,
and she immediately holds on with both
and then fucking sends it,
getting a full grip of the gargantuan inflatable minion
that tops this CSU bell tower.
You hear the swooshing of final coated nylon,
and then...
I'm higher!
Ooh, yeah, eight, one, whoa, ooh, yeah,
it's fun, four, five, six, seven, eight,
kind of, you gotta get it up on the sky
with the Christmas spirit,
and my God fell into helping me aware
whose phone is ringing while we're recording a podcast.
Fucking Justin.
I'm sorry, it's all right, I'm hearing it.
Oh, there we go.
Are we good now, is that, is it over?
Yeah, I feel better, let's go to the ball.
Yeah, let's head on down.
It's time to finally get my prize I deserve.
How is she gonna get down from up there though, guys?
She got up there pretty easily, so.
With the help, okay.
The world works in mysterious ways.
I go down the stairs.
You see the security guard on your way back.
Hey, Jerry.
Same spot, but he'll hop over.
And then at the bottom of the staircase,
you guys enter the, essentially the quad of this campus,
and you head over to the Accord Student Union
that is just across the way.
And as you walk up to it,
you see that there are a couple different entrances.
There are three in front of you.
You can go left, center, or right.
Are any of them lit?
John just walked straight through the center door
without waiting for discussion.
Right on.
Follow John?
I guess.
Yeah, I'll follow John, are we all following John?
Let's head in.
He seems really confident now.
Are we following the guy who was rolling around earlier?
Yeah, yeah.
He actually does a little roll through the door.
Donovan, he's not always like this.
In fact, it's a little worrisome.
I just am trying to keep the eye on the prize right now
and figure that out later, I guess.
Yeah, seems smart.
As you guys walk in, the lights are off.
However, there is a path of colorful string lights
on the ground, like a pathway or a road.
You notice that there is a little sitting area to your left
where there are some tables and chairs set up.
And sitting in one of the chairs is a corpse
that is quite fermented.
It has been here for some time, you would guess,
by the looks of it.
And right next to that corpse is a very alive person
dancing their ass off.
Just fucking getting it.
I've seen pictures of Amelia, is this her?
Nope.
Hey, where's the ball?
The dancing fiend continues their grind
and with their hips motions in the way that you're headed.
Thank you, thank you very much.
I go that way.
I'll continue on too, yeah.
That's not Tim Fate with.
I dance with him for a little while.
It's just like a few bars,
like I am grooving to the beat and then I walk on.
Easy peasy.
You would notice that the student union is-
They have no idea.
The path of colorful lights and thumping holiday base
leads the five of you,
four imposters in city PD uniforms
and a nicely dressed fifth year college student
to a three story atrium,
kind of like a small square shopping mall.
But instead of Forever 21 and Orange Julius,
there's a CSU merch shop and a subway.
You're on the middle level,
so looking down you see the basement of this atrium
and it's decked out in jingle ball decorations.
But in drastic contrast to this festive cheer,
you are surrounded only by pure chaos,
personified by obsessive college students and faculty.
Across the atrium on your level,
there's a girl shaving the fur off a team of reindeer
in front of a photo backdrop
and she is shaking and gluing the loose fur to her own skin.
On the bottom level,
a pair of very tall and muscular men in Santa outfits
are diligently wrapping a college student
in gift wrapping paper.
They are using duct tape and force.
An older woman in a bathrobe
and one of those fur lined leather aviator hats
that cover your ears is climbing a thick garland
from this level up to the top.
The garland wraps around these columns
that encircle the opening to the atrium
every 10 yards or so
and they all meet in the center of the dome
atop this part of the Accord Student Union here at CSU.
Hanging from the middle of this dome
is a massive disco ball, 10 yards in diameter,
wearing an equally huge Santa hat.
That's college, baby.
That's college.
Three people in elf costumes
are in the corner of the lower level
in a little ice skating rink
with a life-size Frosty the Snowman figure.
They keep putting the carrot in different places
while laughing hysterically.
A naked man is using a mop and a mop bucket full of paint
to write out a sequence of numbers
at the bottom of the stairs to the lower level.
Across the room on the bottom floor,
there is a young woman throwing a laptop in the air
and trying to spin around in a circle before catching it.
She is doing this fervently
and she's wearing a shirt that says,
gifts house on the back and best RA ever on the front.
It says, if I make it this far,
a dude doing squats on top of Santa Claus's throne stops
and begins violently chanting,
Towel alico, towel alico, towel alico, towel alico.
That's college, baby.
I look at the man who's chanting and I just,
I just boom out.
I command you to stop.
Roll.
And I wave my hand, I just gotta wave a hand at him.
Roll persuade for me.
Got a 76 on a, probably not higher than that.
We're sitting in new places
and it's hard for me to see my character sheet.
No, that's a fail.
Towel alico, towel alico, towel alico.
And when he keeps going,
I kind of look at my hand in confusion.
John, who were you talking to, was that man?
Oh, you were, gotcha.
I look at Clark, I get my gun out
and I like look at him and point it at the guy
and like questioning the look in my eyes.
John's just nodding.
He must be punished.
Towel alico, whatever, what's that?
I've heard it before, but I,
It sounds like a spell, right?
That's what I'm thinking and I think we need to stop it.
Do we remember what it is?
So far, I don't know.
It could have done a number of things.
Listen, it's been a while since we played, but that is,
We've heard it a lot.
We've heard it a lot, right?
I just don't remember what it does.
I don't think it's done anything yet.
Isn't it just the phrase?
I punched your brother's partner
when you started saying it.
Yeah, so we've stopped everybody.
It's done it so far.
Yeah, maybe we have stopped it every time.
Yeah, so I'm like looking at,
Keith is looking at Clark ready to shoot this guy just,
I don't know why I'm asking for permission this time, but.
Clark shrugs.
I fire.
Roll firearms.
That's a two.
So anyway, I started blasting.
Holy shit, all right, cool, so.
Hey, maybe we should make a role-playing decision
that's not shooting up a college.
Fucking food court.
They're monsters.
Too late, so roll damage for me.
A nine.
Oh my God.
Where do you shoot him?
Right in chest.
Yep.
As two shots hit this man, center mass,
he falls back into the throne of one Santa Claus
and begins bleeding as he continues to slowly,
quietly chant,
Oh, and he succeeds on a constitution check
and stays conscious,
but fewer can hear his chant.
Does the crowd react at all?
Yes, absolutely.
The crowd a hundred percent reacts, so.
Yay, I'm the star of the show now.
Everybody look at me.
Spotlight online.
I'm the DJ now.
As soon as you fire the gun,
everyone in this room turns and looks at the five of you.
Everyone then looks at the Santa throne
where this man is bleeding all over while still chanting.
Reindeer fur girl immediately turns and begins sharpening
one of the horns on one of these live reindeer.
The Santa twins.
Wait, these are live reindeer?
Oh yeah, baby.
Oh shit.
Was not aware of that.
Yeah, I definitely thought he just
more fucked up reindeer.
Were they letting her shave them willingly
or were they struggling again?
She was cutting off their fur.
They're tied up for a photo shoot
and she's cutting off their fur with a blunt knife
that she carries with her.
Holy shit.
Should have shot her first.
Yeah, that's not cool.
So she begins sharpening one of these reindeer's horns.
The Santa twins, the two giant muscular men
dressed as Santa Claus, start wrapping each other
as opposed to this undergrad that they were wrapping before
and they're using duct tape to wrap around
the gift wrapping on each other.
I wanted to ask about that guy who's being wrapped.
Does he seem under the same spell as everyone
or was he maybe fighting against them?
He was compulsively staying as still as possible.
Gotcha.
Cousin Eddie Lady Climber starts climbing faster
and faster up this garland and is trying desperately
to end like to the point to where she's like
losing grip on the garland and still making it up.
She's in very good shape.
The three elves in the corner, they begin sitting
on the ground and unlacing their ice skates.
The naked mop man begins squeezing paint back
into his mop bucket and the girl throwing the laptop
in the air begins throwing it way higher
than she was before, so much higher.
Like she's throwing this laptop 20 feet in the air
every time and still catching it currently.
Luke, you had a question?
So there's the basement level, the middle level
that we're on and then an upper level?
Yes.
Okay, who's on the basement level?
The basement level is the man who is in the throne
of Santa Claus who is chanting and bleeding out currently.
The Santa twins are on the basement level as well
who are wrapping each other with gift wrapping
and duct tape.
The three elves in the ice skating rink are also
in the basement level as is the naked mop man
who is squeezing paint back into his mop bucket
as is the laptop girl.
Luke, ask him your real question.
What have we talked about?
Ask him what it's like to have sex.
You can ask me anything Luke.
That's for later, that's not on the packet.
I wanna know.
Who's on the level we're on?
I want you to show me.
Make him tell us.
On your level.
Who's on our level?
Thomas.
On your level is the reindeer fur girl
and then on the next level climbing up to the next level
is the cousin lady climber.
Gotcha, thank you.
I wanna draw my pistol if I can.
Yeah, we're in free play right now
so you can do whatever you want.
Yeah, I don't know.
Are we starting combat?
No, we are, yeah.
Okay, cool.
I draw my pistol and point it at the reindeer girl
and I say, touch not mine creatures
and then I look at my gun and I'm like,
I must use these mortal instruments
to achieve my divine means.
Fire, I aim in fire.
Okay, so she is across the atrium from you
so as you say that.
I got a 65.
You're just assuming that as you speak
that she'll be able to hear you
regardless of the volume of your voice.
I'm assuming.
Who are you talking to now, John?
Putting it out into the universe,
which is me.
Roll firearms for me.
I am the universe experience in itself.
43 on a 60.
All right, roll a D10 for damage.
Seven.
She gets hit once in the shoulder,
immediately falls to the ground
and the bullet goes through
and one of the reindeer's
and then falls over as well
and she is on the ground bleeding
as she tries to grab on to the hairless reindeer
in front of her to help herself up.
She goes limp and her head just like hits the ground.
Can I have Mercy kill that reindeer real quick?
The look on Zach's face just now is, huh.
I just threw up.
You're the one who made me shoot a fucking reindeer.
I just want to resolve that as quickly as possible.
I'm just telling the story, man.
This is just what happened.
It's not my fault.
It's not your fault.
Life is chaos.
Dude, you can't change the past.
Go for it.
97.
God damn it.
I shoot another reindeer.
That's going to be a fucked up photo shoot.
Well, she fucked it up by shaving him already.
Sorry about that.
Did you just shake your-
He just grabbed his McDonald's cup and shook it.
That was habit.
Oh boy.
Okay.
Love that.
How many drankies are left in here?
We're better than this.
Maybe, I don't know.
I am.
You're not.
I hope that's your character talking.
Hey Donovan.
Hey.
Hey, what are you thinking, man?
Mildly panicked.
Uh-huh.
Do you want to go ahead and roll sanity for me?
Yeah.
I don't know what to roll it against.
You'll roll against a,
I think based on the week that you've had,
you're going to roll it against a pretty solid 58.
Sounds right.
54.
Very well done.
Okay.
You can hold yourself together for the time being,
but just so you know,
this is the first time that Donovan,
I'm assuming has seen anyone get shot
or maybe even any animal.
Yes.
Oh, for sure.
You've never seen a reindeer get blasted in the face.
Raw vegan?
Yeah.
Only sprouts for this boy.
You know what?
That's really cool.
I really respect that.
Thank you.
Anyway.
I think Donovan, after the first gunshot,
it's like, what the fuck?
And like freaking out.
Cause it's the first time a gun has been fired
probably in his vicinity ever.
Yeah.
And it is quite frightening.
I would imagine to a fifth year college student.
It's yeah.
It's the first time he's seen a gun since high school.
Yeah.
Or violence.
Wow.
So America has an epidemic of gun violence.
So as the second gunshot rings out,
everyone begins to panic and obsess a little bit harder.
If Clark wanted to get to the girl
who was throwing the laptop, how would he do that?
He wants to do that.
Okay.
So you would have to go down the stairs
into the basement of the atrium
and then past the Santa twins and the naked mop man
before you got to the laptop girl.
I'm going to yell at the guys, cover me.
And I'm going down the stairs.
So you take off running.
If they successfully cover you,
then you'll make it there no problem.
Well, I mean, I have my own wherewithal.
If something, if something wants to stop me,
I get to, I get to fight back,
but I'm hoping that they'll.
Leon is going to be like, I'm with you.
And is joining you.
I hear him yell to cover him.
And the first person between him
and the top girl is the twins.
Yes.
I'm going to run behind with him.
But right before I start going down the stairs,
take a shot at the one on the left.
All right.
Roll firearms.
That's a one.
Okay.
I say.
Celebratory shake.
We've got our own manual drops.
As I do it, I hear Clark say, cover me.
And I'm like, hell yeah, Clark.
And then I look directly into the eyes of that twin.
And I say, I'm the bill of the ball.
Ding, ding.
And then pull the gun and shoot him
right between the eyeballs.
Yeah.
And Santa dies.
You're the new Santa Claus.
Look at me.
I'm the Santa now.
The other Santa does not miss a beat.
Grabs the duct tape out of the hand of his fellow Santa
as the man just drops to the ground.
The duct tape being the only thing left.
And he just smoothly continues wrapping himself
in this duct tape.
I would look at Clark.
I'm like, they may, they seem like they may not be
our biggest obstacles.
Yeah, they're gonna take care of themselves here, so.
And I follow suit.
Clark is running at the laptop girl.
Yeah.
The Santa guys are taking care of themselves.
No one's fucking with any more reindeer.
Are there any threats we see around us?
You've got old lady maybe potentially climbing your way
or was she above us already?
Climbing to the second floor.
Climbing from the second to the third floor.
And we're on the second floor?
Yeah.
Can I reach her?
Like if I reached over the edge, could I like grab her?
You'd have to like run around the side
and then probably get on the garland yourself
and begin climbing before you got to her.
Cause she, when those first gunshots rang out,
she really started going for it.
She's free soloing this bitch like a moat.
I just watched that.
It was so fucking good.
I mean, I know everybody said it and that's old news, but.
My hands are sweaty.
Unrelated.
Yeah, I want to shoot the old broad.
Jesus Christ.
I'm kidding.
I'm going to cover, I'm going to cover Joe.
Clark, I want to see.
Oh yeah.
Can you ready an action in Delta Green?
You can ready an action in Delta Green.
So I'm going to be on Overwatch for Clark.
Dope.
Sounds good, Justin.
What's Donovan doing?
He pulls out his grenade launcher.
Is there like a weapon nearby that like,
like even like a bat or a plant,
it's like some kind of thing I could use
as a makeshift weapon just to like arm myself.
Actually, as you're looking around for a makeshift weapon.
You see a bat flying around
and you just grab it out of the air
and chuck it at one of the Santas.
You become Batman.
Bad man?
Bad man.
So as.
Badminton?
Badminton.
So as you're shuttle cocking your way,
Leon Simpson, halfway down the stairs,
turns and goes, shit, Clark, I forgot.
And runs right back up the stairs
and throws a gun to Donovan
and then grabs you by the shoulder
and takes you like around a corner
where you both can watch,
but you're a little bit safer away from everything.
Sounds like a good plan.
I mean, you can get out there if you want,
but I would rather you didn't
based on the fact that as of now our current theory
is that you're our savior.
Oh, that's like a lot to put on me, but I, sure.
You're gonna do great things in this world
and if you don't, it's on you.
He just like gets really sad
and looks down at the ground.
Okay.
Okay, so you understand
that you should probably not die today?
That was my, that was kind of my plan was not to be dead.
I think we're good to go.
Thanks.
So.
Wait, wait, wait, how do I use this?
Oh, right, and then he shows you how to use it,
but like very quickly.
Yeah, I'll definitely remember, I'm smart.
Roll a 50-50 shot on whether or not
you know how to use this gun at all.
Do I like flip a coin?
Just roll, if you roll under 50,
you know how to do it, yeah.
Under 50.
With that, we'll give you a 30% in firearms.
Ooh.
Nice.
It feels natural.
Why have I not been using this all this time?
Your new friends certainly like doing it.
So, the Santa twin that's left,
the lady climbing up the garland,
all three elves, the naked mop man,
and the girl throwing the laptop in the air,
all stop what they're doing
and begin chanting.
Tall, we allow the call.
The man in the throne of the Santa Claus dressing
runs and jumps onto,
so there's like a four poster chair
for the elf that sits next to him,
and he jumps on it with his neck landing directly on,
what are those called at the top of like a four poster?
Like a spinet?
We'll call it a spinet.
And if that's not a word,
that's what it means now.
Post?
At the top of a post.
What do you call that thing?
An uppy pointy,
just a straight up and downer.
So he jumps on the chair stalagmite.
It's like a line, but round.
And punctures his own throat
and immediately just like,
and begins bleeding.
Did it look purposeful or accidental?
It looked extremely purposeful
and the chants get louder from everyone else.
Clark, it's your turn.
The laptop is in the air and you have made your way there.
What do you want to do?
I've made my time to her.
Yep, she is chanting and no longer,
and no longer paying attention to the laptop
that is in the air about 20 feet in the air.
I don't know how many actions this is,
but I'd like to catch the laptop
so it doesn't hit the ground,
but knock her in the chin.
Just see if it clocks her.
Is that the way she's throwing it?
I could do that, yeah.
It'll land directly on her head if you do nothing.
Oh, I'll do nothing then.
Yeah, if it's coming down on her.
Let's see what happens.
I'll just see what happens there.
I'll let that play out and then I'll see what I do.
Oh my God.
The laptop comes down in such a way
that the most sturdy edge comes down directly on her temple
because as she's chanting,
she's turning her head to the side completely
in this weird like you just said squirrel
to a dog kind of way.
It hits her directly above the ear in the side of the head
and she goes blank, roll luck for me.
I'm using new dice that my mom got me for Christmas.
Ooh, mama dice.
They're good, 54 on a 65.
Nice.
That will come into play later.
Okay, so did it knock her out?
It knocked her out cold.
Okay, I want to grab the laptop and her
and run retreat back to the second floor.
Okay, so you can get a hold of them this round,
but you won't be able to make it all the way back.
You can start your way there.
What is Keith Vigna doing?
He sees that happen and looks at the people chanting.
Are they looking at us or just kind of out of it?
They are all staring at one of you.
I look at one of the elves and he's staring right at me.
Oh yeah.
I see down.
And he's taken off his ice skating skate.
Yeah, I see down about two feet away from me
is a candy cane, but the end is sharpened
like you're supposed to stick it in your lawn.
100%.
And I grab it and I spear it right at him.
Roll.
Roll spear.
Roll athletics for me.
83 on a 50.
You run down the stairs with this sharpened candy cane
and you launch it at your elven foe.
And it just skies and it lands directly
in the head of Frosty the snowman.
Do they laugh?
And it gets stuck there.
So there's a candy cane coming out
in between the two button eyes.
What are the eyes?
Coal.
And it goes right into the button nose
and the elves die laughing
and they're giggling their asses off as they're
Tommy Lally Cool, Tommy Lally Cool, Tommy Lally Cool,
Tommy Lally Cool, Tommy Lally Cool, wow!
Now Zach, are these really Santa's elves
or are they just people pretending to be Santa's elves?
You don't know.
Roll a cult.
38 on a 10.
Those ears look real, baby.
Give one a tug if I can.
You can give one a tug if you want
cause it's your turn, John Lee Pettymore.
What's the naked guy doing?
He has put the mop down
and he is putting the mop bucket up against the wall
and he's beginning to dip his head into the paint
that's in this mop bucket.
Like you do.
Does it bubble up?
It's creepy.
As he's chanting.
He hasn't gotten in there yet.
He's still chanting.
Twiddle, twiddle, twiddle, twiddle, twiddle, twiddle.
Twiddle, twiddle, twiddle, twiddle, twiddle.
Well done.
Yeah.
Thank you.
You brought out that big bucket of paint and everything.
Yes.
And we'll be right back.
Yeah, Zach's gonna have to clean off
for the next 30 minutes.
Just throw some dirt on me.
He's in the basement?
He is in the basement.
Like the lower level?
Yes.
Okay.
So John jumps off the balcony.
Yeah.
On to him.
Awesome.
And from the way he jumps,
it looks like he thinks he's like,
he literally just kind of like steps off.
All right.
Roll dexterity or athletics, whichever one's higher.
65 decks.
Five.
What do you do?
It looks impossible.
I don't know if you've ever seen being there.
It's very Chauncey Gardner-ish.
He literally just like steps off
and then you just see his feet moving through the air
like he's walking down steps,
but very quickly because he's just falling.
And then perfectly in his stride,
as he steps the foot forward,
it like hits, he steps on the naked man's head
and it breaks his fall.
And he just glides onto the,
like walks onto the floor like he meant to do it.
Hell yeah.
Your foot comes down on this naked man
and shoves his head into the bottom of the mop.
You stand on the other side with literally no paint on you
and turning back around, you just hear
doodle doodle doodle, doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle.
Since he's literally a fish in the bucket,
can I just put my gun up to his head and kill him?
Next round.
I just mean as a casual afterthought to this round.
Donovan.
Tell me more.
What's been going on here?
I don't know, everything started going really crazy,
but you know, I just, I try to keep to myself
and you know, I just wanna have a good time at school.
So I just, you know, just kind of been ignoring all this.
You've just been going about your normal business.
I mean, have classes been in session at all?
I don't go to classes.
Is that why you're still here?
I do a lot of online classes.
Gotcha.
But I do live on campus.
Okay.
For fun.
That's kind of sad.
But I don't really do much.
You know, I always thought I was important,
but maybe not this important.
Yeah, you weren't.
Oh.
From what I can tell.
Oh, God.
Roll for sadness.
I'm sad.
Kind of unaffected, honestly.
Yeah, yeah, that makes sense.
Donovan's a very like non-emotional human being.
Well, let's see if this gets you.
So at the end of this round.
So wait, is Leon just hanging out with me right now?
Like protecting me?
Yeah.
I'm good with being done talking
if you just want to watch what's going on here.
Should we shoot at some of these elves?
Yeah, I mean, we can if we want.
Or you could take some pot shots.
Can you tell me how to aim?
Like ghost style?
Yeah, I'll show you how to aim.
Oh, no.
Go ahead and roll firearms with a plus 20
as he puts his hands on over your hands.
From behind.
And ghosts your gun.
And you just can feel him smell you.
Oh.
Stop plus 40.
Crip fail.
A 99.
It's not a Crip, but it's.
Oh, I thought it was a 66.
Oh, it's a 96.
Nevermind, just a regular fail.
Well, if 69 is a Crip success,
should 96 be a Crip fail?
Not this time,
but that would be an interesting house rule to add.
Let's add it.
96.
Fuck, I know I'm gonna be the next person to roll one
in like two months when I don't fucking remember
this at all.
Head to toe, back to back.
So Leon steps to the side and is like,
yeah, okay, that was pretty good, but more like this.
And then he just, he actually looks at you.
He makes direct eye contact with you while he fires,
takes one of the elves out and then he turns back.
No, he continues looking at you and he's like,
did I get him?
You're really scary.
You're a scary guy.
Yes, I am.
But I am impressed and that almost never happens.
I'll take it.
So the Santa Claus that is left completely wraps his head
up in duct tape and then falls to the ground.
The lady climbing up jumps for the disco ball
that's in the middle of the room.
Misses and falls face first into,
I'm gonna say, let's see, she lands.
Oh yeah, her crumpled body lands directly
on the Santa Claus's throne.
It's like her head landed in the spot where the back
of your butt is.
So it like kind of goes into the seat,
like where you lose change and stuff.
And the rest of her body just like kind of splits
and crumbles on the sides around either arm of the chair.
The three elves, two of which are dead,
the very, oh no, sorry.
The two elves that are left take off their skates completely
and slit their own throats with their ice skates.
Blood sprays onto the ice as the elves continue laughing,
each ha overpowered by the sound of the gurgling.
And the man in the mop continues to,
and Clark looking over at the girl throwing the laptop
up in the air, you see her.
She's in my arms unconscious.
You feel her breathe out
and then not breathe back in.
Oh, who's around me right now?
Bad guys, anybody?
Everyone is dead.
I don't think there's necessarily bad guys,
but the people who cause mental harm.
We shot them like they were.
I'm the only one trying to pull over.
Oh, how can you have enough drowning out all alone?
There's nobody home, no one home, no one home.
Fly to fly to the stream.