What's good, people of the internet and the radio waves
and other people that I throw my sounds at on accident
through my vibrations and gyrations.
It's your sound wave sommelier, Wolf the dog.
I'm thrashing about live from 694.2 PTBP,
the most beloved radio station this side of the Milky Way.
Give me a scoop of that space cream.
And now, speaking of you all loving me,
today's Howlin' with Wolf is from Mistress Yachty,
who tweeted about the show and tagged at Pretending Pod.
Did you know both thumbs are explicitly built
to tweet about this show and tag at Pretending Pod?
Mistress Yachty knows, they write.
Good morrow, Wolfie, how fair ye.
I have stumbled upon a strange box
in the cellar of Duke Arthur,
out of which your lovely voice comes.
Quite strange indeed.
Nonetheless, your so-called cast of broads
is very entertaining while I weave blankets
for the coming winter.
I pray you are not one of the wolves
that come to prey on us in our dark days.
Cordially, Mistress Yachty.
Well, Mistress Yachty, I cannot guarantee
that I won't join some of those feral pups out on a hunt.
It brings me back to my less omniscient days.
But whether or not I devour you this coming winter,
I'm still glad you wrote in to us.
Toodles, Mistress Yachty, for now.
If you wanna write up something for your wolf to howl,
be like Mistress Yachty.
Tag at pretending pod on Twitter or Instagram,
tag pretending to be people on Facebook,
or write a five-star review on your podcast app of choice
and holler about it.
Wanna see what Luke looks like?
Check out our social meds.
Wanna interact with other listeners and Luke?
Check out the subreddit.
Wanna join a thriving community of absolute fucking freaks?
Check out the Discord.
Wanna listen to Wave's sick soundtrack for this show?
Check out the damn YouTubes.
And you want a PTBP shirt or hat or towel or fanny pack?
Check out the merch store.
And you wanna know where to find all those links?
Say it with me, no matter where you are.
The links are in the show notes.
And if anyone asks why you just said that out loud
to no one in particular, tell them it's time for the news.
Last time, the can crew was arrested
for the murder of the mayor of Grover's Gorge,
Sandro the Turtle.
With the trial in the gang's immediate future,
Vernon Covington, the landlord,
led the cuffed crew to the It Pit,
a horrible underground holding cell filled with a few inches
of bodily fluid mud and a specifically strange symbol
scrawled ceaselessly on its dimly lit walls.
As Vernon Covington pushed the party
through the open metal cellar doors,
Cal Colorado was able to pull the landlord along
down into the awful mess.
There, the city action news team attacked,
leaving their foe face down and still in the yucky yuck.
Of the It Pit.
Taking us now to that terrible scene.
It's Altagirl with My Life is Great and It's All My Fault.
And it's all my fault
Cause my life is great
And it's all mine
And it's all my fault
I love being in all the blood and cum.
So you guys have had a week to look over this symbol.
What do you make of it?
It looks like whoever drew it talks like this
and needs serious help.
This came out of the mind of a very disturbed child.
I was just going through some like old notebooks
from when I was a kid and came across this
and was like season two, baby.
That would be a great like a tagline for this podcast.
Made by her.
This came out of the mind of a very disturbed child.
I might've turned 30 this year, but I take it.
You're still a baby.
That's why I make a pretend to be people with my friends.
Like Thomas.
Thomas loves you when I talk like this.
Zach, I don't, but I love you.
Today at work I had to write an email
that was all about rum
and I just couldn't stop making cum jokes.
And everyone clapped.
It's crazy.
They all stood up and cheered for me.
They chanted, cum, cum, cum, cum.
I had some of the copy that I wasn't gonna put in there
was young, dumb and full of rum.
And she's like, that is so gross.
What about like rum in my mouth?
Yeah, that's actually good.
Rum in my mouth is also great.
I thought you meant like you made a movie poster
for the cum diary.
Nice.
Yeah, I really thought you were switching rum to cum.
Cum with rum, which is a little cheekier.
Cum tug tugger.
There's something there.
Yeah, cum.
It's cumbling outside, like rumbling.
Okay, let's play.
Classic.
That's how it's pretending to be people.
The vape hit in the background.
I was gonna point out on this symbol
that you mentioned that this was a hammer.
I think that could also be like a lectern
or like a music stadium.
I like that, yeah.
But it could be a hammer too,
especially with the square up there.
It just looked more like that than an upside down cross,
which is literally one of the examples.
Or if you zoom in, it's a basketball goal.
Yeah.
Because there's a little hoop.
I don't think there's any use in trying
to put any meaning into this fucking stupid scribblings.
I like to think the episode starts with the four,
no, you said stupid scribblings.
I like the episode starting with the four of you.
That's not the part I don't say about.
Just standing, like the episode starts with the four
of you just standing there, staring at the wall.
Beck, do you think it looks a little bit
like a basketball goal?
Ah, yeah, dude.
I like to think of it as a hammer.
It could be also like a music stand
or like, I don't know, man.
I think we almost killed a guy just a second ago.
Yeah, I enjoy looking at shapes and clouds,
but this is neither the time nor place.
Like I was seeing red for a second there, guys.
I'm sorry I lost my cool dudes.
I'm sorry I couldn't help.
I went somewhere else when I got in this pit.
Maybe I'm getting too old for this.
Where did you go?
In my mine palace.
Oh, what's that?
Don't you have one?
Mine's a tree house in the woods.
I have a real palace, but I mean,
it's just like a big house, I guess, like an estate,
but you have one in your mind?
Do you know how to get out of the pit?
She looks up and one of the doors is open
and she's like, well, they do normally keep that shut.
So there's potential here.
I sort of have an idea about that.
Okay.
We need to get them here, at least in my plan.
We should probably vote on it, talk it over.
I was thinking I got that clicker
that opens all the windows in that place.
Is there a clicker for these handcuffs?
Well, we should probably search this corpse, right?
Not corpse, but-
Almost lifeless body.
But this shell, yeah.
This shell of a human.
Yeah, and because Julius Summers
has his hands in front of him,
he's pretty easily able to go through and find a key
to unlock all of your handcuffs.
I use it.
Thank you, Julius, for setting us free.
Now here's my proposition.
Oh, that feels so much better.
Okay, yeah, what's up?
Stevie, we'll need your blessing for this,
but what if we just scream and yell for help?
Say he attacked us
and tried to put Faith Godel in the it pit.
Yeah, I mean, I don't wanna be stoned to death, so-
Would you not be hailed as a leader of the people?
I was gonna mention,
it seemed like you even had maybe a vendetta
against this guy.
There may be like other people who feel that way,
and this is gonna be like a,
hail Godel, the wicked landlord is dead situation.
Whoa, I didn't even think of-
Yes, a Godel come back to the people to save them
from the grip of the horrid landlord.
Okay, but I've been missing for a year.
Does that mean that they would assume
that I was down here the whole time?
We could use that?
I don't think so.
Everyone saw you.
Oh, right, duh.
Oh, shit, yeah, that's my bad.
That's true, Cal, yeah.
I think we-
I swear.
Wait, no, but they saw Stevie.
They didn't see Faith.
The problem is you look very similar.
Wait, hang on, like let your hair down.
Let's see if like you're a totally different person.
Yeah, take your glasses off.
Boing, boing, boing, boing.
Classic 90s rom-com.
Julius, put your boner away.
Now that his hands are free, he does.
Yeah, his pants got ripped open in a fight,
so he tucks it back in.
How far down did we fall into this pit?
That's a great, I was wondering that the whole time.
Is this like just deep enough
that we couldn't quite reach the top or?
No, I think it's 10 feet.
Oh, we could just-
We can just climb out.
Force ourselves out.
We need no subterfuge.
I've got the strongest base.
You guys could just hop off my shoulders.
That's true, you're like a mighty tripod.
Or do you wanna like continue with your plan though
and like it makes it look like we're like hapless
and don't wanna be.
Oh, I think it's still a good idea,
but it wouldn't be necessary for our escape.
Right, I'm saying like should we wait in this hole
for people to see us in this hole
and that we didn't like run away when they-
Oh yes, and then in that case,
we should scream and call for help
because I don't want to wait in this hole
any longer than I have to.
Just a counter argument, what if they don't care?
That is, I mean, yeah, that's kind of in Stevie's court.
Like how do you think this plan works?
On like a scale of one to 10?
Yeah, I'd call it a coin flip, honestly.
The alternative is they come back
and find us with our jailer.
Right, they're gonna see us like this either way.
I think we need a good cover story.
On a scale from one to 10, a coin flip is a five, just-
That's good to know for the future.
I don't like Zach's dick.
Do I have like, do I have my phone on me?
Yeah.
While we're just like talking about this,
Julius gets his phone out and turns the flashlight on
and looks at what's actually down here
that we couldn't see before.
How big a room are we in?
Do you want it in meters or yards?
How many of my arm spans would it take
to hit the next wall?
Oh, probably like 10.
Holy shit.
Yeah, like 20 yards by 20 yards-ish.
How many Volvos could you fit in this bag, boy?
Oh.
Like the station wagon.
Probably four.
Yeah, easily six, probably six, yeah.
Like all standing, like car edge style.
Car nose down.
Like car sardines, yeah.
Yeah, you could really shove more in there, huh?
After Julius kinda like flashes his flashlight
around a little bit, he is kind of like pushing Cal
to stand in front of one of these symbols
and he like flips over to TikTok.
Cal, do you wanna just,
I could just get like a still image
to put in the TikTok later
or do you wanna describe anything?
No, and Cal like leans down to help lift Stevie Gotel's foot
up over the pit.
I get that with the symbol in the background.
I know we're in like viscera,
but is there any remains that are more intact around here?
Is there anybody else in here?
Is this a pit that's been holding other prisoners?
So there's like 40 other, no.
There's no one else down here.
They were all cheering wildly.
Priti Press, Priti Press, Priti Press.
Oh, hey guys.
No, there's no one else down here.
And really with the viscera,
it's more of a leftovers kind of situation down here.
Great show, great show.
Just a lot of hot shirtless dudes on the cover
of down here, what?
You never watched the leftovers, did you?
Oh, I'm thinking of left behind.
Nick Cage right there on the front.
Nope, I didn't.
There's like, there's no-
Well, you nailed it.
It's hot shirtless dudes.
God's jealous.
He left them all behind.
You guys are looking around
and there are no like intact human bodies down here,
but there are seemingly pieces of body parts down here.
And as you pick through, you also,
I mean, if you're,
are you like picking through at this point or?
No, I was kind of looking for bodies that had clothing
and doing a like red or a yellow versus green kind of thing.
Oh, okay, yeah, cool.
Everybody roll search.
40 on a 70, pass.
I pass my search with a 26 on a 40.
Cool.
Cal passes with a nine.
Three passes.
Three pieces of information.
One.
Oh, we can't just make them up.
Julius.
Yeah, you each write down three things
and we'll decide which of the six are the best.
Yeah.
Yeah, so as Julius is like,
basically just like getting a full TikTok film
of what's all in here and then he stumbles on.
It's like a ear.
It's like a weird,
it's like a, oh, it's not a human ear though.
And it seems to have fur on the outside of it.
That doesn't quite narrow it down.
Does it, it's human ear shaped?
No, it is shaped like a dog or a wolf's ear
and it has been severed from the head that it was on
and it's kind of sticking out from within this
just layer of disgusting gloop that's down here.
And Beck Wilder, as you're going through,
just kind of looking around with your cell phone light,
you see that.
Or maybe the light on his camera
that he's whipped out at this point.
They took the camera away from him?
They took the camera away from him.
Oh no.
Remember they put it in a bag.
It's the worst anyway.
Right, in my mind the bag was on his back for some reason.
The camera bag was in Vernon Covington's possession
and so it is just right above you.
Outside of.
Like he set it down outside the doors.
He set it down outside the stores that he came down.
Fucked with some prisoners.
Oh, okay.
So it's just right up there.
I'm glad that.
You can smell it, Beck.
Fucker is, he's not quite dead.
Mostly dead.
Yeah, we'll see.
Yeah, we just left him face down in this muck, right?
Face up, but pretty rough.
Face up in the muck.
I turn him face down.
He says nothing at all.
He's almost dead.
He can't even freaking talk.
One day.
Little red jumpsuit apparatus just for Thomas.
And so you see Beck Wilder,
a piece of cloth actually sticking up out of the muck here.
And as you grab it, it seems to be some sort of like,
yeah, it's a jumpsuit and it's.
Is it red?
It's red.
Monochromatic.
Oh, holy shit.
Damn.
Your brain just made a connection on accident.
I wish, but it's not.
It is a monochromatic jumpsuit.
We went over this.
It's a gray scale jumpsuit, but.
Also not quite the word, but better.
It's almost a gray scale jumpsuit.
It's a gray jumpsuit with a color like a stripe.
Purple.
Oh shit, it's purple.
A third color.
And anyone.
Cal vomits like in suspense.
Anyone who's either one of you.
I got it in my notes.
The purple Jackalope, purple ribbon Jackalope Fox
removed it from that Jackalope and walked away.
We weren't supposed to see the purple ribbon.
Dang straight.
That Jackalope was supposed to die in this pit.
Hey dude, you remember that second Jackalope we saw?
It had a purple ribbon just like this.
And that Fox dude like took it off.
He was condemned to death,
perhaps for killing a frog comptroller.
That was a joke.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you got it.
That was good.
Thank you, Stevie.
Yeah, that was solid.
Stevie, what does the purple mean?
This is where they kept,
I guess they kept, I was expecting this place to be full.
This is where they kept the twenties.
The twenties?
Yeah, it's what they call them.
But yeah, everyone just kind of referred to them
as the twenties.
Did they have...
Meaning what?
Furry ears?
No, I have absolutely no idea what that's about.
That's really strange.
And as she says that, Cal, you find the matching ear.
So it's like the other ear from the one that Julius found.
And do any of you have like biology, any science,
any animal knowledge?
If not, I'll take a intelligence at like a negative 20.
I'll try that.
I'll try that too.
Cal holds the ear up close to his face
and peers into it for some whisper of its secrets.
And fails.
He drops the ear back into the book.
You said a negative 20?
Yeah.
That's a 49 on what would be a 50.
Nice.
I got a 91, so I don't win.
So they're holding up these things
and you walk up with the...
I hold the ribbon between them.
Uh-huh.
You like pop up your head in between them
and put them on either side of you.
And yeah, when Beck pops up his head,
it's very clear that, yeah, it seems to...
It's like fox ears, but they're bigger.
Yeah, like they are the ears of a fox,
but it would be a massive fox.
So you're just really leaning in
for the furry demographic this season.
Always have been.
We got fox people, folks.
It's dead.
Oh, duh.
Yeah, that's why we have its ears.
Okay, actually, because all three of you
succeeded on your rolls,
I'm gonna go ahead and give you one final thing.
So Cal, yeah, right?
Yeah, a little extra, yeah.
Because I thought of something.
Cal, with the detached fox ear in one hand,
as you pulled it out,
you see that there's actually a small piece of paper
sticking up out of this muck
where it had clearly been buried
and you might not have even found it
if you hadn't gotten the second ear,
but underneath you see this little bit
of paper sticking out.
Guys, look, paper.
I look to see what's on the paper.
No, you don't.
I'm standing right over it.
I just called your attention to it.
Yeah.
Shut the fuck up.
This is my paper.
I'm looking at it.
From across the room, Julius stares.
I dive for the paper.
I kick back in the jaw.
I read the paper.
Yeah, as you pick it up,
you're gonna have to kind of get some of the muck
and gunk off of it.
Julius, come here.
Read this nasty paper for me.
Yeah, I go over and I try to read it
after I scraped some muck off.
It's like a small business card
in the shape of a big guitar pick.
And it says the occult
and unnatural investigative journalism association.
Shout out to Intrepid T over on Discord,
one of our $10 and up patrons
over at patreon.com slash pretending pod
for giving us the occult
and unnatural investigative journalism association.
Dope.
What do you think about that, Cal?
Ouija.
What?
O-U-I-J-A.
No, that obviously spells Ouija.
Oh, yeah.
It can't be Ouija.
Before I put it together in my head,
I was like, oh, it doesn't mean anything.
So it'd be funny to say like,
Ouija.
O-U-I-J-A.
And I'm like, wait.
Do you think that Intrepid T
knew what they were doing when they wrote this?
Nope.
One of our listeners.
He looked into that.
Yeah, undoubtedly not.
A Bob Ross situation.
It's so wild he picked out that collection of words.
Did he even know?
Oh shit, this is not my, this campaign note.
This is our original campaign notebook full of notes.
What's it say?
That page wasn't very interesting.
Yeah, before we recorded, it was all pretty boring.
We went to a green box.
Nice.
Bright light and immense noise.
The dust begins to crawl, then fly.
The cave is full of lice.
The cave is full of lice is fucking horrifying sentence.
It is.
What, have you ever heard of this cow, Peck?
Well, I mean, it's, you know,
a well-known band of kooks, of course.
They investigate Bigfoot and other nonsense.
They think the moon landing never happened.
I mean, but do we like have proof, you know?
Like, did you see it?
Yes.
A nice moment of levity in a horrifying dark room
of terror and smelly nonsense.
So like, it's crazy that I'm here
to answer all these questions,
but the 20s are what we called them
because it was roughly, you know how Greg got got?
He was Greg and now he's Fox.
Right, by the mind control.
Yeah, it's kind of like mind control.
But basically when he does it,
there's probably like a 20% chance that it just,
and she points at the walls around you.
It just kind of does this to you.
It makes you a role-playing podcaster
with the mind of a child.
Essentially, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, you just talk and talk and talk,
but nothing of substance ever really comes out,
just yammering on and on about some tower,
getting God back to heaven.
It's just, they just talk and talk.
Is there any left?
I mean, I thought that we were gonna be surrounded.
I was ready for a different kind of fight, honestly,
when we got down here.
Don't worry, in a very real way, they're still with us.
Let's get out of this pit.
Yeah.
Yeah, my camera's up there, dude.
We're the fucking can news crew, guys.
Let's go get our camera.
Julius puts his back up against the wall near the hole
and puts his hands down, ready to lift people up and out.
Okay, we're gonna need a strength check on both accounts.
Each time, I'm gonna make sure Luke passes his
before you have a good shot at yours.
Fail on the first one.
29 out of 50, pass on the second one.
Should he get a plus 20 since he's lifting with his legs?
Fail on the third one.
And also, great question.
Well, what we're gonna do here-
Also, both my fails would have still failed with 20 more.
I meant plus 30.
Yes, both my fails would have still failed with a plus 30.
I got 90s and 80s.
Because you guys have time, not a ton of time,
but you do have time, whoever is last is gonna be the one
who might get stuck, and that's gonna be
the difficult place to be in.
I mean, it would be me, right?
If you were the one lifting everyone up out,
like helping everyone up out,
then you would be the last one
that they're gonna try to pull you up.
I think that's the plan, though.
So, with enough time, only 10 feet up, a wall behind you,
you're easily able to get Beck, Cal, and Stevie
up out of the it pit.
They're all three looking down at you
in this vile, disgusting, absolutely wretched,
like it's hard not to throw up while you're still down.
And we just walk away.
You can't get used to it.
To get a little higher up, I would like to sit Vernon
up against the wall and stand on his shoulders
to have a couple more feet closer to the wall.
That's fucking role playing.
That is Liam Neeson, Ra's al Ghuling,
being aware of your surroundings,
and that will get you out of here without rolling.
Hell yeah.
But we probably need to try to roll.
Should we roll to retrieve him?
That is gonna be a difficult retrieval, I believe.
Fucking leave him in there.
I think we should leave him.
I think this is the best place for him right now.
He's far away to where when he screams,
nobody might hear him,
because we're gonna shut the door behind us, for sure.
Well, we are, but also back to the potential plan.
Should we run screaming into the town now,
saying help, help, help.
As opposed to what's sneaking out of here, I guess.
Or casually strolling in and saying,
we kicked that guy's ass, fuck you.
The former does seem like the better,
if those are the only two choices.
I don't like to fool the public.
In fact, it's my stated mission to never do it.
But our very lives depend on it,
and so does the information we carry in our minds now,
and on Beck's precious camera.
Oh, as Beck just caresses.
Oh yeah, it's out of the bag and back to filming.
What if instead of either of those,
remember we were invited to a certain someone's GIZ?
Greg?
Do you think we could just go to Greg's
and see if we can't get some help?
I mean, he probably wouldn't know
what was happening with us.
If he's just at his house,
he hasn't been paying attention to anything,
so he wouldn't even know that we're heading to trial,
and she looks at her phone, and she's like,
in like half an hour.
Did we ever ask if we have cell phone reception?
I'm not sure if you did ask, but I do have to pee.
What if this whole fucking time
we could have just called 911?
I feel like we did, but I don't wanna say that we did,
in case he thinks maybe we can.
We've had fucking five bars this whole time.
We're getting texts from like, where are you?
I'm using my flashlight,
just like not looking at anything else on the screen.
Your battery is draining to nothing.
I'm gonna go with a solid, there's no way, but.
We wouldn't have had a reason to
up until we got sentenced to death,
so right now exploring that option is probably.
The giant statues are just cell towers.
That fucking 5G.
Turning everybody into freaking werefoxes.
Zach, I remember the thing that I thought of
that was maybe important, and then I forgot.
It was pretty important.
I hit a breaking point.
Oh, I had a question too for you.
Yeah, right when we got down in there, huh?
We'll do a breaking point for you now.
What was your question?
I was looking on my phone to see
what I wrote down as my phobia or whatever.
This is what I had.
I literally, Julia Summers, phobia.
Big pits of blood, flesh, and shit.
And then I looked to see if I had a different note,
and the next one was grip colon in a different note,
and I just never wrote it down.
With no number, amazing.
But I knew it was something to do with that,
and that makes sense.
Good to go.
It's from July 5th.
Grip.
Oh.
Okay, cool.
Well, let's have Luke and Thomas
take off your headphones real quick,
and Joe, let's.
Forget how we're doing it this season.
This season, we're just kinda deciding
what it's gonna be.
Oh, good, cool.
Between the two of us.
Well then, I've got a few options.
Yeah, hit me with them.
Just viscera and gore and gross gore.
Gross gore.
Like beyond just blood.
Yeah.
Or crazy designs.
I like, I.
Joe, the player, loves investigating crazy designs.
Yeah.
Or if you got something else.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that.
It was literally the fight response
was what made me, my sanity broke,
and I had a fight response,
if you want it to be fight related.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
It was the least likely thing I had put.
I rolled a one to get it.
Okay, yeah.
What about?
What about like men wearing suits?
Oh, because of the landlord, you mean?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Or like, I guess that's a little strange,
maybe, I don't know.
Or heights, you could also do heights.
Like falling?
Yeah.
But I like either of the first two
that you came up with, so I'll.
I like the ones you said, though.
I mean.
I'll defer to you.
I'm between the heights, the suit,
and the blood, because I don't.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I agree with you.
Every time we look at this diagram,
if we ever look at it again.
We'll all cut out heights.
Okay, so suits or viscera?
I mean, let's just roll for it,
because either one.
Yeah.
One, two, three is blood.
Four, five, six is the other one.
It's a four.
Okay, so men in suits.
Men wearing suits.
I mean, that's great.
That's good for Beck as a character.
I will say, as soon as we have decided that,
you're gonna need to.
Am I gonna have to fight every person in a suit?
Well, you're gonna need to work on maybe Julius and Kal.
Oh, fuck.
I forgot I was surrounded by men in suits.
Yeah, they both wear those,
and so does everyone you work with.
I was picturing just running into maybe some of the Godels.
Nope, it's everybody around me.
Ouchie, ouchie.
Shit.
So, okay, then I need to clarify with you right now,
like how extreme is this?
Is it a phobia, would you call it?
Yeah.
I'm scared of the suit.
Yeah, scared of the suit, I suppose.
Yeah.
And then if I have them remove their jackets,
would that be enough for me?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, removing of the jacket is gonna be enough.
It takes the power away.
Okay, but okay, yeah.
But okay.
I just don't know how, like, when I go.
I mean, literally, let's say as soon as you get up out
of the pit and you're looking at them for the first time,
and they're also covered in this stuff,
like he was when you attacked him,
you're gonna need them to change
how they look pretty quickly, yeah.
But it's, yeah, it's just an uncomfortable thing for me.
Like, it's not gonna make me lash out at them, per se.
No, but I think that you need
to be pretty intense about it.
Cool, yeah, I get that.
I just mean, like, if I run into my,
like, if I run into his thief, if I run into Typh,
am I gonna be angry with him?
I think you're just gonna be weird.
Exactly, that's what I mean.
Yes, weird, stilted, like, no eye contact,
not cool-ass fucking Beck like you used to be.
I'm all about it.
Women in non-binary, women in non-binary people
in suits are fine.
I dig it.
You should check the recording,
make sure we're still recording after the lights blinked.
We are still recording after the lights blinked.
Luke, you can take your ears out.
Ooh, I was making little beats, you know?
I was like, damn, I would never listen to this shit.
Man, it is.
Dude, it is going nutso.
Gettin' it out there.
You should be quiet and try and get a good take-a-one
that you can then loop whenever you need to.
Yeah.
Wow, that was a good one.
Needs to, like, hit our house.
Famous last podcast.
That was a really good one.
That was really good.
Good job, Thomas.
Thinking about thunder and lightning
brought me to thinking about Thor,
which brought me to thinking about Norse mythology,
which brought me to thinking about Neil Gaiman,
which brought me to thinking about Sandman,
anybody's favorite?
Yeah.
Thinking about Sandman,
anybody started watching that on Netflix?
I have not, but I want to.
Is it good?
I watched the first episode only, but I loved it.
I thought it was a really cool first episode
and it makes, I've never read the book,
so I'm intrigued as to what is gonna happen.
I definitely want to watch it.
I just like, when it came out, I was like,
I'm not in the mood to watch something like this
because I wanted to watch something stupid.
I wanna see it too.
Yeah, so often I just wanna watch something stupid.
Is his name Morpheus or Morby?
It's not Morbius.
I read the description and it was something like that.
Morbius sounds right,
cause he is the God of like dreams,
which is in real life, who Morbius is.
In real life?
Did Neil Gaiman quickly write the books
based off the Morbintime meme
and then they produced a show and released it?
You're thinking of The Matrix.
Maybe.
Oh, well.
Oh, Morpheus slow down the river of live streaming.
Whoa.
Yeah, Joe's eyes just went white
and he floated in the air for a second
and he said that weird shit.
I think it was a prophecy.
That's just a little Rocky Horror picture show for you.
All right.
We're all out of the hole at this point.
All four of you are out of the hole,
looking down at the slumped body
of Vernon Covington, the landlord,
which Julius Summers has just used along with your help
to get up out of the it pit.
Wow.
Did you hear that crackle in the headphones?
It was good.
That was wild.
Whoa.
Yeah, you're gonna have plenty of options
of thunder samplings.
And Beck looks up from his camera,
looks at Cal and Julius,
but with something different in his eyes.
Hey, what's up, what's up, what's up fellas?
It sure is hot today.
Boy, howdy, you guys look like you're real hot.
Would you guys want to take off your coats, please?
Is it hot in here?
Much to you, Beck.
Yeah, yeah, thanks Cal.
Julius, please.
It's covered in shit and blood.
I was planning on removing it anyway.
Yeah, there you go.
They're dirty.
That's it.
Julius is like, yeah, gross, and takes his off.
Yeah.
Yeah, cool.
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
Yeah.
Okay, so we were talking about whether we're going to
like come out all.
Yeah, whether we're going to go to Greg's GIZ
or whether we're going to come out and say like,
hey, what's up, we're back.
We're ready for our trial now, please.
Or we can get the fuck out of here.
Stevie, do the people of Grover's Gorge
know about the It Pit?
Yeah, the people of Grover's Gorge know about the It Pit.
All of them?
Yeah.
Do they know what it's like in there?
Yeah, I think they do, Cal.
Guys, I think we need to decide
what we ultimately want to do
before we go down any of these avenues, aren't we?
Yes, let's make a five-year plan.
Stevie, we were talking like in the hole,
like is there a chance that we're looked favorably upon
because of this landlord situation?
Like maybe he's an asshole and everybody was like,
thank God he's gone.
Yeah, I mean, Fred definitely won't like it
when he gets back, but we should have time hopefully
until, I mean, they definitely told him
that Sandro died.
Like they definitely told him that Sandro died, so.
Like, and he would come back for that turtle.
Yeah, so he would definitely come back for that turtle, yeah.
Was that just a turtle
or was that turtle functionally the mayor of this town?
Not functionally the mayor of this town,
but pretty importantly, the mayor of this town.
In like a community pride sense
or in some weird dark forces way.
Yeah, it's gonna be that second one.
I'm gonna sound really out of control here
while I'm talking, but just know
that this is really out there.
I did see a spirit or dark energy come out of the turtle.
Quiet, Julius.
Stevie was just about to tell us
about the spooky shit going on with the turtle.
Yeah.
No, no, that's go on.
I didn't, you saw, you saw it?
It had a, looked human almost.
It was, I mean, it sounded like it was talking too,
but not anything, not real words
or words that I could understand.
And when I saw it, I got this taste in my mouth,
just salt, salty, saline.
You saw God?
Beck's eyes are wide looking at Julius.
I, dude, like I saw like something too,
but it like wasn't that, dude.
I mean, what?
But it's God?
Yeah, I mean, I didn't.
And she kind of looks down at the ground
and is like, I kind of always thought that it wasn't real.
Like there was some other explanation for all of this,
but I'm starting to fucking freak out, man.
Stevie, Stevie, Stevie, calm down, calm down, Stevie.
Listen to me, look at me, look into my eyes.
She looks up at you.
That's not God, God is a woman.
She only loses two sanities, she's reassured by this.
No, right, that's not God, but then what is it?
Okay, but it is God because it did all this shit.
It did everything.
I mean, it's like, it's like gave him all the power.
It's like, what did you, you saw it too, Beck?
I mean, like I saw something like come out of the turtle
and like go into Chuck.
Did you see it go into Chuck?
To me, I didn't like quite see like,
it didn't look human to me exactly.
And like, I didn't hear anything
unless I didn't ask the right questions.
There's no such thing as the right questions.
I didn't like hear anything.
Dude, like to me, it was just like,
somebody like shot a super soaker
out of the turtle into Chuck.
What did you see, Cal?
Hold on, hold on, you're both talking so fast, it's crazy.
Now someone, I thought the turtle leaped to its death,
but someone shot a super soaker at it?
I mean, it looked like maybe that was what I saw.
You remember how it like leapt off the edge, right?
Yes.
So then the super soaker came out up from beneath
like where that, like where it would have
probably like impacted is what like,
I like inferred or whatever.
And it like shot up and over and like into Chuck.
The humanoid talking, tasting energy went into Chuck
and he exploded through the glass.
See, I didn't see like a humanoid thing.
I just saw like a super soaker blast, dude.
Boys, I need you to look at my fingers, please.
How many fingers am I holding up?
Five.
Yeah, I'm counting five, my dude.
Okay, I just needed to be sure
you could still be trusted with the news.
I mean like, yeah, dude, that's my biggest regret
is that I didn't film this.
I was startled.
You didn't get a date.
Remind Joe, I think I said that there was something else
that startled me at the time, right?
Well, you were shooting the deep healing that was happening.
I think even Julius grabbed your camera or something.
There was some reason that I remember
it like jostled down to the ground.
It was a failed roll, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
Yeah, like it's not there, dude.
It's not in the footage.
Fuck.
I got the aftermath,
because you remember when Chuck went through that window?
Like that was why he got pushed through that window.
Because of God, who is a turtle?
I'm not sure about the God thing.
God turtle, Godel, God, is there something in there?
God turtle.
Cal, you fucking figured it out, my dude.
God turtle, Godel, God turtle, God turtle, God turtle.
Go back, back, back.
But still.
We don't want to reveal our position just yet.
Stevie.
Yeah?
Is that why you're named Godel?
I don't think so.
You're the Godel.
I never put that together.
God turtle, God turtle, God turtle.
Let's mark that hypothesis as a maybe.
No potential.
I mean, it's probably ancient times
they've been worshiping the Godel turtle.
Turtle, turtle, God total, God total.
It's ancient, man.
God damn it, that does follow linguistic principles.
It makes sense.
Stevie, like maybe you're figuring this out
for the first time.
Yeah, I think we cracked the code here, dude.
I think we did, I think we figured it all out.
This is amazing.
Either way, we have to get out of here.
And here it's Godel's all the way down.
Oh my God.
Total, total.
Do we have enough incriminating footage
and usable, good quality television to leave?
I mean, I got a bunch of footage of that viscera pit,
like that's, nobody's supposed to have like that
on their property.
If we can even leave,
it might be time to start preparing our defense.
Stevie, do you think you could get us out of here?
If we stay, I can try.
And if we leave, I'll try to help.
Should we stay or should we go?
Now, we have to decide.
Personally, my vote is stay and risk our lives
for great programming.
If we stay, there could be trouble.
Yeah.
So, do you know what my uncle will say?
There could be double, dude.
There could be double.
Why would your uncle say that?
Yeah, why would he get upset because we're alive?
The same reason I'm getting upset
thinking about leaving this place.
Which is what, you're not done getting your fucking story?
You're willing to risk all of our lives for it?
Precisely.
Oh.
Yeah, I mean, I-
We have the story, Julius.
But I'm sure there's more.
There's a real part of Beck
that is a little bit Julius in here,
that this is footage that nobody's ever seen before.
What else could we maybe get?
I mean, guys, this is the story of the century.
Only if we get it out of here.
But the more we get, it could be its own canned show.
Screw episodes, dude.
We could do a whole documentary special
and you'd win the Pulitzer for this, dude.
I feel like I've lost some grip here.
This is a very bad idea.
Beck, you should know, this is a very bad idea.
No, yeah, for sure, for sure, for sure.
Cal, you know how in your house you've got
pictures of you with famous people?
You could be one of those people
that people have pictures of in their house.
I am one of those people, Julius.
Do you wanna be one of those people?
Because you won't if you die here.
And I won't if I leave with all we have.
With this amazing footage we already have,
we have a treasure and you are getting greedy for more.
I am.
And I won't follow you to this death.
Julius just looks at Beck.
Beck does, part of him really still wanna stay in film,
but I mean, I guess this place isn't going anywhere.
Like, could we come back with maybe like?
We can come back with.
A bigger crew or whatever?
An armed federal escort.
We will report on this place when it is raided
by the federal government.
What we have now is enough to make that happen.
Julius just kind of nods his head.
He absolutely still would like to stay and shoot more,
but he knows that this is a team
and that he has basically been outvoted
and so he's not gonna argue anymore.
Okay, the best way getting out of here
is gonna be around the back of this factory
and then we're gonna get into the trees.
We're gonna take the tree line
all the way to the big plant wall.
We're gonna have our fucking teeth in that wall
as we just crouch and kind of shuffle our way
as quietly and as smoothly as possible.
Across this plant wall all the way to the door.
Possibly like walking, like you're sitting.
I think that that would probably keep us
out of the view of the most people.
Kal is like silently composing a personnel complaint.
Julius is a little bit happier knowing that he can leave
with at least a cool escape TikTok.
Is she suggesting further east?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So just further east, just straight into the forest
is where she pointed, like straight into this tree line,
this thick tree line that's on the far east side
and then going as far south as possible,
like staying in the trees the entire way
down to the plant wall and then walking across the plant wall
over on the south side that you came in
and finding that door and then getting out.
The door that we came in.
The door that you came in.
So we're going east into the woods
and then south using the woods as cover.
Got it, got it.
Is there anywhere we could raid a supply closet
or something for extra onesies?
I like the green ones myself.
The green ones would be in the lab
or in the super nice GIZs.
It is not important, just the nearest ones.
Yeah, I mean those would be here in the factory
but I think we're risking a lot by trying to go in there.
That'd be like a whole other episode probably.
Where are the GIZs to here?
All the way across, like on the far other side,
like the full west side or like the green,
like all the EEs live on the super far west side.
Did they leave some of their EE cummings in that pit?
Oh, thank God.
Yeah, there was punctuation fucking everywhere.
Oh, it fucking influenced so many terrible Instagram poets.
I like the ones where they grab that newspaper
and black out a bunch of words
and just leave some of them that make a poem.
I haven't seen that.
That's kind of nice.
That's fun.
I like the one where this guy takes a piece of bologna
and pokes a bunch of holes in it
and then slaps it on a page and then that's the poem.
Do you think he'd poke the holes first or afterward?
Well, some of them don't work.
So I think he just does it.
That's how you know.
I definitely thought you were just riffing that.
No, it's a thing I've seen.
Well, I've seen a guy take bologna and poke holes in it.
I was like, oh, that's good.
What's mine gonna be?
Yeah.
This footage now from Beck's camera
is like when you're watching a documentary
and shit hits the fan and it pans around
and you see the boom operator is rolling out.
You guys are in front of me and it's hazard.
It's shaky cam.
It's some Blair Witch Cloverfield.
Going through the woods.
Oh, and these woods are pretty intense.
We all look a little panicked.
People do not traipse through these woods.
So it is thick brush.
Is Julia still almost dead?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's at two hit points.
So literally he's barely breathing.
He's able to make all these points and stuff,
but he mostly got hit in the face.
My head, I am bruised eyeballs.
Internal brain hemorrhaging probably.
Oh, that explains it.
Yeah, it's not.
I'm gonna die of a blood clot
and we don't get any help soon.
You look over at Julius and one of his eyes
is completely filled with blood
and it's starting to drip from the wrong corner,
like not from his tear duct.
This crazed half dead man who can barely walk
is like, we gotta stay here.
Yeah.
Exactly.
And Cal, for some reason,
like argued it in a good face
instead of just being like, no, you idiot.
Like, do you?
We need to kill you.
What?
You could like push him over and kill him.
Yeah, like.
There's a 50-50 chance that a punch would kill him.
Or, you know.
I can't punch him.
It's actually a 66% chance now that I think about it
because it's D4 minus one.
Wait, so nope, that's, fuck.
That'd be 33% chance.
That's 50-50 if it's a D4 minus one.
But I have two.
Yeah.
Oh, so one, yeah, you're right.
Fuck.
Anyway, don't punch me.
Julius with his brain not working as well right now.
I'll take a minute.
It's a weird one.
This would be a really bad place to drive a four-wheeler.
I don't understand the reference.
Julius doesn't either.
He's, his brain's just starting to shut off.
Stevie pats you on the back.
She's like, it's okay, grandpa, we're almost out.
What else do we see?
Oh, shit, I mean, oh no.
He's Frank Gotthold.
Ah, fuck, Julius Gotthold.
I mean, Caesar, I mean.
I mean, fuck.
Oh yeah, we're walking.
We finally get to the big plant wall.
And okay, guys, it's shimmying time.
This is when Julius pulled his phone out to.
Shimmy, shimmy, y'all, shimmy, y'all, shimmy.
I'm gonna get in behind and TikTok them walking
however they're gonna be walking.
Yep, not being weird about it.
This is the point where we need to be really sneaky.
So I need everyone to roll stealth.
40 on a 40.
Wow.
You got a 65 on a 40.
I'm sorry, a 30.
Fail.
I only have 10% in stealth.
And I got a three.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
I thought that I would just kind of give an alertness check
for just like all of Grover's gorge.
And Luke, will you check out what I rolled there?
He rolled a 100.
Oh, fuck yeah.
So they are all taking a big long blink.
Literally in my head, I was like, what do I give them?
Like 80% as an entire city?
Like for someone to see.
We're only in part of the city and the part
that's best to hide in.
Well, then it's a great thing for everyone
that I rolled a 100 just now.
Holy shit.
As you guys hit the door,
creak it open and take one last look out at Grover's gorge.
You all actually notice why all the residents
are not paying you any mind.
You see Chuck Bidwell, bright blue eyes,
face lined by the sun,
topped by a tight flat top of salt and pepper hair stocky,
the muscle of his youth turned fat.
And Chuck Bidwell wearing his green polo
is absolutely drenched, wet, soaking
as he walks through Grover's gorge.
You grab the door, close it shut.
Click on the other side.
And you guys are standing,
looking out at the massive gorge
that you saw when you arrived.
Fog is filling up this enormous gorge.
And you see that the train,
the single steel train car is sitting
on your side of the gorge.
Just how it was the last time you were here.
Cal sees Julius tick-tocking all of this.
And he says, Julius, put that fucking phone away
and get on the train.
Julius gets up flush with the train
and is gonna tick-tock you guys walking into the train
and then get in the train.
And he saves it in drafts
with his six other tick-tocks he's taken
since he's been here.
Cal takes a big like stress bite out of his lasagna.
What's up everybody?
I'm Zach.
And I hope you're enjoying season two
of Pretending to Be People so far.
We're having a ton of fun.
And that fun isn't going to stop,
but it is gonna slow down a bit.
Putting the show out mostly weekly
for almost three years now has been my pleasure.
And I'm tired.
It's been affecting my mood for the past month or six,
which sucks.
And I want this show to continue to be a pleasure to create.
And I don't want the quality of the show to suffer.
So in order for that to happen,
we're going to move
to an every other Friday release schedule.
Now the goal is to get back to weekly episodes.
So I've reached out to someone who can help lighten my load
on the editing side of things
by cleaning up the tracks of debris
before I finish them off.
But that process will take time to smooth out
and it will expedite the process,
but it'll still take time and money.
So with our eyes set on getting back to weekly,
we've got two new Patreon goals.
The first is at $5,785,
which is of course $69,420 over the year.
At this first goal,
pretending to be people will move
from every other Friday releases
to three episodes per month,
dropped on the first, 11th, and 21st.
The Patreon goal to go back to weekly releases
is set at, you guessed it, $6,942 per month.
And when we hit the PTBP radio frequency,
we'll be once again swaddled
in Wolf's warm and weekly embrace.
But with the sad news,
I also bring three fun announcements.
First, we recently recorded another side story
for season two,
and we had another mind-blowingly talented guest.
Becca Scott joined us for a four episode
modern Delta Green operation set in the city.
She was fantastic.
We were fantastic.
I'm seriously, I'm so excited for y'all to hear it.
It's nasty.
Second, the Den of Sin will be live on Tuesday, October 25th
for a very special Halloween episode.
We'll be following Clark Bishop, John Lee Pettymore III,
and Keith Vigna as kids at Clinkers Daycare
as they go trick or treating in contention
on what could not so canonically
be their last Halloween ever.
And the edited podcast episode of that game
will be out before the November Den of Sin,
which is the third and final cool thing.
And November Thomas is going to kick off
his Oops All Pettymore's Patreon campaign
with a Pettymore family Thanksgiving.
Joe, Luke, and I will all be playing members of the fam
for the run, and we are really fucking excited about it.
Okay, seriously, thank you so much for listening.
This is a wildly cool thing to be a part of,
and I really hope it continues to be fun,
and rad, and sick, and twisted, because I like it.
["My Life Is Great"]
But it is a little gummy, you know?
If you wadded it up, it'd be...
No, it's a very long gummy.
But it's thin.
You can only fold a fruit by the foot
on itself eight times before.
Oh my God, is that true?
Yeah.
I think it needs a square, right?
Yeah, any loser.
Make them fold eight times.
If you fold a fucking nerd.
And I say, hey, do you want to see how much I can bend you?
Did it just lightning?
Shut up, nerd.