Happy holy days, my friends and my families.
Me, Wolf the dog, and my dog, Wolf the dog,
are wishing you a happy one live from 694.2 PTBP,
the holiest and jolliest station
this side of the northern pole.
My producer also sends his eternal love
through a mix of wild vibrations and chatterings.
What a fun dude.
And speaking of fun dudes,
this year howling with Wolf is from Curtis
and his friend Jared, both in St. Louis.
Curtis tweeted about the show and tagged at Pretending Pod,
the merriest and most cheerful act of giving
outside of ripping a hole in the corner
of a grease-filled diner dumpster
and squeezing that big old nasty metal box
like a piping bag until the sludge slips and slides
right into Wolf's gaping inscrutable maw.
Mm, baby.
But the tweet thing is pretty good too.
Curtis writes, hello Wolf, master of grease,
time travel, trash, and dumpster grease.
First off, thank you for all the new songs you always bring
and for continuing to keep us up to date
on the continual and confusing adventures
of the Contention PD and City News crew.
My friend who's listened to all the episodes
made sure to ask you not to spoil anything for me
like the Christmas episodes,
the fate of Jack Russell's soft, velvety eye bags,
or the Contention Creek Critter Coalition, or the turtle.
Stay frosty and fuck the zuck.
Well, damn, thanks, Curtis.
I appreciate that you acknowledge
that I am the master of both grease and dumpster grease,
two different food groups that I use
for very different reasons.
And Curtis, stay greasy.
Now, if you wanna write up something
for your jolly wolf to how, it's real simple.
Post about pretending to be people on the internet
and tag at PretendingPod, or write up a five-star review
in the podcast app of your choice.
Screenshot that stunning work of art
and get that proof in front of my eyeballs
so that I may provide you with your just rewards.
Your reward of putting words in wolf's mouth
is just a few taps of the fingers away.
Those taps go on links, and the links,
the links are in the show notes.
Quick reminder, we're taking new
and upgrading Patreon subscriptions.
We're matching them and we're donating the total
to a crisis cold weather shelter
in the PTBP Boys' hometown of Springfield, Missouri.
Join the Patreon and you'll get fun rewards
like exclusive merch, access to behind-the-scenes live video
of the Patreon recording sessions in the Den of Sin,
the ability to submit an NPC and location
to be used in the show,
and a confidential audio feed with 38 bonus episodes.
Coming later this month, the first episode
of Thomas' Oops All Petty Mores arc.
You're gonna wanna hear the boys
make their way back to contention.
And since we're raising money this month
to help folks stay warm,
we're combining this thing with a raffle.
Every five bucks subbed or upped on Patreon
gets you an entry to the raffle.
At the end of December,
we'll randomly select three winners.
The first two will receive a PTBP shirt
with the design of their choice from the merch store
or the Patreon exclusive options,
including the new season two Patreon exclusive designs
that will be announced at the end of this month.
And that third winner of the raffle can also have a shirt.
Oh, and they will be invited to play in a one-shot homebrew
written and run by Zach,
alongside Joe, Luke, and Thomas as their fellow players.
So if you want to maybe get a shirt
or play at the PTBP virtual table,
join up before December is over.
Time's running out, baby.
But I am not running out of time,
for time is merely a tool at my disposal.
Mm, I love two things in this here world.
A good bout of disposing.
And the news.
Last time, our assumed heroes showed
some actually unbelievable footage to their editor,
Vivica, perhaps breaking her mind.
And then Kurt, the red-eye siren chaser,
showed up with some wild footage
of a new weather phenomenon.
Absolutely exhausted and spent,
Julius Summers headed to the hospital
while Beck and Cal made their way back to Cal's
to check on Stevie and Greg Fox god-goddle.
But they found neither of the god-goddle's siblings,
and the bindings that tied down the wet god-goddle
had been cut by scissors.
Beck Wilder and Cal Colorado sped on empty tanks
to Bean's Bridge to assess the scene after that
seemingly god-caused freak weather incident
from Kurt's footage.
Too tired to succeed, but too driven to hit the brakes,
Cal maneuvered past the police barricades
and taken us now to a better view
of Bean's Bridge's new, unnaturally smooth hole.
It's Alter Girl with My Life is Great,
and it's all mine, all.
Oh.
What is that?
The noise.
Yeah.
That's part of why I was making that face,
because I was like, if there's a noise,
just say it so we don't have to do this.
But what is it?
The timer for the lights.
Oh.
It's just that it's not a digital one,
it's just literally this mechanical thing
that's just like, so I can absolutely just unplug that.
I didn't notice it, and I bet you it's the kind of thing
that the 30 seconds of silence would cancel out.
It will cancel out.
Sorry, what did you say?
I couldn't hear it over the enormously loud clicking
in my ears.
It's episode 19 of Pretending to be People.
Wham, wham, wham, wham, wham, wham, wham, wham, wham,
wham, wham, wham, wham, wham, wham, wham, season two.
Season two.
Episode 19.
Whoa.
COVID-19.
You know what that reminds me of?
19, nine one, nine 11.
Welcome to the numerology episode
of Presenting to be People.
I crashed my Scion TC at 100 miles an hour.
I crashed my Scion TC.
I don't care, it's numbers.
So Taylor and I were at Ramatai eating lunch the other day
and we went inside and there was the loudest conversation
happening right behind us.
We were the only two groups of people eating
in this tiny living room converted
into a restaurant dining room.
And this loud, loud conversation,
the first sentence that I heard was one young gentleman
college age asked the other young gentleman college age,
what is it about your actions and behavior
make you think you're not an incel?
Oh damn, so it's-
Incelvention?
Yes, it was an incelvention.
Incelvention are just like bullying
and it's the same dynamic as the guys
in White Lotus season two.
They're just still in college.
Yes, it's essentially that,
well, and after the whole thing went down.
The fish, but the one guy wouldn't let the other one have it.
At one point in time, he's like,
you're obsessed with women.
And the guy was like, I'm not obsessed with women,
I'm obsessed with beauty.
And then he's like, don't you think it's not okay
to say things to girls that make them uncomfortable?
And his response to that was, I say things that move me.
They also don't like your skin suits that you wear.
At one point in time, I thought the conversation
was sort of veering into a like,
oh, he actually said, do you understand
that this is serial killer behavior?
What?
He was like, you're messaging these girls repeatedly,
they're not responding to you in their DMs
and you continue to message them.
And he's like, I don't send them questions,
I send them things.
You don't have to respond to things.
Oh no.
No, this is not good.
He's like, when people send me things,
I don't always respond to them.
It's pretty cool.
They were peers, they were the same age.
They seemed to be the same age, yeah.
Much older women in nursing homes.
Okay, they don't respond because some of them
are physically incapable of moving their thumbs.
I was wondering if it was maybe like a dad
having a talk with his son.
Oh no, that would have felt more appropriate.
I was on the side of the antagonist.
I really thought you were about to say the incel.
I was on the side of the incel.
I too am obsessed with beauty, sir.
You should see my campaigns, they're quite beautiful
if dark.
The aggressor was like,
what would Jesus think of your behavior?
Yeah, the guy who was like-
Is that what it's called in an intervention?
It will be in mine.
And if all of you were aggressors,
we'd get out of my house.
It's offensive defense.
Oh no, I'm feeling really suppressed right now.
Y'all are some suppressive people,
and me and the drugs are gonna stay right here.
So it did end eventually with,
actually Taylor got up as we were leaving,
walked over to their table and said,
after we witnessed both servers
coming in and out of this room,
like looking over tentatively every single time,
Taylor went over and was like,
hey, everyone can hear your conversation,
it's making everyone uncomfortable.
And then everyone clapped.
We raised her up in a chair, carried her out,
we got to keep the chair.
I went back to Ramatai a week later,
because I love Ramatai.
They were still having the conversation.
Makes sense.
Is this guy just like a series of copy pastas you read?
Copy pasta.
Is that how you say that?
No, it's not, you say copy pasta.
You could have gotten me.
Yeah, you're a jiff.
Yeah, I would have gotten your jiff ass.
All right, fuck you, get out of the room,
we're role playing, you're in the hospital.
I'm still not playing yet?
Yeah, I know, it sucks.
We're about to play you,
but first of all- For two fucking hit points?
Maybe you shouldn't have gotten the shit kicked out of you.
Joe and I have written up pretty extensive backstories
for your critical care team that we're gonna be playing.
That's what I was doing outside.
I was on nurse talk to see good tips
on patient health care.
Well, let's get this going.
Thanks for telling me it wasn't me in Ramatai.
I'm glad you kept that to yourself.
You're fine with Thomas knowing.
I'm sad.
So, did they look like peers?
I'm like, well, they look about the same age.
Thanks for not telling about me dressing down my dad.
Okay, no lie though, I could see your dad saying,
I say things that move me.
He wouldn't be talking about the same kinds of things
this boy was saying, but.
We're standing at a hole.
Standing at a hole in the middle of a bridge.
So, and you'll remember from the footage
that it did seem to close up in the footage that you saw.
I didn't remember that from the footage.
Yeah, I didn't remember that at all.
It had left a giant hole
and that's why the tugboat was swirling.
So, the tugboat swirled down along with its barge behind it,
but then after some time of the swirling,
after the tugboat and barge disappeared,
it's almost like it got stopped up.
I thought it got equalized.
I thought enough water had rushed in.
Gotcha, okay.
So, now the river is flowing normally,
but there's still a hole in the bridge
that people are very curious about.
Oh, I thought that's what you meant got closed up.
No, the hole in the water.
Oh, okay.
The hole in the bridge is still there.
Yep. Gotcha.
That's the hole we're looking for, man.
That's the money hole.
Oh, boy.
Did you guys follow that at home?
Beck, get a good shot of this big money hole.
Big money, big money, big money.
I'm shooting the hole over the edge.
Yeah, I haven't described it this episode.
It is on the Beans Bridge,
which is the nearest bridge
from Cal Colorado's home through downtown.
And at the end of this bridge, nearest downtown,
there is a hole the size of a revolving door
from a shopping mall in the middle of this bridge.
And it is unnaturally smooth on the sides
where the hole has been ripped through this bridge.
Around this hole, there are countless city, county,
federal, state employees all coming around,
looking at it with their own different
sort of operational awarenesses and their own skills
and trying to figure out what happened here.
It is clearly a multi-agency task force.
Nailed it. Nice.
I'm getting some B-roll of the sides of the hole
because I think you mentioned they were smooth.
You were getting some of that B-roll.
And then at the end of our last episode,
the end of episode 18,
we saw Cal Colorado with a glint in his eye,
wink at the camera, move one of the barricades,
and make his way past onto the bridge and toward the hole.
Follow me Beckwith.
This is Cal Colorado City Action News,
and we're gonna get you the real story here tonight.
He B-lines it for,
you said there were like people in suits?
Yeah, there were people in suits.
Do they?
People in police officer uniforms,
people in like hazmat suits,
people in all sorts of different gear.
Who looks to be the most in charge?
Oh, there is a woman who is wearing a black suit
and people seem to be walking over to her
and keeping her abreast of the situation.
And she's kind of like on her phone
and talking to people and then pushing them off.
Keeping an eye on her for now,
Cal like looking into the camera, like gestures.
Come here, come here, come here.
And we go straight up to the hole.
Get this Beck, get this.
Look at this now.
Show the people what we've got here.
Let's go ahead and roll law.
Whichever one of you has the highest law.
And this is again at a negative 40.
I've got 40.
Oh, I've also got 40.
Did you crit?
No.
Me neither.
Nice.
Immediately upon you hitting the hole,
stepping up to it, a police officer walks over.
Get up.
It's just the Muppet, he can't hurt us.
Gentlemen, what are you doing?
Gentlemen, what are you up to this evening?
Cal Colorado officer, city action news.
And you see that line over there, about that there?
Of course, of course.
And he's pointing over at the barricade
where you just came from.
This is bigger than the line
that we're showing the people what's really going on here.
Get this Beck, get this.
Sir, would you consent to being interviewed
and telling us a little bit
about what's going on here tonight?
Hands behind the back or bodies behind the barrier.
Okay, I understand.
We start backing away towards the people who are in charge.
Yes, we're heading back to the barrier, officer.
I understand, I understand.
Thank you very much.
You are absolutely going the wrong way there.
We're diagonally, our friends are over there
kind of towards the other side of the barrier that way.
So we are heading towards the barrier,
but diagonally in this kind of direction
that also sort of takes us through the center
of the rest of the things over here.
At this point, you're backing into the woman.
Cal Colorado, city action news.
I put the microphone in her face.
Get this, get this, get this.
She puts her hand up to the camera
and she's like, no, thank you.
Your laptop screen light actually makes it look
like you've got a camera light in your face.
Blocking it away.
No, thank you.
So sultry.
Yes, get away from me.
Cal did not say so sultry.
I was like, that was my comment on your vocal choice.
Well, in that case, Zach says, oh, hey, thanks.
Nice.
I'm playing him a little manic,
like how wild would it be if.
I mean, you're like, it's 4.30 in the morning
and it's bad.
Cal takes a huge fucking gamut
and he says, Cal Colorado, city action news.
Do you know me?
And he winks.
Yeah, roll charisma.
Negative 40.
That's a fail.
Would have actually passed 8,385, but.
I don't give a damn who you are.
Back up behind the border.
And the guy comes up behind you and he's like,
that's right.
I said, keep it moving.
Okay.
And it's got hands on you now.
He's like, what did I just say?
Can we get somebody else over here?
Hands behind her back or behind the barrier.
We got it.
Cal failed your role.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah, I understand.
I understand.
Did the woman with the sultry voice
have any kind of identification on her?
Whether it's a name badge or something on her jacket.
Also, is she age appropriate to Cal Colorado?
Yes.
And she says, I don't give a fuck who you are.
And it's like a powerful peer of Cal Colorado's.
He's a little taken.
Is Beck taken too?
The sequel.
So you would notice that there is a tattoo on her hand,
the hand that she put up.
I zoom in on it.
To put in front of the camera.
And it is like the tail.
It's like a tail that's scaly.
That's running up out of her cuff.
Scaly like a rat tail?
No.
Like a dragon tail.
How close to a dragon than a rat?
A dragon rat.
And it just kind of creeps up out of the cuff
from under her suit jacket.
And I just realized she's wearing a suit.
And so as you back up,
what is Beck's reaction to this whole situation?
Oh yeah.
The whole time he's been walking through here,
he's been sweating bullets.
You've noticed that his eyes been
kind of darting back and forth.
And he's kind of been keeping his head down
like strictly into the viewfinder,
pointed directly at you.
And then when I bumped into her,
I was probably backing up and bumped into her
and saw her and I probably,
the camera jostled really bad.
And you saw me start to turn around
and walk toward the barricade like strongly.
And then remember, oh shit, I've got a job.
And I got, I'm pretty far away now
using a zoom to get you guys in frame.
As the officer approaches them,
he's like, I'm sorry officer, I'm sorry.
And he immediately turns away
and you kind of see like a sheepish boyish grin on his face.
And with the waters of the city river raging below you,
the sounds of the lapping waves hitting the rocks below.
The two of you kind of headed off
back on the other side of the barrier.
It's about 4.30 in the morning.
The haze of sunlight is kind of growing off in the distance,
even though it's still quite dark out.
So with all of my stats, negative 40,
I think Beck then is feeling that
and would just look at you
with just the most bloodshot and hang dog eyes.
I don't know if we're gonna be able to find anybody
tonight, like I'm about to just drop on the ground, man.
What do you mean?
Are you not, I mean, I'm so,
I'm taken up in the work right now.
What a day we've had.
We've got to go to the foundry.
We've got to have some drinks at the foundry.
I'm buying.
Come on.
Cal, I can't do it, Cal.
Well, you want to go back to your mom's sad apartment?
I was gonna ask if I could crash at your place,
but it sounds like you're still going out.
So I'll just sleep in the van
and I'll meet you in the morning.
I'll be right in front.
Okay, no, no, no.
We'll go have drinks at my place.
We'll have some drinks at my place.
Come on, let's go back to my place.
Yeah, yeah, we'll go back to your place and then.
It's just like hanging out with Thomas.
Go to sleep.
Hey, I was trying to explore that subtly
through character work.
I was trying to exaggerate it, but I guess, I don't know.
I liked it.
If it was me, I'm ready to go to the foundry.
I know, but other people aren't.
Something I've learned
and I'm trying to express through my character,
Cal, Colorado, who hasn't learned it.
What are you guys doing after this, by the way?
But yeah, I said I'm going back.
Yeah, we get back there.
All right, I'm just gonna crash in the van
and I'll see you in the morning, man.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, Beck, Beck, Beck.
I insist.
I've got seven bedrooms in this home.
You will take one.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, if you're talking about sleeping, yeah.
I am, and Stevie's gonna come back.
I mean, well, you know, we're gonna probably,
I've got some pretty nice whiskey.
Hey, do you, speaking of her coming back,
do you have security cameras?
Like A, could we see when they left?
And B, like get a notification if they come back?
I get all these notifications from the Ring app
and I don't know what to do with them.
I, maybe you can find something relevant in here.
Let me see that, let me see that.
I'm looking at the hours after we left
and seeing if we get any footage of them leaving.
Did you see Stevie and God come and go like seven times
like they go to the fucking bodega.
They are holding pizza.
Yeah.
Arms full of snackies.
They walk away the first time, they come back,
they walk away with $1,500 in their arms in cash.
They come back with pizza.
A little too many, like feed too many red peppers
and God goes crazy.
The app wasn't downloaded on Cal's phone.
Like it had been long enough that he'd clicked on it,
that it wasn't downloaded.
So you click download on it
and as it's finishing up the, oh man, you're asleep.
I see Beck just like passed out on the couch with my phone
and I like pluck it out of his hands,
like plug it in a charger,
walk off with the two glasses of whiskey
I've just poured for me and Beck.
I throw one down my gullet and walk upstairs to my bedroom,
pass dozens of pictures of Cal's career
from the seventies on to today.
And he downs the second glass, brushes his teeth,
gets in like some silk pajamas
and slips into a pretty fucking nice bed set.
This sounds lovely.
I'm warm and soft.
Just in case either one of you are wondering.
Yeah, we know, you're a soft little bitch.
Now I'm hard.
What was that?
You're broken.
You said broken.
I broke and I couldn't breathe.
Can that man not breathe every time he laughs?
He's like a human bug.
Oh my God.
You had wake apnea.
Oh man.
Okay, cool.
We dropped so many balls today, man.
I was like, I can't see a way in character
to get Vivica from just stop her from walking away from here.
We didn't really try that hard to go find Stevie and God.
I mean, like I said, mechanically and what,
because of mechanically what Beck would be feeling,
he just wouldn't be able to.
He just couldn't.
I feel like we could have deployed some energy drink.
Yeah, I mean, I had it coursing through my veins.
I figured that had already been taken into account.
Energy drink coursing through my veins.
Yeah, I think just with the day that you guys have all had
hitting that 5 a.m. spot,
I was just going to be like, nah.
What are we at on recording time?
Nothing.
I have not clicked record yet.
Cool.
I think we can really nail it in the second take
and lose all that mindless bullshit.
Now we're going to double down on the soft bitch stuff.
Go back, go back.
Find anything that really cut anybody deep.
Double down.
Should we bring Luke in?
Yeah, let's get Luke back.
So he doesn't...
Luke!
We got Luke a boy.
I'm back.
They sent me outside.
How was it?
I watched TikTok videos.
Yeah?
It was nice.
Did you have a good time?
Yeah, but I'm glad to be back.
Yeah, back in the hospital.
Beep.
Oh, thank God he's alive and the camera zooms in
and sees that Julius Summers is out cold.
I'm just kidding.
Do whatever you want.
It's zoomed in on the monitor, the heart monitor,
and it's going beep, beep, beep.
Boop.
And then it pans over to Julius,
who has come to from his not very restful night of sleep,
and he's got to pee.
So he's disconnecting that shit.
Okay, it's disconnected.
That's not what happens when you have to pee.
My heart stops and I have to pee.
Right, it's just disconnected because he's got to go pee.
Go ahead and roll a con times five for me
and that'll see whether you get your natural healing
of one hit point back for the eve.
37 on a 50.
Nice.
So take one more hit point of health.
And what does that bring you up to?
Seven?
Six.
Six?
Lovely.
Nurse comes in, puts your TV on,
and you see the same thing that Kurt showed you,
but it's all over the news.
And there's footage from all sorts of different angles,
but you do think that Kurt's footage might be the best
of anything that you're seeing flash before your eyes
on cable news here?
Did it break on can?
Hard to remember.
Don't really care.
How does it make you feel?
Scared.
But you're okay.
You can handle it?
This?
This.
It's some sort of weather tornado they're saying.
Tornado lightning.
That's what they're saying?
Yeah.
Keep believing that.
I've got to pee.
That's what I'm here to help with.
I can handle it.
I can handle it too.
Julius doesn't like this nurse and then looks to see,
does she have a badge on?
No, she doesn't work here.
It's just some wild person roaming the halls.
I hit the call a nurse button and then go pee real quick.
And I get back in bed and wait for the nurse.
When the nurse comes in, he's like, what's up?
There's some lady roaming the halls trying to scare people.
Did you see this?
And he points up at the TV.
Oh, yeah, what's going to happen next?
Global warming, right?
Right.
So you think it's weather?
Yeah, lightning tornado, is that what they're calling it?
Yeah.
So watch the evening news tonight, just so you know.
Anyway, how am I doing here?
Yeah, I mean, everything looks fine.
You're going to be in pain for four to six weeks at least.
You're going to want to stay on the medicine for,
hopefully not too long, but you got to take it when you need it.
Don't be a hero.
You'll have some serious pain in the face for a while.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
But yeah, besides that, you should be fine.
No severe broken tissue.
You're going to look the same after a while.
Thank you very much, and would like to be discharged, please.
Do you need a wheelchair?
Julius wants to send the nurse out while he gets dressed in his clothes and stuff.
Sure.
But he also wants to search around for any sharp objects in the room.
Oh, they don't like to keep those around in hospital rooms typically.
Yeah, but how good are the doctors here?
Not that great apparently.
So what are you looking for?
Something to maybe try to cut part of my face off.
Oh my God, dude. Fuck.
Because the pee didn't take that long, but Julius staring into the mirror in the bathroom,
that was like a solid 10 minutes.
Roll luck 50-50.
You roll under 50, you find something sharp.
Although I guess it should be the other way around.
I rolled under 50.
Okay.
Yeah, you see there is a pair of shears, a pair of scissors that is in one of the cabinet drawers.
And it's the kind with the plastic grip. It's not super sharp scissors.
Julius figures this is probably the best place to do this.
And he's going to go in the bathroom and try to poke the scissors right at his jaw.
Yeah.
And poke them through and try to cut.
He's not going to go full face, but he's going to see at least,
he's pretty sure underneath is like what he's actually supposed to be.
So he's just going to remove that first fake layer.
How much?
Like the right cheek.
The whole right cheek?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Okay, roll grip to go through with this.
I guess he doesn't have to poke through. He can just start at the corner of his mouth.
I'm going to make you roll grip to see if you can follow through with this. This is disgusting.
21 out of 25.
Oh, yeah. No, you're not going to be able to do this.
Oh, because I passed.
Yeah, you passed.
As one half of the scissors is in my mouth and the other half is on the outside of my cheek,
I'm about to cut through.
Nurse walks in and says, oh.
Julius kind of like snaps and like shakes his head and just lets the nurse take the scissors.
And thank you. I guess I'll go.
And Julius wants to just kind of like go past the nurse and try to leave the hospital.
He fucking crit failed his grip check seeing you do that and just stands there, frozen,
staring at the most awful, confusing thing he's seen.
I mean, he just, you shininged him.
He like walked past the door and saw you in there with the scissors inside of your like skin and mouth.
Like you were putting butter underneath the chicken skin on fucking Thanksgiving.
Is he like completely blocking the doorway?
No, no, no, no. You just walk right past him.
Yeah, I just kind of squeeze around him.
I pat him on the back and say, thanks.
And I look at his badge.
Darren.
Thanks, Darren. Thank you. Bye.
And I'm going to start heading towards the exit of the hospital and give Cal a call.
Yeah, absolutely.
And we'll bring those two back.
Bird, bird time.
As I'm leaving the hospital, I call Cal.
Yeah, let's get a little early morning pickup here from the Colorado home.
Yeah, you were in for a while.
You had a full rest.
I was watching the noon o'clock news, right?
Yeah.
So we're talking noon thirty.
Oh, God.
Oh, hello. Hello. Cal, Colorado. Good afternoon.
Hey, Cal, it's Julius. I just got out of the hospital.
Julius Summers. How are you?
Well, they discharged me from the hospital and a clean bill of health.
I guess I wouldn't really go back to that hospital if I had the choice.
Oh, which hospital?
It was St. Luke's Children's Hospital.
Well, now I've had several fine procedures at St. Luke's.
The procedures they gave me were all too small.
I'm sorry, I just woke up. I don't understand at all what you mean.
Well, where should I go?
Luke, what are your max hit points?
Max is ten.
Perfect. On a scale of one to ten, how would you say you feel?
Oh, like twenty percent better.
I'm sixty right now.
Okay. Well, you know, we all had a rough night. I feel like I'm about a sixty-two.
Curious. Cal and Beck, are the two of you down any hit points?
Oh, yeah.
Okay, so you can actually roll a constitution check to regain a hit point of natural healing with overnight sleep.
I don't have Cal as having lost any hit points.
That makes sense to me.
I did not pass my con check.
Bummer.
He slept on the shitty basement couch where God was supposed to be.
That's unsettling.
God fucked it up in the escape, so it's all... your back is just, like, shitty this morning.
Should I come over or go to work? What happened?
Wow, Julius, I'm still kind of coming around here.
Why don't you head over, I'll put some coffee on, and we'll all discuss our next steps around the dinner table. How does that sound?
Great, I'll jog over.
He's got to exercise.
Yeah, that's close.
Beck, what's the wake up situation?
I wouldn't wake up unless you did something to wake me up.
Oh, yeah, remember the intro scene to Beck Wilder.
Face down, tighty whities up, that's the way he likes to sleep in.
Cal doesn't do anything in particular, but he is loudly whistling, and at a few points, like, definitely running from room to room as he grabs different things,
and he's kind of excited and preparing, like, yeah, we're going to have coffee and then we're going to plan our Pulitzer Day, part two.
So, yeah, you would hear him running up and down stairs and stuff, and he's a big enough guy that it's booming through the house.
You hear one stir from the couch.
No, mom, I don't want to walk a dog. It's not my dog.
Oh!
You hear the, like, the basement door creak open, and Cal peeks his head and he says, Beck, Beck, good morning.
Coffee's on in five. Get on up here.
Get on up here.
Yeah, okay, I'll be right up.
We've got to find Stevie and God.
Yeah, big day.
Julius is coming over.
Is he all right?
Oh, uh, 60 percent?
All right, good enough.
That's what I said.
All right, I'll be up in a sec.
Nothing some coffee can't fix.
Julius opens the front door, a little sweaty.
Who the fuck is that?
Got any water?
Oh, he's got some very well-made lattes, each with a little, like, news van in it.
He's like, oh, yeah, yeah.
Those are great.
You can have some water.
Julius takes one and then sips it and has a little milk froth mustache.
I saw the news broke. I saw God on TV.
Cal drops the tray.
What do you mean our news broke?
I turn it to can on his TV, and magically that is on.
You can do magic?
That story is...
I turn the TV on and it's like they're interested.
You turn the TV on and it's in Cal, Colorado's house, so it's on can.
And can is currently covering this exclusively.
They're just about to intro the whole story on can, so it's perfect timing.
Becca's walking up now, up to the back of the couch, into frame.
They're running. What are they running? They're running.
Is it ours?
It's Daddy's. Kurt's. Kurt's footage.
Okay, with our pickup from last night?
Would you have been able to send that in?
Yeah, we sent that in, Link.
I think you have to take it to the station.
The rules of the universe, as we've established, seems like we would have to take it.
I figured we'd run it as an evening news segment, but that was breaking news because people know about it.
People saw it, as far as the logistics of Julius' thoughts went.
When Kurt's footage ends, you see the can studio.
Isabella Kaya back with this absolutely staggering story here on City Action News.
I mean, for those of us watching at home who have never seen Lightning Tornado before,
it can be scary, but I'm being told from those scientists who we love listening to here at can
that there is absolutely nothing to be afraid of.
Isabella Kaya, City Action News.
Kaya was like, didn't they see our footage?
It's not a lightning tornado, it's God! That's God, you idiots!
Everybody at the hospital just thought it was a lightning tornado.
That's stupid!
It's what they're telling him.
Wait, maybe we could spin this as a positive. Now we'll be able to answer all the questions.
Instinctively, Beckwilder reaches his hand in his pocket for the thumb drive that he copied all the footage onto,
and he flashbacks to the moment that Vivica-
Put that kick me sign on me.
Put that kick me sign on you.
She stole it.
And you reach the bottom of your pocket and your heart sinks.
Beck, what's wrong?
You're right, Beck. We can just say teasers that's like the crazy tornado that happened.
We'll just tune into can and we'll tell you what it's all about.
Beck, what's wrong?
Let's get that footage over to the station.
Look at his face, Julius.
Yeah, the footage, it's on the thumb drive. Remember the thumb drive?
Yeah.
And I put it into this pocket and that pocket is empty.
Check your other pocket.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And I check another pocket, and I check another pocket.
Check.
And I check another pocket, and I check another pocket.
Your coat.
And I check another pocket.
Check the fucking camera, Beck. Check the can van.
Yeah, Vivian took the drive. She had to have.
Vivica, she had to have.
When would Vivica have taken the drive?
When she put that hilarious sign on his back.
Oh, we've got to find Vivica.
We've got to find Vivica, we've got to find Stevie, we've got to find our footage.
All we have is your TikToks, Julius.
Julius, like, kind of perks up and then goes to post another TikTok.
I posted the Jackalope one yesterday.
Yep.
Guys, which one should I do?
I don't know what you have.
Didn't we have footage of the medical device, maybe? Was that something?
Yeah, I'll do that, of them healing up your wound.
Yeah.
He posts that.
Do that.
And while it's doing it, he puts, like, the sound that would be in a St. Jude's commercial,
he puts that in the background as the sound and uploads it.
Good edit.
We've got to find Vivica.
We've got to find Stevie and God.
We've got to find out what the fuck is going on at Cannes and where our footage is.
I'm going to call Cannes.
Bec, do you feel comfortable?
Can you hunt down Vivica?
Yeah.
Do you know her?
Of course. I've got to get my footage back, dude.
You don't think she got rid of it, right?
Julius, can you get a hold of your uncle or go to his home?
I call Tyfe.
Boing, boing.
Julius.
Uncle.
My guy.
Uncle Tyfe.
We've got good news.
Yeah? Well, I am, like-
Well, and bad news.
Tell him we've got questions.
What are you doing? Why weren't you answering my calls yesterday?
I'm fucking hungry for good news.
You're going to give me some good news? I love that.
We've got crazy footage, but we lost it.
Well, like I said, we hungry.
All right, tell me about this footage.
Grover's Gorge. Have you heard of it?
Forget about it. Cut. What are you talking about?
We followed that anonymous tip and it led us to Grover's Gorge,
which is a hidden utopia that's ran by the-
Dystopia.
The Godel company.
It's a utopia?
It's run by the Godel company?
That's amazing.
It's nice, but it's bad.
It was an anonymous tip? What was it?
It was just a pin in the middle of nowhere.
Just a pin? Who was assigning all the-
I mean, I assume it was Isabella who assigned you all the stories?
She did a bang up job. She's good.
She's all right. She's the best.
Well, we've got to find Vivica. Are you at work?
Yeah, I'm in the office.
Is Vivica there?
I don't know. I'm upstairs.
Can you check?
Let me slack her real quick.
Oh, it says she's working from home.
Did you-
I get on the slack channel and add Vivica?
What's up?
Oh, no buy? No buy for your uncle?
I am doing that with him still on the phone.
Uncle type, yeah.
When I talk to Vivica, we'll bring you the footage and show it to you, but it's big.
Well, if it makes the Godel company look great, that's fantastic, you know?
They were really haranguing us about that last story.
It got crazy there, but you know, this is going to be great.
Good job, Julius.
Oh, you're going to be on top so soon if you keep it up like this, my guy.
Are you working all week?
You're taking a vacation this week, right?
What?
I thought you told me.
You're taking the week off.
No, just a day.
Just a day.
Had a meeting down at the city, city tower.
Well, you sound like you could get some rest.
Whoa, is that a burn?
Is that a sick burn?
Did I get got?
I don't know.
I'll talk to you later.
I've got to find Vivica.
Bye.
Beep.
I couldn't help but hear like some of that over the receiver.
Guys, we can't show my uncle the footage.
He said as long as it makes the Godel company look good, then he'll be happy.
We can't show it to him.
We've got to find a way to run it without it going past him.
He said only good news for the Godel...
Fuck.
He said...
He threatened you?
He said only good news for the Godel company.
I mean, he didn't threaten me, but...
He threatened the truth.
He threatened the news.
Basically, yeah.
I mean, has my uncle always been like this?
Not in my experience.
Julius, I haven't felt like this since 1983.
What happened in 1983?
That was a personal matter.
But it is the closest to truth and justice I've ever truly come.
And you see a flashback to Cal spending a summer following his brother around
and catching him in this elaborate lie about a Christmas gift.
Beck, do you know where Vivica lives?
You've worked with her closely for so long.
Yeah, I know the neighborhood.
I dropped her off two or three times over the years.
I think I could find it.
Roll intelligence.
Oh my God, it's a 70 on a 70.
Yeah.
Ooh!
Our smiles.
Good boy.
Yeah, I know exactly.
I could take you right there.
Yeah.
Totally, dude.
I think we've got to go get this shit from Vivica.
We've got to get our fucking footage.
We've got to get the footage.
Vivica has our Pulitzer.
I didn't go through all of that shit just to get the footage stolen by some fucking
editor.
Vivica's good, though.
Maybe she just is doing touch-ups at home and forgot to-
You saw her face yesterday, Beck.
She's not just doing touch-ups.
That footage is in danger.
We've got to get to her, guys.
Vivica taught us an important lesson, which is that this footage is more powerful than
even we suspected.
We know we've got something here, but we need to be a little more careful with it,
and to that end, we have to secure it immediately.
Guys, we've got to get this footage from Vivica.
Vivica, if the news is like music, these pieces are The Beatles.
That's what I've always said, dude.
Yeah.
The Beatles were very popular when I was a schoolboy, and-
They're still popular.
I just want to say I resented them at the time, but I do understand their appeal.
Let's go, boys.
I met them once.
You can tell us about it on the way there, Cal.
I figure that's what he says as we're walking out the door.
Cal, you never told me.
You met the fucking Beatles, dude?
That's the coolest fucking shit I've ever heard.
As we're walking out, Cal points to several pictures, like three pictures with the Beatles
at different stages of their career when he's a kid, and then finally in their 70s crazy
phase, one is him as a teenager reporter, and then multiple pictures of him with John
Lennon up to a point, Paul McCartney, George Harrison, and he shows you some extensive
correspondence with Ringo.
You got this last one in under the wire.
He stopped taking mail, famously stopped taking mail recently.
Not for friends.
Nice.
We play chess by mail.
Across the pond, it takes forever.
Why are we wasting time?
Get in the van.
No, wait.
Who else?
Beck, you've never shown any interest in my pictures before now.
I had never noticed that that was George Harrison there that you're sitting on the bench with.
Who else haunts these halls?
I'm kidding.
I figured this was happening in the van.
Definitely happening in the van.
Is it that one?
There it is right there.
The van is lined with pictures too.
Some of the choicer ones.
Vivica has a pretty cool place above a bodega on the corner.
A bodega?
I thought you said bodega, which would be really fun.
She lives above a place called Bodega.
They sell bidets and bagels.
Bodega.
The sign has the water shooting through a doughnut, a bagel hole.
It is also just a standard bodega with a cat, but it's also bodega.
It's bodega.
No, it's clearly not.
Julius really wants to stop in, but knows that there's no time.
Yeah, and her door is just off to the side.
Beck, you would know that when you open up the door, it just immediately stares on the other side,
so you'd have to buzz up, but the last time you were here, the buzzer didn't work.
Now I'm just picturing your old apartment.
They have to run down and meet us?
Well, we hit the buzzer.
It is July 6th. It's about 1pm.
It's a hot day. The sun is shining down.
It's a Wednesday. Less kids on the street than usual, and the ones that you do see, you're like,
It's Wednesday.
There's the urchins.
Cal remembers, and it's weird that he and Beck didn't remember before now,
but he remembers that they successfully downloaded the Ring app,
and that it'll have all the footage from last night.
Oh yeah.
Hold on, boys. Before we go in, let's take a moment to watch what came in and out of the front door last night.
Of here?
No, of my place. Remember how God and Stevie escaped?
Yeah, you guys haven't talked about that much.
Well, you know, we went to the bridge last night, and then we slept in, and it was at a chance since then.
Yeah, I mean, I figured when I saw Kurt's footage that, I mean, I knew that Stevie and God weren't gonna be at your apartment anymore.
So what, did you find anything?
God is everywhere, Julius.
Did you find anything?
We found evidence that Stevie may have let Fox out of his bindings.
And so we went and just, like, did a cursory check at the bridge, but we were both beat, so we didn't get much there.
But then I realized that maybe Cal has security cameras, and sure enough, he does.
So I downloaded the app last night, and I didn't get a chance to look at it.
Let's watch it.
That is a wild sound.
Yeah, there's a bunch of owls going crazy outside.
Is that what that is?
Yeah, take your headphone out.
They're like, shut up, Zach's listening now.
I thought somebody's, like, phone or something.
Yeah, I thought it was his phone.
That was nuts.
What were we doing? Oh, yeah.
The app.
The app, I downloaded the app.
Yeah, the Ring app.
Let's see what happened.
For just $4.99 a month, you can subscribe to Ring.
In grainy black and white.
Get the premium.
No, it's a Ring camera, it's not grainy black and white for sure.
Oh, but it's nighttime.
It's a Ring camera, which is a high quality camera.
Yeah, but it's nighttime.
It's the only camera I would buy to secure my house.
Where can you pick one up?
Amazon is where I got mine. You can get them directly from Ring.com.
We're not allowed to have separate deals, you rat.
So what do we see in, like, the...
So hit those show notes for a link to the Ring camera.
They're both in on it.
Available at Target.
Thank you.
We see high quality black and white.
Yeah, because it's nighttime.
Yeah, but it's high quality, it's not grainy.
Because it's Ring camera at Ring.com.
While Beck is pulling up the footage, I'm ordering a bedagel.
Wow, that app looks so user friendly.
With just a few simple tabs, I can see who's at the front door.
Let's tab away.
Yes, one plain bagel please and one everything bidet.
Suddenly, you see Stevie walk out the front door, followed by Greg Godle.
She holds the door open as Greg passes her and heads down to the front yard.
Stevie closes the door, notices the Ring camera.
Oh.
Everyone roll humit.
I thought she was here and I was like, I don't know why she's here, but I'm excited.
Oh my god, that's why you were waving?
I was going to offer her a bagel.
Oh my god.
What am I rolling?
Humid.
I passed 24 on 70.
I failed a 93 on a 40.
Yeah, Cal fails.
I also got a 93.
Ooh, spooky.
Cal's looking at all the features of his everything bidet on the box.
Cover your ears real quick, Thomas and Joe.
Luke, something in their face.
When Stevie turns back, you see Shane.
So like I can tell from the footage it doesn't look like she's doing it completely against her will.
That's right.
That's exactly right.
And you two see the face of Stevie turn back.
They look at the camera and they turn back away and head off into the street.
The Ring camera footage is so high quality you can see the shame on Stevie's face.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't getting that from this footage.
What did you see?
Look.
Rewind it.
She's not making her do it.
She's doing it on her own but she knows.
Look.
She sees it right there.
She sees the camera.
She just looks ashamed.
I think she looks gassy.
I mean, could be.
Shame gas.
But I mean, Godel's not forcing her to do this.
It is her brother after all.
I mean, she was pretty forward with the idea that she was trying to help him.
Maybe this isn't all bad.
Maybe he talked her into this but she has a plan.
She wouldn't let him jump off of something.
She doesn't want her brother to die.
Could she stop him?
Yeah.
Even if she was on the way to somewhere she thought might help.
She's Trixie.
She might have something up her sleeve.
No, she's Stevie.
Oh, shit.
Trixie was kind of the burnout in turn.
The one with the vape pen.
I assume the buzzer.
Guys, I don't think the buzzer's working here.
We gotta find Vivica.
We gotta find Stevie.
Her window's that one.
Hang on a sec.
And I'm trying to find a pebble to throw at the window.
Oh, yeah.
There's plenty of pebbles.
Tink.
Vivica!
Vivica, it's back!
Is the door that leads up to the stairs a wooden door or a glass door?
What was it, Joe?
It was a glass door.
No, it wasn't.
If you're talking about my old apartment, it had a glass pane that you could see through.
On the outside it did.
Yeah, like the downstairs one.
What?
How tall?
You could see into the stairwell.
It had lettering on the window up to my apartment you could see through.
Interesting.
It said, Joe Terry, private eye.
Very much like that.
Dangerous dames turn around.
He had legs.
Two of them.
Guys, watch out.
They were walking all over me.
He could see through me like the glass door at the bottom of my apartment stairs.
Joe's apartment.
So yeah, you can kind of see, you can see the top of the stairs kind of through the glass,
but then there's the rest of the door is composite.
Guys, we gotta get in there.
And he hikes up his fancy work shorts and is going to try to kick this door in down.
I'm normally not a fan of property damage, but we don't know that our coworker is safe
right now.
Got those big powerful legs.
We should use them.
At the exact moment that you rear back on one of your enormous thighs, one of the...
Rear back on like he rocks the floor.
Yeah.
Eat some fucking spinach and one of them gets like Popeye-age.
One of the botanical employees walks out and goes to light a cigarette and as they're
about to light up, they look over at you as your leg is like up in the air about to kick
and their mouth just kind of drops.
But the cigarette sticks to their lip because it was dry.
Julia says, watch this and kicks.
Wow.
A plus 20 on strength or criminology, whichever one's higher.
Strength or criminology?
Yeah.
Let's see.
I don't think I have any criminology.
Nope.
Okay.
Let's see.
Up and down.
50-50.
With a plus 20 because...
Okay.
12 on a 70 then.
Oh.
Rocking.
Little did Julius know the door was just a little bit ajar.
So when he kicks it, it kicks hard and like smashes into the wall.
It looks like he kicked it open, like forced it open, but it was just gonna happen anyway.
Whoa.
Dude.
What the fuck?
Cal Colorado City Action News, step aside.
No persuing.
That's hilarious.
Did he roll the crit fail?
29.
I pass.
The cigarette trembling, still stuck on his lip as he just like quivers and backs up.
And he's just like going to light his cigarette in front of him, but the cigarette's not there
as he just kind of backs away.
Cal pushes everybody through and after they're up the stairs, I turn around and I'm like,
don't hassle my people again.
He goes, yes, sir.
Good boy.
Which apartment is hers?
I don't know.
Kick down all the doors.
We do know, right?
Yes, Beck Wilder does know.
I mean, in the fiction, I said I dropped her off.
But you said that's her window.
You did point at her window, you creep.
Okay, yeah.
It would be this one back here.
That's my favorite rock.
In the fiction, I said I dropped her off.
I didn't tell you that I'd gone around the back and know exactly where she lives.
I actually rented a place across the street with a good view.
Let me see, if I'm parked over there, then that would make it...
Is it this one?
And there's a doormat that just says Vivica on it.
Welcome to Vivica's place, the editor.
Julius wants to knock very aggressively on the door.
Vivica, give us our shit back!
Vivica?
Cowcall her out of here with Beck and Julius.
Hey, I'm here. I'm here.
We just want to talk.
Zach leaned away from the mic.
He's not gonna...
Yeah, like a toddler refusing to be fed.
Julius is gonna...
Go away!
Okay.
Wink.
You should open the door, though, for the next people to come in.
Great idea.
We'll get plumber's jumpsuits.
And fake mustaches.
Vivica, it's back.
Look, I know that you think you're maybe doing something good, and maybe you are.
Hey, are you just in there editing the footage with another pass like we talked about, maybe?
We just realized that the footage wasn't on us, and we figured maybe you had it,
and we want to make sure that we get backups.
Vivica, I haven't felt this way about a story in nearly 30 years,
and I think that caused me to be fairly short-sighted about showing you what was really on there.
So I want to say, I'm sorry. We're sorry.
We're really sorry, Vivica.
Would you let us in to talk about it?
The door opens.
Vivica stands in front of you, eyes red.
She has been through hell since the last time you saw her,
and she is trying so hard not to burst into tears again.
I was going to delete the...
I was going to delete...
I took the thumb drive, I'm sure that you yelled, I understand.
It was pretty funny, the sign.
I was going to... which sign?
Kick me?
She laughs a little bit.
There's the Vivica we all know.
Okay, yeah, thank you.
So I had a plan. I was going to take the footage, I was going to bring it back here,
I was going to figure out what to do with it, I was going to talk to people,
I was going to figure it out, I was going to talk to people,
I was going to let you in on it too, but we were high energy
and you guys seemed so gung-ho about getting it out
and I didn't want to get it out because I'm scared to get it out
because it's scary and terrifying and I needed to tell somebody else
and I needed to get somebody else's opinion.
So I decided to go wait and hide in the parking lot until after you all left
and then I went back into the building and I was going to go delete all the footage.
I wasn't going to delete it, but I was going to bring it back here
and I was always going to have the edit, but wait, let me fucking finish.
Cops came and they took it. The cops fucking took it all.
Why? They weren't even in uniform, they just came in and they took it
and where were you? You weren't there. No one was there.
And I couldn't do anything.
Did they take the thumb drive?
Yeah.
Can I hear a bit of that?
Yawn.
Yawning.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can I hear a bit of that?
Zach doesn't seem like he's taking this very seriously.
Better throw out a yawn.
Great, great show.
Yeah, good stuff, Zach.
This is great, this is great.
This is not like it when I yell at him.
It's late, I'm sleepy.
I thought it was fun when you yelled at me.
I just thought you sounded insincere when you said that last thing,
so I want to be human.
I don't remember what it was, but what did you roll?
It was about them taking the thumb drive.
Oh, the thumb drive.
Oh, okay, yeah, yeah.
Ooh, 24, a pass.
Yeah, no, she seems sincere.
You said they weren't in uniform, how do you know they were cops?
Came out of a cop car, went back into a cop car, showed me a badge, had guns.
Not nice.
Did you see a name?
It oinks like a pig.
Were the badges City Police Department?
Yeah.
I'm looking at the other guys, why would the police even know about it,
let alone want to come and get it?
Why would they want the footage like that?
Do you have a ring camera?
They got it from the...
At the office?
At the office, not here.
Does the office have a ring camera?
I'd assume the office has...
A lot of cameras.
We can see if these guys are real cops, what kind of car they pulled up in.
So Vivica, you're saying though that at the end of the day,
you don't have any of the footage at all?
You weren't able to maybe sneak some?
Maybe pulled out a hard drive or...
Just a sneaky little...
Her eyes go like blank.
I'm talking like my good friend, Ringo.
I tried to sneak some, but no, I didn't get any of them.
Sounds like it could be God all demons we're working with.
God all demons?
God turtle?
Yeah, like people, you know, God all sending people out to grab the stuff.
Maybe not actual demons, but who knows?
Let's go look at that footage and we've got to find...
We've got to find it.
We can't let them have it.
Cal has had like kind of an unworried little smirk on his face this whole time.
Guys, I'm sorry here, but it's in the hands of the police.
It's perfectly safe.
Cops like me.
Yucky ducky.
Cal answers the phone and you hear explosions and like screams in the background.
And he's like, Oh God, Julius, think, think, fuck, you're out of the hospital.
We got a big situation going on here with Stevie and God.
Got to go.
Peep.
What do you do?
Cal's call.
You get like, you see a call coming back like Cal, Colorado.
I answer it.
I'm sorry.
I forgot to tell you.
I'm dropping a pin.
I know how to do that now.
Click.
I wait for the pin and how far away is it?
How far away is the pin?
Like how far from the hospital is his apartment?
He gave me until noon to imagine what Cal, Colorado had gotten up to with his day.
Oh.
And I imagined we got another pic of it.
I thought it was real.
Yeah, it was all nonsense.
He's been asleep.
You wake him up.
Yeah, I think that's fair.
So you would have the footage on the drives that the camera records the footage onto the drives.
And then you take the drives to work, load them onto the computer.
You tell me how to do my job?
Cause my life is great.
Oh, that reminds me.
I already backed it up to the cloud.
We're good.
Oh, sweet.
I'm going to make pancakes.
Cool.
As you pull out your phone and look at the cloud and it's like...
It's raining.
Oh, it's not there.
Well, that's so weird.
No, no, no, Zach.
I'm sorry.
The end of music episode already started playing.
We are not there yet.
End of music episode.
The day the music died.
The end of music episode.
Yeah, that is some fucking dark ass shit.
And then Cthulhu comes out and he steals music.
Do you want to sing a sad song about it?
You can't, nerd.
Cut to a child's birthday party.
Happy birthday to you.
You're putting too much stank on it.
It's still like a third of a song.
Putting too much stank on it is my Spotify party playlist.
In the morning, Thomas was putting too much stank on it.
It's How Far is Heaven a hundred times.
Julius runs back down and sticks his head out and says,
put that on your bagel and smear it and then runs back up.
And he's like, Julius is like, fucking nailed it, yes.
And it's all my fault.