Welcome, y'all,
to the raddest, baddest radio show in the city.
The time is sometime.
The day is July 6, 2022,
a day that may or may not be important.
Who even knows anymore?
And the host is I, Wolf the Dog.
Oooooooowwwwwwww!
I hallett, y'all,
so y'all will hallett me.
This hallettin' with Wolf is from Wren,
AKA Trash Bandicoot, in Manchester, UK.
They tweeted about the show and tagged
at Pretending Pod, a thing you should do too.
Be like the Trash Bandicoot.
You know you have it within.
Wren writes,
Hey, Wolfie.
I've been writing this email since 25 slash 09
slash 2002 too.
That's the 25th of September for you contentioners.
Time's a fuckin' lie, and ADHD is a wild ride.
I just wanna reiterate whatever Mads wrote
in season two, episode 10.
How dare they beat me to thanking Cameron
for introducing the Neo Scum Discord to PTBP
and introducing me to Mayday Roleplay and Penumbra Pod.
You've improved my life,
and I can't wait for you to ruin it.
Neo Scum good, love hugs and kisses, Wren.
Well, damn, thanks to Wren for writing a thing
for me to read.
I don't know what all these random words are
that you made me say, but I'm happy
they seem to make you happy, I think.
If you wanna write up something for your wolf to how,
tag at PretendingPod on Twitter,
tag at PretendingPod on Instagram,
and tag PretendingToBePeople on Facebook,
or write up a five-star review on the podcast app
of your choice and get it in front
of these here hairy wolf eyeballs.
And while we're at it, can I get a quick fuck Elon Musk
from the people in a car or bus or other wheeled vehicle?
And can I get a fuck Mark Zuckerberg from people at work
or from people just sitting in a coffee shop
waiting for their coffee?
And if you're not in a car or bus or other wheeled vehicle
or at work or a quiet coffee shop, congratulations.
Y'all just won the opportunity
to support this show financially
over at patreon.com slash pretending pod.
There you'll find bonus content,
the chance to name a PTBP NPC or location,
BTS live streams, exclusive merch, and more.
And guess where the links are?
Do it.
Guess.
No, like out loud, come on, don't be shy now.
Say it with me, y'all.
The links are in the show notes.
Where even are the show notes?
Have you ever seen them?
Are they even real?
Have the show notes been reported on?
Because it ain't real if it ain't on the news.
Last time, after a quick flashback to fill in a time gap,
Julius Summers went a tad off the map
and revealed that he's strapped when he pop, pop,
popped a couple of gops
and the brother of the wife of his pops.
And SG, Stevie Godel, revealed the plan
to blackmail their dad with the footage they were acquiring
from officers Richard Riley and Wilson Wiley,
who are new on the Godel payroll and easily swayed
by the daughter of the great Fred Godel himself.
The main issue, seemingly,
is that Julius just thinks he's a bit wet
instead of covered in blood and viscera.
Taking us now to a pearl of a scene
that would make a weaker wolf hurl
and scream for a bowl of curdled cream,
it's altar girl with my life is great
and it's all my fault.
And it's all my fault
Cause my life is great
And it's all my
And it's all my fault
All right, so Thomas and Joe, you both got luck then.
Yeah.
You can see it from my shiny luck token here.
Look at there.
Why don't you flick that in the air for me?
Oh, that's nice.
Joe, how about you?
No, no, no, wait, wait.
Whoa, wow, that was good.
I liked it.
Let's go.
You guys wanna go?
You were just, okay.
You were just taking the temperature
as far as the luck is.
Sorry.
Luca.
It's impossible to explain that joke.
Luca reached over the entire table.
It was very funny.
Oh, it was the, it's four 20 everybody.
Wow.
This is the energy we're bringing to the four 20.
It's the day where you smoke weed and don't ask for help.
That might be an issue for the gang tonight.
Can you guys, can you let me in?
Let's set the scene real quick.
You guys are on the Northeast corner
in a downtown intersection of the city.
You're just Northeast of the Natcher Hole.
You're in a parking lot.
You are sitting in Cal Colorado's white Mercedes C-Class.
Nice car.
Thanks, you're the one who told us it was nice.
And Julius Summers just pulled up.
Cal Colorado, Beck Wilder and Stevie
were in the Cadillac there
and in the Mercedes C-Class there.
Come on.
Who would ever say that?
What is this?
Ants.
A car that you all don't recognize pulls up.
It's a car driven by Jeremy, the intern who-
Classic character.
Everyone loves him.
He's very, very rattled at all times.
What's he sound like?
His eyes are super wide, that's for sure.
And Julius, oh, you're getting out of the car.
Okay, oh, thank God, oh, thank God.
And we're just sitting in Jeremy's car for a second
after Julius has left and he breathes
for seemingly the first time in a while.
And this is where we leave you
as Jeremy slowly starts pulling out
of the parking spot next to you.
I wave my hands in the air and get behind his car
or not like where I could be hit,
but I'm like, Jeremy, Jeremy, Jeremy, hold up, hold up.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, Julius sees Cal waving
and he like slaps Jeremy's car to get his attention.
It pulls back into the spot.
I go up to the front window
and I like motion for him to roll it down.
Do you think they can hear us?
You mean the other two?
Julius is like standing right there like watching this.
Julius, could you go help Beck
with a weird fungal problem that he has on his body?
No.
Well, he needs someone to vent about to it
and I'm tired of hearing it.
Could you just go be a friend
and listen to him for a minute, over there?
Well, can you unlock your car and I'll hop in?
It's really important that you talk to Beck
about his embarrassing skin problem.
Where are you at?
Am I in the car still?
I don't remember if I got out or not.
I think we ended with-
I think plausibly you could be like standing
outside the passenger seat watching this go on.
Episodes start in different places all the time.
Yeah, that's true.
The reason I clarify though is because
Stevie was doing weird shit.
I don't know if I want to-
Stevie is still in the car, yes.
So you can just roll down the window and talk to him.
That's what I'll do.
Roll down my passenger window.
I'll stick my head in Cal's car.
And I'm kind of grossed out by that, right?
He's covered from head to toe.
Oh, absolutely.
Cal shouts, hey Beck Beck,
don't let him stick his head in the car.
Yeah, Julius, yeah, covered in blood and brain matter.
His nose is bleeding and you can see a shoulder,
like a gunshot in his shoulder.
Jesus, is it healed?
Like, has it been attended to medically?
It happened less than an hour ago.
It happened so fast.
It happened, how long did it take me to get from can to-
Very little time.
Jeremy drove very quickly.
So speaking to Jeremy, Cal's like, okay,
I don't think Julius is in much position to relay-
Headphones, boys.
What's going on here?
So as quickly as possible,
can you tell me what the fuck happened?
Yeah, get the fuck out.
I love you.
Bye.
Wait, but, oh, nevermind.
Okay.
Okay, so we hear gunshots, multiple gunshots
and nobody went in, obviously, but we called the cops
and Julius came out of Type's office with blood all over me.
And over and over and over and over, beep, beep, beep, beep.
And then he just came out and then everyone was taking
videos and photos and it was so sad and it was just like,
he's just like, he's got a gun on him and he's dangerous.
He killed the high-freaking.
If he looks up, he would see that Cal has been filming
this all on his phone.
Yeah, no, he's in no state to try to roll there.
I don't know what to do.
He told me to drive him to you guys
and he knew where you were.
And so I drove him because, you know, gun and murder
and he's covered in blood and he thinks he's just wet.
Wow, yes.
Who kills their uncle?
Who shoots anyone?
Wait, what?
It's too early to speculate, but Type may not have been
the man you thought he was, if what you thought he was
was a good man.
Cal, that is not the reaction that I was expecting from you.
Well, Jeremy, unfortunately.
You're saying that the victim was a bad guy?
Well, yes, I think objectively.
He was a bad man who did not care about the news.
He was ill-suited for his position.
I'm not happy he died, but Jeremy,
big things are going on today, strange things.
We have reason to believe Type was involved
with corrupt police officers.
That doesn't mean, that doesn't, oh.
Working for the Godel Corporation,
they stole our footage of the most insane news story
that I have ever personally covered.
Type was a part of them, Julius is now too.
I guess we already were, but we need your help.
No, no, I'm not fucking, wait.
Roll persuade. Yeah, I was like,
I'm so sorry, I meant to persuade you
that we need your help.
He's gonna pass with a 16.
This is contested?
Yeah.
I pass with a 67.
Oh, you done got him.
No, absolutely not.
My duty is to the news,
cause I'm an intern and I don't work for money,
I work for truth.
Yes, that's right.
Cal is like, tears are in his eyes
and he's swelling with pride.
And he says, God damn it, Jeremy.
Yeah.
That's what I'm fucking talking about.
That's what I'm talking about.
Beck, you might wanna get away from Julius.
All right, let's get him back.
That was fun.
Thomas, if you could walk out real quick.
Yeah.
The TV looks at Julius's blood-covered head
that is through the window and without missing a beat,
Julius, what the fuck happened?
And I need you back to roll a grip check
for this face being so close to you.
This man being so uninterested in his own...
I failed.
Bodily health.
That's a 91.
I need my other character sheet.
That's hilarious.
Hey, while you're doing that, Beck.
Yeah.
Joe, if you could roll a grip check for me and fail.
And now if you could roll a...
Did you fail?
If you could roll a nothing, you just lose one.
Lose one grip as this face is just inching near you.
You were like...
Utterly grossed out just because it's blood and viscera.
But then I see that there's maybe a bullet wound
in the shoulder and I'm like,
oh fuck, this could be a mortal wound.
He could be dying in front of me.
Holy shit.
Julius, my dude, I think you're bleeding out, dude.
Julius looks down at it.
I mean, I told you, I just got wet.
I mean, I'll dry off, it's fine.
I mean, I think you will dry off eventually
because of death.
There's no more to be coming out, yeah.
Julius is literally looking like,
what the fuck are you talking about?
Luke, how many hit points do you have?
Two.
I sneeze and headbutt.
Oh shit.
Julius dies.
I'm gonna put my hand past his head and pound on the roof
and Carol, we gotta get him to a hospital.
At that exact moment,
he is yelling something equally loud at you.
Which was what?
I believe he said, Beck.
Yeah.
Oh, Thomas.
Tommy.
Tommy Pickles.
Tommy Pickles was the first Tommy
that popped into my head too.
Really?
For sure though.
Beck, Beck, get away from him.
And at that exact moment, Beck is yelling back at you.
We gotta get him to a hospital.
Cal, come on, get in the car.
Put him in this car, it's already ruined
and Jeremy is on our side.
Beck, I love you like a son,
but if you let him in my car, I'll be disappointed.
I don't know.
Is our cherry removable?
The thing that we've been running around, the siren light?
Yeah, it literally just is like suction cups on top.
I pull it out of like the dashboard or out of the glove box
and I toss it over the car to Cal.
All right, we'll get him in that car.
We just gotta go, we just gotta go.
Cal catches it pretty nimbly.
Oh yeah?
I gotta imagine he was like.
Let's get some athletics checks.
See how smoothly this very intense,
very serious situation goes.
I guess it has been a while since high school baseball
and Cal fumbles, I do not pass either.
So it's already like a wild throw.
It's a wild pitch off to the side and you reach out
way for it and it touches your fingers though.
So you know deep down you could have caught it.
Just like the story if it gets away from us.
Julius, man, we gotta get into that car
that you just got out of.
We gotta get you back into that one
and we gotta get you to the hospital, dude.
You're gonna die.
What?
Beck wants to, he feels like he needs to snap Julius
into it and he wants to poke the wound
to see if that elicits a response.
Holy fucking shit.
When he reaches out for you, do you counter?
No.
Poke.
Lose one hit point.
Oh!
Fuck.
You killed Julius.
Can I use your pencil?
Thank you.
No actually.
That would take me to one hit point.
Let's have you roll con to see if you lose
one hit point here.
Roll con.
Can it be taken into account that I wasn't
like trying to injure, I was trying to shock.
56 on a 55.
You did both.
Well did it?
Did it shock?
Do you respond to that other than?
Julius Summers vomits through the window.
Into the car.
Into the car, onto your lap,
into the white Mercedes C-Class.
Now do you believe me, dude?
That's a wound, man.
You're injured.
Julius, when you look down,
you see yourself absolutely covered in blood
and you are in a wild amount of pain
seemingly out of fucking nowhere.
What the fuck?
Yeah, yeah, exactly my dude.
Get in the car.
He stumbles into Jeremy's car.
Cal slaps the cherry on top,
slaps Jeremy in the face.
Thank you.
Get him to the hospital.
Do it for old lady news.
Absolutely, sir, yes sir.
Hand to my, hand to my, hand to my forehead,
fingers flat.
Julius hears like get him to the hospital
like they're not coming with me
and he gets out of the car.
We gotta solve it together.
Julius, you know, the last time you tried to pull this,
no offense, we lost God.
So why don't you just go to the fucking hospital?
If I recall correctly,
you lost God when I was in the hospital.
Who knows what happened when Julius.
Good point, I will not be going to the hospital.
And he starts to just kind of try to wipe himself off
and like holds the bullet wound.
Go ahead and roll a first aid on yourself
if you have it to try to look around and find.
Fail again.
Are you excited about that?
No.
Do you have any first aid back there?
You find some fast food napkins in Jeremy's glove box.
He shoves it in the wound.
I turn around to Stevie.
Stevie, is there any chance that you know like
maybe how to stop the bleeding on this?
Hey, I do have one luck that I have written down.
It's been scratched out and then replaced, but I have it.
That's extremely confusing based on the conversation
we had at the top of the app.
Okay, yeah, then I don't, nevermind.
I believe you, but it sounds like a lie.
I need you guys to answer a question for me
because I rolled for first aid.
I think base is 30, is that correct?
10.
10, yeah.
Okay, so I gave Stevie a plus 20.
I rolled both D10s and one said 80
and the other one rolled off the table.
Reroll them both.
Am I supposed to reroll them both?
Yeah.
Yes, of course.
As we've always played.
So reroll both.
Okay, so then I rerolled both and I got a 69.
That's a critical success.
That's good news.
He's back to full health.
So Stevie is like, well, the only time that I ever had
any sort of like first aid training was this one summer camp
where we just learned how to like dress like bullet wounds
in the field.
What kind of summer camp was that?
Rich people.
Oh, okay.
I'll have to do a story about that.
Good news, Stevie.
I think it's a bullet wound.
Summer's camp me.
Scamp?
He leans his shoulder towards Stevie,
points at it with the napkin sticking out of it.
So she hops out of the Mercedes C class.
She rummages through Cal's trunk.
Which has a full first aid kit probably.
Which has a full first aid kit in the back of it
and she pulls that out, goes over to Julius.
Okay, I'm gonna need you to just kind of lean up
against the car and just, you know, bite down on this.
Julius lays down and then bites on this.
You get three hit points.
Hell yes.
Nice.
What is your max, Luke?
10.
And you're at four?
It's like I never poked you.
What do you need from me, Mr. Colorado?
What does lady journalism need?
I guess we need you to watch the exits.
We can only cover so many points of entryways
to the subway to watch the meeting.
So if you can keep them, you know,
if you can take up the rear.
Subway?
Eat fresh.
We're meeting Stevie.
Julius accepts that as an answer.
He did?
He's back, baby.
We're meeting, or Stevie is meeting, the gops.
The ones who stole our footage
and she's gonna recover it.
How many?
Just the two, as far as I know.
Which ones?
As far as we know, it's the guys
that we went to the apartments of.
Richard Riley and Wilson Wiley.
Oh, okay.
Beck is still kind of side-eyeing Julius.
Not sure if he's gonna die or not.
If you don't have good medicine skills,
then yeah, you might be very much still worried about that.
But he's not bleeding.
Blood isn't coming out of the hole anymore.
Whereas before, it seemed with every heartbeat,
there was just like a little glug.
Can you look at your phone and text me back?
Yeah, absolutely.
Here's my phone, looking at it right now.
It says, do you like me, yes or no?
Luke, roll grip.
Not to lose any or gain any,
but to know whether you...
I got a 13 on a 23.
Okay, with your grip and check, you do.
I do.
Yeah.
Now we're married.
You're meeting Richard Riley and Wilson Wiley.
Yeah, because they have the footage,
so I just need it back.
And that way I can...
That way I can...
You're not gonna meet him.
Blackmail my dad.
Well, no, of course we're not gonna meet them.
We're gonna ambush them while they meet Stevie.
Yeah.
That's the plan.
Julius picks a piece of brain off his face and says,
this is as close as you're gonna get to meeting them.
Oh, shit.
Julius, what do you mean?
They're dead.
Both of them?
Yeah.
They were, well, they were at Cannes.
I have so many questions,
but I think the first one is,
did you get the footage back from them then?
No.
What do you mean no?
Where was the footage?
Well, I'll be honest with you.
It all went down so fast.
And then I think I just broke.
You killed them.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
And Julius is like a thousand yard stare.
You killed Tife too, right?
Yeah.
Hey, Brack, he killed Tife.
He killed...
Tife.
You killed your uncle?
Yeah.
Well, he was gonna destroy the footage too, I think.
He didn't want it out.
I think Beck is like sort of in shock.
Like this is too much.
Do we need to roll grip or?
Yeah, if you could both roll grip.
Cow passes just fine.
20 on a 41.
I got a 69.
Holy fucking shit.
Hell yeah.
That's my first 69 in a long time.
All right, you're gonna gain a D4 of grip back.
Ooh.
That's a four.
Hell yeah.
Oh, nice.
It says four on every side of that.
Yeah.
Beck is able to internalize this real quick and easy.
What is this resolve that Beck has attained?
It's that, I mean, as crazy as this all is,
it's tied up some loose ends and answered some questions,
even though others are now posed.
But it's like kind of weirdly making sense.
Yeah.
So Julius, like, holy fuck, you killed him.
But you don't have the footage?
Where'd you get the gun?
Don't worry about that.
Who shot you?
Well, one of them.
It was a player, one of them.
RR or WW.
Or, or Tife?
No, Tife didn't have a gun.
And he looks even farther than a thousand yards.
Holy shit.
Could I, could I?
Wouldn't even say it.
Could I see your gun?
No.
Please?
He like pulls up his shirt for a second
and flashes you and you see two guns on it, on either hip.
And then he puts his shirt back down.
Holy shit.
Okay, so.
I'm sure if we went back to the stationers,
they were meeting with Tife, you know, the cops.
Yeah.
So he was bad, right?
Yes, he was a bad man.
A bad man who hated the news.
I mean, I wasn't there, but yeah,
it sounds like you did what you had to.
I mean, they're not like bad.
I mean, they just do whatever the Godot company
wants them to do that doesn't make him like necessarily.
They follow orders without thinking, no matter what?
Exactly, yeah, like you said, yeah.
They're just following orders?
Yeah, agreed.
It's like, what's the big deal?
Can I hear that, Steve?
Oh shit.
A serious look, yeah.
Right, okay, so if the, okay, huh.
And Jeremy's like, wait, wait, okay, so like,
if all of this is happening,
do you guys need coffee or anything?
I think we will be able to grab some coffee
on our way through the door, back at the station.
Real quick, back to Stevie.
The Godot company is bad.
Not all Godot's are bad.
You're not bad, Stevie.
You could be, depending on what you choose to do.
They like smile.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But you're not bad because you're a Godot.
Yeah, not yet.
Exactly, none of us are bad yet.
I used to be.
I used to be a good guy.
I used to be a good guy, then I went insane.
Hey, Zach, will you check your phone?
Julius is texting while you guys are talking.
If we go back to the, Julius is, I mean, like,
do people know other than Jeremy, like, this all happened?
Like, is there, is it a crime scene?
Is it, are there gonna be a lot of cops there?
He seems lost in his phone.
We've got to accept that there's probably a lot of cops
and a crime scene environment there,
but we're the perfect cover.
We're Can News.
We are Can News.
We've got to come in and cover it, you know?
That's, they'll believe that.
I'm Cal Colorado.
Do we know that the footage is there?
Stevie, were you supposed to do the handoff here
or was this money being exchanged
and then you were gonna go get the footage somewhere?
No, they were bringing the footage here.
So maybe it's on them.
I mean, it could be, it's,
if they were gonna meet you guys,
it was probably in Tife's office.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe.
I didn't look too hard.
Also, I don't know if there'll be cops there or not.
Kind of depends.
And he's like staring at his phone, waiting for-
Depends on what, Julius?
Okay, this is the last one I'm sending.
Julius says.
Okay, Julius, like, is staring at his phone for a while
and you see it kind of deeing.
Synesthesia.
Yeah, I got synesthesia.
I heard your pussy stink.
I can't do it.
Guys, I, I want to tell you-
That's just a tweet.
I didn't make that up or anything.
That would have been nuts.
Yeah, I'm not that good.
Guys, I want to, I want to tell you something,
but if I tell you, it's nothing's ever gonna be the same.
And you don't take it lightly.
I, I don't, but nothing's been the same
for a couple days now.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I think we were past samesies.
Yeah, the It Pit pretty much did it in for that.
Okay, well.
Well, do you, I, you know,
I don't normally carry guns around, right?
I wasn't sure.
Yeah, yeah, no, no.
You didn't really seem like a big gun guy before,
except for, you know, those cannons
and your, and your, that you call thighs.
Right, I've had these, I've had these guns a long time.
You are a gun guy.
Well, I have to be in my line of work.
Beck is just staring at you.
What, what, what's your line of work, son?
Well, it's technically government.
I work for, it's like maybe kind of like the FBI,
but for, you know, the shit we've seen the past few days.
Extreme.
Basically, that's, that's the closest I'd compare it to.
I don't know, I just have a connection that,
that pays me and tells me to, to do things and...
Can I, can I human this?
Yeah.
70 on a 70.
How does he feel?
Do you think he's telling the truth?
You know, Julius, you've had a really tough day
and I believe that you believe
that you're in the X-Files or whatever, but yeah.
I mean, so why don't we just get back to the can building
and try to find the footage?
And we can talk all about your little alien adventures
or whatever.
Okay, well, just so we know,
you guys are kinda, I mean, kinda in now too, in on it.
So don't tell anybody.
Are you, Julius, are you telling me
that you have like an assignment?
What do you, yeah.
Do you know more about what's going on than we do?
Well, I know that we need that footage
and I need to kill Gops.
We agreed we need that footage.
What do you want the footage for?
Same reason you do.
To show to the world.
Yes.
I want to human that.
Roll it, baby.
Nice.
36.
How does he feel?
Julius is telling the truth.
Fuck yeah, baby.
Holy shit.
Okay.
We find the footage and we put it out on the TikTok.
Yeah, are you like a real producer too though?
Beck sees Julius texting they need that footage.
Beck sees Julius texting they know and sending it.
Well, Ty was my uncle,
but no, I never had any real training.
It was, I mean, I'm lucky that he was my uncle.
That's how I got the job, but.
Well, we, yeah, we all knew that part.
Probably could have clocked that a little sooner,
you're right, yeah.
No, no, no, I mean, that was, yeah.
But at the end of the day, I feel like I, you know,
I have the same kind of heart that you guys do.
I want the truth.
I want people to know the truth.
Well, at least enough truth that they won't, you know,
go nuts.
You mean the whole truth?
In a lot of cases.
In this case, we just rolled about this.
Yeah, Julius, yes.
Definitely in this case.
Julius text.
Julius, who are you texting?
We can call her X for X file.
If that's, you know, that's the easiest way to refer to it.
Have you ever met X in real life?
Yeah, she's my roommate.
Oh shit.
Okay, so like, but this is like a source
that wants to remain anonymous.
What's her real name?
We'll need to get clearance to interview her
and everything for this.
I don't know that that'll be happening,
but I do have good news.
She's got the footage.
X has the footage?
She just texted me.
Like at your place?
Is X gonna give it to us?
What?
Ha ha.
Pfft.
Ha ha ha.
And it's all my fault.
Is that enough to be the end of the episode?
That's the end, right?
That's the end.
Unfortunately for...
We're doing two episodes, so.
Was that enough time?
It's like 50 minutes.
Oh, all together?
Yeah.
So it ended down to like 30?
No, like easy 42.
33.
So unfortunately that can't be the end.
Yeah, sorry Joe.
Ha ha ha.
You should end it there and then have like
still like 20 more minutes of episode after.
Play the music and then here's the rest of the episode.
Yeah.
You can, yeah, just like play the first 10 seconds.
Not a full fucking song.
Nobody would listen to it.
Two seconds.
Yeah, I think she's gonna give it to us.
And he...
X?
X gonna give it to us.
But he texts back a house emoji or Z, question mark.
The house.
Okay, you guys wanna see my house?
What's Z?
Secret meeting spot.
Oh, for your little alien club?
It's, well...
What are you guys, like an internet discussion group
or something or?
Do you have like training?
Did somebody train you?
Peck.
Come on.
I mean...
I'll tell you guys the full story later
but I mean, unless you wanna hear it right now.
Ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, tell it to us on the way.
Okay.
This is perfect.
Okay, so what cars are going where?
Where is Jeremy going?
Beck is FaceTiming Julius
who is in Jeremy's car following behind us.
Or no, we're following them
because you've gotta lead us to your house.
Who am I in the car with?
You're FaceTiming from Jeremy's car
and you're only in the car with Jeremy.
You're back in your bloody seat.
Clark.
Beck is getting the...
Beck is putting the phone on,
like trying to balance it on the dashboard
while he rummages around for like Arby's napkins
to start wiping the vomit off of him.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Oh, were you sick?
It's not mine, Cal.
I poked Julius in his gunshot wound
because he didn't think it was a gunshot wound
and I was trying to show him it was a gunshot wound
and when I did that, he threw up on me.
Checks out.
Cal just...
Julius says over FaceTime.
Cal just kind of blinks
and turns his eyes back to the road.
Well, I mean, yes.
It started when I was in high school
and then the screen fades away.
Dope, dope, dope, dope, dope.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We see Julius Summers as a teenager
wearing a black and white track and field uniform
with the suburb sharks emblazoned on the front.
We see clips of him talking and smiling with friends
and teammates interspersed between highlights
of his sprinting, pole vaulting, high and long jumping.
Whoa, Julie, you jumped so high.
It cuts to Julius on top of a podium
wearing multiple gold medals and holding flowers.
Julius is surrounded by his friends and fans
and being showered with congratulations and praise.
His thighs are so big.
Eventually the crowd...
That's how I jump so much.
Eventually the crowd thins out as the event wraps up.
The other teens head home with their parents
or older siblings.
And eventually Julius stands completely alone
near the pickup lane at the high school.
He flags down someone walking to their car
and asked to use their cell phone.
Julius dials a number and holds the phone up to his ear.
Hey mom, are you...
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I won.
Yeah, okay, I'll just walk home.
See you tonight?
Julius hands the phone back.
Politely declines a ride home
and begins to walk the four miles to his mom's house.
About three miles down the road,
Julius steps off the pavement
toward an overgrown path in the woods,
a shortcut he's taken a thousand times.
About 50 feet onto the trail,
Julius hears a twig snap and a low gravelly voice.
Nice race.
Julius spins around to look at a man
in a tight, ratty black suit,
dark aviator sunglasses and worn combat boots
with thin waist-length pitch black hair
leaning up against a tree.
Julius's stomach jumps to his throat
as he manages to squeak out.
Yeah, thanks.
I've been watching you.
We've been watching you,
rooting for you,
keeping track of all your accomplishments and failures.
You're good.
Almost as good as some of our guys.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Come here.
Let me get a closer look.
Let me,
let me feel your strength.
Get the fuck away from me!
Okay, damn, we're gonna have to play it this way, huh?
Well, I'll give you a head start.
Julius stares at the man.
He notices how unevenly shaved the man's face is.
A patch of three or four hairs
inches longer than his five o'clock shadow
protrudes from his chin.
The man raises his hand up to stroke the longer hairs.
Five,
four,
three.
The man ever so slightly flicks his sunglasses down,
looks over them at Julius
and motions his head toward the trail.
Go, Mr. Summers.
Julius takes off sprinting towards safety.
Two.
He hurdles over fallen limbs,
rusted scrap metal and loose rocks.
His vision narrows as his flight response fully kicks in.
One.
Julius hears quick heavy footsteps
begin falling behind him.
He can almost see the end of the tree line
that opens up into the back of his neighborhood.
Looks like I'll be taking those medals today, boy.
Julius falls to the ground as he's tackled from behind.
His face is shoved into the mud as his legs
and hands are zip tied behind him.
The man flips over onto his back.
Can you say that again real quick?
His face is shoved into the mud.
The fact was so close.
Julius falls to the ground as he is tackled from behind.
His face is shoved into the mud as his legs
and hands are zip tied behind him.
The man flips over onto his back and stands over him.
We'll get you in proper shape.
Trust me, bud.
The screen goes dark as the man's foot comes down
on Julius's face.
And then, yeah, pretty much just training every day.
And then they tell me to do something and I do it.
Did they ever tell you who they were?
As far as you guys are concerned,
for now they're X-Files and I'm X-Files.
Wait, these are your nerd friends?
Yeah.
Sure, Cal.
No, wait, that, that heroine story felt very real.
This is the, you're, son of a bitch, you're an X-Files.
I am.
There's like a look of like relief and a resolve in Beck
because it's all fucking real.
He fucking knew it.
Fuck yeah, fuck yeah.
Cal vomits in Beck's lap.
I'm gonna need some more of those napkins.
Julius looks over at Jeremy.
I guess you're in now, too.
Jeremy's eyes are so fucking big, dude.
That's an ep.
Sweet.
That's fucking dope, dude.
It's great and it's all my fault
because my life is great
and it's all mine
and it's all my fault
because my life is great