Howdy-doody, my spooky-poopies.
It's your turd-blasting, time-traveling, greasy, and parental figure wolf, the dog.
And I'm here to provide sustenance to all of my little baby buddies.
I'm tootin' at y'all live from 694.2 PTBP,
the city's only radio station that also doubles as a crawdaddy bio-farm on the weekends.
If we eat only the crawdaddies, what happens to all the crawmommies?
Speakin' of weird shit that I'm forced to read that makes people mildly uncomfortable,
this week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Kyle.
Remember, listener, Kyle asked for this.
Kyle writes,
To my darling wife, Steffy.
Hundland, Hundland.
Ow!
Cough, cough, cough.
Hundland, Hundland.
Uh... thanks for that, Kyle.
I hope your wife enjoyed that.
I know I did.
At certain parts, but mostly I didn't.
If you wanna write up somethin' for your guttural wolf to how,
tag at PretendingPod on Twitter or Instagram,
tag PretendingToBePeople on Facebook,
or write up a five-star review on the podcast app of your choice.
Screenshot them deliciousnesses and send them my way.
If you refuse to post on social media, but you still wanna support the show,
give us money in exchange for a whole bunch of bonus episodes,
access to submit NPCs and locations,
behind-the-scenes livestreams,
exclusive T-shirts,
and et cetera, et cetera.
It also helps give Zach the little bits of sausage he needs
that keep him goin' as he produces, GMs, and edits this fine show.
Links to all that and Wolfie's merch store are,
you guessed it, in the show notes.
For those just tunin' in, I'm Wolf the Dog.
You are listening to 694.2 PTBP,
and this is the news.
Last time, we learned about the new field producer, Julius Summers,
and his childhood connection to the City Action News Studios.
And when Julius was a child, crawlin' around gnawin' on marbles that were,
of course, securely fastened to the floor,
Well, back then, Cal Colorado was the frothy film of the slot bucket, my babies.
He was on top.
His trusty field camera operator, Beck Wilder,
sided with Julius against Cal Colorado
when the team was asked to follow a lead that Cal balked at.
Let's see if we can top that.
Here's a brand new rock act.
It's Alter Girl with My Life is Great and It's All My Fault.
And it's all my fault
Cos my life is great
And it's all mine
And it's all my fault
I never record the good jokes.
I swear, that's not what this podcast is about.
I've got a month of Bumble Premium.
Hell yeah, dude. Find somebody in to piss play.
Did they maybe give you the first month free?
No, no, no. My phone did this in my pocket while we were at brunch,
looking at the charge.
Cos I was talking to somebody and stuck my phone in my pocket while we were messaging.
Oh no, how much?
30 bucks. Could be worse.
That's still insane for a month.
That is insane for a month.
But I was hoping, oh wow.
You just made me feel fine about this, I guess.
No, actually I don't. That's almost an eighth of weed. Fuck that.
I was gonna hit up my person today.
And instead I have a month of Bumble Premium.
I guess I'm gonna have to make the most of this.
Yeah dude, go fucking wild on Bumble now.
Fucking unlimited swipes.
What is Bumble?
Bumble's the one where the women message you first.
Oh, okay. Got you.
So you never get like anything live?
No, no. It's all a trick.
I don't think they're real.
Yeah, mine was broken, I think.
Welcome to episode three of Pretending to Be People.
I could add weed, y'all.
Instead I might get a life partner.
Fuck me.
How's it going?
Oh, it's fine.
You know, a little miffed.
I've been scrolling through TikTok,
disappointed that Kan hasn't updated in a while.
City Action News, if this is your first time
listening to the podcast.
Also go back and listen to episode one.
If this is your first episode,
this is the perfect time to go back a couple episodes.
We only got three now.
This is the only time where we can say
just go back a couple.
Now is the easiest time to make sure you go back now.
If you're in the next episode listening for the first time
and you go back a couple,
ooh, I'd rather you went back a few.
Hey, fair point, but it's not like we're at 10.
It's not like we're at 10.
I don't have a fun folksy word for nine.
Say it like Mr. Lemon.
Well, I say you have to go back nine episodes.
Did you like that? Say it like the editor.
Oh, well, you'd have to go back nine episodes.
Was any a little weird? Vivica?
Oh, who was the guy who sounded weird?
Do you mean Jeremy?
Oh, the intern.
Oh yeah, I do.
Yeah.
Oh, speaking of Jeremy,
this episode starts with a shot of Jeremy
standing in the parking lot,
standing in the empty spot where the can van
just was holding a hot iced latte
and two energy drinks.
It's about now in the van that Beck remembers that,
oh, damn it, we forgot our drinks.
Damn it.
And he begins sprinting down the road
through traffic holding these three items.
We didn't get very far, did we?
We did not get very far.
We're stuck.
I said that you got pretty much trapped in gridlock
almost immediately.
So let's see the inside of this van.
Hey, does the city suck?
Oh, I mean, you're here at what?
Like 6 p.m. in the middle of downtown.
Shit is.
So?
Shit's fucked.
Right, and when he says, does the city suck?
That's actually the beginning of the TikTok.
He's asking the person in front of us in their car
that question.
What?
Does the city suck?
I don't think Cal Colorado would ever say those words.
Yeah.
We've only known him for two episodes,
but there's no fucking way Cal Colorado's saying that.
But you could try to talk him into it and scene.
Wait, that's at the end.
How do you start one?
Fire.
That's why you don't yell fire in a theater
because they'll think it means well.
It's time to start.
Fire!
Beck is holding the phone ready to film a TikTok,
but he still doesn't have a clear idea
of what he's looking to the producer for guidance.
Julius is scrambling for ideas
and just kind of looking around
and he sees a pizza at Cal's own shop.
And he looks at Cal.
Oh my God.
And he looks back.
Cal is blinking and smiling and here at TikTok,
so he's telling you the time.
Cal, how do you feel about eating something?
I had a sensible lunch and breakfast.
I, no, I don't think I could eat right now.
Just a bite or two.
I'm sorry, I don't know if you've noticed,
but I do keep my figure trim.
Then let's ask these people some questions.
And I just point to like people walking.
Man on the street, I love it.
You see a guy who with a massive beanie,
it's like way too big and it's drooped over his eyes almost.
He's walking like he's sitting down, but he's walking.
And-
I'm sorry, Zach, what?
He's walking like he's sitting down,
but he's walking.
So he's ass-
You've seen people, right?
Oh man.
His ass is like even with his knees.
Yeah, he's like-
Zach, what do you think walking?
He's just like squat walking
and kind of like dancing around.
Cal has a microphone in his face.
You, sir, what are you doing?
Roll, roll, roll.
Hey, I'm just dancing, I'm dancing.
And he's just kind of doing this weird,
like sitting dance thing, like a silly walk.
And he's just like, you know,
I like to get through the city by dancing.
You see these cars here?
They're stuck.
I'm not stuck.
I'm free.
You're never stuck if you have your legs.
A disturbingly ableist message.
From the Cal zone.
Hey, Cal, how about instead of that,
we try like you try to dance like him with him.
That might be amusing.
He reaches out for your hand.
Oh, a street man.
Okay.
Cal takes his hand, but then yeah,
Cal is nailing it.
Cal is like athletic.
Awesome.
Cal watches this guy move and then moves like that.
The Cal zone is a thing that you had already coined
in your basketball days.
Well, yeah, I mean, I played some D
and when they got in the Cal zone, they got slapped down.
Your sign off needs to be,
and that's another slam dunk from the Cal zone.
That's some more hot D from the Cal zone.
Oh yeah.
That's a wild catchphrase.
Just like my basketball dance.
Beck stops filming and on TikTok,
he's doing, he's maybe adding a filter
and he's putting the text over the top
and it's when you in the Cal zone.
Oh, fuck yeah, dude.
That face when.
What's the song?
Whoop, there it is.
Oh, fuck yeah, whoop, there it is, whoop, there it is.
Before I hit send, I give it to Julius.
Julius adds, Julius looks at it and looks at Beck
like just stoked that it's perfect.
And he just adds the caption, another fresh hot Cal zone.
Fuck yes.
As soon as it's blasted out,
literally the second it posts a TikTok,
you get a notification on your cell phone, Julius
and Tife has hearted the message that he sent you.
Oh, the-
Make a TikTok, bitch.
Oh, right.
I text him back, like open the news tonight
saying that we posted a TikTok or something like that.
Like make-
Open the news tonight, saying that we posted a TikTok,
something like that.
Or something.
Breaking news, a new TikTok is dropped.
As you guys are all reconvened, as you were all-
Recalvened.
After you've all recalvened back in the can van.
Jesus.
Can we start the season two over?
I'm not feeling the can van.
You see a man running, sprinting in between two lanes
of traffic in the rear view mirror on the can van.
And he is holding one hot ice latte and two energy drinks.
And he approaches the van and he's like,
Okay, I got your hot ice latte.
They were not happy about that order, Julius,
but I got it funny.
He takes it and he's surprised that it is somehow
both very hot and very cold.
And here are these for you, Beck.
Hell yeah, man.
I almost had to go to the backups and he pets the backpack
that he has with him that has a bunch of extra cans
of energy drink.
And a patch with energy drink on it.
Cal has Julius's phone and he's just watching the TikTok
like repeatedly with a huge grin on his face.
Awesome.
And he kind of like absentmindedly notices
that the intern has run up and he's like,
and if you could get me a black coffee, please.
Cal, you get a text message at the exact same time
as Julius.
It's a group text between Taif, Cal and Julius.
And he says, her name is Kaylee Silver.
Shout out to Distant Egg Song in Houston.
Hey.
For Kaylee Silver, we'll likely meet her soon.
Kaylee Silver, it says, specifically asked for Cal
because he is a truth above all type of guy.
She grew up watching him on TV and she trusts him.
So that first thing he likes,
then I grew up watching you on TV.
That gives him pause.
Sure.
He's heard that.
That can go a lot of ways.
And as you're reading that text,
immediately back is Jeremy.
Whew, wowzer.
Yeah, that is a hot black coffee.
The quickest coffee run, I time myself, thank you,
that I have ever made.
Thankfully, because, and he points behind him.
The Cal zone plays sold coffee.
I went to the U zone.
Oh, thank you, Jeremy.
Cal kind of realizes what he's done.
He like realizes they're in the street and not the office
and gives him a big thumbs up.
And he thumbs ups back and then sprints off backwards
from where he came from.
He sprints backwards.
I think we found our first horror mystery.
I said what I said.
Yeah, and he's sitting while he does it for five seconds.
So we could talk to this weird pervert
or we could go find out what's going on
with backwards running, man.
Traffic moves at a snail's pace for like 15 minutes.
And then eventually it kind of opens up
and you guys get to your destination
in a matter of like five minutes.
It is a mid-rise, downtown in the city.
And on that piece of paper that you have
says apartment 836.
I pull the van up and park right in front.
Beck hops out and is already getting some B-roll
of the outside of the building.
But he's also bringing everything he's gonna need.
So he's got a tripod under an arm
and his case of camera equipment.
What's Cal doing?
What's running through his mind?
I was talking to this girl on Bumble
and we've hooked up a couple times
and she was like,
hey, this guy just sent me this really weird dick pic
and I don't know if it's like diseased or what.
And I was like, well, I kind of want to see that.
And she just sent it to me.
You did not want to see that, no.
Oh man.
Cal has a crazy life.
Yeah, we all make decisions.
I'm not sure I would have made that one.
Was that like a play of some sort?
Of like just showing off your personality early?
No, again, this is a person I've had sex with.
Yeah, like he could have that.
That's what I thought.
No, no, no.
She was like this dude sent me a dick pic
and it looked really weird.
Is it the dick pic that you sent her?
No, I'm about to send her one to show her a normal dick.
Cool, that was a question mark.
Did you look at it again, you freak?
Oh no, she just sent a description of it.
Hot.
It's got a weird texture.
Sounds like Bumble Premium is worth it.
Yeah.
She's like doesn't it look like a tongue and it does.
Well, that's going to be in season two somewhere.
Doesn't it look like a tongue?
And it does.
It won't be a dick though.
You guys want to see this dick?
No.
Not really.
Good call.
I'm sorry, I'm going to pee.
I'm kind of bummed out by my own decisions.
Fucking idiot.
Why did I have taste buds?
Did you go to the bathroom to jerk off to that picture?
Yes.
That's why it took me 20 seconds.
Fucking pervert.
Where the fuck were we?
Well, I was jacking off to that dick pic in your bathroom.
Let's start with me getting out of the van doing B-roll
and you're asking Cal what he was doing.
Yeah, that's what I was doing.
I asked Cal what he was doing and then we got into that.
Julius, what are you doing
as you guys approach this mid-rise?
Julius is going to go in and wait for Beck
to get some B-roll of him hitting the eight button
on the elevator.
Yeah, so people know where she lives.
No, just not for this story, but for, you know,
you can always use B-roll.
Oh yeah, that's good.
Beck is always, the B-roll doesn't have to be
for that story.
Like videography is his passion
and he knows that he's always filming for stories these days
but he likes to keep a collection of stuff
he could use for art projects.
And he's just kind of like elevator button projects.
Yeah, that's why Julius was keeping him in mind.
He's like, is there anything that could be like a quick shot?
Oh yeah.
You're familiar with his YouTube page.
I had to do my research before I worked here.
Joe, when you said like you were, Beck is always filming.
I definitely pictured a John Wilson how-to situation.
It's not funny.
Yeah, well, I mean, he was an inspiration
as far as the idea that he's always filming stuff.
He inspired how-to John Wilson.
Who knows how or when he'll use it.
Exactly, Beck inspired John Wilson.
Beck's like hot underground YouTube,
experimental YouTube page inspired John Wilson
to make how-to.
As you guys make it to the front of the building,
the doorman sees that your city action news
and opens the door and lets you get in.
Are you sure you don't want us to have like a 10 minute
interaction with the doorman?
Where we try to get in?
Julius, you're in the elevator now,
you're on your way up to the eighth floor of this building.
And when the elevator door opens,
you are in a stagnant, stale hallway.
It smells like old cigarettes and Chinese food.
It's not a bad smell.
It's kind of comforting if you're me,
but if you're me.
I lived in an apartment building
that smelled exactly like this.
It's not comforting at all to Julius.
It's propulsive even.
He grew up with marble floors and privilege.
And the carpet in the hallways of this apartment building
is only made more timely in its interior design
by the wallpaper that lines these hallways.
It feels almost suffocating.
Apartments 809 to 814 are to the left
and then 819 to 836 are to the right.
Kaylee Silver in apartment 836 will be to the right.
We go to the right.
How do you knock on the door?
Apparently this is an important aspect of season two.
So how do you knock on the door?
Oh God that scared the shit out of me.
I get my TikTok out and hand it over to him
and I'm like, get like the surprise on her face
when he knocks at the door.
You hear the heavy breathing coming
from the other side of the door.
Cal makes this big step back.
Shh, is it Cal?
Yes ma'am, this is Cal Colorado.
Wow, okay cool.
My name is Kaylee Silver.
I'm in a lot of trouble.
Can you help me?
Well, I'd love to see what I can do ma'am.
Could you let us in?
Unlock, chain unlock, deadbolt unlock.
Is she saying all that?
As Kaylee Silver pulls the three of you
into apartment 836 and shuts the door,
this 20 or 30 something and a choker necklace
repositions a towel against the door's threshold
and your noses tell your brains to tell you why.
It smells like death in this apartment
and there, strewn over the armrest of the couch
is a sight that could affect your grip on reality.
You see a pair of legs and your mind fills in the rest.
I grab my phone back from you
so that you can get your camera out.
But there's a little bit of resistance
that Beck was getting a shot of it instinctually.
I want you guys to picture Seinfeld's apartment for this.
That way we know where everything is.
Are you familiar with the impossible geometry
of Cherry Siderealm?
Okay, roll grip.
All right, but for real, I need everyone to roll grip
which is your grip on reality.
It is directly attached to the score of power.
Power times five is gonna be your grip.
We're replacing the word sanity in this campaign.
Because we've found it problematic.
And we really like the word grip.
Losing your grip.
It's cool.
Yeah, we like it a lot.
Plus maybe if in some instance we have,
I don't know, some kind of situation in the past,
you could really make it old timey.
Oh yeah.
Oh, you could make that word anything you want.
Almost anything, yeah.
We might have an array.
It'd be really fun to do one of the 30s.
I don't know what you're planning.
Foxy.
I mean, that's more of a teens, but yeah.
You guys can play teens, whatever.
So, I need you all to roll grip.
I failed.
Beck has pretty good grip.
In fact, it's one of his best skills
because it's related directly to your power
which is my highest.
Yeah, exactly.
I rolled a 76 on a 75.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, dude.
Damn.
Well, Cal is an old professional
and he rolled 39 on a 60.
Yeah, Julius got a 62 on a 60.
Beck, you shoot the news.
This is not, you're not a police officer.
This is not your job.
Why are you here?
She shouldn't have called you.
This was just a story.
He likes to film interviews and everything was fine
and oh fuck, there's a body.
That was not on the docket today.
You don't have to look at her.
Julius looks.
Cal looks.
Beck definitely looks.
You're all gonna have to roll grip again
as you see there's a streak of blood
on the floor of the apartment
where Kaylee Silver clearly dragged the body
to then put her on the couch.
You notice out of the corner of your eye,
Kaylee's wincing as you all look
and see the body of another 20 or 30 something
but this corpse has been almost completely decapitated
by something sharp enough to get the job done
but blunt enough that some of the cuts
look more like the skin was ripped apart.
As you approach, you notice between the shoulders
where this poor woman's neck and throat should be
with blood caked all around it,
you can see the top of her spinal cord
and you can see right down her trachea.
Did you pass that grip check?
I did.
39.
I got a 92.
Beck just needed to flip into oh shit, it's real mode.
Now he's there.
This isn't the first time
he's had to cover terrible things.
He's seen bodies before.
Sure, just not unexpectedly.
He just wasn't ready for it.
He thought he was, yeah, this was a fluff piece.
Same for Cal except he failed this role.
He thought he was prepared after seeing the legs.
He wasn't prepared for this.
He vomits quietly in the hallway.
I'm gonna need you both to roll a D4.
Two.
One.
You lose two grip, Julius,
and Cal, you lose one grip.
Cal is taken so far back, he is out in the hallway.
I said he vomited quietly.
Oh, sorry.
How are you dealing with this, Julius?
The legs made him very uncomfortable walking in
and seeing a little bit of it.
Even worse, he's just frozen there staring at it.
Like, can't look away.
I think that now that Beck passed,
he's a little more in the moment for a second,
and he's suddenly aware that he's standing in a room
with a dead body and a woman saying, I didn't do it,
which sometimes they did did it.
Yeah, sometimes they did his did.
The most likely person to have did it
is the alive person in the room.
He's putting a little bit of distance
between himself and Kaylee,
just in case she's maybe got a knife on her currently,
even still.
Everybody roll alertness.
Fail.
Pass.
I failed.
Julius, you see that there's a broken beer bottle
under the coffee table
that is absolutely dripping in blood.
And Kaylee walks over to the kitchen
and leans against the countertop
and just turns back to you and is like,
okay, I did it, but I had to do it.
I did it, but I had to do it.
You have to trust me.
Julius is immediately looking over at Beck like,
you've got to be getting this, right?
She's already been in a closeup zoom
to try and get micro expressions and everything.
And she just confessed on camera, but she doesn't care.
Killed them all, of course.
It was self-defense.
She was, I don't know how to say this,
but she was trying to tear me apart.
Why?
Get it together, Kaylee.
Kaylee is a young adult.
She's got dirty blonde space buns
and she's wearing a pink crop top with neon green ringers
on the sleeves and the collar.
It's one of those happy bunny shirts.
When you say space buns, do you mean Princess Leia buns?
Oh, I guess kind of, but just like buns
that are on the top of her head, like little buns.
What makes them space?
Was it Xenon of the 21st century?
Did she have those?
You said she's mid thirties, space buns, cool crop top.
Yeah.
What's her deal?
She just killed somebody.
Yeah, but in self-defense.
Yeah, it's like Xenon if those pigtails
were like all wrapped up in buns.
Oh yeah, I thought she had them.
It's one of those happy bunny shirts from like Hot Topic
and it says, it's not your fault, I'm blaming you anyway.
Nice.
She did it on purpose.
That's Thomas's take.
She said it was in self-defense.
I promise.
Cal has gathered himself a little bit
and he wants to, I guess,
humant that statement or what else would I look at?
I want sincerity in her voice
and then I'm also looking for signs of a physical struggle.
Humant for her, forensics for the scene,
if anybody wants to roll.
Oh, fucking three.
Nice. Nice.
She seems extremely genuine.
I did it, but I had to do, it was self-defense.
I fucking promise you.
Who is she?
She's my best friend.
Kaylee.
What's her deal?
I'm Kaylee, she's Kaylee.
It's spelled differently, but we're best friends.
We like bonded on that.
Is this what really,
because that's difficult podcasting.
Is it?
When we're talking about Kaylee at any moment,
it could be two different people.
One of them is dead.
Yeah, it also sounds like a great situation for farce.
Her name is Carolee.
I did what I did.
In the moment.
I think you're the one that expressed
that you regretted naming an NPC John
and a PC John in the first season.
Okay, but like, are we going to be talking to Kaylee
for another 40 episodes or just right now?
I think it's pretty fun.
Also, Luke had an elegant solution.
Carolee is her name.
Kaylee, K period Lee.
K dot Lee, Carole.
Carole is the daughter of Cal.
Yeah, that's her full name.
If we're going on those rules.
Yeah, her name is Kaylee.
Spelled how?
K-Y-L-E-I-G-H, Kaylee.
Oh no.
And her last name is?
Kaylee.
Yeah, I mean, it's gold.
Oh, Kaylee silver, Kaylee gold.
We're like, we're destined to be best friends.
And for the past, fuck, 12 years,
she's been my ride or die, you know?
And then she comes at me, her eyes went somewhere else.
She was just staring at my gut
and she was trying to tear me apart.
She was trying to tear me apart.
Sorry, shit, fuck, keep it down, Kaylee.
She was literally trying to get inside me.
How often was it brought up
that gold is better than silver?
She starts crying.
And Cal's like, was better than silver.
I look at back, I'm like, please say you got it,
please say you got it.
And she just nods.
Cal is kind of taking this all in
and there is usable footage,
but basically like this segment can't air as is, right?
We can't just throw this on the news.
Ms. Silver, if I could huddle with my crew for a moment,
we wanna discuss the best way to cover your incident here.
Yeah, no, of course I trust you.
Like I said to whoever I talked to on the phone,
I trust you, Cal.
I know that you believe in the truth
and I know that you are gonna find it, okay?
You have to.
That, like that stabs at Cal
and he lingers a moment on her gaze and nods.
A cat jumps up onto the countertop and she says,
oh, hey girl, hey girl.
That's Kaylee bronze.
It's girl.
I mean.
Either way, Cal is walking away from,
like he's huddling up.
Yeah, totally.
And Kaylee is just petting the cat
and trying to calm down.
And Julius is a camera off camera.
Against Beck's better judgment,
he doesn't ever like to turn the camera off
in a place like this, but he goes ahead and does it.
You've been in a place like this before?
Yeah, Cal kind of leads everybody out in the hallway.
The backs of your brains are fucking on fire.
None of you can think straight.
This is not your job.
This is not normal.
You are not having a normal day.
You have some serious decisions to make
that might have ramifications on the rest of your lives.
We have to call 911.
The police, my dudes, the police are needed here
and like fucking yesterday.
I'm glad to hear you both say that.
I don't think we can err until the police are notified.
We have to call them immediately.
I'm gonna put you on that, Jesse.
Pfft.
Which is what he says.
I'm looking around.
Fuck yes.
Beck and Julius are looking at each other.
I'm looking for Mr. Lemon.
But yeah, Julius is calling 911.
911, what's your emergency?
There's been a...
Wait, hold on, let me take that again.
911, what's your emergency?
Now, why is everybody in the city caging?
Okay, let me try again.
It is city funeral tradition to have a crawfish oil.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, but that was like Mardi Gras in St. Louis.
Like, I don't talk like that.
911, what's your emergency?
911.
The Calvin story.
On the 911 plan.
911, what's your emergency?
I need to report a murder.
Oh, what?
Holy shit!
Literally, she's like, oh, okay.
What's your address?
I tell her the address that is on that piece of paper.
Yep.
Oh, that's downtown.
Is that an apartment building?
Yes, it's on the eighth floor, 836.
I didn't do it, but I know who might have.
Cal's like.
And they left.
They're gone, long gone.
Julius is obviously not reading the signals
from his partner as well at all.
And he's like, nevermind, they're in the apartment.
Cal is fierce.
What are you, no.
Hold on, hold on.
This is someone who knows more.
Hello, Cal, Colorado, City Action News.
Oh, hi.
They're, wow.
May I ask who I'm speaking to?
Yeah, my name's Jennifer, and I am speechless,
but I need information as soon as possible.
Well, Jennifer.
And I'm talking to the right guy.
I'm having a hell of a day.
How's yours going?
I, it was fine until now, I suppose.
Tell me more about this homicide.
Well, we were called to investigate a news story.
You know, that's what I do.
I do know that's what you do.
With those, nope.
It's fine, it's fine.
With those piercing blue eyes of yours.
I know.
No, Jennifer, when we got down here, oh, I got Southern.
I'm Southern, I see it, rubs off on people.
Sorry, I thought I left this accent
when I got to the city, but.
Oh, no, it comes back so quick, don't it?
There is a terribly mutilated body in this apartment.
Now, the young woman here says she did it,
but she says it was in self-defense, an act of necessity.
The violence visited upon this corpse might belie that fact,
but we are not the police.
That's why we need you here to look at this.
I think I'm going to Obama.
Well, yeah, I mean, take this as high as you can.
Take this as high as you can.
Do you know Obama?
Roll the tape, you know Obama.
Well, I don't want to brag,
but I did interview him when he campaigned in the city.
There is a picture of you and him hanging in your hallway.
Yeah, one of the many pictures in the hallway
is of Cal and Obama.
It's not as big as the one that's Cal and Michelle.
Sir.
Okay, so I need you to stay on the line with me.
Officers are on their way
and they will be there very shortly.
Was there a murder weapon?
There appears to be, again, we're not investigators.
We are journalists.
We listen to the people who have found the facts
and we try to report them as best we can.
Now, is there a horribly bloody
broken beer bottle on the floor?
Yes.
Is that the device that ripped this woman's neck apart?
I could not say.
Wow, okay, thank you.
Have you talked to the woman who said that she did it?
Has she told you anything more
than just the fact that she did it?
Well, she told us she did it
and we immediately called you.
Well, that was a very smart decision.
We felt that literally anything else
would be incredibly incriminating
and it might implicate us in her crime.
I'm very glad that you are not gonna go to prison, yes.
Well, me too.
That would have been not as fun to role-play,
I don't think.
I'm sure we could have come up with something.
And role-playing prison would be another cool thing.
You're right.
Cal Colorado in prison.
Holy shit.
It might have to happen.
All right, I have word that officers
are on their way up the elevator to your location right now.
And down the hallway, you hear the elevator.
B-roll of cops pouring out of the elevator.
Ding.
Bex on it.
Like smoke billowing from a chimney.
These cops bumble out of this fucking elevator.
Don't remind me of my.
All right, it's clearly the premium team.
And they approach you.
It's two officers and.
Two officers come pouring out of the elevator.
Oh, sorry.
It's six officers.
After they get close enough
that I've got a good shot of them,
I wanna kinda put the camera down tiny bit
and I wanna talk to them before they talk to us
and I'm just gonna say,
officers, she's not violent currently
and she kinda has a rapport with Cal here.
You might let him ease you guys in there.
Ooh, role persuade.
Fuck.
It's a 60 on a 50.
I'm gonna go ahead and use my luck.
Ooh.
Cause I wanna film Cal talking to her more.
Awesome.
Six, that's a good one.
The first officer, you can tell by the look on his face
that he's about to talk down to you
and as he goes to talk,
he's got a frog in his throat
and one of the officers behind him says,
yeah, I think that's probably a good idea.
Cal, dude, she trusts you
and like, I think at the end of the day,
turning herself into the police is the right idea.
I just think you need to make sure
that she's convinced of that
and maybe get to the bottom of why she did this
and he's kinda winking so the cops can't see.
You know, ask her some questions
about what put her in a state of mind to do this
and maybe get more about like what was happening
right before they did this.
And try to do a dance with her if you can.
Hahaha.
Cal has been like nodding, preparing his interview.
Yeah.
And then he hears that last part.
Hahaha.
And he kinda like, I will do what I can.
Julius gets his phone out just in case.
Hahaha.
Yeah, Beck is definitely pulling up the camera
and gonna just follow him into the room.
As you go back in, you see Kaylee is at the kitchen island.
She's hunched over and looking at her phone
and she has wide eyes that cannot look away.
And she's just staring at the screen.
Cal kinda waves his hand in front of her eyes
and like snaps.
Kaylee?
Miss Silver.
I have a furbo.
I'm sorry, what?
Ger, when I am out at work, I have a furbo.
It records motion.
Cal, she's got a camera.
My producer is telling me that's some kind of camera.
She holds the phone up to you
and you're looking at footage from inside this apartment.
You see Kaylee gold before she became the corpse
laid out on the couch.
In this grainy video, she's sitting on that same couch,
petting Ger, shooting the shit.
In the kitchen, you see Kaylee Silver
before she killed her friend.
She walks through the background
and grabs a beer from the fridge.
There's no label on the bottle, all is well.
Kaylee gold is laughing.
Kaylee Silver cracks her beer open, all is well.
Kaylee gold begins telling a story.
Kaylee Silver takes a swig.
Something changes.
Kaylee gold's neck snaps like she's a dog
and Kaylee Silver's a squirrel.
Gold's posture gets weird.
She lunges, reaching out for Silver's stomach
just under the neon crop top.
I need you guys to roll grip.
Pass with an 18.
I pass with a five.
I pass with a 26.
We're still at Missleman.
Kaylee Silver cries out.
You can see the fear and panic and confusion in her eyes,
both on this Furbo footage on her trembling phone
as well as on her trembling face.
In the video, she shoves her berserk bestie backward
out of frame, but when Kaylee gold comes back into view,
she's propelled herself horizontally through the air
and she spears Kaylee Silver
into and over the kitchen counter,
out of the Furbo camera's view.
You hear screams of anguish and glee
and you hear a glass bottle break
and a splash of beer hits the fridge.
But then you just hear a percussive and visceral
scrunch, scrunch, scrunch, scrunch, scrunch, scrunch.
Then silence.
Then a heartbreaking wail.
Kaylee Silver stands here, phone out, frozen,
tears filling up as much of the eyes as possible
without yet spilling down her face.
Kaylee, I'm glad you called us.
I'm glad you could trust me.
You're gonna have to go with the police now.
Can you send me that footage before you go?
Cal like glares at you
but doesn't necessarily say anything to stop that.
She hands you the phone.
I email it to myself.
Beck is just gonna kinda chime in.
He doesn't normally do this.
From behind the camera, he's a silent viewer,
but he's now seen that she's 100% been truthful with us.
You've got the proof right here, you're gonna be fine.
She attacked you.
Just as a little comforting word.
She's looking at the door
and she can sense the cops on the other side of it.
I don't think we closed the door.
Oh, okay, then she can see the six cops
just kinda like peering in, staring.
One of them's got handcuffs in their hands ready to go.
I load up the video that I just sent myself
and like go to show it to one of the cops.
As you do so, the other one walks in.
Ma'am, you have the right to remain silent.
Everything you say can and will be held against you
in a court of law.
As he's like Miranda-ing her, Cal is saying,
Kaylee, the video shows you acted in self-defense.
Just tell them the truth, everything will be fine.
It wasn't normal.
It wasn't.
What the fuck was it?
They'll find out.
Or will find out, please.
And she is walked out the door
and one of the other cops is like,
all right, camera boys, get on out of here.
Can't have you in an active crime scene.
Can I try and use my 30% stealth
to have kind of inched my way further back
into the apartment to maybe get some wider angles
of everything in the room?
I think you can do that for sure.
One.
Yeah, dude, are you serious?
I rolled a one.
Oh my God, that's amazing.
I don't know if this is the best roll to have that on,
but it's fun.
You can get any shot.
As you're getting a roll around the apartment,
you see that Kaylee Silver is an avid home brewer.
She made the beer.
Oh, that's dope.
That is super dope.
Which one?
Silver is the brewer?
Silver is the brewer, Silver's apartment.
Gold is the friend.
As soon as Silver drank the beer,
Gold's neck snapped to attention.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Thank you for that.
That's a good nugget on a crit.
That is a good nugget.
Also the kind of shit we would have spent
like five episodes not finding out.
And Zach would be like, why don't you solve my mystery?
Perfect, perfect impression.
I want to get pregnant with you.
Don't do my normal voice on the show, dude.
I've been working really hard on the podcast voice.
I want to have a baby, Thomas.
I want to have a baby with you.
Julius texts his uncle, just like two thumbs up.
We've got gold.
Fuck.
Hey Joe, should you be like a sleazy news producer?
Cal looks blank.
And he's kind of like looking around the apartment
and just shaking his head.
And he starts to walk out
and he puts his arms around both of you.
Boys, I haven't had a drink in 25 years.
As the elevator doors are about to close,
you hear Kaylee Silver holler out through the hallway.
Help me, Colorado.
You're my only hope.
You see Cal's throat like completely close up at that.
And he gulps.
I'm taking you boys to the foundry.
Ramona is scanning face to face to face
around the table.
What are you guys doing right now?
She licked me.
With that penis tongue?
She was like, so did you zoom in on it?
Oh my God.
Had you?
No.
Did you then?
Will you in the future?
For you?
Yeah.
No, not for me.
Jesus fucking Christ.
I don't want to look at it.
No, please don't.
I was never into like looking at any of those,
like, oh, two girls, one cup, a donkey man.
Like I didn't watch any of that shit.
Luke does.
Donkey man.
Oh my God.
It does look like a tongue.
You're right.
I'm bummed out.
I know.
Well.
I say again, can we restart season two?
Cause my life is great, and it's all mine.
I'm bummed out.