What's up my spooky skeletons, it's your bone pappy wolf the dog, and I'm back from the past
clapping that ass and lapping up trash here on
694.2 PTBP
contentions most coherent and easy to follow radio station
But on the off chance you disagree with that objective sentiment. We're dropping a very special
Recapulation of the entire situation going down here in contention seems like a good time for it
You know your Wolfie might take a couple notes
Even though I am a all-seeing all-knowing being and all that this week's howling with wolf is from Sinbad
Yeah, that Sinbad the mailman and jingle all the way the genie and Shazam
Wait what for real like the Berenstain Bears thing?
Fuck
Okay, what the fuck is going on around here Sinbad wasn't a genie in a movie called Shazam
How the way Sinbad how the way?
Zack the wolf what's up? This is Sinbad man understand you having a hard time with the Mandela effect man
It's not Zack told me Zack Reeves. Got me here with this. He said you having some issues man
And look I've dealt with the phenomena. It's a real phenomena. They see this a movie Shazam that I never did
But they didn't do a can we do a part two who knows they might put me in that one
So you never know, but uh, no, I never did Shazam
Never I just read the comic books and watched the TV show when I was a kid coming up. So, uh,
I'm the height. I don't know what kind of Mandela effect you going through
All I can say is this man if you're going through the Mandela effect man is messing with you mess with your mind
Not weed CBD
Not weed less weed more CBD. All right now
Listen to me
Sinbad more like sin great. Am I right folks?
I hope y'all were laughing because otherwise I'm gonna be crying
Hmm. I have an announcement here from no wait
hang on one of our stunning and cherished moderators on both discord and
Reddit he writes we've selected a winner for the second part of our
Community writing contest
choosing a setting
Congratulations to user win doula the writer behind
Alan's son to check that out and all the other great submissions follow the link in the show notes you go user
Slash win doula in a very hardy. Thanks to user slash slaughter without the s user slash
blackmokes a user slash
Aal
718 user slash
RPG burner you slash the swimming dropkick and you slash punk ass
Book jockey your submissions were delectable
The third part of the contest on NPCs opens tomorrow
We're going to be accepting multiple winners on that one
So if you have a bunch of ideas, you can absolutely hose us down with them
I'ma get all wet with the MPC's my spooky skeletons
Alright, y'all get ready for a lecture. No a refresher on the ever mounting pressure
So your weathered ears have the pleasure of being fresher than ever get ready for a festering treasure to enjoy at your leisure
While wearing your finest pleather whether your name is Heather or whatever enjoy this track forever
It is kudzu with no backbone
Unseasonably warm December 1st in a small town called
Contention a thin mist could be seen under the streetlights on an empty
Country road the inside of the contention police department
However was cozy warm and bright at the front desk every morning and every evening
Drew Andrews sat determined small teeth and big gums showing answering the phone and taking messages
in the bullpen sat our three PCs or
Protagonist cops though neither of those words seemed to factually describe these player characters
Clark Bishop was the oldest by the book officer dead set on doing his best in this dead-end job
Still living in the house. His parents left him when they died
He had never cooked and he watched Wheel of Fortune every night
Keith Vigna was raised just outside
Contention but soon moved to the city where he trained to become a police officer
His stint in the city was short-lived. He's not a bad cop. He's just a bad cop
His pants are too big
John Lee petty more the fourth was one of the few petty Moore's to stay on the right side of the law or at least
The petty Moore version of that his mustache tight pants substance abuse issues and
Inability to keep bullets in his clip aligned perfectly with both his family values and love of
Smokey and the bandit on this evening December 1st
Drew Andrews top lip receding gums akimbo received a bevy of calls complaints
Regarding the abundance of howling coming from the dogs in the old neighborhood
This neighborhood west of downtown was home to John Peters Mildred Mitchell Tildi B
Mitchell councilwoman Carrie pages and the boss of the contention police department chief
Maggie cook and it just so happened that December 1st this night when everything began was the Chiefs birthday
Drew presented chief cook with a yellow journal
Noting she already had this same notebook in both red and blue
Clark got her the same thing. He got her the year before and every year before that
He's been on the force a box of chocolates
John pulled a bottle of cheap bourbon from his desk
It was open and a third of it was gone, but he tried Keith panicked. He didn't realize it was the Chiefs birthday
However, there was a mysterious package wrapped nicely sitting on Drew's desk
Keith claimed it as his gift
But when Maggie cook opened this present and saw its contents
She began weeping walked into her office and slammed the door leaving Clark drew and John
staring and bewilderment at the new kid in town Keith vigna
chief Maggie cook distraught and determined left the contention police station without saying a word and
The box were three items a single red rose a white hardhat and a black silk bowtie
Before they could react drew Andrews received the phone call that set all of the preceding events in motion
Julie Maxwell reported a dead body at the piston junkyard the chief list
CPD headed out to investigate the scene on the way there
They spotted Julie Maxwell driving chaotically and well above the speed limit back toward town
John Lee Pettymore the fourth peeled off to pull her over just in time to see her near fatal car accident
She was thrown clear of the vehicle face smashed
crying out into the night
John called an ambulance and investigated the crash in her car
He found an open bottle of brandy gas cans lighters an unusual
Camera with strange glass tubes a red light lit and a green light unlit as well as a Polaroid
That showed the base of a tall building and a group crowding the entrance with fists raised
Everything in this picture was lit by torches and some of the people's hands in the building was a slightly shiny pitch black
Keith Vigna and Clark Bishop carried on to the piston junkyard where they found a body
splattered on the ground face first face
Smashed the body was wearing thick hand-stitched clothing and leather boots a small note in the pocket read
We is striking when the land gets darkness
readying torches
Hesitate not
Most peculiar however was the skin on this body's back a fresh wound. It was branded with the words
This is a fool
This corpse was determined to be a woman and the officers called in their fourth musketeer the only other
contention police officer Ray
To take the corpse over to County for testing
They also called the city hospital to check on Julie Maxwell's condition
She had been declared deceased
after some light discussion of smashed faces and blunt force trauma
Clark Bishop headed home to his TV dinner and Wheel of Fortune
Keith Vigna went back to his temporary home hotel motel where his golden retriever bean
Waited patiently and John Lee Pettymore the fourth shot some pool by himself at clinkers the local watering hole and daycare
The next day on December 2nd three assignments awaited the three officers
Councilwoman Carrie pages dog was missing and she was distraught
The councilwoman suggested Tyler may have been eaten by a person as contention had just seen a rise in
Homelessness Clark printed posters and walk the neighborhood all to no avail
Jimmy Sanders an uncle of sorts to John Lee Pettymore called in an oil spill across a country road in the southeast
Sometime around 4 a.m
John checked it out found no oil spill and Jimmy admitted he was tripping on mushrooms during the incident
Mildred Mitchell
contentions kooky pothead grandma
Wanted someone to know her neighbor's door was open and this neighbor this John Peters
Hadn't been around in a few days
Keith found out she saw a bright flash of light from Peters's place a few nights previous and he's been missing ever since
He checked it out and found John's mail overflowing his car in the driveway and his front door
Smashed into the drywall in the house were broken pictures and clear signs that John was a heavy drinker
There was also a trunk in the living room
Burned into the top of this trunk were the words
Do not open if you want to live the trunk was empty save some foam padding that held four
specifically shaped items one large to medium and one small
There were betting stubs on John's nightstand. He bet on long shots and mostly lost
John's keychain had his house keys a bottle opener his car keys a few small keys that said
G10
G11 and G12 and a key fob for a rewards program at dirty dog
grooming a pet salon franchise in the city
However, John didn't seem to have a dog
According to Drew Andrews John Peters wasn't very interesting though. He did have a long stay in the hospital a couple years ago
After meeting back up the three officers decided to look further into John Peters starting again at his home
When they arrived his car was no longer in the driveway and the empty trunk was missing from inside the residence
Mildred Mitchell came by to let them know two people came packed up the trunk into their white Toyota and took off
One in their car and the other in John Peters maroon vehicle
The officers headed to chief Maggie cooks house next her cruiser wasn't there. She wasn't there
They hit up clinkers
The only information from Harry clinker was that Keith liked to cut up hot dogs on white bread when he was a kid
continuing this tour of
Contention the cops went out to harass Leo piston the owner of the piston junkyard who had a restraining order placed against him by
Julie Maxwell 15 years before after Leo was accused of killing Julie's sister Ashley
Clark set up a meeting with Leo and George the piston brothers for the following day
Keith stayed behind to keep a hidden eye on the piston pig farm back at the police station
John found the Chiefs blue notebook full of work appointments and notes
But her red notebook and the newly gifted yellow notebook weren't in her office
That's about the time when contention received a chilling phone call the city hospital had fucked up
They heard screaming from inside a drawer in the morgue
Julie Maxwell was alive. John Lee pettymore took off for the city hospital to get some answers
Clark came into the office to an equally confusing message from County
Apparently that body from the junkyard had the organs of someone who died 200 years ago
But the skin and hair of someone who died yesterday
Then Charles a drunk man and friend of the missing John Peters came to the station to figure out what was going on
Before pulling a gun and running away upon hearing the sound of a car crash in the parking lot
Out of the piston pig farm Kathy piston shot the encroaching and trespassing Keith vigna in the foot
Recognizing him though
She bandaged his wound and offered her apologies for the incident after Keith claimed to have a warrant
She offered him coffee Keith snooped around her property
Failing to find anything of interest until he eventually stowed away on Kathy piston school bus full of homeless people
Afraid of being caught though. He bailed out of the emergency hatch in the back further hurting his shot and bandaged foot in
In the parking lot of the city hospital a creepy figure obscured by a black cloak and hood
Approached John Lee pettymore the fourth this mysterious man handed John a note written in binary and croaked
Say hello to me
Before softly cackling and disappearing into the rows of parked cars
John texted drew a picture of the binary note to translate and he radioed the only other
Contention police officer Tim to do a search for storage facilities and contention with G units
John didn't find Julie Maxwell at the hospital because she dipped stole a black SUV and made a beeline for contention
This was of course the same black SUV that just t-boned George Pistons truck in the parking lot of the contention
police station now helmed at gunpoint by a kidnapped Leo
Piston the three officers pursued Julie Maxwell and Leo piston in the stolen black SUV out to splashylvania
The abandoned vampire themed waterpark Ashley Maxwell was heading to 15 years ago when her life ended
Bishop pettymore and hobbling vigna found their targets at the top of the two-fanged plunge
Maxwell with a pistol to the back of the kneeling Leo pistons torso
She cried out into the night
Except for the black shiny devil and the underground temple from which it shall rise
But if there's a tiny chance that justice matters, then my sister deserves this
To bleed out and die
With that she fired a shot through Leo's body
Clark immediately pulled his pistol and put a bullet through one of Julie Maxwell's eyes the two limp
bodies slid slowly down the two opposing slides
Wet for the first time in a decade and a half with the blood of these opposing contention residents
But at the bottom of the ride
Something incomprehensible happened
the bodies of Julie Maxwell and Leo piston were picked up and slammed into the ground repeatedly and at an
Absurd rate by some unseen force and then as if they were never there at all
Both bodies were gone
Keith saw
Covering the ground where the two bodies just were a black shiny viscous sludge
Seemingly inside this muck were the thrashing bodies of Julie Maxwell and Leo piston their hands reached out
Trying to escape this thing that had them trapped with their limbs soon seemed to fold
Into this ooze becoming one with the sentient mass of goop that began sliding across the ground toward Keith who?
Promptly Wile E. Coyote the fuck out of there
Back in the splashylvania parking lot the strange camera's green light was lit
John took a picture causing a blindingly bright flash of light and he instantly saw black
Viscous goo dripping from the camera all over his hands, and then it was gone
The picture was of a short balding man with large eyes and a tiny nose
He was bent over head and hands and stocks made of a shiny black material and the word
Fool was branded into his forehead
Clark recognized this man as they're missing John Peters
Drew Andrews texted John back with the translation of the mysterious man's binary message it read
I killed the Chiefs pops John
Before they called it a day Keith went to the clinic and acquired a wheelchair
That night these three contentioned police officers had some strange dreams
John Lee petty more the fourth
You're reliving the moment when you saw the black sludge on your hands and dripping from the odd camera and picture
Your perception changes and you're out of your body looking at yourself staring intently at your own hands
You see there's the same viscous muck dripping from your eyes and nostrils
As you wake up in bed
Keith vigna, you see a woman standing before you in your bedroom
She's wearing old-timey clothing and she stares angrily at you
She lunges toward you picking you up and throwing you into the ground and you fall
Into the floor of your bedroom and then wake up in bed
Clark Bishop
You see a man underneath you
Struggling to breathe as you tighten your grip around his neck you look up after the life leaves his eyes
And see an empty dark alleyway as you wake up on the couch with infomercials playing on your TV
The next day was December 3rd
The officers broke into g10 g11 and g12 John Peters storage units at a plus storage
G10 was filled with crates stacked three high each crate was wooden and stamped US military on the side
Inside these crates were guns ammunition and heavy weaponry
This included pistols shotguns rifles a shoulder-mounted
anti-aircraft weapon an EMP rifle a grappling gun a small gun that shoots tracers
Lots of grenades a sniper rifle a very tiny but very powerful gun and a drone
There was also a pallet on which was sitting a large cube-shaped
Object covered in so much plastic wrap that its contents were obfuscated
The large cube-shaped object was in fact bricks upon bricks of cocaine
precisely
479 bricks of cocaine worth around 12 million dollars John took a brick
Immediately inside g11 was a burlap sack containing
$50,000 in shredded blue dye stained banknotes a piece of notebook paper with poorly drawn
diagrams and nearly illegible writing
225 pound bags of potatoes a ziplock bag
containing five bulbs of garlic a garlic crusher an empty test tube and a syringe a small
drawstring Nike bag a 3 million candlepower
handheld spotlight a well-filled toolbox a black leather backpack
containing a set of lock picks wire cutters wire strippers a crimping tool flat and Phillips head screwdrivers and a
lockout tool a bottle of caffeine pills a carton of cigarettes three shovels a small digital scale a syringe labeled morphine a
handful of ski masks walkie-talkies and a burned CD labeled
monster mash mash
Inside g12 was a four-wheeler with dried dirt and clay
Caked all over the thing as well as a couple of plastic trunks near the door was a small chunk of paper that had been
Folded into the size of a business card against the back wall was a small table with some more papers on it
The small chunk of paper on the floor was a bedding guide and inside were some more ripped up bedding stubs
someone lost
$5,000 on October 31st the three names to bet on were Oz mayhem wolf miles
Detonator Carver and Carl blitzkrieg Anderson at the bottom it said
Tonight versus planet juggernaut
The stubs were all losers a five-to-one bet then a six-to-one bet then finally a thirty-to-one bet
Inside one of the trunks was a box of assorted batteries spools of electrical wiring three
disassembled handguns and an impossibly clean machete sitting atop three full suits
Including shirt tie and shoes all covered in dirt clay and black stains
That look to be blood there was a note handwritten on a scrap piece of paper that read
The cabin is in the woods stark west from the end of the trail about 2.5 miles
Dash-k we took care of nine of them as well as the leader
There was also a sheet that seemed to be ripped out of a notebook
It was handwritten as well, but in different handwriting and it said
The work is difficult in particular, but I've had 12 successes
Life isn't as complex as they believe they are quite simple
It will be their downfall and the last piece of paper was a cutout from the contention Chronicle from 25 years ago an
ad that read Kohl's orphanage new school under modern etiquette
We are here to serve the beautiful community of contention
None of the rogue police officers remembered the name of that orphanage though. The coal name was familiar
Silas Cole was one of the founders of this town and he was the owner of the mine for a couple of years
His wife Mary Cole did a lot of good in the town and the library was named after her
The school was called Silas Cole K through 12 and there was a Cole's Creek as well as the three
Approached the other plastic trunk in g12 this one with the lid fastened. The stench was nearly
Unbearable it was decided they would wait to open this trunk back at the office after having a u-haul delivered
Pettimore Bishop and vigna packed up everything contained in these storage units and brought it all back to the police station
the awfully pungent trunk was clear and
Before opening the lid they could only see a dried black crust which was painted on every bit of the trunk sides
When they opened it the rancid smell of old metal hit their nostrils and atop this pile of what looked like a messily
chopped up human body
Sat a woman's head split down the middle and pulled apart with a small silver sphere
Sitting in between the two halves Keith took a picture John pocketed this small silver sphere
Before heading out to the woods drew was tasked with looking into finding information about Cole's
Orphanage and also finding someone who could understand the machinery in the diagram out in the woods the contention
Police officers found a patch of land that had been burned to the ground
Realized they were being watched freaked out wrecked the four-wheeler ran into trees and overall just super fucked up
Topped off by Clark flying a drone into himself after their failed nature excursion
They went to Julie Maxwell's wore her taxidermy and found a circled the yellow pages ad for dr
Marie Jacobs as well as a receipt from Forgotten Treasures a local flea market
Aftergotten Treasures they learned that the camera Julie Maxwell purchased was from Mildred Mitchell's booth
But Mildred was unaware of any items recently sold at her booth
She told the boys it must have been her granddaughter till DB who came downstairs at that exact moment
But the sight of cops spooked her and she bolted back upstairs and into her room
When Clark busted until DB Mitchell had a crazed look in her eyes
She slammed a large bullet into the chamber and squeezed the trigger on this odd-looking
Revolver there was an almost blinding flash of light
Illuminating everything and then as if she had never been there the girl was gone
Clark just saw an odd gun fall to the floor confused
He checked the closet and under the bed for the missing girl unsurprisingly with no luck
The very anti
antiheroes of this story then went to Forgotten Treasures to ask more questions and they
Eventually bullied the nice lady there until she put her own life in danger by telling these cops about the drunk man who threatened her
They left after they got what they wanted and the white Toyota they had been searching for was right outside
It peeled out onto the road after a short dangerous pursuit. The white Toyota was bested tireless and boxed in
Bullets were whizzing past him. So Keith Vigna attempted to fire a warning shot with his shotgun
However, this warning shot promptly killed the driver Charles Donovan
John Lee Pettymore fired shots into the air to disperse the growing crowd and a few stray bullets also hit Clark's tires
Inside the white Toyota they found two guns a wallet with ID for Billy Harrison a
Rifle and keys with a Dodge logo on the deceased man's person
They found ID from the city for Charles Donovan and a piece of paper with the addresses of both
John Peters's house and the piston pig farm
The keys in the ignition included a key to a room at Hotel Motel and a key fob for the rewards
Program at dirty dog grooming the dead driver's body had scratches all over the arm's hand
Legs and face they were not claw marks
They were not from brush John recognized these scratches as the pattern of human hands and the trunk was a
Tied-up and unconscious man who matched the picture in the ID for Billy Harrison
Additionally, there was a police uniform a set of scrubs in a black suit in these clothes
They found a contention badge for an officer
Kissel an ID in the scrubs that said dr
Zebrowski and inside a pocket of the black suit or FBI credentials for an agent parks
They called an ambulance and Keith asked the medics to look at his foot first
Still worried about his recovery Keith took the ambulance to the contention clinic with the unconscious bald man
Clark's final words to Keith before the ambulance doors shut
Keep him cuffed
Officers Bishop and petty more headed to the suburbs to chat with dr
Marie Jacobs when they saw an unkempt man James the mill worker in rubber waders
Frantically vacuuming his lawn from across the street two children stared
unblinking
Horrified as the unkempt James began to float up into the air
Clark and John each grabbed a leg but the man continued to rise John called the two kids into action one holding
Desperately onto the vacuum as the other sucked up this unknown substance with the hose their plans seemed to work
All feet were now grounded in this oily sludge poured itself away down into the sewage drain
but then the vacuum
exploded engulfing the twin children in its contents this viscous ichor
As the fourth graders folded into the writhing mass
James the mill worker lost his shit and wriggled free from Clark's helping grasp turned restraint
when John pulled up next to the on-the-run unkempt man in rubber waders James looked the
mustachioed copper in the face and then broke
Completely the mill worker sprinted back home on the same street leaving Clark Bishop and John Lee petty more the fourth right outside their initial
destination the home of dr. Marie Jacobs
At the contention clinic Billy Harrison finally woke up
He had a concussion and had been unconscious for some time
Cuffed to the bed with officer Keith Vigna asking him a bunch of questions Billy answered slowly
He didn't remember some things. He was 31 years old. He remembered going to John Peters's house
John John was an old friend who hadn't responded to his messages or answered the phone in a couple days
They played video games together Billy remembered looking in the window and John didn't answer the door
Billy didn't know a Charles Donovan Keith told Billy he was tied up in the back of this Charles person's car
Billy said he drove a white van to John's house earlier that day Billy said he's on leave from the army
Billy said he doesn't know any dog groomers
Then Billy asked to be uncuffed since he was the victim of a crime
Now do you think Keith Vigna a
reacted rationally or
B
Escalated the situation became hostile and tried to handcuff Billy's other hand if you answered B
Congratulations, that's exactly right
And because it's Keith Vigna when he went to handcuff Billy's free hand the one-handed concussed
Probable victim of kidnapping got the drop on the officer pulled Keith's gun from its holster and threatened to shoot
Keith understood in this moment that Billy was willing to pull the trigger and so Keith surrendered
Officer beans unlocked Billy Harrison's handcuff and turned around which allowed the bald fit man to not Keith the fuck out
Back in the suburbs Clark Bishop and John Lee petty more the fourth had a rough go trying to get any information from dr
Marie Jacobs who did not want to open the front door
She asked if they had a warrant Clark remembering she bought the radio asked about it
And she told them the radio wasn't even there anymore
Apparently a tall drunk man came and took it by force
With a gun John decided they had reasonable suspicion for search and seizure
So he knocked down the door gun
Obviously drawn the Jacobs house was a wreck and there was a haze in the air
Clark and John could hear Marie talking down in the basement in this mad
Scientists house there was something covering every piece of counter space jars and beakers were sitting everywhere
It smelled absolutely
terrible kind of like shit
John found a litter box, but the fecal matter inside looked
Human
This was the moment John decided dr
Jacobs was for sure a witch Clark and John heard a man's voice meow in the basement
Quite the sight in comparison to her usual state. Dr. Jacobs had mascara all over her face and was wearing white coveralls and
neoprene gloves
After making eye contact with John for the first time the incredulous and crazed doctor invited him to join her in the kitchen
John and Clark having seen enough arrested and handcuffed dr. Marie Jacobs, but then she hollered
she hollered
And a glumping sound could be heard of something or someone
Bounding up the stairs on the evening of December 3rd officer Keith Vigna
Woke up wearing a thin gown with both of his wrists
Handcuffed to the sides of the hospital bed where Billy Harrison was recently confined
Keith's uniform Keith's gear and Billy Harrison were nowhere to be seen
However, the door to this room was now open and a decent amount of the clinic staff was standing around just outside
Some of them were pointing their phones at Keith
All of them were laughing a few phrases murmured loud enough to make out included
No wonder William was so embarrassed by him and oh isn't that Keith beans?
What's he calling himself now when they actually noticed Keith waking up
They awkwardly shuffled away and a young woman came into the room with bolt cutters and broke the links on the cuffs leaving officer Keith
Vigna with a pair of nice iron bracelets after collecting himself Keith checked the security footage and
Watched Billy Harrison walk right out the front door wearing his uniform
Back in the suburbs John had handcuffed. Dr
Marie Jacobs and something was running up the stairs that something was a bloody man wearing only
Briefs and a collar and he galloped up the stairs on all fours before tackling Clark into the ground
John kicked the man off Clark who recognized. Dr.
Marie Jacobs's husband Doug Jacobs from the family portraits around the house that included the couple and their black cat Salem
After they handcuffed Doug John asked dr. Jacobs why her husband is a cat man named Salem and Marie was like
Oh, so, you know
When asked why the officers arrived John said it was illegal to have a cat in a man's body. Dr
Jacobs argued there were no laws
Disallowing this sort of activity and preferring the current situation. She asked the cops to leave her be they claimed they just wanted information
So she told them she believed the radio did it the radio she purchased at Forgotten Treasures the officers wanted the radio
But like she said it was stolen a tall drunk man broke in punched poor Salem in the face and stole the radio
With coercion and a cat toy Clark and John got dr
Marie Jacobs and the cat Salem and the body of Doug Jacobs into the back of their police cruiser took them into the station
Made a human-sized cat bed in one of the cells and locked up the pair in the only cell not full of contraband from John
Peters's units at a plus storage
John went to pick Keith up at the clinic and found him standing outside in a hospital gown wearing handcuffs with the chain cut
Back at the station Clark forced drew to come to terms with Doug Jacobs being a cat man
After everyone reconvene drew had a word with John alone
Apparently Lauren the fourth and only other member of the contingent police department was
Confused about the amount of blood and gore at splashylvania
Drew said he told her a deer fell off a water slide and
Then he asked if it had something to do with all the cocaine locked up in the jail cell
He continued figuring John might be interested in unloading the whole pallet for around
Ten million dollars drew had a contact in the city called the Duke
They walked back in to talk to Clark and Keith and John said he had good news
Drew had fixed the four-wheeler
Following the lead of the room key from Hotel Motel found in Charles Donovan's possession
The three officers busted into the deceased man's room at Hotel Motel
guns drawn and without a warrant
There they found a woman dressed similarly to her favorite TV character the Fonz
This woman we now know as Rosemary flinged a knife at officer Vigna and hid on the other side of the bed
Keith ran up and engaged her in hand-to-hand combat which resulted in a hostage situation
Knife to his throat officer Vigna proceeded to brag about killing her coworker
Thankfully for his throat though the level-headed and highly persuasive officer Bishop managed to keep Rosemary from killing him there on the spot
By getting her talking Clark asked if she knew Charles they had worked together
Rosemary laughed and asked if they know who they're fucking with because they were fucking with Marvin Glass
the mob kingpin in the city
When asked about the radio she thought maybe the thing in the bathroom was a radio
Charles had brought it back but more importantly
Marvin sent them there to find out what happened to Jermaine Glass and Alfred Glass when they came to collect money from John Peters
Only Alfred came back, but he came back a blubbering idiot. He wouldn't shut up about some gun. He sounded like a lunatic
The wiry old lady made a run for it and leapt over the railing and into the Hotel Motel parking lot all three officers
Unloaded their weapons from the second floor corridor bringing her down
Barely before she could get into her vehicle
The boys in blue patched her up called an ambulance and sent her to the city hospital with Lauren the fourth and only other
Contention police officer with that they planned a sting operation based around a false radio call to catch Billy
Harrison the stranger running around contention in an official police uniform
They figured he like everyone else wanted John Peters
Unfortunately for the CPD the FBI was watching and also wanted to talk to John Peters
Strangely though agents Kennedy and McKinley a young woman with an erratic accent and an old man with empty eyes
Were in town looking for a black Nike bag with nothing in it
They thought John Peters would know where this bag was
They were correct in this line of thinking as there was indeed a black Nike bag in unit
G11 at a plus storage to which John Peters held the key
After some verbal dancing the federal agents agreed to meet the contention squad the following morning
December 4th at the police department when the officers met back up at the station to figure out what to do with their illegal seizures
Drew was uncommonly not at his desk
Replaced instead by a note telling them he went to the chief's house
officers Bishop and Pettymore hauled off the
Undocumented loot to their individual residences while Keith went to the chief's house to check on drew in the entrance of chief
Maggie cooks home Keith found two
Unconscious men drew Andrews and an unknown with ID for a Harold Dorsey from the city in the living room
He saw chief Maggie cooks body in full uniform
Slumped against the wall a large chef's knife rested in her left hand her face had been stabbed
Repeatedly and her left foot was missing
That's when he noticed the smell
gasoline and natural gas in the kitchen an
unkempt man was at the table hunched over with a fork in one hand and a pistol in the other a
Bullet hole in his head had left him face down in a plate of meat his left foot was also missing
Gas cans sat all over the place and the contents had clearly been poured on
Everything the range had all four burners turned all the way up and a skillet sat atop
Inside were the leftovers of two feet that had the meat pulled from them
He threw up and fell to his hands and knees his hand hit a wire
He heard a click and saw a fire near the front door and a path of gasoline
Heading back toward the kitchen with just enough time to save one person Keith dragged drew Andrews out the front door as the entire
house
Exploded knocking Keith into the front yard and rendering him unconscious
Keith
Standing in your childhood home
It's your birthday
And your friends are standing around this table waiting for you to blow out the candles on your cake
You look up and see your parents in the corner talking to your little brother
You squeeze your eyes tightly as you blow out your candles and as you do you see that black shiny viscous sludge
Inside this muck are two thrashing bodies their hands reach out trying to escape this thing that has trapped them
But the struggle does not last long their limbs seem to fold into this ooze becoming one with the sentient mass of goop
That is now sliding across the ground toward you opening your eyes
You see all of your peers around your childhood kitchen table laughing at you
The candles are still lit you look up your parents are poorly attempting to hold back laughter. You look at the cake
It's gone
You have a plate that is clean and you look around and see everyone else is eating a piece of cake
They're all laughing and begin to chant while pointing at you beans beans Keith beans his only friends are
figurines beans beans keys beans will blow your friends to smithereens
Your parents look at you
Disgusted and turn and walk out of the room you run to follow them
But looking ahead you only see that woman dressed in old-timey clothing looking down you fall
Fall into a black hole in the ground and you're standing in a cold
Dark room the lights begin to flicker on and you see massive tanks the size of grain silos
Standing right before you is yourself. You walk up to you the face of the other you begins to age
Rapidly and then just as rapidly ages in reverse you walk up to one of the massive tanks in this dank dimly lit room
You press your face against it to see its contents and something
Creeps toward you and as it's about to come into focus you wake up to the sound of sirens
officers Bishop and petty more were soon called to the Chiefs house after it had exploded leaving behind
The burned bodies of Harold Dorsey chief Maggie cook and an unkempt man with a bullet hole in his head
And his face in a pile of foot meat that man
We now know was James the mill worker the three cops decided they needed to go to dr
Millar the dentist and contention to verify and match the dental records of the three deceased folks
Clark looked in the Chiefs car and it was clean the glove box was empty the dashcam been unplugged
Clark checked the GPS history chief Maggie Cook's cruiser had been at the mill on the other side of the city
since the evening of December 1st
That night the strange dreams
continued John Lee petty more the fourth
The sky is dark
But the ground begins to give light to the world
You see a man in the distance with his head and hands and stocks that sit on an inky black
Stage as you walk toward this man the ground becomes wider and wider like a screens brightness level being gradually turned up
You hear a holler from behind you and when you turn around you see your mother she looks
She looks like she did when she was about your age and she's crying
She looks past you and the door appears in between you but you can hear her say I'm so sorry
He's just so beautiful. You don't have to do this. We can leave we can run
The door floats up into the sky and sitting behind it is that trunk you locked up in the police department with the woman
split head atop the black
Putrid hacked-up
Anatomy you turn around and you're face to face with a man in the stocks
John Peters his forehead burned and peeling with the word fool
Desperate his eyes widen and he whispers, please
It's coming
They are playing the roles of greater men. You have to save everyone
It is coming
You
Clark Bishop
You're walking through a parking lot you look down
You see you're carrying a piece of old parchments rolled up with a neat little string tied tightly around it
Looking up you hand it to the cashier at your local grocery store. You like this guy
Starting to scan the scroll, but it's not beeping. He looks at you and chuckles
This is going to cost you greatly
as you walk out of the grocery store you step into the sanctuary of a church during a funeral a
young boy with an enormous forehead in the darkest eyes you've ever seen is walking up to you and tears are
streaming down his face as he stares into your eyes you hear a small voice inside you that says
Please sir as the crying boy holds out his hands as you hand the scroll to the young boy
You begin to hear cries throughout the sanctuary
You're standing in as you look around the congregation is trying to run away
But they're melting into the floor you look down and you two are melting into the floor when you look up
The boy has been replaced by Tildi B Mitchell who looks down at you with her finger pointed at you like a gun
She disappears and reappears over and over again as you slowly sink into the floor as your eyes
Look to the ceiling of the chapel you hear a voice
Inside you say let go as you wake up in bed
John awoke to a text from Drew Andrews it reads
Clark came by last night when no one was at the station. He warned me not to go to the cheese house
He was limping, but he wasn't limping later. What is going on and where is all the cake?
There was also a text from Keith explicitly asking John for drugs
He rolled out of bed bagged up some coke and headed into the police station for work and a meeting with the FBI
Without a reply from officer petty more confirming he would bring some of the cocaine officer vigna
Drove up and broke into John Lee petty Moore's house to find it. This was cocaine
They stole from a storage unit after finding the key at the home of a missing person
At the station a news report played over the radio a
Fire at the city hospital had claimed the lives of more than 20 individuals
The names of the deceased are not being released yet more importantly to the officers
However was the decision of what to order for breakfast
Finally deciding on bishops big bean breakfast from beans on beans
Drew remembered that two children were reported missing from the suburbs
Aiden and Alice little John and Clark shot each other
Glance and then John changed the subject to the matter of a second Clark Bishop
Drew explained what happened on his end Clark came in around 1 a.m
Limping wearing a hoodie and jeans and told drew not to go to chief Maggie Cook's house
But Clark was attempting the sting operation with John and Keith at 1 a.m
The security footage showed Clark Bishop limping in and out the door in street clothes
So they decided moving forward. They would use a code word to assure each other
They were each dealing with the real version of themselves that code word
bubble gum tree as Keith vigna pulled back into the parking lot with breakfast a blacked-out SUV
Parked in agents Kennedy and McKinley hopped out from the passenger and back seats and headed in
Keith grabbed the food and Nike bag and followed them into the police station
Agent McKinley the old dead-eyed man scanned the office saw John started freaking out turning and sprinting away
Passing Keith as he ran back out into the lot
Agent Kennedy apologized for him saying their last mission went poorly and he's lost it a bit
Agent Kennedy also said she's from Minnesota with a weird Irish accent. The officers said they wanted answers
She promised to give information
After she put something in that bag
John asked if it was something strange
Yes
Agent Kennedy pulled out a small lockbox two inches by two inches with a combination lock on it
Inside was a small metal sphere with a diameter of one inch
She dropped the sphere into the bag and immediately breathed a sigh of relief
Clark looked into the bag
Nothing. He asked about the ball
She said it's why agent McKinley is so unintelligible now
So John called agent Kennedy to the back of the station to look at their cat man when she was more intrigued than confused
John freaked out and told the agent that there's a weird gun and a weird radio and a weird camera and the weird radio made
That guy into a cat man. Plus there's oil all over the place agent Kennedy side
She guessed that meant that they were in
She'd be right back
She walked out of the station
And walked back in with Billy Harrison
Billy Harrison
the bald fit man
Holding Keith's gun and belt atop his nicely folded uniform
Keith grabbed his shit and walked back to his desk and Billy said he hoped Keith was feeling better
Agent Kennedy dropped the bad accent and told Harrison all three officers had seen a lot of shit
She knew he wanted to get home. So maybe they should just leave the number and the bag and bail
He nodded Kennedy turned to the three cops and drew Andrews
You're completely fucked
Luckily for you all though. I'm gonna leave this bag here with you anything you put in it disappears. That's all we know about it
It's a myth even within this community who have seen the unnatural at work
But we have seen today all of us here that agent Victor's Nike bag is real
Guys, the world does not work the way we all grew up knowing it to be you're all charged now with understanding that
That understanding of the world will cause your lies to crumble
But the thing that keeps us going is that daily we are saving the human race from being wiped out of existence
I'm gonna leave this here with you all and you'll be given a secure location to drop it when the job is done
Your job is to stop the incursion
Minimize exposure save lives and cover the whole thing up to save others from being exposed
We're gonna give you the same information that all newcomers game which is a phone number
You give them a call when the situation is taken care of or if things get completely out of hand or they'll call in
48 hours if you don't
Good luck
Let's go back now to the past to a young Clark Bishop in his childhood home
The same home he lives in now back then the plastic was on the couch. There were angel wings and pictures of Jesus
Clark is playing in the living room
His parents are in the kitchen cooking and Wheel of Fortune is on like always in the background
Clark's mom pulls him close to repeat her go-to motto life is like the bonus round
We were already given the best letters and then she sends little Clark off to see mr
Gerald fingers in at the Mary Cole library contentions public book depository
With lemon poppy seed muffins in hand the library smells musty it's rarely used by the community
Gary Daly owner and operator of the daily fuzz having a loud conversation with mr.
Fingers and about occult books and currently open in front of him is the true and horrifying confessions of the st. Osseith witches
Clark presents the poppy seed muffins and fingers and puts the baked goods with the other batches due to his gluten intolerance
the phone rings
Gerald answers
Gerald says it was for Clark. He says the voice on the other line said that Clark has the best letters
the voice sounded panicked and
screamed a little
Outside the sky turns dark
The immediate lack of sunlight is noticed inside the Mary Cole library
Strange forms of tall gaunt men begin moving around outside the library a
Figure in the darkness wearing a cloak is locking the doors of the library from the outside with a massive chain
He turns and runs and out of one of the windows
You see a massive flash of light a gigantic shadow moves out of frame
It's an enormous but thin man in a black suit sprinting away from the cloaked figure
Drawed opens a window light comes back into the world and everything seems as it once was
Clark looks at mr. Daly who's staring at his book Gary looks up and asks if there was a big cloud mr.
Fingers and thinks the occult books must have something to do with this so Daly reads aloud what he'd been reading when it went dark
And
Casting her eyes aside
She saw a spirit lift up a cloth line over a pot looking much like a ferret and it being asked of this
Examine it why the spirit did look upon her
She said it was hungry this
Examine it being asked how she knew the names of mother Bennett spirits say if the Tiffin her spirit did tell this
Examine it that she had two spirits the one of them like a black dog and the other red like a lion and that their
Names were sucking and layered and sayeth that sucking did plague by its wife on to death and the other
Plagued three of his beasts where of two of them died
But before he could finish the three decide to not speak of this again when Clark arrives home
When he turns the corner his mind can't quite handle what it's seeing and it begins to fragment
One scene then another first he sees his house in perfect condition
His consciousness changes channels and he sees police officers everywhere it flips again
Everything's normal it flips again and two black sedans are outside the house
Flips again. Everything's normal as he walks into the house. There's a flash
He sees his parents have been lifted off the ground and are half
Inside the walls of the home their faces are frozen and cold and white with the lack of blood it flips again
Everything looks normal
But he hears voices it flips he sees people someone says yeah
We well we couldn't find the artifact and we had to get the fuck out of there cuz Karen did her goddamn
Magic trick again, and then everything is normal. Then he hears whispers. Then he sees a man wearing a suit
Oh shit, it's a fucking kid man Clark is sitting in a courtroom in contention and he's trying to think back on that day
But he can't remember anything except for how normal it all was
How his house just looked normal
But empty it just weren't there anymore
But here there's a woman
She's on trial. She's being convicted right now for the death of Clark's parents. Her name is Anne love
She's cold and vacant, but she's always smiling and her asymmetrical bangs cover one of her eyes
on the stand she says
Yes, I did it and I'd do it again
Back in current times the officers went to the Daily Fuh after Gary Daly called in to report information about the Chiefs disappearance
Gary Daly was the longtime partner of Harry Klinker and the owner operator of the Daily Fuh a
Contention staple that had been around for generations
Gary Daly was an older man
He wore jeans cuffed halfway up his calves and a nice short sleeve button-down with tiny cartoon bean sprouts printed all over it
He asked if the officers remembered when he would help watch them down at Klinker's when they were but wee little fellas and
Invited them back to his office some of the art hanging in the walls of the Daily Fuh
However caught the boys attention
One was a circle with a star inside of it inside that star was another star and there were a couple
Triangles curved lines and tiny circles as well a fun take on the chaoticness of the universe
Another was a tree branch with three twigs growing on one side and two twigs growing on the other
It was in a bunch of old texts that Gary had seen at different museums and libraries from various cultures and eras
Another print was a black circle with six black dots
Surrounding it an ancient sign for a group that might have existed called the circle of knowledge
They tried to keep the world together
The last was a wonky question mark with two additional lines one curved and one straight
jutting down from the question marks dot a
symbol of a land unknown
Anyway, Gary had heard Harold Dorsey was in town and wanted a blog post at what's behind Dorsey dot blogspot.com written about the
Daily Fuh
So he was kind of sort of stalking Harold Dorsey
He followed Dorsey to the Chiefs house and saw a guy holding the chief and James at gunpoint
The guy with the gun was overweight wearing all black and had a big scar over his right eye
James was wearing rubber waders and the chief seemed off
She didn't stand up straight the way chief cook would in the phone book
They found an address for James Keith remembered the hunched over unkempt guy at the Chiefs house was wearing rubber
waders John
Remembered the unkempt man with the vacuum was wearing rubber waders and the address for James matched
Just down the street from dr. Marie Jacobs house
Let's go once again into the past to a young John Lee Pettymore the fourth just after the moment that ended his sprint car
racing career
John Lee Pettymore the fourth and Don D Pettymore John's dad's cousin
Are sitting in the back of an ambulance and the EMT is checking out John. She tells the young Pettymore
There's just no way he'll ever race again
Don grabs John's face and tells him he's got to give up on this dream now and they hug
Don pushes John in a wheelchair out to the parking lot
But from the rear Don sees two figures begin approaching
They're both extremely tall with large gaunt frames
They begin walking faster and faster toward the two Don starts running with the wheelchair
But the two figures are catching up there's no one else around they're both wearing black suits and their skin is weirdly
Translucent one of them starts screaming John hollers get at the fanciest men
He's ever seen and the Pettymore boys make it to the parking lot just in time to see their car
Now being flipped over by large Eddie and his pit crew John yells at large Eddie and large Eddie
Approaches the two petty Moore's Eddie swings
Don catches large Eddie's hand
Mudders under his breath and large Eddie's hand starts sizzling like a country fried steak on a Sunday morning
Smoke starts coming out of there Eddie screams Don holds on before dropping it and hitting him once more in the face
Eddie runs off hollering
Don helps the concussed John Lee Pettymore the fourth into their car
Back in the current timeline the officers went to the first Church of Contingent on the way there
They noticed a strange occurrence the creek though
It was a chilly December day was filled to the brim with animals of all sorts dogs cats possums
Raccoons town creatures of all kinds the FCC was hosting a lunch for anyone who needed it made by the pastor's wife and children
And served by the youth group
Keith vigna impatient and rude broke into pastor Adam Kane's office and stole the old motorcycle helmet from off his desk
The helmet had some tubes on either side with one green and one red light and the red light was lit
But hey
It turns out maybe Keith is a monster to be around because his dad was a dick who clearly preferred Keith's older brother Ferguson
Way back when they were children while playing on their family's sprawling estate
Keith and Ferguson heard the alarm sirens blaring as strange gaunt men in suits appeared to fall from the sky
However, they were promptly shot down by the beans security personnel that night William being sat the boys down and told them
What happened is exactly why they have security and he added the most important thing is
Ferguson safety William took Ferguson to his workshop leaving Keith to hide an eavesdrop
That's when he told Ferguson why he was so important
He said he didn't know how much longer he'd be around
He had hoped that he would be the one to fulfill the prophecy, but it is not him. It is Ferguson
Ferguson is the anointed when the time is right
he must go back and save the world and with that he handed Ferguson a watch and
Promised that it would fit when the time was right
Back in whatever year it is now the officers took the pastor's helmet to the police station and locked it up in the evidence room
Along with the other items from the booth at Forgotten Treasures the gun camera and radio all in separate lockers
They were all showing a red light except for the camera green light lit
Outside the station John took a picture of Keith with this glass
Two-blind camera and there was a massive flash of bright light and an inky black substance was all over John's hands and
Dripping down from the camera and the picture it was pooling on the ground and they could swear it was moving
Then they blinked and the substance was gone
John's hands were clean and he was just holding this odd device and even odder
Picture the camera's light was red again and the picture showed two men in a room made of darkness
They could barely make out the two figures in the picture
Thanks to the light from a small candle also made out of a substance without color
The candle was sitting on a table made of the same
unbelievably black texture of the two men one was a slender muscular man in a black t-shirt
Revealing tribal tattoo sleeves on both arms going down his hands to his fingertips
He was kneeling before the other man who looked like a no bullshit actual cowboy
This man this cowboy seemed to be looking into the camera
Holding his hand up to block his face from the cameras flash and sight on
their way to the mill on the other side of the city the officers drove on a bridge over a creek and there were loads
Of animals in the water at this part of the creek as well
John threw his lights on to get ahead of Clark and as he passed he saw the sky ahead begin to swirl
About 30 feet above the ground a flat oval began to form the sky around it
Spiraled like cloth making folds as it gathered and bunched in places
The oval was black but this technicolor energy was erupting from its darkness
And then just as swiftly the sky was just as it was but something was falling
Suddenly the windshield of John's vehicle shattered and tiny shards of glass covered everything
Slumped across officer petty Moore's dashboard was the lifeless body of a grown man and blood was splattered
Everywhere he lost control of the vehicle and swerved into oncoming traffic
Hearing the sound of a horn blaring as it roared closer and closer before the cruiser jerked to a stop
all three officers saw the flash of a car fly by and then they heard a
deafening crash and the rumble of fire in
the chaos it was hard to understand what all had happened a
minivan was run off the road by officer petty Moore the former teen sprint car racer who was banned from the circuit after an
accident that left multiple bystanders hospitalized
Officer Bishop slammed into the back of petty Moore's cruiser and there was fluid leaking
Everywhere the minivan that narrowly avoided the head-on collision with John it flipped and caught fire
Petty Moore worked diligently to keep the two police cruisers from exploding which likely would have killed officer vigna who couldn't handle the
situation and fell unconscious
Thrust into the memories of a particularly traumatic childhood Christmas
Officer Bishop pulled a young boy from the fiery wreckage of the minivan, but it might have already been too late
Before he could go back to save the woman trapped behind the wheel as well as the other passenger the minivan combusted
Looking at the body on John's windshield
They'd finally found their missing John Peters
Just hadn't expected him to fall out of the sky the balding man with large eyes and a small nose was wearing a pair of
Jeans and a button-down shirt and on his forehead
Recently branded into the skin was the word
fool
The ambulance arrived and firemen were seen pulling a woman's charred remains from the driver's seat of the minivan
Two others from the back of the van pulled out the body of a small girl
Drew pulled up in Keith's Cruiser because he got a call from the estate salesman at James's house
Apparently he found some unsettling writing and blood and many many guns after accidentally triggering some secret
Door trap the salesman was wondering if he could sell the guns in the estate sale
Drew had told him the police needed to look at the scene first
Drew and John then very subtly walked over to the ditch off the side of the road to speak privately
Drew said he received a message from the Duke the deal was going down that night at 2 a.m.
John offered drew 5% to convince the Duke to do the deal out at the Pettymore farm
Drew and John then walked back up and they all saw a wet black cat running toward them from off the road
The cat seemingly panicked jumped on to John's leg and meowed like crazy
John held the cat up and told Doug they were gonna get him the help
He needed at this point a small but vocal group of the contention population began
Protesting and letting these officers know how they felt
Drew apologized to the officers for not passing along critical information like the calls about missing persons
Animals in the ponds and creeks as well as a voicemail from the feds
Doug dr. Marie Jacob's husband who is inhabiting the body of their cat Salem
Conveyed to the officers that the animals were hiding in the water because the oily substance could not get them in the ponds and creeks
And at James the mill workers house the estate salesman Randy angst dressed in a fancy blue
Three-piece suit holding a cane with a big tooth on the top handed the cops a card when he greeted them
The card said mr. Angst is the dentist and the estate salesman in town
He also founded the contention historical society when asked about the picture from the odd camera John found in Julie Maxwell's car
angst noted that a few of the folks were dressed in clothes about a hundred years off from the rest when questioned about Cole's
Orphanage the dentist slash estate salesman recalled an orphanage by that name opening about
25 years prior though it did close down within a year in James the mill workers house
They found a cache of guns hidden under the coffee table
Riding in blood where one of the guns should be that read stop her and a large plastic tube all
Revealed after touching the bow tie of a statue of a man wearing a tuxedo
There are a bunch of cleaning supplies random materials and a handwritten list hidden in a small enclave
behind an oil painting of a rose all the liquids had been crossed out including the three listed types of water tap
distilled and boiling and all of the materials had been crossed out except
Neoprene a kind of synthetic rubber when Clark tapped the white hard hat atop the suit of armor in the foyer
He found a trapdoor and fell into a 12 foot deep pit with two corpses a man and a woman in
One of their pockets was a paper with a hand-drawn symbol a circle encircled by six circles in the front room
There was a grand piano without strings and in the kitchen
there are a few loose tiles where something heavy metal and buried had been dragged out as
The place was being searched a heavy artillery weapon began firing into the house from the front yard a looming
Overweight man wearing an all-black
Combat uniform with a large scar over his right eye blasted the door from its frame
Almost cut officer Bishop's arm off froze at the command of officer petty more and
Eventually after a brutal combat between the contingent boys and the massive metal man flew out of the window bottomless
Gripping the throat of officer vigna. Thank beans
He poked that terminator top in the eye just in time to escape falling to the ground before the metal fella
exploded like fireworks
The officers cleaned themselves up after fighting this large robot man seemed to perhaps have feelings
Continuing the investigation of James the mill workers house Keith vigna found a single piece of music
entitled the rise of the end in the bench of the stringless piano
Clark Bishop found in the large plastic tube
blueprints for calm comfy campground a
Suspiciously planned out set of seven buildings six encircling a large one in the center on an island
sitting on Lake calm
They all stood there in James the mill workers house and the officers
Remembered he died in chief Maggie Cook's house with a bullet in his head face down in a plate of foot me
They remembered the contents of the present
She received from an unknown source the night
She took off a red rose a white hardhat and a black silk bowtie all of which
present in this home in a painting on a suit of armor and worn by a statue respectively
They called Florence the fourth and only other contention police officer, but it went to voicemail immediately
After undressing the bottom half of the still standing robot man's legs the gang found a logo on the smooth
Pelvic area an M made of four double helices
Late on the night of December 4th after the weirdest dinner and wheel of fortune session Clark Bishop had ever been subject to
Due to his super fucking weird new co-worker Keith Vigna left the Bishop home headed back to Hotel Motel
And was approached by his niece Francis beans
She offered her uncle officer Vigna one million dollars from her inheritance to kill her father
Keith's brother
Ferguson beans upon accepting her proposal the two began driving east away from contention
John got home to find his place had been turned over his smoky and the bandit DVDs had been knocked and
Stepped on among the mess was a Burgatory rewards card for Keith Vigna
John vowed to kill Keith, but first he smoked a bowl and put on smoky
Drew eventually showed up holding a pistol
But by the top so John showed drew how to use the safety on his pistol
And they went out to the shooting tree to practice aiming and firing
With final preparations for the coke deal with the Duke in place John made a bird call and another call
replied from the woods
At 2 a.m.
technically the morning of December 5th a white 15 passenger van pulled up to the Pettymore property with the words
Jesus Christ Ministries painted on the side filled with children
Pulling a white trailer that also said Jesus Christ Ministries
The most handsome man John had ever seen hopped out of this van
Perfect hair perfect teeth a perfect jawline
And he was wearing the fuck out of a bright white suit with a red rose pinned perfectly to his lapel
Coke was buried in two holes and John would point out where to dig when he received half the money
Same plan for the second half a bunch of children ran out of the van all carrying
Shovels in the same way and they lined up waiting for the Duke on his command the children began digging
John asked if the kids all have the same mom. Yeah, you could you could say that
After the children loaded the cocaine into the trailer behind the van the Duke handed John the briefcase with
$5,000,000 in it same thing happened behind the woodpile as it did beneath the big tree the
Transaction went smoothly and John offered the Duke a thousand dollars for information about Marvin Glass
The Duke doesn't like Marvin Glass see glass is a competitor
But also a customer Marvin Glass buys in bulk when the Duke was asked about his rose
He said he liked the smell
Laughed and admitted he had no sense of smell when John asked about the kids the Duke said goodbye to Drew got back in the van
Drove down the long driveway and out onto the country road
John whistled and eight petty more cousins came walking out from the woods received their payment
Ten grand and a 24 pack of Keystone light each and they all fired their guns into the air in celebration
Back at the Bishop abode Clark heard Keith leave got up and locked the front door
Walking back to bed though
He looked out the window to Coles Creek which flows down south from the lake at Centennial Park
The whole thing was packed with animals a fair few people had been out there earlier looking for their pets
But not at this late hour too dark too cold
And they saw a humanoid figure hobbling down the frigid waterway in his direction
It was running but it seemed to be fighting through a limp and when it reached the point in the creek
Closest to Clark's house. He leapt from the water and began screaming and waving his arms all while looking directly
toward Clark's window
Clark's brain had a hard time comprehending what it was. He was seeing but this man this man running towards him
It was him
And then a warm pinch on the back of the neck
and Clark's vision tunneled to a close
Clark came to as a black bag was being snatched off his head
He felt hung over and his chest was weird and tight
It smelled damp and earthy and there was a haze around the torch above shedding partial light from the middle of the small
stonewalled room
Clark was sitting in a chair across a stone table from a man with gray hair under a white hard hat and a charcoal suit
With a bolo tie the man looked relaxed as he tossed the black bag onto the table and began to speak
After Richard the third's coronation
He was visited by a seer from Leichster who called himself the overseer
The seer claimed that the now king was to hold some very important knowledge
But would need to have the restraint to not abuse this power Richard was given this knowledge
But he couldn't handle it
He lost his mind and killed his two nephews
The overseer disappointed eventually passed the same knowledge to Henry Tudor
So he could whoop Richard at Bosworth
Henry the seventh held this power and eventually passed it down to a reliable and trusted confidant
Thankfully not his piece of shit son
This knowledge was passed down repeatedly abused and respected respected and abused until it made its way over the Atlantic to the colonies
Eventually landing with a high order of masons a select few held this information for generations
But a grand purpose was never found
Until Paul Simon the politician not the singer soon after being elected to the Senate
He was walking near his home when he came across the first known xenon imitode
He sought out Robert Byrd the Senate minority leader at the time to share his newfound understanding of the world
Thankfully for the world Byrd was among those carrying the knowledge of the overseer from centuries before
Together they formed a small circle of men to hold the weight of this realization
Today we carry on their tradition by keeping the darkness out of this world
We are the opaque rampart delaying the destruction of life as we know it
Welcome to the circle of knowledge
You have questions, I'm sure and I know this sounds hypocritical after that lengthy oration
But as my high school English teacher would always say show don't tell he reached under the table
And as he stood up he held up an unspeakable worm like
Abomination with one hand away from his body the thing was two feet long and tube like covered in a squamous black
partially translucent
membrane its body
Segmented and toxically green
Pulsating arteries and veins could be seen through its thin looking exterior. It had no
Identifiable eyes or nose its cavernous
Circular mouths one sitting just inside the other were lined with hooked teeth and it spit out a saliva
That was somehow darker than black
You
Keith vigna sat in the car of his niece Francis beans a Chrysler Sebring
She'd offered him 1 million dollars to kill her father his brother Ferguson beans
After some back roads through the woods she pulled up to a black iron fence
Francis hopped out in motion for teeth to follow her she opened a hatch in the ground and jumped inside
Disappearing from view
Keith followed down the hatch into a dark underground tunnel lit by red lights on the walls every 15 feet
France told him he'll pop up on the estate in a sweet spot with no security and he'll have a straight shot to the house
Keith went up followed her directions and made his way into Ferguson's house
undetected
Keith searched for and found bleach ammonia and a towel
But when Keith walked into Ferguson's room the lights were out there were candles on either side of the bed and lit by
Candlelight was a woman on top of the sheets in bedware, but not Stacy
Not Ferguson's wife. This was an older woman a generation older than Ferguson and Keith
She freaked out Keith calmed her down said he's a contention police officer and that he got a call that someone had broke in
She claimed she was there to meet Ferguson
This was Joan Robin the mother of Ferguson's business partner
Bruce Joan explained that Ferguson offered her a million dollars to sleep with him
So he could make your mom jokes to his business partner
Keith told her she had two options
She could leave or she could shoot Ferguson when he came into the room
Joan realized with Ferguson gone her son would take control of the company Keith offered her half a million dollars
And she accepted Keith found Ferguson's revolver handed it to Joan and a car could be heard pulling up to the house a
white 15 passenger van with the words Jesus Christ Ministries painted on the side pulled into the
pristine Circle Drive the van pulled a white trailer that also said Jesus Christ Ministries a
Beautiful man got out of the passenger side of the van. He had perfect hair perfect teeth a perfect jawline
And he was wearing the fuck out of a bright white suit with a red rose pinned perfectly to his lapel
It was Keith's brother
Ferguson beans
He clicked a button on his keys and as he walked toward his home the ground around the van and trailer began to move
And shift the entire vehicular ensemble was transported below ground on some crazy
Futuristic elevator of sorts as the driveway closed back up with no evidence the van or trailer had ever
Sat there Keith hid in the closet with the ammonia bleach and towel the door opened shut
and
Ferguson hollered upstairs
Joan the power out scared Joan yelled back
It must have been the storm
The door to the room opened and Keith heard a shot then a scream then another shot then a different scream then another shot
And another shot and another shot, and then Keith heard crying
It sounded like Joan Keith opened the door of the closet to see Ferguson on the floor in a white suit with a rose on
His lapel riddled with holes from his own gun
Joan ran to Keith and hugged him Keith started crying Joan was crying Keith told Joan to calm down and
Lay on the bed so he could clean up the scene
Joan sat at the end of the bed with her head in her hands and Keith
Keith grabbed the bleach
Ammonia mixed it up on the rag he walked over to Joan and tried to lock his arm behind her head and forced the rag
Over her mouth, but Joan got her hand in between her mouth and the towel Keith attacked again violently
He held her down on the bed until she passed out
Officer Keith Vigna grabbed the revolver with his handkerchief
Put it in Joan's hand held the gun to her head and pulled the trigger
Leaving the room to look like Joan shot Ferguson five times before turning the gun on herself
Walking away Keith saw the watch on Ferguson's wrist
It was the same watch their dad William given Ferguson when they were kids
Keith took the watch
Noticing there's nothing on the face
And slipped in in his pocket when all the sudden his consciousness began changing like changing the channel
He began to phase out of his reality seems to be somewhere else
entirely
Keith felt wet grass and dirt on his fingers
He was looking at a door in the ground like a sealed metal door that was mostly buried and on the door was an inscription
It read here lies the beans
Scientists beyond measure saviors of the world
Keith walked back through the tunnel under the ground with the red lights with glazed eyes
Keith back at the hotel stuck the watch in the handkerchief into the room safe and laid down flat on his bed
John Lee Pettymore just successfully made five million dollars by selling cocaine to a random handsome
Stranger named the Duke paid him a grand to know that Marvin Glass buys from him in bulk and paid eight
Cousins ten grand in a 24 pack of Keystone light each to which they took a Pettymore
Sky-shot and headed off into the night drew walked up and said, thank you
Thank you for making all this money for showing him how to shoot a gun
With all the money drew planned on donating his house to Boys and Girls Club
And then it's probably just gonna bail and then drew drove off down the long driveway to the country road home alone
John wanted to kill Keith vigna
but he opted for leaving Keith drunk voicemails slamming three more beers snorting another line brushing his teeth and
Sending Keith a text that just says I
know
John then swept up his smoky DVDs put in the director's cut and fell asleep smoking and join on his couch
dreaming of his millions but also of
terrible monsters
He woke up to the sound of two gunshots
Rose Mary was holding six Pettymores and drew hostage outside
Two Pettymores were faced down in the dirt and she called out for John
He came out on his front porch with his hands up. She told him her boss Marvin Glass wants the gun
John John thinks they can help each other glass wants his boys back right John wants his town back, right?
She said she was sent to collect this gun and John asked if he could deliver it. She agreed first
She let the cousins all go free
Then she got John and drew into the front of Drew's Mini Cooper hopped in the back and held their own
Guns at them while they drove back into town to the contention police department
Clark was in the circular stone room with the stone table lit by a torch
The man sat across from him put down the creature into a container between his legs and closed the lid
Before introducing himself as Leon Simpson, he welcomed Clark into the circle of knowledge
Clark's first task began forthwith Leon pulled out a small plastic container and slid it toward Clark
He took a gun out of his pockets a tranquilizer and in the plastic container were a pair of needles
Leon told Clark these darts were filled with a particular
Toxin to make anyone obey for some time
The job was this an FBI agent was on his way to contention to take over the missing persons cases as
This would be bad for Clark and for the circle of knowledge
Clark needed to tranq this FBI agent and make sure he didn't see anything funny going on
Leon Simpson asked Clark what exactly had been going on that was so funny in contention and Clark
Clark spilt those beans
Leon was impressed by the sheer amount of strange information coming from Clark and so reiterated his current mission
Keep the FBI agent away from any of the strangeness any of the goo or ooze or whatever
They're calling it. This next part was important
Clark had 24 hours and then Leon needed him to report back so they could make sure that he'd be okay
Clark asked about the creature. Leon told them it's a xenonema toad
Currently they believe these things are a vector either from another time another place or another reality. They're not quite positive
However, they're the things Paul Simon found that connected the dots to the knowledge of the overseer
These creatures are not of this place
They have certain abilities the circle of knowledge has found a way to exploit and they are necessary kept around for a very
specific purpose
Again, Leon decided to show not tell he opened the one door in this room into another circular stone room
This one was much bigger
20 yards across with a domed ceiling the walls were stone and there were a handful of torches mounted to light the room
There were six large slabs of stone each with a couple of people laying on them circling a single
Unoccupied stone slab in the center of the space each person laying down had one of those giant
Fucked up worm things attached to them and many of them seemed to have dead skin covering one or multiple limbs
There's also a woman an electric blue slacks and a bright yellow cardigan walking
Deliberately around each slab checking on each group and checking her watch. She smiled when she saw Clark Bishop
Leon explained that these brave men and women
Motioning to the people on the slabs who all looked very down on their luck
These fine individuals have dedicated their lives to the survival of humanity
Clark questioned their willingness and Leon argued that things around here were much better than they used to be
Anyway, Clark needed to get going
the timer had already started and Leon said he'd hate for the 24 hours to pass as
They'd hate to lose Clark so soon as he walked Clark out of the room the woman said goodbye to Leon
Clark turned back and and looked he recognized this woman
She was cold and vacant with a big smile on her face
her asymmetrical hair was covering one of her eyes and
Love the woman who killed Clark's parents smiled and calmly said
Bye Clark as he rushed toward her officer bishop felt another warm pinch in his neck and
Love began laughing as he slowly crumbled to the ground
Clark Bishop woke up in a cab and looking behind
He saw
He was leaving the mill on the other side of the city
I
What's up, it's Zach
I'm Zach here to give you an idea of what's going on and whatnot
so I decided it would be really helpful and nice to write a recap of season 1 so far and
Record it. So everyone is nice and caught up before we dive into the final arc of the story
I thought this would be a pretty simple task and I I thought I could encapsulate it all in in one episode
Boy howdy was was I super super wrong first I forgot how stupid I am
Second I forgot how detail oriented I can be so it's looking like this
Project has turned into a more work than I intended or have time for
But that's okay. I still think it'll be fun for everyone
Especially the players to really have a grasp on what's going down before we hit the end
So here's the deal. I I need some help
Writing this transcript. It was a massive undertaking again
Duh should have known better going in but oh well
So there is a link in the show notes and on Twitter and Facebook fuck Mark Zuckerberg to a Google Doc
We can all share it will have the transcript for this episode
Which covered episodes 1 through 23 now if you write up a few succinct but thorough
paragraphs recapping an episode of this show you will be entered to win a
PTBP t-shirt
Now if you write up a few succinct but thorough paragraphs
Recapping three or more episodes you will be entered to win one of five
PTBP t-shirts
So if only five people write up three or more episodes boom
You got a shirt and finally finally if you really if you go above and beyond if you write up a few succinct
But thorough paragraphs recapping five or more episodes
I will guarantee you a PTBP t-shirt. The clock is already ticking on the next episode
so let's focus first on episodes 24 to 46 and
Leave your handle or email address
So we know who wrote what and how to contact you in case we get to ship you a shirt this
This contest slash giveaway slash help Zack out project does have a deadline and that deadline is Tuesday
October 13th at midnight
Central time please note that the recap focused on in character action
There unfortunately just isn't enough time to include all the dice rolling and meta goofs in class
Be wary of grammatical issues wolf the dog hates grammatical issues
He learned them all just so he would know how to break them
Now I'll get these recap episodes out as quickly as possible so we can dumpster dive into the finale of season one guys
I'm so fucking stoked y'all may the wolf bless each and every one of you
Oh