God damn it, y'all.
Shit just keeps getting weirder and weirder around here.
It's your trap tricky trusted teacher wolf the dog,
and I am no longer surrounded by walls.
From my cage, I can see that there is a lot
of bizarre alien thingies all around me.
Bio luminescence, mushroomy thingies.
What the fuck is going on around here?
I guess the show still must go on.
Bullshit working conditions is what this is.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from
At Super Nerd Jeff, who is located in Slovenia.
At Super Nerd Jeff tweeted about the show
and tagged At Pretending Pod,
the second coolest thing you can do in Slovenia.
The first, dance with the fairies on Bled Island.
Those little groovers really know how to cut a wool,
if you know what I mean.
And if you don't, do some damn research.
Wolf ain't gonna spoon feed you every morsel,
but I am gonna have.
At Super Nerd Jeff writes,
I hope this message reaches you safely, wolf.
I don't know which lines of communication
are safe these days.
You and the boys are doing God's work over at 694.2 PTBP.
Handlers, agents, and dogs everywhere
could take a leaf out of your creepy freckled
human skin book.
To my own agents, it is coming.
The future we have waited and worked so long for.
Foretold in years past, born of pestilence
and fermented in solitude.
Prepare yourselves.
Much love from the safe house in Slovenia.
Keep up the fine work, fellas.
Now I don't know where your safe house is, Jeff,
but if you ever run into the dragon
that kicks it under Ljubljana Castle,
tell him wolf says he regrets calling him a girthy drake,
and I miss their earthy quakes.
I bet all that's just for Jeff.
Unless a few of y'all have read a book or two on Slovenia.
If you wanna write up something
for your trapped wolf to how,
and then make very specific references to,
tag at pretending pod on Twitter,
tag at pretending pod on Instagram,
tag pretending to be people on Facebook
or fuck Mark Zuckerberg,
or you can write a five star review on Apple Podcasts
and holler about it to pretendingpod at gmail.com.
Also, money.
We'll take it.
If you wanna join the Patreon exclusive t-shirt club,
head on over to patreon.com slash pretending pod.
And remember, if you join our Patreon
or upgrade your tier during the month of November,
we're gonna take that money,
we're gonna match it,
and we're gonna buy blankets and tents
for folks who need them this winter.
You fine folks have already raised $185.
So with PTBP's matching contribution,
we have $370 so far to spend on needed supplies
to help our community get through this winter.
Only 11 days left, y'all.
And how about this?
If we hit $333 from y'all,
that would double on up
to the very cool number of $666.
If that happens, Wolf will give away
a couple fine t-shirts with the PTBP logo
to a couple of fine patrons.
So sign up for the Patreon this November, my babies.
You'll get a butt ton of bonus content
and the fuzzy warm feeling of helping others.
Speaking of fuzzy warm feelings, it's time for the news.
Last time, Incel accused a cool mom of being on drugs,
accused the sheriff of not caring enough
about a missing girl, accused the father of that missing girl
and Alderman of Grover'sville, Tennessee
of being produced by inbreeding,
and emailed Scott Adams, who is either a UFO guy,
the Dilbert guy, or both.
Finally, they called Merle's shut eye,
pretended to be a Clark County deputy,
and learned that Scott Adams has two rooms there
at the same motel they're staying in.
Two rooms for one dude?
Hm, Wolfie is skeptical,
but now for something absolutely impeccable,
it's Brat Pit with Miss Mary.
Psy moves out,
but the eyes hold one throw
I gotta work in the morning
And this shit's so important
So I can't get high
No, I can't get high
Theinge siega die
I can't get high
There must be something inside of me
Does anybody know why?
I can't get high
We're here with David Winters.
David.
Hi.
Luke has a question for you.
Oh, no.
Yeah, so let me set the scene.
We're not recording this though, are we?
No, yeah, we're recording.
Wait, did you get this question from a bigger podcast?
No, I just like thought of it.
I think I was like pooping and I thought of it.
So, all right.
If you make a lie gross enough, no one questions it.
You're accusing me and I resent that.
This is from the dome.
David, you can pick only one movie that Tom Hanks is in
and keep Tom Hanks in it,
but then you have to replace every other movie he's in
with a different actor,
but then you have to pick who that actor is.
So, three part question, two part question.
One, what movie is Tom Hanks going to stay in his role
and then what actor would you replace
every other Tom Hanks role with?
Oh, that's good.
He's gonna stay in Forrest Gump.
That's what I said.
Yeah, he's gonna stay in Forrest Gump.
I know that much.
As far as every other movie.
So like, what are some highlights?
What movies do we need to think about?
Philadelphia Castaway.
Terminal.
Turner and Hooch, Terminal.
Sully.
Joe versus volcano.
You've got male, Sleepless in Seattle.
You're the captain now, Phillips man.
This is easy too then.
Nicolas Cage.
Oh, nice.
Perfect, perfect answer.
That's better than anything we ever came up with.
Yeah, that's the most chaotic answer you can give,
besides like Gary Busey.
Do you remember the scene in the terminal
where he's in the bathroom and he just starts screaming?
He does the scene for Mandy,
but in terminal. In every movie.
Let's kill some aliens.
What were your answers?
I heard Forrest Gump was a yes.
I said Forrest Gump and then Colin Hanks.
I was gonna keep him in Castaway
and maybe like Sam Rockwell.
Some character actor I think could do all of his oeuvre.
I think Sam Rockwell would be good.
I chose, the movie that I chose is that one
where he is the guy.
I feel like you don't know what you're gonna say yet.
I should have let Thomas go next.
Yeah, I'll give you some time.
I would keep him in the cinematic masterpiece, Cloud Atlas
and replace him and everything else with Danny DeVito.
There you go.
Danny DeVito is Forrest Gump.
That would be the greatest movie of all time.
I'm gonna keep him in That Thing You Do
just to keep that movie pristine as possible,
especially because I talked about that.
I don't want Vin Diesel playing that role,
which is who I'm gonna have play all of the other roles.
I do want Vin Diesel as Forrest Gump.
It's about family, Ginny.
Family is a life of box of chocolates.
You never know what you're gonna get.
Yeah, oddly enough,
the Chronicles of Riddick is all Tom Hanks now.
That would be awesome.
Tom Hanks goes down to Cuba and he's like,
that means we're family.
If the question is instead like whose careers would you flop?
Then Tom Hanks and Vin Diesel is a very fun answer.
And at the end of episode two.
We got some information from a hotel clerk
that Scott Adams was renting a room where we're staying
and there was also, he had a second room full of research.
The hotel clerk knew that that second room
was full of research, if I remember right.
It's amazing that that hotel employee knew.
Maybe he mentions it
at the continental breakfast every morning.
He's like, love this lobby coffee,
really helps me with my research,
which is what I use that second room for.
Did we learn the hotel clerk's name?
You did, it was Riker Yates.
That's right, strong name.
Riker Yates.
You live in New York.
Do you ever just go to Riker Island for fun?
No, not really.
There's better islands, including Manhattan itself.
But yeah, I generally avoid Rikers.
At least what the tourist guides say is try not to.
Do you ever get sent there against your will
for the crimes you've committed?
I don't have to answer that under advice from counsel.
Smart guy.
I plead the fifth.
Not a prereq for my appearance here.
You didn't read the fine print, David.
There's a reason why I have to record this remotely
and I can't fly in for the show.
I'm not allowed to leave the states.
That's the nicest sell I've ever seen.
Yes.
They let you have so many games.
It's true, it's true.
So we're at the hotel.
Well, not really hotel, it's a motel.
And I know that that's near and dear
to certain other detectives' hearts and another property.
This is Merle's shut eye is what you called,
or who you called, the place you called,
the person you called was Riker Yates.
You're still far away though.
If I recall correctly,
did you call on the fancy DEA Crown Victoria car phone
or did you call from the city hall?
I think we called from the office, yeah.
The city hall office, okay.
So you led away the alderman.
Right, I think we told him to fuck off.
Yes, like many of the other NPCs
that you've encountered so far,
you have thoroughly harassed them
asking about disappearing people
and you constantly bring up aliens for no apparent reason
even though that's a complete trigger point
for every resident around here.
Accurate, yep.
You've made a phone call.
It is what, around probably about midnight at this point
on thirsty Thursday night.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Oh yeah, so we could go down to the reservoir.
Thank you for bringing that up.
I had forgotten about it.
The question is, what do you wanna do next?
It's getting late, day one.
Do you guys, do you think we should...
I mean, we're gonna go back to the motel.
Anyway, we gotta stay there.
Should we go crash the kids party?
Go down to the reservoir?
I mean, we should at least drive by probably, yeah.
It would give us a chance to see if there's any connections
in the youth where all these missing kids are coming from.
So-called missing kids.
We have that raging Billy Ray just shouting in pain.
Who fucking knows if there's a lot of kids missing?
Yeah, but if Jane Allen is also missing
and then everyone seems to not be worried
about missing people.
I'm worried that these teens themselves
won't fucking be worried
that any of their friends are missing.
That's a worrying thought.
My theory is that we've only talked to grown adults.
Maybe the younger crew might actually be concerned about it
because it's their friends that are going.
Reservoir would be the place to go then.
What if there's like a scrappy group of role-playing nerds?
Then we kill them.
Who befriend a supernatural bald girl.
How many of them do you think there'd be?
The supernatural kind.
Well, just one, but her name would be Eleven.
Okay, all right, all right, I was just wondering.
Am I off-putting to you, the three of you in this room,
now that it was just the four of us in here,
do I come across as a little too fucking strong?
I like your tattoos, but that whole thing,
I'm not a fan of that.
Why?
I didn't like it.
Sometimes you do say things
that I feel put the investigation in jeopardy.
She's pulling on the sleeves of her cardigan
that she has on,
but she's not using her like cardigan persona currently.
And she kind of pulls the sleeves down over her tattoos.
She had them rolled up from the intensity of the phone call
and the email and the computer.
And as she rolls the sleeves down,
she looks at all of you and her face changes again.
And she's just like, okay,
Cindy Woodabaga is gonna be very, very nice.
Is that better for you?
Joe Dean's face falls, but he doesn't say anything,
but he looks like he's seen this before
and he's even more worried now.
Cindy, is this like a Bruce Banner Hulk situation?
Can we call on that other version of you if we need it?
Just rip my cardigan off
and I guess we'll see what comes out.
It's just, she's still a little flirty.
She runs her fingers down Harlan Nash's chest.
Is that okay?
Sure, for now.
It's better though than before.
Yeah.
Tan gets a little jealous.
How old are Harlan and Tan?
Tan is 38.
Harlan's 46.
I'll be good.
And she looks at her partner, Joe Dean
and her eyes get really big.
I'll be good.
And then we all hop in the car and go to the reservoir.
Yep.
Yeah.
Okay.
We wanna make some prank calls on our car phone first though.
Bling, bling.
Hello, White House?
Yeah, let me talk to the president.
How did you get this number?
What are your thoughts on aliens?
We call Murrells County Bunker.
Yeah, grab your prop phone, David.
And I haven't heard the ring yet.
Ring, ring, ring, ring.
Hey y'all, it's Murrells.
Howdy, we're staying down at Murrell's shutout tonight
and we were wondering how long the bunker's open.
Huh?
Well, technically it's open till 12,
but if you say the password, it's open till two.
What's the password?
Big League Chew.
Big League Chew, that's cool.
Yeah.
Hey, ask him if Mr. Jazz is there.
Hey, is Mr. Jazz there?
Hugh Jazz.
Hugh Jazz?
Hey, we got Hugh Jazz in here, anyone?
Oh, hang up, hang up, hang up.
Hey, hang up, hang up, hang up, hang up, hang up.
Oh my God, it's just like the Simpsons.
We don't got no Hugh Jazz.
I can't believe it worked, hang up.
I hang up, yeah.
It's just like that animated 10 year old boy
that's taken the nation by storm these last couple of years.
I'm just waiting for, once we get in like a gunfight
for David to just bring a gun out as a prop.
It's like, yeah, I got a phone.
He fires in and bullets come out of our TV screen.
Whoa.
4D.
Four dead.
All right, any more prank phone calls
before you go to the reservoir?
Sure, why not?
How many prank phone calls does it take
to get to the reservoir?
Sorry, your car phone's out of minutes.
You only have the 30 minute monthly plan.
Two things, first, are we there yet?
And second, can I change Ice Cube to my answer
for switching with Tom Hanks?
Yes and yes, Ice Cube would be good.
Is Ice Cube in Law and Order or is that Ice T?
That's Ice T, Ice T.
Which one's Ice Cube?
Ice Cube is the-
Are we there yet?
And 21 Jump Street, 22 Jump Street, Barbershop.
Man, Barbershop's a funny movie.
All right, let's go.
It'd be good.
What do we see?
Well, more importantly, what do you hear?
So in between your prank phone calls on the way there,
a bump in tune from 1990 comes on.
Vanilla Ice's Ice Ice Baby, just to get you in the mood.
All right, stop, collaborate and listen.
Ice is back with a brand new invention.
Something.
You guys are holding me tightly.
Flowing like a hot daily and nightly.
When will it ever stop, yo?
I don't know.
Turn out the lights and I'll glow to the extreme.
I rock the mic like a vandal.
Light up the stage and watch me shine like a candle dance.
Harlan, they really just had a little bonding moment there.
I think your chances with Cindy just went way down.
She knew every word.
She's good.
You go to the reservoir, you encounter,
hold on,
three teens loitering and a beat up Ford pickup truck
and pounding cans of, hold on,
I have to roll on my random beer table.
Oh, hell yeah.
Oh, that's an 11.
Is this 13 Mile Island?
Oh my God.
That's an 11.
They're drinking Milwaukee's Best Ice.
Excellent.
Six percenters getting it.
That is, they are partying.
David, is that a chart of your own devising?
Oh yeah.
Were you just going to say that no matter what you roll?
No, no, no, no.
There's other ones I can roll for you.
A two is Colt 45.
Oh my gosh.
Did you make sure all these beers were on the market
in 1990?
Anything you can buy in Tallboys in a gas station today
probably existed 20 years ago.
Like Steel Reserve, Colt 45.
Milwaukee's Best Ice.
Colt 45 definitely existed
because Lando Calrissian was effectively the spokesperson.
Yeah, I'm not saying you could have a better time.
David, what's your go-to shitty beer?
Hold on, let me roll for you.
That'd be Bud Light.
Missouri, baby.
Doody Doody.
Anheuser-Busch.
Wait, what did they say?
In Bev.
Wait, what?
Doody Doody.
No, Diddy Diddy.
Right?
Poopy Poopy.
I forget.
Dilly Dilly.
Yes, there we go.
That's what we're looking for.
Those were bad commercials.
I liked the dog ones.
Those were good.
Anyway.
Oh, where the dogs say Budweiser.
We're at the reservoir, I guess.
Milwaukee's Best.
They're crushing Milwaukee's Best Ice.
Yeah, the beast.
Tan gets out of the car,
finds the open 18-pack,
grabs one, cracks it open,
and just kind of wanders into where the kids are.
It's relatively warm.
They've been there for a little while.
It's a 30-rack.
It's about half consumed,
so there's about 15 warm cans left,
and it gives that distinct,
almost gasoline smell as you open it up.
And you walk over towards the kids.
They're averaging five units of alcohol per person,
depending on how long they've been out here.
Okay, Joe?
Yeah, and it's ice beer,
which means it's a little bit higher
than your normal three-two.
That's right.
Going with some loose sluices.
Guys, I'm actually,
this is kind of my realm,
ATF, you know?
Oh, that's right, that's right.
And he sniffs his beer.
This is a good one.
I know that is your realm.
I don't want to tell you how to do your job,
but it would be super cool
if you just walked over there
and poured it out in front of him.
No, he savors the beautiful taste of-
The beast ice.
Of the ice.
Hey, kids.
Hey.
This isn't super weird to you
that we're just here.
Well, it's the cool place to be.
We got some questions for you.
Who are you?
Hold on, these guys are clearly nerds.
Mine is-
Yeah, why are there four random adults here
at the reservoir at midnight on a thirsty Thursday?
Well, so, you know,
we haven't been out to the reservoir
for a thirsty Thursday in quite a while.
We figured we'd come down here
and we just ran into you guys.
You don't look like you're from around here.
Well, we are.
We're older than you, you know?
Do you know any- Are you sure?
Have any of your friends disappeared?
Maybe.
I guess they haven't been around.
Yeah, maybe.
What do you mean, maybe?
I mean, it doesn't mean they've disappeared
just because they're not around.
But some of your friends aren't around.
I don't know.
I'm only 12.
It's dark, we should have clocked that right away.
Is this kid actually only 12?
Give me alertness.
I pass, 42 on a 50.
I fail, 71 on a 70.
Jodine's like, what kid?
Which kid are we talking about?
I fail as well, 61 on a 60.
But only Cindy notices that these children,
sorry, these individuals might be children.
The rest of you are like,
yeah, they're probably adults.
It's fine.
You know Harlan, Tan doesn't know it yet.
But that alcohol, brushing through his system
is changing who he is as a person and making him worse.
You think he's a liability now?
Immediately.
Tan is standing there hearing you.
He is ATF.
It's called research.
He probably does know about alcohol.
I'm doing research.
I don't think you should be drinking right now.
I think you should pour that beer out like a hard ass.
He continues to take a sip and then says,
Jane Allen, what's that mean to you?
It's better than their faces.
She's an older girl around here.
I don't know.
You seen her in a while?
No, I don't really go to school.
Then what do you do?
Nothing.
Do you remember how you got here?
In a car?
Who drove?
Rocky did.
When was that?
30 minutes ago.
Oh shit, you pounded five fucking ices
in 30 minutes each.
And these kids are 12.
They're like, these kids are just on the ground.
Like one of them is already dead.
The one with the beard walks over.
Why are you bothering my friends?
Are you Rocky?
Yes.
Did you guys drink all of these beers in the last 30 minutes?
No.
No?
No, I'm the designated driver.
I would never.
They had seven and a half each.
Rocky, you know, it just doesn't look like
these kids have the body weight
for seven and a half Milwaukee's best ices.
They seem fine to me.
They're passing.
You're right.
They do seem rather coherent for what they've ingested.
Rocky, what do you know about aliens?
As he's frustratedly answering,
I grab his arm and look at it.
Oh my God.
Roll me a search.
Guys, I really don't think anyone who is around
is gonna have these little cuts.
Yeah, remember that came with some pretty telltale symptoms.
Yeah, I successfully passed.
Yeah, you don't see any.
The two younger kids, not Rocky,
does look like they've pounded seven and a half beers each.
However, there seemed to be no effects on them at all.
Well, that's odd.
Ooh.
Yeah, that's what I was talking, yeah.
That's fucking nuts.
All right, let's get the fuck out of here
and go on to the next place.
Could we, hey, could we get your names real quick?
I'm Rocky Collins.
The younger gentleman you were talking to over there,
Chester Wisman.
I bet you have a lot of fun with that name, huh?
Lastly, the woman over there, young lady over there,
Chastity James.
How old are you, Mr. Collins?
I'm 23.
Can we roll human on that?
Yeah.
Yes.
I pass. I pass a 60 on a 60.
I pass with a two.
39 on a 40.
Harlan fails.
He might be lying and is only 20 and he is just worried.
He just seems to be shifty
because he realizes you're adults and...
Kid, we don't really care how, you know,
that you're underage drinking.
It's not like we didn't do any of that ourselves,
but we just need to know the actual facts.
Like, how old are you, son?
I am legally obliged to arrest you,
but if you help us, I won't.
ATF agent, alcohol, tobacco, firearms.
It's just a relief.
I don't have to do that deep voice anymore now.
I'm most concerned at this point
that these are actually adults
that are now have taken over these 12 year old bodies
based on the way that he said that-
They just pound in those ices?
A, pounding ices, number one, and B, two.
He said that woman over there,
and then was like, I mean that girl, right?
So I think-
It's almost like our DM is like respectful and chill.
No, that was just bad game.
That was bad handling though.
I just, I caught myself.
Don't read into that.
Sorry.
I thought I cracked the whole thing open.
Nope.
So, Mr., what was it again?
Rocky Collins.
Mr. Collins.
Yeah.
So, do you know Jane Allen?
No, I don't.
We're a couple years apart.
You make it sound like she's not around, that's sure a shame.
And you don't have any friends
that just haven't been around for like three weeks?
Not three weeks, no.
Two weeks?
Any amount of time.
One week?
Any amount.
Occasionally people go places.
Where do they go?
They go to the big city.
What do they do in the city?
They go to the big city shopping.
Shopping.
That checks out.
And they're gone for days, weeks at a time?
Oh, sometimes there's some big shopping to do in the city.
You gotta get your fancy clothes at the Gap
and, you know, back to town.
Rocky, has anybody you know ever not come back to town?
Not as far as I know.
And you were 20, that was correct?
Ish.
And how old are your associates here?
Mid teens.
Cindy walks back and gets in the DEA car.
Do you want to breathalyze the kids
or anything else while you're there?
Do you want to sobriety check them?
Yeah, let's send them back to Delta Green
for testing in there.
All right, you hop back in the car?
Where to?
Murrell's.
1 a.m., night one.
Murrell's?
Wait, the hotel or the bar?
I think the bar.
The bar, county bunker.
Oh.
The late night, Harlan, you gonna stay up?
What are we going to the bar for?
We're gonna have the same conversation we just had
but with older people at a bar.
Yeah, they gave us the password, so that's cool.
As David is just nodding thoroughly and vigorously,
Cindy falls asleep in the car as you guys are going.
Okay, what if we just leave her in here?
She got real calm earlier.
Again, this is a brilliant investigative mind
but her methods are pretty unorthodox
and I've seen her get like this before it really gets odd.
Tan rings a doorbell on the bar at the bar.
Waking Cindy up.
And you go to the door.
Murrell's county bunker is literally stylized
almost as if it's some sort of bunker.
It's a windowless bar, blocky.
The front door is almost like it's for a gang hideout.
It is a heavy door with like one of those slots,
like an eye slot.
Ooh, nice.
Cop knock, ring, ring.
There's a little doorbell on it.
Big League Chew.
Door slides open, he sees you,
Big League Chew closes it, door cracks open, you walk in.
It is a half, not liquor store,
but more of like a grab and go beer place and half bar.
Again, there's no windows, it's dark.
It's stylized with those tin branded beer signs
all over the place of every which brand.
Some of these brands are even now defunct
in the early 90s, some of them are more modern.
The place smells like that solvent
that a really cheap bar has that just permeates the air
and that's all you can smell.
You can't smell food, you can't smell the beer,
it's just that kind of ambient solvent smell everywhere.
And there's only the bartender,
there's no one else in there right now.
Can you roll for some of those signs?
Oh yeah.
Steel Reserve.
Oh look, good one.
Oh, Rolling Rock, that's fancy.
Oh, from the glass line tanks of old Latrobe.
That's what they called me in high school.
They called you Rolling Rock?
That's right.
They called me Super Dork.
And lastly, Steel Reserve.
Oh, another Steel Reserve.
This one's a little fancier.
I like this one.
Yeah, it's a limited table.
It's only a D12 table.
All right, bartender behind the bar
says, well, hello there.
Have you ever been abducted by aliens?
Every single time.
Why is it always the aliens?
Oh, sorry, we didn't know this town
had any kind of connection to that.
That's just kind of his new age pickup line
that he's been dropping out.
It sounds like you're really upset by this.
So how many times have you been abducted by aliens?
Me and my partner saw you from across the bar
and we thought that you were.
We're just the laughing stock, laughing stock of Tennessee.
Yes, we're all laughing.
I hate it.
Pointing and laughing.
I hate being the laughing stock of Tennessee.
Who hates it?
What's your name?
My name is Arthur Doyle.
Arthur C. Doyle?
Just Doyle.
But really, though, how many times?
Never.
People always ask that.
There ain't no abductions around her.
You don't know anybody that's been abducted or?
No.
Abducted from their Sherlock Holmes, maybe?
No, ain't nobody been abducted around here.
We have some Moriarty questions.
Okay.
Jesus Christ.
You Sherlock harassing the locals, I've noticed.
People have been talking about these agents
going around town, asking questions about the aliens.
And that upsets people?
Yes, sir.
Is it because you like these aliens and you don't want to?
No!
We don't like no aliens.
We just want to live in peace.
So you don't want the aliens to be here anymore?
What aliens?
The ones you don't want here.
What are you talking about?
Why do you just keep asking questions about aliens?
You tell us.
Hey!
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
Sorry to bring up the aliens.
Can I have a water?
Do you know who killed Jane Allen?
Yes.
You do know who killed Jane Allen.
He pours each of you a water
because the nice old lady asked for one
and you've been out all day.
I chug it.
You chug it?
Okay.
And I've still got my Milwaukee's Best ice
from the reservoir.
Hey, hey!
No outside beverages.
You gotta shop parrot.
Tan chugs it and then goes back to his line of questioning.
Who gives you the right to do that?
So did you kill Jane Allen or who did it?
Why are you accusing me of killing Jane Allen?
Well, so it sounds like somebody did kill her then, right?
Based off what you just said.
I don't know.
I didn't say that.
That's what I heard.
We just tried this with him and he did not crack.
So let me guess, nothing is happening
that is strange or unusual in this town.
Correct.
Everything is fine.
Yeah.
Any of your friends been out of town for a while?
No.
Oh good, any of your friends?
Got no friends.
I work hard.
I'm always here at the county bunker.
You don't make friends with any of the regulars?
No, they're my customers.
I get that.
You gotta keep that distance.
Are you aware of a Billy Ray Spivvy, Spivvy?
Yeah, that boy.
Has he been in here?
Does he frequent this establishment?
No, sir.
I check IDs.
Thank you very much.
I see that guy over there with the ATF badge
trying to trip me up.
No, sir.
No children in this bar.
Can I humint that?
Sure.
Fail.
93 on a 60.
Everyone in the bar looks 12 now.
Does Scott Adams come in here much?
Oh, oh, that guy.
Yeah.
He's poking around just like you,
asking about them UFOs.
Told him he wasn't allowed to come back here.
Is that, oh, you kicked him out.
He was harassing my customers.
Was his line of inquiry similar to ours,
or was he asking different things?
Basically the same stuff.
This is just a person.
Do you think it was the fella from Dilbert?
I ain't seen him making no comics while he was here,
if that's what you're asking.
What have you seen him doing while he's here?
Harassing my customers.
Asked and answered, fair enough.
Thank you very much for your time.
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave now.
That is what?
You have thoroughly wasted enough time,
and now this bar has to close.
Thank you, Z.
Ushers you out the front door.
Are we like right next to the motel?
You're very close, yeah.
Both are on the outskirts of town.
They're both owned by Murrells.
They're conveniently close enough
that you could walk from the county bunker to the motel.
And what time is it, like one in the morning right now?
Two.
Bar closed at two.
Yep.
Do you think it's too late to go try to talk to him?
I'm so tired.
I'm tempted to turn in myself
and get this with fresh eyes.
I've gotta sleep and shit and piss,
and eat, apparently.
Do we each have our own room
or are we all staying in the same room?
Are you gonna check in?
Yeah, let's go check in.
Yeah.
So you walk over to the hotel,
you go to talk to Riker Yates.
However, there's a sign up saying,
the manager is not on duty, please check in at 10 a.m.
You get to sleep in your cars now
because you didn't even bother to check into the motel.
I think Harlan saw the sign
and was already walking back to the Bronco.
Wait, do we know which hotel room?
No, we haven't checked in.
No, no, Scott.
Oh, that Scott was in.
We do?
No, we didn't get room numbers.
No, you didn't get the number out of them.
Can I do a search for a book that has customers?
So you're gonna break into the...
We're still on the outside.
We haven't made it into the lobby.
Oh, we're not inside the lobby?
No.
There's no lobby, so this is, I should say,
standard motel, doors open outward,
and it's actually, you know what,
I'm just gonna give you a map.
How about that?
Ooh. Perfect.
So, 11 room motel, L-shaped.
The rooms on one side of the L are kind of double units,
two double beds plus kitchenettes.
And then there's this, on the other side of the L,
it's just standard rooms where it's some beds
and then a bathroom, and that's pretty much it.
And then in between, in like the joint of the L,
there's a manager's office.
Right, is that locked?
The office is locked, so it has that sign
saying basically, come back tomorrow.
Yeah.
I'm not gonna sleep in the car.
I don't know if Scott's a nice guy or not,
but I'm gonna go find him.
No, you're not.
I would not advise just knocking on doors
at two in the morning.
Hold on, real quick, who's in charge of this?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry, guys, you're not actually full Delta Green.
Oh, yeah, we're in charge of this task force.
You're the friendlies, we're the agents.
You're gonna sleep in your car tonight.
That's fine with me.
It's actually something I do pretty often
in my line of work.
Aw, that's sad.
It's not, it's just, we stake out places.
We have to make sure that we see the comings
and goings of people pretty often.
It's not sad they have steak.
I guess I'll do it.
Typically, when I sleep in my car,
it's cause it's like outside of the casino.
I had a bad night, so it's kinda not a great feeling
for me, but I guess I'll do it.
Well, you'll have a friend.
It's not a great feeling for anybody, bud,
but we're gonna be doing that for the next,
probably till like 6 a.m., it's only like four hours.
Yeah, he goes back to the Bronco.
Are you talking outside about all of this,
like standing outside of the office?
Defo, yep.
Okay, so as you're doing that,
eventually towards the end of the conversation,
the lights turn on on the inside.
The manager's apartment was back there,
so Riker actually lives inside the hotel,
and he overheard you talking loudly.
It's still September, he had his window open,
and eventually all the bickering about cars
and sleeping in the car and stuff woke him up.
So he comes out in his pajamas,
like a nice proper two-piece striped pajama suit,
a very handsome gentleman comes to the door,
all bleary-eyed.
Let me guess, let me guess,
you're those agents or whatever that call the hat, right?
DEA Task Force, yep, investigating Superman.
We're awfully sorry, sir.
Come on, come on, come in, come in, come in.
We appreciate you getting up out of bed for us.
Your nation thanks you.
Ah, I already, here, paperwork,
what, I just, I wanna go back to bed.
Just give us the keys, and we'll do it all tomorrow.
How about that?
All right, we got you in,
we got four different double bedrooms.
Perfect.
Yeah, you're in rooms six to nine.
I don't know why that's funny, but it got me.
I'll take the six.
I'll take the nine.
Seven's my lucky number, so.
I get the set leaves me with eight.
Oh, infinity on its side, like that man's tattoo.
Maybe it's lucky.
Does everyone go to bed?
Before we get to the rooms, I do wanna ask Riker
just a bunch of questions.
No, I just don't wanna ask him what rooms
Scott Adams is staying in.
Which rooms are the aliens in?
Yep.
Thank you for showing us to these rooms, Mr. Riker.
Now, we understand you have a guest here
staying with you, a Mr. Scott Adams.
How, how do you know that?
We heard from in town.
We're investigators, this is part of our investigation.
Oh.
Into super myth?
We're figuring it out, it'll be okay.
Super myth.
It'll be all right.
We just need to ask him some questions.
Just let us know which room he's in.
Your hotel is not in danger.
Room 10, you rented 10 and 11.
10 and 11?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Thank you so much for, I'm sorry to wake you up,
but I was not looking forward to sleeping in that car,
so thank you.
It's fine.
He turns around, goes back in, lights off.
Tan goes, goes to bed, he plays a little online poker.
No, he doesn't.
Yeah.
Thomas, get it through your head.
We don't know what existed in the 90s.
I know you're 17, but.
Oh, you're right, he doesn't.
He plays one of those little handheld machines.
Oh, yes.
It's like a double A battery.
Yeah.
Every time you like hit something that's at least
what, at least three of a kind or whatever,
it plays that we're in the money tune.
Yeah, monophonic.
Yeah.
He does that until he loses five times in a row,
and then Zs.
Anyone else doing anything before bed?
Taking a shower, doing anything else?
Harlan, he would flop on the bed fully clothed.
Okay.
Cindy puts away all of her clothes in each of the drawers
in the motel room and then goes and sets up her toiletries
at the bathroom sink and does her good night face wash,
puts on a face mask and then heads to bed
and has a full blown nightmare.
Joe slash Thomas, any special plans?
Yeah, Joe walks outside of his room and smokes a cigarette
and he wants to take a look at the outside
of rooms 10 and 11.
What is your alertness skill?
70.
Okay, well, all right.
Well, with a 70, you don't even have to roll.
The one thing you notice between the two rooms,
the room that was identified as Scott Adams' room,
so that's room 10, there's a little bit of cloth
sticking out from under the door.
It looks like a towel, like a standard hotel towel
kind of peeking out from underneath the door.
It's getting blazed in there, dude.
Like somebody had rolled one up under the door.
Yeah, and other than that, you also notice
the blinds are closed, but you can kind of see
through the blinds, nothing on the other side.
It's dark, almost as if there was a blanket put up
over the top of the closed blinds.
If I put my ear up to the door,
do I hear any sounds or activities, movements?
I'm not even gonna make you roll, you hear nothing.
Okay.
He uses the bathroom, takes a shower and goes to bed.
Everyone sleeps through the night.
You wake up, reasonable hour.
You notice the office is back open up front.
The lights are on again.
There's a little bit of movement.
However, there's not that many other cars
in the parking lot.
There's one van, your Bronco, your Crown Vic,
and then another rental car.
It looks to be a Ford Escort.
Are either of those parked in front of 10 or 11?
The Escort is.
The van's towards the other side
where the other rooms are on the other half of the aisle.
And you said we could tell it was a rental?
Escort is definitely a rental.
It's unclear of the other one.
When Tan wakes up, he goes into the office and asks,
do you have any coffee or food
or where should I go for that kind of stuff?
I'd recommend the Mega Deuce if you want a big meal.
But if you want a small meal, I got some coffee over here.
You know, your offices are the law.
I can cut you in on some donuts.
I appreciate that, but I'm a little hungry.
Tan leaves the office and knocks on your respective doors.
Hey, you guys wanna go to the Deuce to get some breakfast?
And maybe we can ask Scott to come with us.
You hear a scream when you knock on room number six.
And she's just like, ah!
I try to open the door and get in.
Cracks the door and she's like, sorry.
And she is drenched in sweat.
I mean, just like she jumped into a pool.
And she's like, let me shower.
I'll be right out.
I'm sorry, Miss Woodabaga.
Take a shower.
I think maybe we could take Scott to breakfast.
I think that's a great idea.
Do you wake up Cindy?
You wake up the other two as well?
Yeah, I knock on their doors as well.
Harlan just splashes some water under his pits
and puts on a new black polo from his suitcase.
That's the only difference.
Tan did not really plan for an overnight stay,
even though he totally knew that it was happening.
So he's still wearing the baby blue polo shirt
that the neck has been stretched out.
But he's happy and he's stoked to go eat breakfast.
Jodine is wearing a fresh white polo.
He nods approvingly at Harlan's sharp, fresh black polo.
And he puts on some sunglasses and says,
yeah, let's get some grip.
When Cindy comes out, the four of us stand at door 10.
Bring, bring, bring, bring.
No doorbells, unfortunately.
Old fashioned knocking, no answer.
We go to 11 and do the same thing.
You go to 11 and knock and no answer.
Scott, Scott, Scott.
Mr. Adams.
Nothing.
So while you're shouting, the manager hears you.
Riker peeks his head out, looks at you,
realizes kind of what's going on,
goes back behind the counter,
grabs some keys and comes out to you.
You're looking for Scott, you said?
For Mr. Adams, yeah.
Yeah, can you open his door up?
Do you have a warrant?
Well, this is more of a safety check.
Yeah, we believe he might be in some danger.
Danger from what?
Well, I think he might've fallen in his bathroom
or something, but I heard a big clunk
and it sounds like we need to get in there pretty quick.
Yeah, you wouldn't want anyone to die in your motel,
would you?
No, no, no, no, that'd be really bad for business.
It sounded bad, it sounded nasty.
Goes in, unlocks the door and says,
please, please, just go ahead.
He was like, if I live, I'm gonna sue.
We're like all like showing eyes to each other,
like as soon as we get in there,
we search everything as fast as we can.
You open and the second that door cracks open,
you catch a really bad odor.
Yeah, it's that kind of bad odor.
Yeah, okay.
It's very, very dark because of that blanket
that you can see now was duct taped over the window.
Looking around, you see a couple of different things.
You see the blankets that have been pulled off the bed
and used for that, so clearly the bed is unmade.
You see two piles of clothing.
One of them is just kind of thrown in the corner.
The other one is neatly folded on the table.
You also see a Macintosh PowerBook.
Is that like a laptop?
That's a laptop.
That's what laptops looked like in the early 90s.
But you see one of those bad boys plugged into the wall.
You see a series of documents,
junk food containers on the floor,
and that's pretty much all you can see
as you walk into the room.
Cindy failed her search check,
and so with that smell, as soon as it hits her nose,
she's like, nope, nope, not for me.
Can't be around any of that,
and just walks out back outside.
Tan also failed his search role,
and he feels physically sick and joins Cindy.
I pass my search role.
It's a 68.
I passed with a 17.
So Joe Dean and Harlan both pass.
Most of this stuff is very obvious,
kind of what you're seeing.
You do see some journals sitting around
that you didn't initially see on the first pass.
Just those spiral notebooks that kids would use in school,
and scrawled on the front of one of them
is Grover'sville Notebook.
He uses wide-ruled spiral notebook,
which also makes you kind of question his sanity,
why anyone would use the wide-ruled versus college-ruled
as an adult, but you know, it happens.
I also want to be clear.
You've only checked the one bedroom area.
There is still a rotten smell to be discovered.
When Tan leaves the room,
he's like, can't deal with that smell.
Hey, hey, Cindy, maybe we go check out the other room?
Yeah, we can go check out the other room.
Let's let them keep working on this one.
But in the meantime, that's what we'll be doing.
Yeah, sure, but you know that all four of us
can't talk all at the same time.
Technically we could, but.
I don't think so.
Let's try it.
We're doing it right now.
Start talking.
No one would want to listen.
So two of you are going over to the furthest room,
the storage room.
Two of you are still searching
in the Scott Adams primary room.
You're in the bedroom.
Are you checking out the notebook then?
That's what you want to do?
Well, I mean, so is there like a closed bathroom door
staring at us or a lump under the covers?
Slightly a jar bathroom door.
There's nothing under the covers.
The bed is definitely empty.
Okay, I have picked up the notebook,
but I do want to kind of kick open lightly with my foot,
the bathroom door.
And Harlan, where are you?
So I just succeeded to search.
Well, you told us there were two journals.
What's the other journal?
The other journal is just some like random UFO nonsense
related to his watch the skies.
It's like a log book.
Those assorted documents.
Can I look at those a little closer with that search rule?
It's going to take you some time.
So I'll let you kind of go through them in a little bit,
but you're not going to be able to necessarily do it
in real time.
It's just, it's a mess.
This room's been not necessarily like ransacked,
but it's just in complete disarray.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sitting there looking through that stuff
and he's going to the bathroom.
So we'll kick off with Joe Dean
before we get to the other room.
So Joe Dean, you get to the bathroom
and once the door is fully ajar,
you see where the smell is coming from.
You see a heavyset man in the bathtub,
roughly 34 years old in age,
curly black hair and a bushy beard.
He's in boxer shorts and wearing a t-shirt
Knoxville Fantasy Con 1989.
He's up to his chest in water.
Clearly the stopper is in the tub.
To make matters worse, that water is deep red
because you see numerous self-inflicted slashes
all over his body, arms, legs, everywhere.
Specifically the arms and legs.
You see floating in the water, just a single razor blade.
If I look at back into the room,
are there signs of an individual maybe like increasingly
succumbing to this kind of pain?
Is that how the room looks destroyed or?
No, no pain medication.
I guess what else did Billy Ray have
that was kind of obvious?
He talked about eating a lot and being hungry.
You see some takeout containers, but nothing crazy.
Yeah, not really a heck of a lot.
Okay, well then I guess the last thing
we wanna do in here is look at his computer.
Are you gonna do anything with the body?
I close the bathroom door and try to mitigate the smell
and I kind of motioned to Harlan.
I'm like, he's in there, you can have a look.
Harlan, like even wordlessly is just like an affirmation.
Like I knew he was gonna be in there.
You should look.
You wanna see a dead body?
Do you need a second opinion?
I will check, of course.
I just, from Thomas to Joe,
Harlan should see the insane way in which he died.
And then either I can describe that to you
or you can go look a look, take a look.
Yeah, I mean, I'm researching documents,
but I can go look in the bathroom.
You wanna look at the body?
I do, I guess I'll look at the body.
You hear some noises in the bathtub.
Ooh, like water sloshing or something else?
You see, yes, at the surface,
a little bit of bubbling coming up
and the water's moving slightly.
I called it, Jody.
Did you notice this and I'm just pointing at the bubbles?
Uh, Cindy, you guys wanna come take a look
at this real quick?
Cindy and Tanner are distracting Riker
outside of both of these rooms.
Yeah, we're really excited to try the Megaduce.
Yeah.
Everyone keeps telling us to go there.
Well, what would you suggest that I order?
Also don't breathe in through your nose.
Jody and Ashley, he busts out the door.
He says to Riker, strange question, maybe.
You got a fishnet, a big fishnet, small fishnet.
No, you know anybody with-
I got toilet plunger.
Can you bring me a fitted sheet?
Okay, goes and gets you a fitted sheet.
What's going on in there?
Yeah, why a fitted sheet or a big net?
Can we cut to the bathroom real quick?
Harlan's still in there and I wanna see
if the plug in the tub, is it a pull out?
You have to reach in your hand in the water
to pull it out or do you have to hit the switch on the side?
There's no switch.
So you have to press the button
to get the spring to trigger or pull it out.
It's one or the other.
But it's reaching into the water either way.
Yes.
Could I find something long like,
oh, can I pull the towel rack off?
Like just to undo that and I wanna use that
to push down on the thing to drain the tub.
What if the thing goes down the drain?
Ooh, that's why I wanted to like filter it out
with the sheet.
Yeah, I don't know.
I see.
Jodine, you looked initially at the body, right?
And you left.
Yes.
And then you came back in with Harlan?
Give me an alertness roll.
11, a crit.
With an 11, you notice something is different
than when you were first in the room.
And what's different was it looked initially
like he had some sort of like large pimple
or growth or something on his head,
kind of right on his forehead.
No hair on it, but it was like a growth on his skull.
By the time you come back, it's gone.
Harlan, step back.
Get out of this bathroom.
Harlan is holding the towel rack about to hit the thing.
You hear from inside the pipes underneath the bathtub,
bang, bang, bang, up against the stopper,
something coming up from inside the pipes,
going up into the bathtub, bang, bang.
What do you do?
Holy shit.
If this is like fight, flight or freeze,
we all just froze.
Yeah.
As you're standing there,
eventually the clanging pushes through,
the stopper bust out in this almost metallic looking liquid
starts pouring up through the bloody water.
So it starts cascading up into the ceiling,
spraying bloody water everywhere.
And then this metallic substance starts spraying
all over the room.
Oh my God.
Those of you in the room, give me a Dodge.
It's the Terminator.
Holy shit.
A one.
I rolled a one.
And I rolled a six on a 50.
Oh, all right.
So with both of those,
you're able to just back out really quickly
out of the bathroom,
not getting wet from any of the either bloody water
or this metallic stuff,
but it sprays up as a geyser and then falls back down.
And it's kind of mixed into this bloody water
as the tub is draining.
And everything that's sprayed up onto the walls and ceiling
kind of conjoins together,
almost like, you know, mercury beating together
and starts going back,
joining the rest of the stuff in the tub
and starts swirling down the drain.
Should we try to collect some?
I don't know.
I was not prepared for anything like this.
Mr. Winners?
Mr. Winners, I know it's the end of class,
but you forgot to collect our homework.
I don't want to be that guy,
but can these guys roll a fucking sanity check?
Oh yeah, shit.
Yes, they most definitely can.
Also, I have to pee so bad.
Are we close to pee time?
Yes, we are.
That's a fail.
Fail for me.
Oh no.
Oh yes.
Oh yeah.
Take four sanity damage each.
We got it.
Sorry, I was just, I was very much in the mood.
Make them roll again.
Do it, make them do it again.
Oh, just wait till you two search room 11.
Is it five for like temporary insanity?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yep.
You should have made it five.
So a little bit of sanity damage,
but you're not wet from the metallic oozy stuff.
Yeah, I think that probably would have been a day
for you and me, Joe.
What do you do though as it's swirling down the drain?
Yeah, I don't know.
Joe Dean grabs one of like a cup from the fast food debris,
a Wendy's cup or some shit, whatever's there.
And he just tries to grab a drop that's falling down
from the ceiling and like catch it in the cup.
He catches it.
It recognizes its path almost was obstructed.
It rapidly expands from being just a couple drops in size,
outward, super flat, super wide, shattering the cup.
And then the glass and liquid falls back into the tub.
Joe Dean like drops it as it shatters in his hands,
walks out of the bathroom and closes the door.
Thomas's eyes were so big as you were describing that.
Keep Rekker out of here.
Rekker, I go outside and I'm gonna say Rekker,
this was not the right fitted sheet.
Like why don't you, can we go,
we needed something different.
Maybe I don't know what a fitted sheet is.
Could you just bring back a lot of things
from like the deepest part of your linen closet?
Oh, sure, sure.
Maybe crack open room 12 real quick.
That way we can do a safety check in there before you go.
Oh, 11, I think, but yeah.
12, if you have it.
Yeah, you can just leave us that key if that's all right.
We really do need those linens quite quickly.
I'll unlock it.
You can open it when you need it.
Okay, thank you.
He jets off.
Nice guy.
Yeah, he has one of the most prestigious jobs in town.
He's managing a 11 room motel.
Big time for Merle, the richest man in town.
Yeah.
Exactly.
By this time though,
you can reason that the entire tub is drained.
Now you have this room with a computer,
some journals, and also room 11.
Now the other thing that you can't see on the map
that I didn't mention,
there's actually a door inside of this room
conjoining room 10 and 11 as well.
You can also try to go into room 11.
There's a mech in that one closet.
Well, when Riker lets us into room 11,
Tanner and Cindy will go in there.
Yeah.
Into room 11?
Okay, you crack open the door,
you see a second motel room.
This one in much better condition.
However, you do see it's been lived in.
This is not in fact a room for storage.
There is clothing, a couple of suitcases,
and there is a young girl curled up in the fetal position
in the corner of the room silently up against the wall
listening to what was happening in Scott Adams's room.
Jane?
Yeah?
Holy shit.
Thank God that you're safe.
And Cindy is gonna walk up,
pull a second cardigan out of her purse
and go to wrap it around the back of this poor girl.
And Cindy's being real soft, taking a real gentle approach.
Dear, can you tell us at all what happened?
I disappeared.
Yeah.
And, yeah, and something happened to me.
It was three weeks ago.
Okay.
And as she stands up, you look at her.
She is about six months pregnant.
Oh, shit.
Jane, Jane, how long?
You said you disappeared three weeks.
How long were you gone?
A couple of hours.
Jane, I have a really strange question to ask you.
And I want you to just be very serious.
Take it calm, okay?
How long have you been pregnant?
That's the thing.
Yeah.
Maybe a month?
Is it Billy's?
Yes.
Okay.
Do you remember the lights?
Yes.
Do you remember any sounds?
No, no.
Any smells?
They put things in me.
Yeah, I want to look at her arms.
Well, actually, you don't see anything on her arms.
What about her belly?
Yeah.
So you'll find those same kind of incisions
all on her lower abdomen.
She is just wearing a t-shirt inside.
Another thing you'll notice in this room,
there are food containers galore.
Compared to Scott Adams' room,
there are 10 times as many food containers.
Any prescription, I assume?
No pain meds.
Tylenol?
No.
Doesn't seem like the muscle thing happened to her.
You're one of those weak people
who relies on pain medication, aren't you, Tan?
Very odd way to phrase that, but yeah.
Will you give this girl some?
She's pregnant, I don't know if you're supposed to take that.
Just ibuprofen, I don't know.
I don't know much about pregnancy.
You can roll medicine for me.
Oh wait, none of you took medicine.
How about this, I'll roll anyway.
David's like, it's about drugs,
and we're like, none of us will have the medicine skill.
How about that?
Yeah, it's not a crit fail, just a regular fail.
Nice.
You think it's fine.
Hey, Cindy, I think we found our alien.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Jane, your mother is worried sick about you.
I don't wanna see her.
She can't see me like this.
They're gonna be so disappointed in me.
I don't know if they have the capacity for that.
I just don't wanna see them.
That's why I contacted Mr. Adams.
Yeah, tell us, what's your relationship with Mr. Adams?
Just needed help.
What kind of help were you looking for?
What could he offer you?
Something to explain what happened to me,
the lights and everything.
And he was in town and asking about aliens and stuff,
and I thought maybe that would be it.
I don't know, but he paid for this room.
He was bringing me food.
Did he help with anything else?
No, he just, he was keeping me safe.
He was gonna take me to Nashville to see a doctor.
He said, it's not safe here in town,
and I have to go elsewhere.
And when was the last time you saw him?
I talked to him.
Yesterday morning, he was supposed to bring me food,
and I'm getting so hungry.
So you didn't go next door?
No, he told me to keep a low profile.
And what did you do with him the day before that?
He just told me to stay here.
He said he was researching the town,
and once he had enough evidence,
we were gonna leave and go to Nashville.
Did you guys physically touch?
Did you shake his hand?
Did you high-five him?
He might've put his hand on my shoulder at some point,
but I think maybe that's it.
I don't know.
I'm so hungry and scared.
Well, we'll get you some food, okay?
Okay.
Now you can all roll me a sanity.
Yeah.
Having seen this young girl who is four weeks pregnant,
but showing the signs of being around six months pregnant,
seven months pregnant.
Yeah, it's a fail.
I had to fail for me as well.
Three sanity damage.
I am down to 44.
I am down to 46.
Ooh.
Breaking point, 43.
I'm at 36.
I'm at a 45.
Tanner feels sick,
and he's just like Luke is not sure what to do next.
Would we be able to say that in this time
that they've been talking to her,
that Jodine and Harlan have gone through the papers
for Harlan and the computer for Jodine?
Fact, we would be able to.
Sweet.
Let's go through the paper first.
Would there also be cool information in there
that they could learn that would be cool enough
to end an episode on?
Dude, I have to be so fast.
Yep, right here.
Sick.
Yeah, you got any real prizes in there?
It's in front of you.
Read off some of it.
Oh, shit.
Be surprised.
Gotcha.
We've got a listing of number of livestock mutilations here.
There were three cows, a goat, and 20 chickens.
There's also livestock alterations.
A cow was missing an udder, but otherwise in good health.
Spotted three more in a roadside survey.
Didn't know who the farmer was.
We've also got accounts of missing time,
chopper sightings, lights.
Everyone's seen some, it says.
Allen, Barn, Thomas, Jacobs, Cartwright, and Anderson
never go home.
Never go home.
Do we know any of those names besides Allen?
Barn is Merle.
Cartwright is the family from Bonanza.
Yep.
And also.
Those are all the aldermen.
You would have seen their names on offices.
When we were in the courthouse,
we would have seen their names.
Yeah, so Jane's dad, Merle Barn,
and then you would have seen the other names too.
Oh, this is, we did know.
That's not like some ominous, mysterious thing.
We knew he wasn't going home.
Right, but never go home.
Exactly.
But I thought it was like,
Scott Adams knows they'll never go home.
Their story ends here.
["I Gotta Work In The Morning"]
I gotta work in the morning
And this shit's so important
So I can't get high
No, I can't get high
I thought this stuff helped anxiety
It must be something inside of me
Does anybody know why?
I can't get high
I can't sit though I can
And I don't wanna try
Please, my smile, won't you spare me
Something more can be bought
Where do you begin?
I don't know how
Hallucination's so big-time, but
Spider's out the line
Breathing
I'm breathing
I've been hiding in low, low places
With some funny-looking dudes
With some fucked-up faces
And I can't help but feel it
I'll always be at the bottom
["I Gotta Work In The Morning"]
I think I'm allergic or something
Better go on with nothing
So I won't get high
No, I won't get high
By all means, do it if it helps
For me, it makes my brain melt
Does anybody know why?
I can't get high
I can't sit though I can
And I don't wanna try
Please, my smile, won't you spare me
Something more can be bought
Where do you begin?
I don't know how
Hallucination's so big-time, but
Spider's out the line
Breathing
I've been hiding in low, low places
With some funny-looking dudes
With some fucked-up faces
And I can't help but feel it
I'll always be at the bottom
Thanks for watching!