hello there my adoring children it is your dog wolf the god and i'm bringing down my
righteous and infallible judgment here on 694.2 p t b p contentions most holy and blessed
radio station you're all seeing all knowing wolf has a correction to make from my previous
transmission see judge f from courtland isn't actually at fault in regards to my kidnapping
he was simply a patsy a cog and preacher sheriff talked to bobby custard's dastardly scheme
wherein i mean a scheme which was perpetuated by the other three are still alive okay okay
a scheme which was perpetuated by the despicable three custard's minions everett pace jack
pearlman and professor horace green do not trust these real life versions of kevin stewart
and bob our last hope is my personal lord and savior silas kohl the only begotten son
of wolf the way the truth and the light no one comes to the dog except through him glory
to coal in the silas forever and ever um y'all knew that shit weren't me right what old wolfie
do you dirty like that fuck no silas and mary kohl ain't up to no good and they can somehow do
some cursed shit but they can't quite recreate wolf the dog i don't know how they got so damn
close but i do know two things to be certain i need to go on and get the shit out of the past
and this here is a brand spanking newfangled bop that puts a pop in your
slop it's the creek rocks with can't you hear them wolves are howling
can't you hear them wolves are howling all around my poor little darling
all around my poor little darling i'm afraid they'll get my darling
can't you hear them wolves are howling all around my poor little darling all around my poor little
darling i'm afraid they'll get my darling can't you hear them wolves are howling all around my poor little
darling all around my poor little darling i'm afraid they'll get my darling
you guys remember that mandy moore movie which one a walk to remember of course i do oh where
she's in two places at once yeah shit i was thinking of the one with the was that the main
inspiration for the primary campaign zach yeah of course as a the uh the son of a preacher man
as a son of a preacher man i love that song and that movie so yeah of course uh when the when the
ball destroys everyone in that if you like that song so much name five songs from that song
a walk to remember uh six pence on the richards greatest hits no i was actually thinking of the
movie with julia styles i fucked up fucked up the whole that season of dextre about you
no shit what movie am i thinking of julia and julia
julia styles and julia that's not an snl sketch uh we should uh we should edit that together
uh no who is in save the last dance i don't know uh was it freddie prince jr joe's on it
joe tell me the answer you were correct julia styles is in save the last dance
thank you i don't know like maybe i should have given more hints
what happens in that movie why did oh she's just trying to make a documentary about michael jordan
really no but did you have any did you have anything to say about that luke
uh did you have anything really really really good to say about the michael jordan documentary
last night and i like i was doing something on my computer and i look up and in it there's this
dude that looks like he has like ramen noodle hair and he's like walking by and for i literally had
to rewind it because i thought it was kyle mooney like doing a character because he like walked like
kyle mooney and was making some weird like joke and like making his hands and arms do exactly
kyle mooney shit but it was just some old like dude with like terrible hair oh are you talking
about his weird security guard guy yeah he like doesn't look like a real person but i was like
i'm like is kyle mooney in this and then realized no because he was probably 10 years old when that
was filmed you were right luke it was good that we discussed that on the podcast instead of before
we recorded well i just wanted something to say i think he said he had multiple things to say
about the documentary well i ended up looking up who that guy was so we've gotten the first one
oh oh one b so part two of the first thing who is the skiff fellow i uh don't remember his name
but he was like worked security for the for the united center and that was it that's all i could
find about him wow we've struck gold once again luke that's still your first thing really detective
luke is on the case he just blew vape smoke directly into his camera as if to put it in
each of our faces simultaneously and put a lovely point on the uh had i not said let's
record this on the podcast we would still not be recording the podcast and that's a very good
true yeah he engineered it he made it happen he hacked us all and some would argue we're not
recording the podcast yet only if it takes it in are we technically recording the podcast
getting ready to play ephraim i've never been more happy to say luke take your headphones off
you're being punished luke hold on i'm getting a call from my dad let's see if we can engineer a
real uh a real luke's mom moment here here 80 episodes later uh i'm in the middle of recording
say something scary to who just say something spooky i don't know
trump gets reelected
perfect all right
he's right that's fucking horrifying love you back
all right what is ever at pace currently doing uh last i remember i think i was just i just was
covering the front door with my gun the last episode i was headphones off for a good portion
at the end so i don't know how things have progressed from there judge ephraim courtland
had gone in after silas kohl who went in handcuffed you haven't heard anything
since i believe you failed some listen world and you have your gun trained at the door jack
pearlman what is the in the words of the name on our zoom call sex icon and probably dead soon
character doing i have a one hp and not much sanity and i believe i failed my first aid
role on myself so i just like oh yeah you hurt yourself i think i hurt myself even more yeah
and i'm just like on the ground i don't i don't with one hp am i able to like do anything or am
i like i'm down on the ground yeah no absolutely because you succeeded on your constitution check
you don't have any mechanical disadvantages toward you currently based on the way that
i like playing this game cool okay good to know i mean if you try to sprint after someone i'll
probably be like hey maybe take a massive negative yes yeah yeah besides that what's professor horse
green doing i don't know where are we yes that is correct that was my question for you
yeah no one answered no i'm covering the door and he's injured outside the door
right yard of this the coal home i think you're also injured next to me no i'm very hurt i know
that but i got a little healing so i'm yes i was i was close to dead no i'm not you just blew the
brains like you just blew the head off of the preacher doctor sheriff bobby custard right but
i didn't see it so i missed the sanity and you're the only one who didn't lose sanity
so horace horace shouts uh by god maybe he'll listen to the law or a man of god where's the
preacher sheriff he just starts reaching around him trying to feel out for the the preacher
sheriff everett is not going to look back but just kind of gesture back to where the body is
you done nailed him you done nailed him and you're gesturing to the back of the wagon where his body
flew but the head is sitting about 10 feet away from horace green on the ground where it landed
with a thump and if you were golfing you would have to fix the divot that the head made when
it landed initially in the dirt horace green vomits good heavens
pearlman's just clinching his his leg and he's just like god damn it but somehow due to his
his sex icon status i think is really powering to stand up because you can't be sexy while you're
bleeding on the ground i thought you're gonna say sitting down or sitting down
zack trust me no one's ever looked sexy sitting in a chair ever or sitting on the ground or
laying down has anyone ever been sexy laying in a bed i'm looking at five really sexy dudes
sitting in chairs right now we should record the show standing maybe oh no i think the vibe change
the people couldn't handle that there'd be way too much chaotic energy happening if
i we weren't bound to our chairs over each other more sorry i stood for a second
god damn it i i have to download these files luke no you don't you literally don't like it's not a
rule that you have to look at what luke sends us over the chat while we're recording minions
pornography it's true it's it's not a rule but luke if you want people to look at them you need
to send a link or something because these make you download the file and i'm not gonna do that
he doesn't have a headphone on he does not have a headphone oh god damn it he's just being a little
terrorist throwing bombs into the session okay exactly i'll text him and let him know stop it
just says stop jack pearlman standing up and standing next to everette with his rifle out
also i want to holler into the house judge you in there you got him you got him cornered
and do i hear any reply we'll find out
oh god he's not in this window
he's smoking the hella dead he is he definitely is he's not dude no he wasn't
hi it was just right when we right when we started flipping the bird is that what we're
calling that yeah when we started birding to get him to come back he blew the smoke directly into
the camera i've always thought of uh thought of it as asking um them to fly away home oh like
come back to their home like that movie i didn't see hey guys check the links i sent on the zoom
no thanks no that's what i was trying to tell to you um when we we have to download those and i'm
not gonna fucking do that so just upload them to imager or something and then send them that way
you can't just click and download it no i'm not saving your bullshit on my computer
wait don't do that judge what do you see literally doing it currently i'm doing it right now
look at the general idea oh is it the the chicago bulls guy yeah his name's mike no let's see can
we all agree that these links are stupid and ruinous what why do you guys hate this so much
i'm trying to record a goddamn podcast well if you would have just looked at the fucking pictures
oh dude if you would have sent this like literally 20 minutes ago it would have been perfect this guy
is hilarious looking also it does not look like kyle mooney dude if you could just get the second
picture we love you we hate this
i'm ready whenever
i wish luke was like i'm i gotta photoshop some a couple things real quick
it's just the same picture with minion oh my god there's another one luke i take everything back
this was worth it yeah yeah especially for the people listening to this audio medium look up
john michael was what's his name wasniac there you have it folks all right good night guys
luke how does the judge uh well i was gonna i thought i was gonna be by myself
can we uh get these other guys off oh no he's like what i'm about to do is unspeakable to other
humans all right everybody else taking their headphones off so judge ephraim courtland having
just been removed from his own body and replaced with mary mary cole you are in the bedroom silas
coal is still handcuffed he was hiding behind a turned over bed however now he is uh still behind
the bed and still in handcuffs but he's not cowering in fear he's now crouching in concentration
focusing deeply on the words he is chanting into this disheveled bedroom a beaming light forms on
his lips and a white hot blaze of color begins dripping down viscous and alive and it puddles
beneath silas cole's chanting mouth onto the dusty floor below before flowing gently toward the far
side of the room okay luke you can also see as mary cole there's an oily black substance leaking
from your facial orifices you can kind of feel it like a like a perpetual runny nose and eyes
and ears and mouth and this squamous eye core seems to almost pull itself down to the ground
where this mesmerizing brilliant light has pooled between the two doors of this room
the syrup made out of the absence of color that just came out of you begins swirling into its
opposite and the two unnatural ungodly glass-forming liquids at first refuse to blend
like oil and vinegar but then the most beautiful awe-inspiring color you've ever seen forms from
this bond and another equally mind-shattering color joins it and another and another and now
the old wooden floor on the far side of this bedroom between the only two doors
is covered jam to jam with a perversely extraordinary technicolor portal
right so i'm gonna go over and take the handcuffs off of silas look at him and be like okay i'm gonna
lead him in here just be ready for him wide-eyed silas is just nodding uh ephraim steps over the
portal carefully and opens the door shuts it behind him and as he enters back into the living
room are you going the living room or the back door do the doors open in to where the portals
are or out they open in cool good okay so i'll shut the that door behind me and then
i'm just gonna exit the house the front was yeah was it the first room that all the gore and stuff
was in yes okay i was in the front okay i'm gonna exit and head out and as you're in there you hear
ever at pace yell out judge you in there you got him you got him quarter uh open the door and
look for him hi hello did you guys have a good time alone like you always
get to do mm-hmm zach never gives me alone times anymore you just have to make bold bold character
choices and then you get alone time with the handler and it's always good yeah guys i guess
we're hanging back on this one to uh let justin get some alone time so i store them in alone
wherever i could go alone i run everyone take your headphones off i have to tell zach something
important i love you
secret kiss secret kiss
okay okay they can get their headphones back on
now that we're all back here were you guys secret kissing in here
no you didn't see anything or here joe you fucking keep your mouth shut
or join us next time so judge ephraim courtland opens up the front door to the cole homestead
as ever at pace and jack promen have their guns set on the front door and professor horace green
is horrifyingly staring at the head of pastor sheriff preacher doctor pastored preacher
doctor pastored preacher sheriff doctor bobby custard which is on the ground about 10 feet
away from him judge ephran courtland as you walk out you see that head just sitting on the ground
and you do not see the body blood is everywhere and the three of these men
are the only ones out here you no longer find the wild crazed teenager
like one of those teenagers at one of those concerts that you might find just wild smoking
reaper oh my god can you even imagine that's probably what made her this way every every uh
jumps and it almost shoots but oh it's judge horace sees its judge and shoots
i come outside and look and see the head and i just look at them like what
what what happened horace is slowly crawling like in amazement towards the head well yeah
we had we had we had a little accident out here what's what's going on in there did you get did
you get silas well yeah in a way um i got him we cut he ran in there cuffed up and uh you know
there's some stuff in that front room y'all probably need to see and and i got him back in
one of the one of the other rooms but ephraim what happened out here what's got you so shaken
up he takes a long drag from the flask that is in his jacket pocket i think you just need to
come see it horace horace i walk over to horace horace has reached uh has reached the head
and he's just grabbed it by the hair and he's looking it in the eyes horace now i know you
ain't much for fighting but sometimes things just happen in battle you can't you can't always
predict it i've been in plenty of bar fights where i accidentally punched some fellers i
didn't mean to and when you throw guns in the mix you just know you're asking for trouble it ain't
your fault so just to if you could if you could put the head down and and we might need you in
here but there's there's things happening so if you put it down of of course of course we're
needed inside and he takes he doesn't put the head down he carries it with him
it's right through here boys
excuse me right through here
and i just kind of point to the first room inside i'll carefully start dottering up but i want to
keep my gun kind of at the ready i'm not pointing at anything in particular but i could if i needed
to and i'm cautious about it all every night doing so hot if you want to take lead i'll back
you up though as i'm i assume i'm like dripping blood all over the place at this point 100
professor horace green is also dripping blood from the head he's carrying are you carrying it
with you into the home with two hands or by the hair with one hand or you buy the hair with one
hand uh-huh why just curious uh horace green doesn't he doesn't hear that question
no yeah i'm asking thomas i guess what's going on inside professor horace green's
mind well it's because this is a comedy podcast and that's hilarious
yeah i don't know why you're slowing it down like this sack
oh i was thinking that we could have like a good character moment
you're you're interrupting a good character moment
he's dazed carrying a head around and not saying anything
he's busy downloading my pictures of wasniac that won't make sense because i'll have edited
it as the three of you head in specifically horace green uh the smell of rotten flesh
is the first thing you notice as you pass through the swinging open front door of the whole abode
at first you think the stench could be from the unattended dishes strewn throughout this living
room the remnants of several meals now covered in a few buzzing flies but that static hum of flies
it's so loud in your ears and looking over you see that that is due to the large swarm hovering
about the body of miss kitty which is laying lifeless across one of the sitting chairs
lifeless to be sure because this body the skin is chewed up so badly that chunks are hanging off
or completely missing and the dripping dark red blood pooling below on the floor but especially
lifeless due to the way this body is crumpled her back held directly in the middle by one of
the armrests there's an unnatural angle there as the top half of her torso dangles straight down
perpendicular to the floor i'll never get a chance to string her up now
uh go ahead and roll sanity for me pace pearlman and green oh god my dice
oh god god damn it uh so i have a super oh no wait i'm good uh 78 on a 78 is that oh that's huge
orange green rolls a seven baby oh congratulations to all
none of you lose any sanity and you're all able to make a listen check
i heard it here coins in a glass
what's happening
what was that nice putting all the other dice away because i spilled them all out like an idiot
just wanted you guys to pretend like you didn't notice for once
you're doing a hearing check i got 14 what did i roll
a 14 no but i mean what was a listen oh i barely passed we need to talk
uh i fail a 49 on a 40 we're we're doing listen not anymore you failed your listen check by
not hearing me say that before well no then justin did his deal and i made a joke about it
i was doing the professor horse green and jack pearlman please keep your headphones on
hey um do you want to do uh do you want me to fail a sanity test earlier on when i see the
head or something that is why i to give that a little more omph yeah i just figured it's it's
delta green let's get weird with it but he would be emotionally devastated exactly that's all i
wanted you to say earlier so okay hold on hold on hold on real quick hold on roll sanity you said
88 that's a critical failure
i think he's gonna fix it on that head
so
horse green jack pearlman judge ephraim courtland the three of you hear a slight murmur
from the next room deeper into this house
bob he's oh i chased him in there and he's uh tied up but he's been yet just saying those
mumble words over and over again which room's he in do we know a bob the one that you got
right there horace holds the head up and looks at it quizzically i don't think he'll like this
this is the first time ever he's noticed that you've brought the head in with you
what the hell you why are you holding up the head you should have just left that outside what
are you why'd you bring a head in it what's going on here horse so he can see he's dead horse he's
dead he killed him okay professor horse green starts laughing no no no yeah no he doesn't
horace looks really confused and he looks at you and he looks at the head and then he moves the
jaw holy shit and he's like i'm not dead oh my god
ever ever exchanges a glance with like jack pearlman but it's not of like scared it's just
like well we lost one i guess uh jack just shrugs yep you're getting the floors dirty with all that
blood there i don't horse if you could put a napkin under bobby that would be he's dripping
he's causing me oh my oh my how how rude and horace takes off his um his handkerchief and
ties it around the stump on the neck i don't think you're gonna be making much more of a mess
that's already in here those other two rooms ain't too ain't too good either well it ain't
proper for a head not to be covered on the bottom i think he's quite dashing now aren't you yes i am
why are you all looking at me like that maybe we should continue upon our our our business here and
talk to horace about some stuff later yeah well if we i think i hear him still chanting in there but
uh he's just passed in through those doors what did you do to him i just i got him
beat up pretty good and i got him hogtied and and and cuffed up and he's just i don't know i might
have hit him in the head too hard or something what do you reckon he killed his kitty for i i
didn't really have time to find out i just kind of lost it on him and then uh came to see what
you guys were doing i'm you know didn't want to do it alone you think maybe she was breaking into
his house last night and that's he must have caught her that's that's got to be what happened
could be why to keep her inside though he didn't he didn't mention her back at the at the church
seems like that something he would have never liked silas maybe he stole something from her
like he stole something from me but what do you think happened teddy i think the zombie girl
later oh well now that's a thought perhaps what do you guys think maybe we ought to just go ask
him yeah i think it's best we talk to silas cole face to face right man figure this all out if you
want to lead the way go ahead because i feel like i'm gonna lose it on him again if i go in there
first and can't promise he'll have much to say after i get to him any of us check if mary's here
mary mary upstairs do i hear any response from upstairs there is no upstairs so probably i don't
then roll sanity wait wait wait wait if we roll can we make there an upstairs you said we could
roll stealth for rocks can we roll listen for upstairs it's a 40 story skyscraper i don't have
to tell you that role-playing is a collaborative storytelling experience roll listen just ever at
pace i pass a six on a 40 you hear what is definitely a couple of squirrels hanging out
up on top of the house i don't know if mary's here or not there's a couple squirrels up there though
i didn't see anybody else sad's kitty and silas when i came in where you reckon mary's off to you
i don't rightly know and i head towards the first door and just kind of
shove it open with my foot and i point he's in there uh i get yeah i'll i'll i'll make my way
into the room that silas is being kept okay real quick i just gotta do a wicked piss okay oh got
you sorry i've been drink drinking a lot of this bubbly to try to get burps and now my stomach hurts
that's uh it's workers comp i think in the podcast world i'm gonna have to draw on
disability from pretending llc
did you hear about the florida marlins thing they had eight new cases today oh they had
a total 14 oh i oh okay i got you i i think baseball is going to be canceled again oh it's
100 canceled you think the nba is not next like the nba has no way football can even start the
nba had zero cases recently it's not going to be long until it's over all right let's wow zach
i'm just an optimist baby depending on when this comes out that'll be super dated
optimist well like baseball is about to shut down again yeah probably for good for the forever
it's over forever everyone decided they didn't you're over forever football's stupid
baseball rules shut up it's golf or uh i think you can probably play cornhole still dude that's
too high contact every flip through to one of those like shitty alternative sports channels
and they're showing cornhole tournaments and it's just like it's more like a dad bod tournament
it's like who can be the roundest like right in the middle yeah they got really thin calves
real thin everything except for except for the perfect beer belly and their corn arm their corn
arm yeah how about the five of us challenge the five best cornhole players in america
to a game of cornhole um to promote our podcast and the losers have to live on moron mountain
forever yeah yeah you need to say you don't like the idea with swack hammer as their boss
it's a there's a space jam ref so uh
if i could get a text speaking of space jam i was watching this michael jordan
did you see anybody weird oh dude let me tell you
i got a 43 on a 45 oh shit that's gonna be very good that's great jack
professor was green you're gonna be at a negative 20 yeah that does not matter because i already
went way over a 72 on a 40 okay i'm a 79 on a 30 okay 30 on a 60 i love how nimble this
towering behemoth man is because of my horse riding capabilities you've adopted the way of
the horse for your legs you've got very thin calves in my free time i run around my house
on all fours and jump over stuff oh god oh how horrifying to imagine a man in the 1880s
uh-huh specifically just barely yeah he burns down three houses a year with all the oil lamps
silas cole saved you a lot of money why are you after him he stole my damn wire
i can't prance around like i used to
do life went back to the dark ways pace begins hobbling toward the door that courtland
has just opened up and it is jack pearlman's turn what would you like to do uh what do i see
where are you going i was following ever at pace uh you could easily pass him if you would like
or you can continue to walk behind him i'll still stay behind him with my gun kind of tracked on the
door so i'm trailing him i'm letting it is your turn i uh sorry finish that thought oh me yeah
i stood up for a second that's my oh that's cool i'm gonna stand up more now you big bully
i don't even remember it was stupid
horace isn't going down the hallway uh because he's just also not his turn judge courtland
you're in thomas standing up oh shit sorry i'm standing up
it seemed like a moment to stand up i was just gonna get one little bit in
uh but now zach's all like let's make this a forecast but that was really good no
what was that a pun of podcast oh forecast anyway
horse green isn't going down the hallway towards the door because he and the skull
and the head are just standing there going like after you after you after you after you
so i'm like holding the door open for them and i see that and i just kind of like
gently grab a horse by the sleeve and like pull him like guide him into the room
horse and the skull look at each other and they're like after him
and they follow you do they say it at the same time
yes they do professor horace green as courtland escorts you past ever at pace and jack pearlman
into this room right as you are at the threshold of this door looking down you see hey if uh
ever at pace and jack pearlman justin joe if you could take off your headphones real quick
as well as luke that would be phenomenal
professor horace green as you keep direct eye contact with preacher sheriff doctor
detached head bobby custard you notice out of the corner of your peripheral a disturbingly
magnificent technicolor swirl of light covering the part of the floor in this room that's
immediately in front of you it's likely the most beautiful thing you have ever seen and yet there
is an endlessness about it that inspires both awe and dread i need you to roll sanity
uh fail um 73 on a 60 you're gonna lose one sanity um horace uh horace walks through the
portal horse green with this head in one of your hands you step down into nothingness
and immediately you feel content
that's all i can say at this time oh dang did i just turn myself into a tilde zombie i can't
answer that question currently well a zombie with a zombie with a little head buddy would
be really funny it would be very fun all right so you can uh you can leave the zoom call if you
want honestly okay i'll stay i mean i'll be by my phone so yeah you can hang out on the zoom call
but stay by your phone and oh yeah i'll just watch you guys yeah there you go uh okay
ever paste jack pearlman judge ephraim courtland the three of you see professor horace green walk
into the room however you are at a current angle where you are right now walking towards this door
to where you can't quite see where he went once he got into the room and you can't really see
into the room quite yet into the next room where silas is exactly okay and ever at pace it is your
turn the fact that we're in turn order would make joe nervous but ever it's just walking in to see
where judge ephraim courtland tied up silas i think ever pace would be nervous due to the odd
chanting that you can now hear coming from this room that you know is silas cole who is apparently
tied up hogtied uh who is saying bob da hahaha bob da hahaha bob da hahaha and with the door
open you can hear it quite clearly and there's that body that was all munched up on i kind of
stop when i hear wait what oh the miss kitty you mean yeah yeah there's reasons to be uh nervous
not forever namely everything that's just a chewed up body ain't nothing here now found
miss kitty she's dead that sucks so it goes but mission accomplished he hears uh he hears the
chanting and stops and listens for a second and kind of looks back at judge and pearlman
bob da hahaha ring a bell for anybody bob da hahaha is he is he in town you think he's a relation
or something maybe it's his lawyer he needs his lawyer bob da hahaha maybe i i don't know judge
is there a is there a lawyer in town bob da hahaha i think i've dealt with him once or twice
that's what it is he's gonna need a good lawyer for this one and i keep walking in
uh yeah justin and luke take off your headphones real quick for me
joe as you walk toward the open door you see a technicolor swirl has taken over the entirety
of the floor right is you where you're about to walk in on i need you to roll a sanity check as
all of these rainbow colors just wash back and forth in a circle around where your next step
might be i pass a 16 on a 78 you lose no sanity ever wants to look up at the ceiling to see what's
projecting this down onto the floor there's nothing up on the ceiling that would affect
what is happening here on the floor does anything change with my step
like into like onto it do you step onto it i thought you said i did you don't have to
well fuck i think i think since he didn't pass a since he passed a sanity role he doesn't he's
not too worried about it he just thinks that a pretty light show going on in here somehow
there must be a stained glass revolving uh candle lit thing and as that first step goes down you
feel your foot continue to move through the floor as ever it pays trips and falls face first into
this technicolor swirl and you feel your body become wholly content in this moment welcome
evert professor horace green says to you in a space of pure darkness and somehow at the same
time completely technicolor welcome evert horse is that you yes eddie's here too oh you you
brought the you brought the head with you too all right where are we who cares doesn't it feel great
yeah i mean i don't know if i ever experienced a time when i was so it just it's relaxing i guess
and the two of you are just falling but you're falling up seemingly you reckon you think we're
on our way up to the big man in the sky i think that's probably what this is what do you think
happened you think we we must have stepped in a bear trap got us got us through an artery or
something in that room to me it looked like a beautiful gateway to an ascendant plane
that's what i saw too that must have been the last drags of the blood leaving our body and
making our brains see the something that would give us comfort in our final moments evert uh
normally i'm a man of of reason and science but uh well science never made me feel like this
i think probably we just yeah we died you're right yep we died don't question it we're going
to heaven this is great uh just enjoy this this falling upwards as it were clara here i come
and above you you see only darkness it'll take me a minute i don't even see the light yet but
i'll be there jack promen yeah hey man hey it's your turn uh i'm following evert into the into the
thing gun out and as you walk up to the door that is slightly open that both professor horse green
and evert pace have walked through you see on the floor an incredible swirl of technicolor
vibrancy just washing about in circles around and around the floor and i need you to roll sanity for
me but it's so party it is but it is crazy as hell oh 51 yeah on a 39 it'd be cool if i could
pass one sanity check well with a failed sanity check
you're going to be at a negative depending on what you want to do here okay but looking into
this room uh you just see the majority of this floor about half the room is covered in this
gorgeous rainbow colored swirl like light that is mesmerizing light like bioluminescence or whatever
you do not see ever at pace you do not see professor horse green you only see
a bed that is flipped over and from behind it you hear
silas what the hell are you chanting that for who's bob to hob and i guess i'll have you roll
a dexterity at a negative 20 to keep your footing as you enter into this room negative 20 because
you failed you're saying fuck 29 on a 25 so close that'll do it as you uh
as your foot steps into this room without being able to make the jump
over it or stop yourself from stepping onto it your foot moves through the floor
and you begin falling through this technicolor swirl of a portal and you begin falling upward
and upward and you feel completely content physically oh that sounds nice except for
the part where i'm in an endless hell of some kind yes it is complete darkness and at the
exact same time every color you've ever seen swirling around you and above you there's nothing
but the absence of light and the bodies of ever at pace and professor horse green who are having
a perfectly normal conversation oh shit jack did the bear trap get you too we just all plumb ran
into it didn't we hello jack um long story short we're probably in heaven uh i don't want to get
too into it because we're probably gonna have to do this again with the judge really quickly here
so uh but if you could if if you can just wait if you could just wait wait we're gonna get to
it in just a moment i'm sure we'll answer all your questions and you wait and you wait
and the judge does not come oh thank god the judge must have skipped over that bear trap in
that room kind of bear trap sends you into another goddamn i guess it could have been some kind of
trap that fell from the ceiling but either way something killed us as soon as we walked in the
room and now we're on our way up to heaven most likely you sure we're dead can i touch ever at
pace's face like i put my hand out to touch his face like face off where i go yeah and touch his
face you're asking a lot of questions for a content person you're kind of ruining the vibe
here man when i when i reach out to touch his face do i feel it feels like someone else's hand
is touching his face yep jack it's me oh but that feels right to you well i don't know what we can
do did you all try looking around are we walking right now are we like floating we're floating up
we're going to heaven it's just a matter of time when jack says that though ever it's like hey i
didn't i didn't try that and he puts his arm behind him and tries to get momentum in one
direction or another see if he can move through the air i feel so graceful i've never felt this
graceful not for not for 50 years at least seemingly out of nowhere the three of you are
sitting on the ground above you is pure darkness the same darkness that you've seen above you this
entire time and beneath you the ground is made of pure light well it would appear we've made it
holy fuck sack
yeah i thought there'd be more clouds and harps do you think jesus is up here jesus
jesus jesus you here jesus me every jesus you come out now jesus jesus
and as professor horace green opens and closes the jaw of the decapitated head
of preacher sheriff dr bobby custard as he's jeff dunham's jesus
that's right that's right that's what i think of you professor horace green
the biggest insult i can think of you belong in the gutter
the eyes of preacher sheriff dr decapitated head bobby custard open and then the camera pans down
into the bright pure light and as the camera pans down into this bright white light it begins
traveling through this technicolor cylinder and on the other side goes up into the bedroom
of silas and mary cole moves directly up to the face of judge ephraim
courtland uh well silas that was a hell of a lot easier than i thought it was gonna be
oh fuck you holy shit chanting stops the technicolor swirl on the floor dissipates
and silas pushes the bed back over into its horizontal position and he rushes
to judge ephraim courtland and throws his arms around the back of his neck
judge ephraim courtland places his lips right on silas's mouth and a deep deep kiss
holy shit and silas cole pulls back and says i love you mary
what the fuck back i love you too silas oh my god so i can never trust any of you again
like in a zack game
i was like okay i'll just get them in here i'll probably have to fight them into the portal
damn it nope
so
my poor little darling
around my poor little darling all around my poor little darling i'm afraid they'll get my darling
and you hear them wolves howling all around my poor little darling all around my poor little
darling howdy y'all zach here i'm zach we hope you enjoyed this arc we certainly had a blast
playing it a few programming notes since i can't exactly ask wolf to apologize on my behalf this
episode took quite a bit longer than usual to publish that's my bad i'm still getting used to
working full time on another continent i just couldn't get it all done last week i have i have
so much love for this project and i end up pouring more time into it than i have to make this thing
i'm absurdly proud of uh so the next episode episode 96 will come out next friday october 2nd
uh for those of you blessed generous demented folks in the patreon i am working feverishly
to put up the audio for both luke's homebrew delta green one shot as well as our delightfully silly
game of roll for shoes set in a very goofy outer space if you've enjoyed this show so far i would
really love it if you could take a minute to leave a review on apple podcasts follow us on
twitter and instagram or i don't know maybe go and make a post on reddit recommending our lunacy
or something like that i don't know maybe those are just a few nice things that would uh oh boy
howdy it would just make me feel real good now from the bottom of my black oozy squamous heart
thank you for listening we love y'all
hot dog
so
drown
oh