Hey y'all, just in case y'all forgot, it is indeed 26 years ago, and for some reason,
my voice can transmit to the past, from the present, and speaking of the present, y'all
know I am here to bestow my vocal gifts upon all of y'all, no matter the when.
Live from 694.2 PTBP, time traveling dogs named Wolf can be scary, but what is not scary
is howling with Wolf, a segment I am definitely not forced to do against my will by my amorphous
producer who may or may not possess ownership over my soul.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from At Perfect Us Nemo, who tweeted about the show
and tagged at Pretending Pod.
They wanted to hear your boy Wolf vocalize the frustrations of the BBEG in their own
campaign.
They write, I am the ancient, I am the land, I was vain, and due to my hubris, I lost my
beloved.
When I let outsiders into my own home, I was met with trickery and recklessness, going
through my domain like a plague, destroying everything that was dear to me.
Let them rally the creatures in the valley, let them storm my castle, all they will achieve
is a long and painful prelude to an eternal march.
And I shall wait as long as it is necessary, for nothing is gone forever.
I will reclaim what is rightfully mine.
Well that was certainly very fun and light hearted and not at all super fucked up dark
and weird.
Thanks for writing in some very normal sounding stuff for your dumpster daddy to deliver.
Remember if you want to write up something for your wolf to have, tag at Pretending Pod
on Instagram or Twitter, you can tag pretending to be people on Facebook, although y'all know
how we feel.
Fuck the zuck.
Or write a 5 star review on iTunes and email us at pretendingpod at gmail dot com.
Of course you can also support the show financially over on patreon dot com slash pretending pod.
Five dollars a month instantly unlocks access to 9 exclusive bonus episodes.
The most recent one is a real fucking treat.
Ross Payton from Role Playing Public Radio came on to run the PTBP boys through some
Dennis Detwiller's classic Delta Green scenario, Night Floors.
This one comes in around 2 hours and 45 minutes and it is fully edited with Justin's soundtrack
and everything.
Also the very first Den of Sin livestream for those backers at the $15 level on patreon
is happening this upcoming Tuesday, that's February the 25th at 7pm central time.
Zach is gonna run the crew through the first scenario ever written for Call of Cthulhu,
The Haunting.
It's gonna be wet and wild and sp-p-p-p-p-p-pooky y'all.
Keep your eyes peeled for ooze and your ears tuned into the news.
Last time we met our new friends in the meeting room of calm comfy campgrounds and followed
along as they checked in for the weekend.
Walter Grimes a totally normal 16 year old boy and his father Alan are in cottage number
3.
Bradley Cooper a surreptitious go getter is in cottage number 5.
Charles Digby a plain but curious creep is in cottage number 7 and Roger Fairfield the
uptight newlywed is in cottage number 9 with his bohemian bride taking us back into the
corner free meeting room for orientation.
about edging it's dream girl with pretty sexual
stormy do you have any guns i need to shoot my friend he would definitely drive over here
with his pistol if i was like hey i need to shoot luke i love your dad and the thing is
you he would act like if you asked him to he would probably kill me oh i don't know
about that now he'd make me do my own dirty business yeah he would he would provide all
the materials son i don't want you to do this but uh the man who passes the judgment ought
to pull the trigger that's a good impression of your dad what was that fucking dude before
we start i went and saw the gentleman oh yeah how was that fantastic oh so dying i love
it was fucking good cool that makes me really excited who's the director is uh guy richie
guy richie am i here no i've been doing that i'm sorry dude it was leaving the theater
my parents were like yeah we thought it was going to be a stupid action movie and it was
but we loved it oh hell yeah that sounds right in my eyes i'm totally fan-fucking-tastic
a good guy richie it was yeah it was without some stinkers yeah yeah well it was not a
sneaker it was like like snatch i never saw snatch what that's good yeah is it unlimited
breath sticks what snatch is unlimited back six for sure it's my favorite rotten tomatoes
anyway that's all i have to say all right so this man who just walked into the circular
meeting room is wearing a white dress shirt gray slacks and black shoes there are six
chairs and a half circle all facing a single chair that this man stands in front of as
he introduces himself hello there folks my name is james and i am the executive director
here at calm comfy campground i need everyone to roll a constitution check what pass fail
pass solid fail okay so justin charles digby and thomas bradley cooper would both realize
that that's your name that this room is sort of tilted as you're walking to your seats
you feel an uneasiness in your balance as this room is tilted a bit toward the chair
that is alone on the other side and you all sit down in this half circle and he sits down
with you i pull the chair out for angela even though there's nothing that she's scooting
up to i just kind of stand behind and pull it out let her sit and push it under thank
you so much for really like seeing me in that moment and acknowledging that i'm here of
course i want to start by introducing myself and telling you a little bit about this place
we obviously as you know uh specialize in taking people who need to focus on something
and get that focus either a little bit more accurate or there at all some people need
to be forced all the way in so uh we're just here to help you achieve whatever desires
you may be heading toward we can help you with that goal and i just think the group
session is the best way to start any of these sort of weekend events so if everyone could
go around and introduce themselves i think that would be absolutely fantastic well i
am angela fairfield and i'm here with my husband raj hey hey there hey there folks and we're
here to really focus on like moving forward in our marriage and making this thing last
and and really like we both care so much about each other that i think that we're going to
be able to do it right raj we're certainly gonna gonna try of course i'll do i'm open
and uh i'm willing and was that walter clapping walter claps james looks around the room at
the others okay well uh let's uh jump in here uh i like to play two truths and a lie to
get things started so basically how this works is we'll go around the half circle here and
everyone will say three statements two of which are true and one of which is a lie and
after you say the three statements we'll each go around and ask a question about the three
statements to try to determine which one the lie is right so we'll ask a question you'll
have to answer it and then we can all kind of gauge who each other are and how we react
to each other i've got a question shoot psychologically what is the point of this game oh it's just
to help with these group sessions moving along we really want there to be an air of openness
and vulnerability and so we think the best way to do that is to have you all know each
other why lie in the background i ask alan what is openness it's just a willingness to
connect with others i believe who the fuck is alan thank you alan is the older man who
is the tall lead man wearing the charcoal suit who is there with the 16 year old walter
when he notices that they're there together i give you guys both like a strange look i
am still just looking at my feet taking this in i lean to the council it was like a batman
situation as his ward puts yeah i think it's definitely a batman type situation uh they
can probably explain to you their father-son dynamic more than i could but let's go ahead
and start with uh charles digby down there you got two treats in the life for me sir
yeah i got a couple for you fire away i blackmailed the mayor of the city i have an overweight
cat named rolo
she's working on it she was you guys stopped i sold one of my kidneys to buy my new car
oh those are some spicy ones all right let's go around the circle here and ask some questions
let's start with you bradley why'd you sell your kidney i mean what kind of car
it's a uh a new mobile lie that's the lie i agree did you show us your belly i would
like to ask openness i would like to show us go with his line of questioning and ask
to see the renal scar i don't feel comfortable enough with you guys to to do that i look
at uh what's your character's name bradley cooper that's not a famous person's name yeah
i look at bradley and i go i agree with your thought it is a lie thanks charles how much
is uh kidney going for these days it's about 20 000 or so did the car cost all of that
money or did you have some left over i had some left over what'd you spend it on got
a new camera what was your first lie my first lie that you ever told the first lie that
no the first lie of the three that you read you uh you blackmailed a mayor what was that
about i had some stuff on them what did you have on the mayor dad i can handle this oh
i'm part of the group as well and i would like to contribute so what what did you have
on the mayor there alan let the kids be i accept the line of questioning i'm not allowed
i'm not allowed to discuss it that's part of the blackmail deal did you get money for
it or was it some other yes you got money for it for blackmailing the mayor yes i do
want to reiterate that this is two truths and a lie both of these seem like lies but
one of them isn't one of them's fake he got money from either blackmailing the mayor or
selling his kidney that's how i pulled up here in a new mobile i but he wouldn't need
money twice no one needs no one needs more money so i i reached my things i reached my
hand out and poke him in like the side walter i like where where a kidney scar would be
walter you can't just poke people i i also go in and start it is part of this is part
of the game i have to win the second thing he said let's go ahead and try to not touch
each other during this game if that's okay with i'm pretty uncomfortable with what's
happening here what was the second thing he said hey do i feel a scar through my can i
roll that can i roll like search or something yeah roll search no roll surgery tied i got
30 in surgery that's a 10 oh my god okay you go ahead and roll a d10 for damage three
okay and so if you can i get a pencil please as you reach in uh before charles can pull
away charles does he feel a surgery scar there he does not oh i believe that that is the
lie if he touched him and there's no scar if there's no scar i bet that's the lie i
agree calm down i get like really fucking uncomfortable and i'm like kind of like hugging
myself a little bit like looking down at the ground and i'm like what was the second thing
he said i have an overweight cat named rolo why don't you put it on a diet or something
she's trying i feel like that is the truth all right let's go ahead and uh i think everyone
is made vocal their choices there hold on buddy so what'd you get from the mayor i'm
not allowed to say i want to human that okay roll human for me you said money though didn't
i thought he said money oh i did say money i successfully roll human and i say wait a
minute earlier you said it was money oh fuck how much money what was the secret
i i can't say all right i think he's repeated that a couple times so let's go ahead and get
you to come clean here which one was the line what were the truths the truths were i did in fact
as you guessed blackmail the mayor i also have an overweight cat one might say morbidly obese cat
named rolo after her favorite candy that might have something to do with it yeah what do you
say once she lost weight she has she hasn't lost weight all right well i think we all got to know
each other pretty well there through that little exercise for charles yeah we know he's a fucking
liar well that's part of the game there bradley i know this all right well you're up next so
okay well my name is bradley cooper i'm a father my my friends recommended i come here
and uh i'm also a widower what's your son's name i don't have a son what's your daughter's name
jessica how old is jessica seven which friend suggested that you come here a few of them they
could you name well names steve and and this this is the lie and
no they all think i have problems what are these uh problems that you're here for they think i'm
not invested enough in my personal life like your daughter who oh yeah jessica
this is the life yeah no um she's great she's great what school does your daughter go to
i i swear this isn't the lie i mean what do i care if you know i'm lying or not but
i've been assured it's a very good school is it a high school or elementary school she's
seven so what grade is she in i think that's first nope
are you wait are you sure that would be first or second grade
nope nope no sir uh so i was seven in the second grade no big deal
okay bradley how did uh if it's true how'd you lose your your wife cancer sorry sorry to hear
that if it's true what kind of cancer did she have bone what is that called
this is just the thomas test
uh i also don't know osteo something i think it's just called bone cancer
there's gotta be a technical term for it bone cancer names learn a name osteogenic sarcoma
i called osteo or osteosarcoma i went to nursing school for a year i know things she
it's an osteocarcoma sarcoma sarcoma she had an osteosarcoma that spread to her lungs and kidneys
and also her other bones and her brain did it make you sad yeah as much as anything i
cannot determine which one is the lie yeah i don't know what the lie is either what do you
think roge i uh it sounded to me like the friend's names were made up i'm gonna say the his friends
didn't tell him to come here i'll go with him steve and bill you think those are i think that
stevenville are names that you might have just thought of so i agree that is the lie i'm gonna
say it's the friends doesn't seem like a guy that uh has a lot of caring friends in his life
and everyone laughs at you holy shit
thanks for coming to calm comfy campgrounds you fucking idiot you can you can tell that bradley
is really unaffected all right so bradley if you want to go ahead and tell us which one of
those was the lie my wife didn't die we just got divorced i'm sorry to hear that she did not die
yeah me too i take back my sorrys that's for sure but yeah i'm sorry i said you didn't have
any friends i'm sure you have many stevenville charles actually feels the man too charles like
kind of like is looking inward and he's like fuck because he's like this is my job to like
and he fucking failed he fucking failed at it roll sanity now i'm just kidding here we go you feel
helpless roll sanity uh yeah no i'll i'll go for i'll go next yeah uh i got three right here my
favorite food is steak my favorite steak is a ribeye and my favorite show is the beverly
hillbillies i feel that i cannot participate in this because i know the answer hey kid what's
the answer i feel that i look at my dad can i tell what the answer is i i think for the
purpose of the game you better yeah i i don't think maybe you should participate in the
questioning on this one but i look down at my feet and stand motionless who's your favorite
character on the beverly hillbillies milburn driesdale he's a good businessman and he's just
trying to keep the money in his bank what does steak taste like steak oh i like the meaty
just ripping something apart questioning what's uh what what's that's a ribeye part from from
other steaks why is it so special to you i love the fat i like how fat it is uh nothing i like
more than just the fat on a steak do you uh know the theme song to beverly hillbillies flanston
no uh i i do i do i do just let me get there black gold oil that is i lean over to and yeah
i lean over to angela that's how you figure it out pretty quick
okay you're right okay it's not my favorite show i've seen it a couple times i i like
that milburn driesdale but i i just couldn't think of anything else on the spot you got me
okay well i guess that was pretty short wind damn got it oh my god walter looks up and says
black gold oil that is uh walter if you want to go next following your father there this is going
to be very difficult for me because i do not like to lie but i will do it for the sake of community
i don't own a bed i had a total hip replacement last year and i have only owned one pair of shoes
as an adult i want to look tennis yeah i look at the shoes what do them shoes look like what
do they look like they are pristine white new balances okay i'm pretty sure i know the lie
but just to be sure i want to kick them in the hip not like hard i want to like knock them over
with my foot what i just want to see if he can stand or if his hip got replaced bradley that is
not the kind of behavior that we want to do here well but you're reacting to that as what was the
result of my behavior is he on the ground as bradley's foot comes up to my hip i grab it that'll
be a strength yeah let's see hold on strength or can i use martial arts you can use martial arts
either way i got martial arts i got an 85 unarmed combat don't roll don't roll worse than me
i got a one so fucking kill him he shatters your hip no it's contested whether or not it was
you destroy this child what do you want to do oh i just want to kind of like push him with my foot
and see if he can stand up i want to test his hip all right as his foot comes into me i try to
grab it but his foot is moving too fast he hits me in the hip and pushes me over like three inches
but then i immediately stand back up completely straight roger jumps out of his chair hey whoa
yeah that's not the kind of behavior that we want to like do in these group sessions like i said
about touching people earlier it's mostly a physical thing that i'm talking about right now
so if we want to not do that from here on moving forward otherwise i'm gonna have to
as soon as this happens i i stand straight and look down in my shoes are you all right walter
i am fine bradley is telling me that i am lying he's like in a practiced kung fu stance he's kind
of bouncing on the heels of his feet but he sits down when you sit back down walter alan kind of
pats you on the leg and he's like you did a great job just then my father has told me three strikes
and you're out that is one strike but i don't hold it against you cool
tell me how i'm lying if you don't own a bed let's say that that's the truth
where do you sleep i don't typically lay down usually i tend to sleep standing where are you
a vampire yeah what are you a vampire angel no i he's funny i can't consume blood so no i'm
not a vampire okay i want to get this over with i feel uncomfortable telling a lie because it's
against what i believe in what do you believe in well many things but that's not the point of this
exercise to get to know one another right yeah but that's it what's at your core kid you would
have to ask my father that i did not i've not asked that question but i i think that is beside
the point of this exercise please tell me how i'm lying you should walk across the room for us
i walk across the room can i see if he's favoring one hit versus the other yeah uh we already tested
i i walk across the room perfectly normal oh roger is just gonna point at your shoes i i think it's
the shoes guys they don't look like he's had them all his life yeah i'm gonna go with the shoes
that's wild otherwise same i look at my father am i allowed to tell the truth now go ahead i
have not had a hip replacement i have the hips oh i forgot about the hip god damn it that was
obviously the lie i have the hips that i was made with all right and let's uh let's move on to who
we got next here uh yeah i'll go uh hi i'm roger hello roger hi roger i'm a champion flautist
i have won competitions with my fluting i am a member of the international knot tying guild
and what's a good lie oh no no babe babe i hate chocolate oh he does i have determined that you
like chocolate oh would you like a twix bar got it in one and i i stretched my hand out towards
him but i have nothing in my hand i'm just beating him
would you like a twix bar yeah if you got oh dang i have determined i am the winner i have
he is lying about chocolate roger not the point but i think we got to know you through that
exercise there uh what is your favorite not my father has told me to ask questions like this
i mean a winsor and a tie is my favorite uh if you're doing boats a healthy slip is good
it depends on the situation i have learned to tie ties and winsor is a great knot okay so i've uh
i've traveled to four different continents i've never gotten the hiccups and that is one time
determined to be the lie you don't even have to say the third one she has to though that's the
continue i am sorry it's okay this is the coolest one actually uh one time i smoked a joint with a
senator which senator did you smoke a joint with from any kind of cultural acceptance on that so
that's a really radical and like scandalous thing to say maybe 26 years in the future that'll be
more where did you smoke a joint with bernie sanders it was actually bobby bird and we were
at a charity function and he for what back what were you raising political campaign you have had
the hiccups that is what i have determined what are the hiccups like uh they're the worst oh my
god that is the lie gotcha wait do you like hiccups what's going on you said you've never had
oh my god wait really you totally got me you totally got me i didn't even god yes no i've
been to south america europe asia and antarctica and one time i smoked a joint with bobby bird
robert bird she she did she did have you ever smoked a joint no thankfully i met her after
that that was my past my wild and crazy past that he was dating me during do you have any
weed with you no she looks really like wide-eyed at james and uh roger looks at her do do you no
can i roll human
that's an 11 a crit pass yeah she's got weed on her i look at roger i go you may not know your
wife as well as you think that you do she does your battery time
i look down at my feet that kind of language is not why we came here we came here to have
good social interactions with people and try to become better people and i don't understand why
you sir i've taken every chance to step out of line you want to do something about it big man
oh you were looking at this old old lean man who's just like come on i'm gonna have a smoke
and he just gets up and walks out of the room i kind of follow him a little bit
yeah i kind of like see him out of the circle and then sit back down oh my god you big man him
you put your body on him i put my body at him but well that is horrible you're a bad person
all right i said well i do sit back down and i kind of i place a weird awkward like paternal
hand on uh luke's shoulder my name is walter
couldn't have been more perfect it was i said the world's full of weak men but you're a bright boy
i do not acknowledge the touch i'm still looking at my feet i do not acknowledge the touch episode
title so again bradley we're gonna want to steer clear of that kind of intimidation
and physical activity during our group sessions and the whole weekend here sorry i've been i'm
really tense that's why i'm trying to i whisper to angela and we're gonna steer clear of him
no joke i look up at raj and angela duly noted me too and look back down on my feet
so the four of you you're being led around the property of calm comfy campground by
james who just led the group session with all of you and he's pointing around to different places
on the island so these are going to be your cottages right and our bellboy told you which
ones that you're going to and uh he's got your your accoutrement and everything already at your
cottages ready for after the tour you can head back there but you'll see we've got some beautiful
sights around here and he points up as the sun is going down and he's like look at that sunset and
you just see the sun is going down behind these mountains off in the distance and on this side of
that sunset is just trees for as far as you can see up until this lake hold on hold on i'm sorry
i've got to take this and uh bradley waters off from the group on his cell phone that'll happen
so i i don't know if he's gonna get very good service out here but can i try a role that lets
me uh eavesdrop on his side of the conversation but from the group like i'm just gonna stop paying
attention to james and try and hear what he's saying on his side of his phone yeah for sure
roll uh search active perception i pass a three on a 60 okay fantastic i told you it needs to be
off white not cream not white not whatever the fuck kind of gray you thought this would be it
needs to be off white okay off white cool flowers of all different shades and shapes you know have
been uh given to us here and we've got you know all these uh trees on the island really gives for
some good oxygen around these parts it's quite nice you can smell that smell and uh we got this
beautiful lake here and you look out over lake calm and it is black it is a completely dark water
lake is that a thing it is an ominous uh short fiction yeah
and he's leading you to the two-story boat house on the north side of the island before we head to
the boat house i grab a rock look at my father this is how chuck a rock at him no uh this is
how you taught me and i skip a rock and it skips like 18 times alan just stands there with his eyes
wide and kind of looks at everyone it was like the boy knows how to throw a rock that was nice
distance good work that's what it's what alan has taught me you can see in the background that
that uh bradley has like got his phone down at his shoulder and he's looking at you thank you
for teaching me that father yes of course he's a very skilled young man i tend to think so just
because you tell me that i am you're a very good boy okay so let's go on and uh move on up to the
next site you'll see here i've shown you all the different cottages and how to get to each of your
individual places for the weekend but uh heading down here is the boat house and we've got our
boat man down here mr russell and he's a good guy i'll get you to meet him and he'll give you the
rundown on how to use these canoes if you want to take a little solace time out on the water and he
leads you down to this long what is a bridge on a dock called doc bridge on a dock like a bridge to
a dock yeah uh is that a wharf wharf no that's like the whole thing just the like a dock yeah
like the walkway leading up to the gangway just yeah it's pretty long it's like 20 yards like
yeah that's just the wood planks ramp like this is great right here so we've just got you're the
one who didn't do his research fucking google fucking look at what's the bridge to i think
it's called a ridge yeah you have the worst one what do you call the bridge to a dog i think it's
called a uh this is a walkway i think it's called a little i don't think it's anything weird it's
just it's a walkway it's called little lakey walk floating walkway will do okay yeah there we go
did you say lakey walk a little lakey walk so you guys are walking down this is a big lakey
walk the big lakey walk the big long walk and this is a handsome lakey walk you got here this
is this sure is one floaty lakey walk i'm looking down on my feet as i walk and i'm like this is a
great lakey walk we like to guess this is new we like to give jack his uh his his amount of space
that you know he requires he's been here a long time and i'm sorry is his name jack russell yeah
that's his name jack russell like the dog bouncy dog that's hilarious that's actually
and you walk up to this boat house which is a like uh it's a two-story apartment and underneath
there are pillars coming down and there are spots for canoes that are floating in the water
underneath the second story apartment are there any other boats here or is it just the canoes
just six canoes and as you walk you see that a man is walking down from the apartments and
i'm in the wrong google doc you sure you're not still on the floating walkway
you mean the little lakey walk and so from the little long big wakey walk
wakey walk because you're awake and you're walking uh you see jack russell who's the boat man who's
walking down some stairs on the side of the apartment down to greet you he's a short
stout man in his later years and as you approach you see that he's got a thick white beard that
makes his round face look even rounder the bags under his eyes are large and fluffy and he's
wearing a dark fluffy fluffy okay the thick luxurious fur you started to say puffy and then
you changed to fluffy you just really want to take a nap on these bags he's wearing a dark navy beanie
and a wool plaid shirt underneath olive corduroy overalls i'm thinking about the guy that plays
trumpet in neutral milk hotel well i'm always thinking about the guy who plays trumpet in
neutral milk hotel uh yeah so everyone this is jack russell the boat man and he'll be taking
care of all your canoe needs i'm gonna head on back so after you wrap up here and get all your
information you can go back onto your cottages or feel free to roam the grounds and he takes off
back down the large flaky flock and walk a flock of lake and he walks back and he's gone roger
holds out a hand to jack jack i'm roger i'm curious what kind of not to use around here
honestly for uh for my ties you know i go with the fucking shit yeah i was doing you doing you
oh fuck oh i thought you were i was doing i thought you were doing jebediah from the
plus what kind of uh knots are using here on the stock uh i assume a clove hitch you
got anything uh special up your sleeve hey you know it's mostly clove hitch you know it's uh
do it again for ties you know i got windsor man after my heart i see and yeah so everyone here
you know come down come close you know get around here we got six canoes right and so there's enough
for everyone to take them out whenever you need them you're gonna want to go ahead and grab a life
jacket there's life jackets right over here and he points at a bin it's got a bunch of life jackets
in it you're all seemingly adults he looks at you walter he's like except for you how old are you
what is the number that you need to hear all right it seems smart enough so all of you will
be required to take out life jackets in the canoes with you and you head on out but you don't have to
wear them except for i'm guessing you if you're under 18 you might want to have that on for the
galatee reasons should i put two of them on you can put two of them on if you want but it'll be
safer if you just have one duly noted all right so you're never gonna go out without them and
you're never gonna go out by yourself in a canoe if you go out by yourself in a canoe you're gonna
have a bad time we always say stick to two in a canoe right so you gotta have two people in the
canoe what do we gotta have in a canoe to make it work that's right the canoe good job everyone
thank you for paying attention honestly this is great so many groups get into in talking and
doing different voices it's very obnoxious what do you mean i don't even know why i brought it up
that's on me that's my bad everyone i'm so sorry why did i even invite that into the realm of
possibility so that's why we always stick to two in a canoe so stuff like that doesn't happen all
right now these waters these waters out here you look at them they're very calm right but
that's tricky isn't it it is it no not so much it's very easy to can do around this lake
however some people get a big head right i'm guessing you just looking at everything about you
you're probably going to get a bit cocky out there and there's nothing that the water takes
as such a dis to its face i say dis all the time it's one of my favorite words i mean it's
perfectly acceptable 26 years ago hey we're living in the past mate i'm living in the future i mean
hypothetically and so the water right it's it's mean
right it's me but it's yeah i'm scared it's super fucking calm right but you know it can be mean
at times right because the water is the most powerful thing that exists on this realm outside
of all and he looks up into the sky and the sun has gone down now so you've got just a beautiful
sight of the countless stars up in the sky except for those right mate right the endlessness of
space isn't it if you get out there there's nothing more powerful sometimes i feel like
maybe i'm just floating and all of this is some sort of mental reaction to everything
that i'm having as i'm just losing oxygen i'm i'm sorry jack russell have you been to space
no no but sometimes i look up there and i wonder if maybe i'm not down here you know you ever get
that yes i would also posit that water would still be powerful up there in fact maybe more
so you could use it to stay alive or to push off of something if you needed to you could
shoot it out of a hose or when you were talking about this clouds are also water so technically
in the sky there is water as well so i think that just adds to what you are talking about you guys
are all really validating me at this time and i appreciate it you know it's not too many times
that we get people who are not so raw and ready at the beginning of the weekend you know some
people are a bit meft in the head so it's nice that you guys are all taking a group mentality
to try to validate each other's existences and thoughts and i really appreciate that so does
everyone have well it's just shit we are doing each other i do in the same voice oh i want brad
lincoln i'm gay and i want your job um honestly i think we're all just uh i think we feel a little
protective of you because of the the thick and fluffy patch of hair underneath your eyes it's
pretty adorable he rubs it and he's like yeah it's been on my face a long time in there is it
now i grew it over the summer it's nice though to have a bit of protection from all this wind
and you know if you happen to get into water it's nice to have it and you know not you just sort of
feel are you laughing at me this is like a if snl try to do colin farrell i am colin farrell
and i'm bradley cooper and maybe in 26 years those names will be famous but not today no
it's a fucking fairy tale here though but also isn't your name jack russell yeah my name is jack
russell what's happening hey i think we're just terrible hey jack if we do take a boat out is
there any place you recommend maybe a nice cove somewhere or something yeah you'll find no coves
around this area right so it's just circles on circles so we got a circular island with a
circular lake right around it engulfing it eating it alive from the inside you're gonna find just
roundness at all the points around i'm so sorry jack wouldn't be eating it alive from the outside
of the you know what you're right it is it's an external force this water is right pushing against
just over and over repeatedly just thrusting thrusting thrusting there's water at the bottom
of the ocean oh does anyone have any questions uh are these our boats like uh stand down one
so we got is it but specifically like is my boat that one no or or take out any of them that you
want anyone that's left here you can take out right and so to answer your question there sir
young sprightly man it's gonna be right over there and he points to this spot that the shoreline has
clearly even from this distance you can tell canoes have like entered this shoreline and left
a bunch of divots up there and he's like right there that's a good trail that's the best trail
on the property so like a cross yeah across the water yeah got it yeah there's no trails on this
side except for the walkways you know from the cottages back up to big house charles digby takes
this time to pull out a little notepad that he always keeps with him to take notes and looking
at the like creepy almost obsidian like water he starts like jotting down notes for ideas i love it
there you go i'm into it yeah thanks for saying it you're welcome i think it's a good character
choice for you yeah it might have something to do with something gotta keep an eye on this one
he writes shit down i approach the water and i scoop a handful of water up and then i put my
hand in my back pocket i just see his pocket get wet i'm noticing the rings of the water the ripple
effect yeah kid i'm not paying attention i'm looking back down on my feet again kid are you
any good with computers no reaction sometimes he just doesn't react is he good at computers hey
he's fine with computers what about you sir are you a computer man me bradley cooper yeah what
do you do i i manage a gas station wow interesting yeah what's that like as you can imagine it's
hard an oil man and i look back down indirectly i suppose yeah petroleum byproducts he's a bit of
a middleman do not degrade this man father i do think of myself as uh more of a salesman than
anything okay so i guess we should head out is there anything else jack that's pretty much it
unless anyone has any more questions about the water the canoes or how to get from here to there
on this cold water but just remember what do we remember always have a life jacket for each
person in the canoe two canoes or something two canoes for each person two canoes for each person
that's right i don't i don't think that was no that's what he said like a chariot trick horse
racer one can one foot in each and i think it was uh one canoe 23 skidoo you can split your
pants but it's it's a good time can you remind us what it was again yeah so we always say
i looked at my computer and it says two truths and a lie
that's why we always stick to
what hold on what did i roll 50 to a canoe
that's why we always say 50 to a canoe all right two in a canoe anyone have any more questions are
we done here if uh somebody hypothetically wanted to get out on the lake and they were alone would
you accompany them how does that yeah yeah if you ever want to go out there by yourself and have a
bit of quiet i got these and he points up at the wall and there's some like noise canceling like
gear that you would wear if you were doing construction or something like that if you
ever want to have a bit of peace and quiet you know i'll just put that in and read if that'll
be all then i think your name really i started i think maybe we should leave where your next
campground members the beatings we're here for fun and relaxing non-spooky weekend it's 56 years ago
that's right can we take a picture of rb road
can we do that what's on the other side of the lake oh just woods mate just woods and woods
it's some nice trails there if you got some some time are there any uh fish in this lake oh i
thought you're gonna say on the trails and no there aren't but there are my question is could
i have never been fishing before but i've heard about it is it possible to go fishing in this
lake unfortunately for you there so walter you're not gonna find any fish in this lake well that's
well that's fine why are there no fish in this lake yeah roger's looking puzzled too
no no fish in the lake they stocked all these lakes back in the day when they first dammed
them up as long as i've been here there's been no fishes in this lake is this a man-made lake
yeah it's a man-made lake what do you have a deal with that no then i guess we don't have a problem
what holy shit that was a bit strong it's jack sparrow hiding out
and you're poking the bear i could go a bit of a problem that's the day you almost caught jack
russell
you
this
i think