hello one hello all hello y'all it's your best friend with the trash eating problem
wolf the dog it is december 6th and the time is one o'clock y'all mmm sounds like it's
about garbage bin o'clock for your wolfy boy speaking of trash earlier i took my dog wolf
the dog to go find him something to fill his big old belly up with but upon venturing
outside the sky suddenly darkened all around us for a little bit y'all ever seen an eclipse
it was uh like that but different it was real spooky y'all wolf nearly shit his big ass
britches which wolf did that you ask i'll let y'all figure that one out when i came
back down to the studio i found a note attached with a thumb tacked to the inside of my door
it is emblazoned with a solid green triangle and says for wolf at the top i guess it's
this week's howlin with wolf it comes from user chuckling boy over on the subreddit
he's an android user but logged on to itunes on his computer to leave a review this boy
sure knows how to make old wolfy blush chuckling boy writes the cowboy years introduced a turn
of phrase for dealing with a shitstorm we called it a night at the opera you boys have
taken care of few off screen but damned if your debut isn't like the metzone debut fost
somewhat fitting isn't that and remember the mission is over when the world ends follow
you out there listening be sure to stop by the subreddit we are starting to see
more discussion around the greater delta green cannon as well as game running tips and general
show stuff see y'all there wolf bless you chuckling boy and i will take you in my arms and hold you
right where you belong till the day my life is through this i promise you if you want to write
a message for your wolf to read on air tag us on instagram or twitter pretending pod or write a
five star review on apple podcasts and email us at pretendingpod at gmail.com and the murderer of
pretending to be people wanted me to reiterate here that they are taking questions for a third
q a episode so if you have any questions for any of the children who make that show tag at
pretending pod on twitter or instagram there's also a post in the subreddit where you can comment
your questions there's some good ones already in there or go all out record audio of you asking
your question and send that so they can use it in the episode same as the second q a episode this
one will be for our honorary police officers over on patreon who breathe green life into this show's
lungs five bucks a month at a time the fiscal lifeguards who hold that specific title currently
have instant access to six exclusive bonus episodes baby now if you want a question answered
but you can't splurge on this here patreon decadence fear not the pt bp crew will answer
some of the questions they don't get to in the q a session right there on the interwebs maybe
your question will be one of them or maybe fuck your questions fuck a whole lot of people but
especially mark zuckerberg it's time for the news a tall gaunt humanoid figure
where an old version of himself just stood none of that made a lick of sense to me but
that doesn't mean i'm not hungry filling me up always is kudzu with no back
bowling
so
i just want to hit it it's pretty cool though it's a very fun noise can i just like point at
you and have you hit that yeah very dramatic it's like the law and order svu thing
not really oh that kind of was yeah yeah that's pretty good mic stands
mic stand solo i could be in ozark mountain deer devil's playing this get 30 seconds of room noise
la la la la the room you're tearing me apart lisa the three of you wake up
your bodies are fully in shock your ears are ringing your stomach feels full and content
but also just like wretched at the same time somehow it's dark it's cold and it smells
there's some sort of what is that it's it's like savory it's in the air there's a sweetness to it
and your eyes begin to adjust you see there's a pool of blood on the floor
and next to it is a coffin on the ground in this mausoleum you look at each other
blood splatter has speckled each of you john kevin lee pettymore in all black tactical gear
keith vigna and his brightly colored polo and boat shoes clark bishop in an old contention pd
uniform currently holding a thick black cloak as the shock begins to wear off you feel a searing
pain on your chest on your back on the bottom of your left foot and inside your dominant palm
you remember everything that has happened well obviously not these last like seven episodes but
everything before that you remember but you wake up in this spot that you've woken up in before
so you mean we remember um the fight and everything yes we remember i remember being
planet juggernaut you do uh i am a little disappointed to be a man again
like with his first actions as not a giant robot ball like the the just like sheer mundane humanness
of his own movements sends an existential depression through john lee pettymore
at while at the same time like eliciting a comforting nostalgia but he's like
ah fuck that was that was pretty cool what the fuck is going on are you
are you do you remember the last thing i remember is riding off on planet juggernaut
yeah that's what we i wasn't imagining that the last thing i remember is being planet juggernaut
you were you were planet juggernaut yeah and you were there and you were there what are we doing
back and is that crawfish i smell crawfish that smells great but i'm full you're all unnaturally
at full hit points and willpower your sanity and your luck will start where they were the last time
you woke up in this tomb and because of everything you've seen i'll give you each 2d 20 in your
unnatural skill you can roll on your unnatural skill to gain insight but if you fail the role
you'll lose 1d6 sanity you'll still gain the insight sure oh we're still getting the insight
oh wow cool but you're all at such low sanity right now that losing 1d6 is a pretty hefty toll
can we have our character sheets you can have your character sheets now so i'm gonna hand you
i didn't have time to do them up but i'm gonna hand you blank character sheets and i have pictures
of what your character sheets look like at this point in time nice okay so we're gonna take a
quick break we'll be right back are you holding our old ones hostage yes okay
the only Joe i know is Joe mama
he he he hey it's me it's clark bishop shout out to Jane Terry fan of the podcast big shout out
number uno fan that that's just that's Joe's mama who's Joe oh shit we just doxed her
and you Joe can you read the description of the new vape juice that you got
yeah i can it's called mystic magic it says let the sorcerer tell you let the sorcerer tell
your future with the paranormal vapor that tastes like ripe mangoes sweet tangerines
and fresh raspberries wow you definitely just picked the one that's like gonna make you the
most ill right like oh this definitely has the most additives chock full of vitamin e
yep i asked for the most haunted one and this is the one they gave me he can also freestyle
rap now a rip rap rippity rap rip rippity do because he you know because he's so ill
yeah this one killed a bunch of 17 year olds they're haunting our vape store
oh dude that would be the worst fucking ghost in the world is just a jeweling teen
who died from a lung illness and now he haunts the goddamn bathroom at the common
goal i just see these wisps of vapor from time to time oh yeah you got one of the jewelers i
i think i've been hearing popcorn long taylor's like yeah i had to i had to move my uh classroom
there was a few ghosts in the in the bathroom across the hall it's just like disaffected size
i'm like that wasn't really those are very very disaffected size thomas you can like hear the
eye roll like okay so i need you guys to roll 2d 20. it's it's not me it's the vaping ghost
vaping ghost speak to us trent are you there i got a 10 and an 18 oh shit okay so you get 38
and you're on natural skill nice damn it i got a 16 and a 14 i got a 5 and 11 i was playing a
juggernaut okay so what's everybody's unnatural skill at now smack dab at 30 38 16 oh wait i got
a 10 and an 18 would i be at 28 then yeah you said 38 yeah 10 and 18 you said 38 you said 38
oh i'm an idiot okay i was like i thought maybe we added 10 to whatever we got or something okay
yeah i'll take that no i'm just stupid so adding adding 10 to whatever we have i've got 26 but
we're not doing that are we we're not okay some of us just did thomas is so good at role-playing
games life is a negotiation zach often okay what else are we doing what else you're doing is
you're currently in this dark mausoleum and you've just recently realized you are here again
clark looks at his watch that has the date on it is it the same day it is indeed december 6th
at 1 p.m zach that's really wrong are you okay i need you all the real sanity
so when i was filling out my sheet remembering seeing
the last sheet you're at at this point yeah i'm one away from my breaking point oh perfect this
will be a one slash 1d4 sanity check so if you succeed you'll lose one sanity if you
fail you'll lose 1d4 i failed god damn it four i got a four also
my current sanity is 16 oof i got a one my breaking point said 28 but i'm now at 23
i don't know if i just didn't i think maybe you just didn't update your breaking point last time
my new sanity is 15 i hit my breaking point my new breaking point is three nine is eight all
right clark bishop we're gonna roll for a phobia this time so you're gonna roll 3d 100 and then
we'll choose which phobia you would like to take and let's go ahead and uh do you want to make this
a secret and have them leave the room if you want yeah let's do that get on out of here boys we're
just gonna start guessing random fears and throwing them at you throughout the campaign
it might become depending on what it is it could be real obvious real quick
all right joe roll d100 for me a 45 45 is going to be herpetophobia which is the fear of reptiles
it's fun that would have worked out well last arc are fish people reptiles yeah i don't know
no uh 50 50 is iatrophobia which is the fear of doctors
uh for story reasons that'd be great for uh role-playing game reasons that'd be awful
and the third one let's see what you roll here a 46 46 i did 45 50 46 oh weird uh
homoclophobia which is the fear of fog fear of fog fog i mean joe would love to take that one
would you let me take that one yeah i don't know if it would ever come up if i mean we'll we'll see
it would be fun when it came up if it came up to be afraid of fog yeah let's make it happen i like
that yeah yeah let's go with fear of fog that's fun all right we'll get the other boys in here
wait am i still do i still think i'm god because that was i think what i got when i broke in the
mausoleum the first time what do you think well i never played it very well so i'll leave it up
to you do you want another shot at it oh another time that to be better at playing it sure uh
i mean i'll give it a shot i'm worried that i wasn't good at it because i never remembered
it we'll see let's yeah let's try it okay yeah i'll try and keep it into both of them all right
cool thinking he's god is so antithetical to the way i like created clark it's really hard to play
him that actually makes sense well that's i part of the whole point of this game right is to have
a character that just delves into madness and darkness i'll try and dig a little deeper for
you babe oh thank you just tap that well tap that dark viscous well and pump it out i dig it
so you guys are all looking at each other in the darkness you see the blood splattered on each
other you're having all these memories flashback and you remember everything that already happened
and you remember being here keith rips his shirt off to see if the same words are still branded
when you rip your shirt off the first thing that you see is the word marvin that was burned into
the flesh of your chest has a strike through it it is completely crossed out looking around at
the other burn marks that you remember from last time tilde is still written inside your dominant
palm it's not crossed out each of you kind of check each other drew is burned into the flesh
on your backs it's not crossed out i was planning on getting one of those anyway so
a drew brand yeah for the boys and maggie is burned into each of your left feet the bottom
of your left foot says maggie and clark as you saw last time and the other two saw as well the
flesh on the bottom of your left foot has been eaten away in the symbol of the circle of knowledge
but her name is not crossed out that is correct what about our injuries sustained like fighting
the robot and things those injuries are not a part of your body do you do you fellas think it
think it all happened did it happen i want to go back i want to go back at the juggernaut we we we
we saw marvin die and now now his name's crossed out oh i mean we're back here we're back we're
back now i don't know i don't know what i don't know what it means i mean to really get to the
bottom of it we'd have to go figure out if he's dead right now or not what if we i think we should
just go take care of this other shit cross brands off our body we lost other people in there is
there somebody is there some way we could we don't have to figure out marvin's there now just
something we did between now and what we remember that we could check on we're at the funeral right
now right yeah there's ari's body right there you see that ari's body is inside the coffin
were the agents at that funeral did we notice them i didn't look around and see if they're
here peeking your head out you see the the sun is shining and uh it is scarce you see the bodies
of three men that you fought they're the men with the scars on their faces and necks wearing all
black and their bodies are still strewn across the makeshift stage of ari manstein's funeral
what happened rosemary yeah did we see her die first i need an intelligence check from
whoever has the highest intelligence i think it's me 75.
79 oh do you want to do you want to spend four luck in order to succeed on this check i'll spend
two luck life isn't always a highway thomas um no i'm comfortable feeling that okay
luck is a precious resource for me right now i only have 20 joe and luke the last time you
saw rosemary was when you were standing on top of water right and she reached for the gun
john lee pettymore wasn't there but clark bishop oh yeah keith vigno were then why did i roll the
chest that was it for a different piece of information gotcha do we have a way to contact
rosemary a better piece of information i don't yeah i mean i've got our number do i have kevin's
cell phone yeah like yeah but it might be weird me and uh keith saw rosemary die in glass's office
so if she answers the phone we'll know that whatever we did didn't didn't happen i don't
know i don't know i don't know how any of this works well let's just doesn't happen let's just
assume that some happen somehow he is dead and we did kill him what do we do now i mean start
crossing off more names yeah the name got crossed off that's do we need to kill maggie
and drew that seems odd are we supposed to not be crossing names off we ain't got no cause to
harm tility maybe we just happen to kill one but the other ones we just gotta make go to some
we gotta send them on a vacation away from here i'm tired of this damn game we're playing
it's like our lives are decided on the rolls of dice well we we could go we could go try to find
drew why don't all right i'm gonna call rosemary and we'll see if we've taken her out of all
existences in worlds or just the one we can also if she's still alive we'll just call her back in
an hour and see if she see if she's dead then then we can get an idea of the the causality that's
going on around us i mean we should yeah let's go ahead and do that but i'm starting to wonder if
it even matters if the name is crossed off on our chest and like we just don't we just don't mess
with marvin this time what if we just walk away from all like possible loose ends and in like
three months x like no marvin's just been building his crime empire you didn't call rosemary so he
lived uh i'm gonna call rosemary okay would you like to put it on yeah all right there it is and
then we have taylor yeah click all right we'll try that again in an hour and i text rosemary sorry
but though okay you get a call back but then it immediately goes away because she sees the time
yeah exactly happens all too often okay well i like the idea maybe maybe here in an hour or so
all that might be going down did we need anything else from marvin because if that somehow is all
going down right now we could it's a huge distraction have we asked ourselves what we
even got from marvin in the first place it feels to me we're more lost now than ever well that's
yeah so we went we went over there to see i haven't been clark in a while
oh yeah we went down to the goddamn marvin glasses scrap pittin uh we went we went up there to figure
out if uh cousin fucking good time what his plans were for contention and we were going to stop him
and i mean if his name is crossed off on her chest maybe we stopped him maybe we stopped his
evil plans he did kind of clue us in on that right what was that zack what were his plans
for contention i think he told us right i believe that clark bishop and keith vigno were in the room
and got to ask a few questions of marvin glass i don't know if we ever asked him about kevin
oh kevin asked and then they were just like you idiot like you know do you remember much about
that conversation i don't remember i remember that i remember the big one i asked him that's
the interesting thing about being alive and dying and then being alive again is it's really hard to
remember some stuff listeners that feels that feels like a lifetime ago well do we still have
the gun at this point or no i mean theoretically marvin would have it still because we there was
another thing that we were going to get right because he had it i don't think no no he wanted
us to bring the gun to him yeah oh well no we did yeah and then we got in cages and then we died the
first time man if only there was some kind of let's say app like discord where interested parties
could clue us in on what we might be missing if you have any notions on what leads we should be
pursuing just head on over to the pretended to be people discord help your boys out where is the gun
zach marvin glass as far as you know marvin glass is in possession of the gun that is what your
vision john kevin lee pettymore showed you right after the funeral of ari manstein yes earlier
today that is correct okay remind the listeners of what happened in that uh vision it was a
television screen that's all i remember did it have yours it had your uh my little
culture and what letters yeah i remembered mine john as your eyes roll backward your vision goes
dark images begin flashing through your mind just snippets moments and you try to keep up as the
speed of the sequence waxes and wanes you see a motel safe shiny black and closed you see the sign
for beans pond the little pond behind chief maggie cook's house in contention you see a television
it is blinking with different letters on it r s t l n e you see a small clearing in the woods
and the ground is scorched in a dark room lit by various electronics and machines you see a
massive shiny metal sphere 20 feet tall with silvery arms extending from either side
a tube connects this gargantuan ball to a machine below the machine begins whirring and you see a
small metal sphere roughly one inch in diameter begin moving up through the tubing into the larger
armed version of itself as this happens a vast circle opens up in the ceiling and a disorienting
amount of light and sound pours into the room revealing text painted on the back wall that
says the same thing you hear violently chanted by an unseen crowd planet juggernaut
the scene changes again and you see marvin glass standing at his desk in the grand room you
recently stood in as kevin alongside rosemary marvin is holding the odd camera with glass tubes
closely inspecting it tapping its lit red luminaire on his desk are two file folders
two file folders splayed open entitled the real files on clark bishop and keith vigna
contention police officers you can see in keith's file are various clippings about the beans family
the tragic the tragic accidental deaths of william and lena keith's parents the takeover of the
family business by ferguson in clark's file there is a newspaper article about the murderer who
killed clark bishop's parents and love there is a mugshot of a woman smiling a cold vacant smile
behind asymmetrical bangs covering one of her eyes written in sharpie underneath the mugshot
it says in all caps karen as he kind of remembers and comes out of it just like planet juggernaut
planet juggernaut is still kind of ringing in his ears and they just see like a single
tear go down his eye and like touch the the faint smile on his lips john you all right
yeah yeah man i'm fine i just miss an old friend well i've i've kind of got an idea
marvin has the gun and the camera if we think our actions might be permanent
like our old actions in this world like they'll happen here and later on in the day let's just
hang around town until afterwards slip on in after everybody's dead take that gun and camera
and then head on back to contention i'd get a burger or something in the meantime you're quite
full john lee pedemore was always down for a burger what if we somehow interfered with what
we had already done if we do that that's why we wait but we would be here now wouldn't wouldn't
we i look around i mean wouldn't we be here now if we if the motion was still going forward in time
back then well this isn't where we came back into the world i'm this isn't when we came back into
the world like look out there what happened at the funeral's already happened what's your point
i think the bottom line is that let's say let's say old clark me in the future put these brands
on us they set us into a tizzy and we went over and did stuff against marvin and then we woke up
back here where old me has put brands on us and marvin is crossed out so maybe he's trying to tell
us not to worry about marvin anymore and go after something else on our body list yeah i mean it
seems that way well one thing i was thinking in your vision you had beans pond was in it right
yeah i remember when i got that watch from my brother when i put it on i had a vision of of
digging through dirt and mud and and finding like a door or something in the ground and for some
reason i just think i just feel like i i ought to go get that watch and we maybe we should go to
beans pond and i think there's something there for us you still have that watch oh it's in it's
in my safe at my uh at my hotel room hotel motel hotel motel i mean if we want to just choose a
course and go that's that's our first most readily available i mean and i feel more comfortable
putting it back on with you guys around because it was making me go crazy you were seeing you
were seeing things keith when you put it i felt like i wasn't i was in a different dimension or
universe or timeline or something i had to take it off because it was i felt like i could have
got stuck there but with you guys watching me you'd be able to you know make sure nothing too
bad happened and i think maybe if i put it on around beans pond i might be able to remember
exactly where i was digging or it might show me something else but it's the only thing i can think
of and i don't i mean i just came from fighting planet juggernaut and dealing with marvin already
i don't really feel like doing that again let's say we do that can you think of what name on our
body that might relate to well if it's in contention it could be maggie or drew i mean
i feel like also uh we'll find out what name is connected to when we get to the pond yeah plus
it's in contention so it could be maggie or drew we see tilde waiting for us beneath the door like
holding a gun like you've discovered my brilliant plan detectives yeah you haven't heard her voice
yet but that's definitely it so i mean the last we heard from drew was that that creepy
voicemail what voicemail was that just said don't go back to contention yeah when's the last time
he listened to drew i mean we got his name printed on us and you know he's our co-worker he's our
he's our friend i feel like if he was in trouble we might as well go back and try to find him and
investigate this this watch i didn't do this last time but i could check in with maggie
my my job here was to kill stan manstein and i did that and last time she said i'd have some
downtime between here and there if i wanted to help you guys whatever but get a hold of her this
time i guess i could call her and say shit's fucked up yeah call her tell her i mean you
basically did your job you check back in with her see tell her what happened but don't tell her that
her name's on your foot but i can tell her about the future past i don't know if you trust her i
don't know i guess i could just not say just check in and tell her that stan's dead and see what she
says can you summon old clark anyway i just like thinking real hard about wheel of fortune or
clark does that and he's like i want to return to this point in the future now clark roll unnatural
set a reminder on your cell phone for 50 years from now
oh no that's a crit fail you're gonna lose six sanity
fuck see you later boys what are you down to now at the start of this next venture
clark becomes a raven lunatic i'm at nine oh shit dude okay so what's your breaking point
three oh good you're 60 away from the phone number what did you roll oh it's a crit fail
so we're gonna call that the over the power situation god damn it
are we gonna you're still in this dark space i the door to the mausoleum is open and so there's
light shining in but this tomb is you know small crowded you three are in there there's a coffin
on the ground what do you do oh this fucking sucks uh because this happened last time so it
happens again uh i charged john screaming why'd you make me call oh clark that's the stupidest
thing i ever heard keith remembers this from last time i kind of step in the way put my foot out
trying to trip him while he's running it john and i roll dodge okay perfect go ahead and roll
dexterity luke that is a fail what is your dodge thomas well it's a lot lower than 89 which is what
i rolled so and joe go ahead and roll unarmed combat for me this part didn't happen because
you shot me last time i'm glad we've reached a new level in our relationship that's shooting from the
hip to the hip isn't it it's readily available
unarmed combat so i fail my hell yeah okay the three of you all trip onto the ground
in a pile on top of each other all three of you are in a pile on top of the coffin like
i gave ari a kiss on the cheek goodbye ew
that was horrible inappropriate why'd you say that
clark's in the middle of it probably right yeah i was charging you you'd probably fall
on me and fell no i fell on the bottom i was trying to trip you up if i'm on the top i get
up and kind of i don't um that happened last time i don't i don't know what it is about being in
this mausoleum i just it gets me every time while he's disoriented i draw my gun and fire
oh no into the air to calm things down i i walk outside the mausoleum to get a breath of fresh
air so does clark after that you finally fully make your way out of ari manstein's mausoleum
and the sun is beating down on this frigid december day aside from the three android men
bodies you notice the crawfish boil still going strong and then there's that old lady in a
wheelchair who's like trying to get out of here as fast as she can it's taking a while but only
because she's super old do you want let's help her keith is doing some weird gymnastics in his
head he's like if rosemary's still alive but she's dead and we came back in time but what we did
still counted does it matter if we help this old lady yes by your own questioning emphatically yes
if what happened still happened when you guys approach this old woman she looks at you with
wide eyes what what hey lady did you by chance see us come through here earlier
what is happening ma'am you look like you've seen us before
you you came through you you walked through and then you you didn't walk back in you walked
through you didn't walk back in no no we walked back in we walked back in it's roll psychotherapy
for me what about persuade you can roll persuade yeah it's fun 97 oh and you knew it you know
you know that you've been who are you i show her the name marvin like crossed out on like the burn
and i'm like that's the last person who asked me too many questions demons demons you're all
demons and she rolls as slowly as possible away from you well we definitely didn't help this old
lady but we got some questions so what did you what did she mean she said we we went and walked
out and then she saw us come out a second time without going back in that means that means we
are already on our way good so maybe we should just fucking hang around until after we see
planet juggernaut burst out of that pit with ye boys on its back and then we just go in and
collect do you think we can just get into the audience maybe well i mean we risk getting froze
we just won't we just won't sit in that section i know which section it was the butterfly i mean
oh i have disguise i could i could dress up as a little kid since it's family night did you
just spoiler this for us you said the butterfly effect that means we weren't there the first time
haha i haven't seen it okay keith is pretty steadfast on this me dressing up as a kid
idea is there a particular reason it's family night so we could we could blend in better it's
not what i meant we escaped we all got out of there fine what if we let us take care of us do
something else i mean let them do their job but we need to find the way yeah we need to find the
camera and the gun the camera's probably in in marvin's office you think it was there when we
were there and then did rosemary use our gun at the end there was it just uh oh yeah she she used
the uh glass gun with glass tubing on it well we can't can't really steal that before we wait till
it's after all the commotion is done and we just walk in there we need to get away from this
mausoleum in case some more of ourselves come out of there let's just go all we have to do
mechanically speaking is wait for several hours and then clark's mind is blown thinking about
another group of us coming out of that mausoleum after us i can't come right none of this is making
sense hey man maybe they'll have tilde crossed off maybe they'll have maggie crossed off then
we just gotta sit here till they're all done oh shit
you got him fucking all right hey we won the campaign you win you win this has been really
fun guys honestly 53 episodes pretty solid we wrapped up every loose end yeah
i mean i know you're joking clark but do you want to try it well i mean if we came back we
got to cross one of these off i agree i think one of these is meant for us i think it'll be
the first one we happen to well what do you want to wait around and try to get those things or
just think we should try to get the items if we could let's work and bring them back to contention
do you want to literally wait or do you think we should work on something else and then we're like
oh yeah we're probably finishing up at marvin's about now then go get those well look we never
you freaked out before you called maggie call maggie real quick oh yeah do you guys want me
to call maggie yeah guys remember don't try to summon clark again oh that was the other thing
yeah you failed but you still get the knowledge don't get something from that i thought that's
what you said yeah you absolutely do you'll tell me later or he's gonna make it doesn't
remember the question there was no question you just told me to roll it oh you were trying to
like think real hard about coming back to the mausoleum as old clark's to maybe and then i
started yelling clark thomas and look if you want to leave the room okay hey man no he can't push us
around we're gonna stay
so joe but because you crit failed that check on a natural you're gonna get hit with a big wave
a crit fail on a natural is a good thing as much as a bad thing i get it yeah so
basically how this works is when you freaked out this knowledge wasn't in your head at all
you literally just broke a part of your brain just snapped apart right but then when they bring it up
you start to piece together what you had seen and what you saw was a dark room surrounded by wood
and stone and beautiful ornate candlesticks curtains it's really lush and beautiful in
this room it's very clearly not this time period by candlelight you see huddled over a desk is a
figure wearing a black cloak scribbling furiously into a book the book itself is extremely ornate
seems to be made of some sort of leather that you don't recognize almost uncured and bleeding
and as the camera pans around you see lit by this candle is the face of a very old
very decrepit clark bishop
you hear a knock at the door and this giant wooden door opens up
lord my lord and then you're immediately taken to a car and it is flying down the highway and
behind the steering wheel is maggie cook it's a silver accord and she grabs her phone and starts
dialing furiously at it can i see what she's dialing she's dialing the number for clark bishop
my number the number that i know is mine the number that you know is yours and she looked
frantic she looked extremely frantic okay you had all those memories flash through but they were
more full last time but your mind couldn't even comprehend them enough these are the traces of
information that you could pull out that you're remembering now and as you're remembering it and
you're staring at them in this moment the phone in your pocket starts to buzz fucking dope oh my god
okay
went to whatever town he was from and got me a pin that i still have that says uh
i lost my heart to alfred packer
the the university where they went was in that town and they're like sardonically in the 60s
the students named the the meal hall like alfred packer that's great that's so good we need to have
more cannibalism on this show you know there's there was some early on i got a feeling it's
coming up oh yeah there was there was an awful awful one early on so as you guys are questioning
clark bishop about oh yeah yeah as you guys are questioning clark bishop about this information
you see him reach for his pocket reach for this and i just in once with motion it comes out of my
pocket to my ear maggie yeah yeah hey hey i'm on my way to the city cemetery right now i need to
get to the parking lot get to the parking lot right now uh uh uh uh hey i'm putting you on
speaker it's it's it's maggie fellas hey maggie mags long time no see is that keith and is it
john it's uh it's sort of i'll explain i'll explain when you get here last time i saw you
were dead yeah how's your feet i have no time for these such conversations we gotta get going
you know how i said i'd give you some downtime that downtime is gone it's game time i i i'm
looking at the guys let's play ball yeah yeah we're good we're gonna all right i'll be at the
parking lot we're gonna hang up now what the fuck did you tell her i didn't i didn't did you tell
her about our feet i didn't i didn't tell her anything did you tell her our name was on us
that was the first time i spoke to her since we parted ways i told you i told you about meeting
her earlier all that let's get to the parking lot i guess i mean if you trust her do you trust her
i'm old you said not to right it's maggie no i don't think so who told us not to trust maggie
i don't think anybody told us not to trust her we've had maybe no there was the whole um you
found a letter the letter right from jim cook yes yes it's the first page of notes in my new
thing nice yeah yes jim cook maggie's own father gave us a hidden message it was there was the
cipher we did it was a cipher yeah i mean i guess if she's on our way here we just gotta be on our
toes i told you guys where i stand uh whether she's with us or against us she wants to stop
that thing i solved it yeah and i want to stop that thing i saw so well we'll be on our toes
since she's on our toes i think she has all her toes too which is weird take it on the arches
because there's a name in my boot there we go uh yeah let's head towards the parking lot pushing
past the old woman in the wheelchair good luck you make your way through these above ground tombs of
the city cemetery and head back into the parking lot and there you see that the only car in the
lot is clark bishop's silver honda accord on loan from the circle of knowledge i trailed behind a
little bit because i uh when they were out at earshot i told the old lady that she might as
well just stay here because how slow she's going she's gonna be back pretty soon and then i laugh
and then i run back to the parking lot that old lady rolls sanity she passed she's good
yeah you think you can fucking disturb her with shit like that she's like son i fucking know like
two deaths i've been on my game for 95 years you're not gonna fucking push me through the
southwestern war two two deaths have made keith a little mean
which war was that oh the great war they're all pretty great where's maggie coming from well i
guess we'll find out do we happen to hear the whine of a motor open absolutely i think that
might be her fellas clark roll alertness for me
what's the wheel of fortune song i fail wheel of fortune are you going to be the one who wins
wheel of fortune a fortune can you be the one who crushes the wheel that's it tight all right so
you guys are standing around and a silver honda accord comes flying down it matches the one that's
sitting in front of you and driving is maggie cook john lee pettymore and keith vigna have not seen
her in the flesh but you've been told that she's alive so i'm not gonna have your old sanity but
she pulls up right next to you guys rolls down her window and she's got big ass sunglasses on
and she looks at clark clark we got a mission we got a this is okay so i sent out everybody else
and i you you three might be the only one who can handle this right now because if he sees me
he will lose his marbles but you know bruce robin and then she looks at keith vigna specifically and
keith you would know that bruce robin is ferguson's business partner okay and he is now the full owner
of bar corp do you get it bruce robin like batman and robin yes yeah yeah like a hundred percent
you would know bar corp is beans and robin corporation they just go by bar corp he has
gone just fully insane he is a danger to everyone around him he is a danger to the mission of the
circle of knowledge and he is a danger to the world as we know it i hate to do this to you
again right back to back but i think he might need to be taken out physically with death do you think
round trip that could take us less than three or four hours absolutely i mean he i would imagine
he's at one of the businesses right now which can't be more than an hour away so well hey we
we were looking for something to do to kill the time before we get those things maggie is this
this is gonna help stop that thing i saw it's the only thing that can help stop that thing you saw
can i human that yes critical fail shit i wanted you to pass it so bad 88 on a 50 i believed her
that works for me hey maggie this is john even though it doesn't look like john uh hey max how
you doing and she just stares john same shit different day am i right wait no no no no john
lee pettymore the third and fourth no i no what no mac we've all been missing for so long i which
john you john you've been missing for so long where have you been the third or fourth you the
third john lee pettymore the third all right so john lee pettymore the third got his mind
uh hijacked in a way i think by marvin glass uh and he was forced to kill is he just talking in
the third person now because he had to do some fucked up shit what's going on maggie listen to
us is he gonna be all right on this mission maggie this is this is the john that i worked with yeah
i'm john lee pettymore the fourth on the police force in the body of john lee pettymore the third
surprise her face just turns pale white and roll sanity yeah all right
i rolled a 40 she deals with weird shit i think her bread and butter as far as clark has learned
lately is weird shit so i don't know how she'd react to this just learning about this shit though
has driven us insane so where's she oh that's she doesn't have anything to spare she has very
little to spare and her eyes just begin tearing up no no no no no no no and she grabs a pistol
out of the seat next to her and she just like holds it directly up into the ceiling her hand
is so tense that the gun is just shaking you're not who you see you are i can't okay all right
maggie all right maggie maggie mag put the gun down i'd like to use um my cop skills
criminology to like police her down like ma'am it's fine put the gun down calm down go ahead
and roll law for me oh 16 no no maggie maggie it's all right remember your training put the gun down
take your finger off the trigger and her finger goes off to the side put your gun away and she
sets it down in the shotgun seat next to her and she looks up at you and she's like
john yes max i need your help anything
this is this isn't it's not how i wanted it to go but if you can't do it and she just starts crying
clark doesn't know how to deal with that so he kind of takes a step back
clark as you take a step back you see out of the corner of your eye the burner phone that was left
in your car is sitting in your shotgun seat in your silver honda accord and it's lit up
i'm gonna go look at that while he's doing that i just kind of want to fill maggie
in on what's going on like calm her down but also just kind of like calmly explain to her how i got
to be like this okay just like confront it straight up be like man this is scary shit but here's what
went down and then like ask her what help she needs when you explain everything to her she
looks up through tears in her eyes she's just like john that's some that's some crazy shit
all right yeah this guy this bruce robin he's gonna end the world i don't mean that lightly
i need you to fucking kill him john leap anymore like looks her dead in the eye and nods i overhear
it and i put my hand on my gun i say it wouldn't be the first robin i kill and then i twirl my gun
out it accidentally shoots a shot up in the air and i go two birds and a bald eagle falls dead
out of the sky and i i'm shaking a little bit and i look at maggie i'm like i meant to shoot it and
then i put it back in my holster all right thomas and look if you could leave the room again this
is a joe-centric episode as they all should be
so you go over and you grab the burner phone can you remind me and the audience what the first
she this she i said because i thought it was a woman who dropped yeah it looked like a woman
who dropped in the car she or somebody else on who had the phone i don't know so there was a
text that came in and then i texted back and there was nothing beyond that right nope that's it okay
there was a text on the phone when you got it that said do you want to know how your parents died and
then you texted back who is this yeah nice and currently you have a text on this phone that says
your parents owned an artifact of immense power too much power for them to be trusted with
i'm gonna text back what artifact
how am i the only one trying to
heaven
bye