my closest comrades.
Some of you may have noticed a strange occurrence
in the past couple weeks.
I, Wolf the Dog, your fearless leader,
have been held against my will for a time.
But I have escaped the torturous restraints
of Judge Ephraim Cortland's sloppy meat trees
he calls hands.
And I am now back triumphantly crawling
once again into your ear holes.
Here on 694.2 PTBP,
contention's oldest and only radio station.
Now that the true wolf is on the bone throne once again,
I think it's about damn time for some truth.
Fuck every billionaire.
Greed should only exist in the dumpster.
Mm, what's wet, stinky, and made for sharing?
It's the news.
No shit, that disgusting excuse of a human,
contention's so-called Judge Ephraim Cortland,
was keeping me locked up in a cell.
I'm deeply sorry to leave you so unsatisfied
for so long, my pups.
I promise to never get caught in a slop trap ever again.
Trapped me with slop bait once, shame on you.
Trapped me with slop bait twice, shame on you.
Trapped me with slop bait three times,
what the fuck is wrong with you?
It's clear I can't help myself.
And your crew would just take an advantage of that?
Jesus.
Anyway, maybe we should burn down the courthouse.
Silas Cole can host any trials or legal matters
out on his property by the mine.
And he may as well preside over them too.
He is, after all, the reason contention
is so very prosperous.
Slap your knee to the beat if you agree.
It's the Creek Rocks with
Can't You Hear the Wolves Are Howlin'?
["Can't You Hear the Wolves Are Howlin'?" plays in bright rhythm.]
Do you guys know where the word howdy comes from?
No.
How do you do?
Yeah.
How did I not know that?
Howdy.
They shortened how do you do down to how do ye.
Which then became howdy.
Howdy.
How did I not know that?
Hey.
Ooh.
Got it.
I've got something that good for you here.
Why did the cowboy take hay to bed
to feed his nightmares?
Oh my God.
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Got any others?
Yeah, you got any other good ones?
No, no more good.
No, no good ones, but I've got another one.
What did you Google?
It looks like he's really enjoying it.
I'm Googling cowboy jokes.
Am I frozen or something?
Yeah, you're frozen, but you're doing a cute little smile.
It's a very cute smile.
A hand behind the head.
Oh, another cute smile.
Very mischievous, Luke.
Oh my God, that one's even better.
What do you call a happy cowboy?
A jolly rancher.
Oh.
Got it.
Luke, have you delivered this joke before?
No, but I just was trying to think.
Luke's been sending him these all week.
Okay, my internet seems to be fucking up,
so let me try, okay, my hotspot is on,
but it's not showing up in my, oh, here we go.
Okay, I probably will disconnect for a second.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Quick, let's make all our Luke jokes right now.
Am I still here?
Fuck.
Okay, that worked.
You could have kicked Luke
and we could have had an all out Luke roast.
It's not a roast unless I'm here.
Yeah, you're yeah.
Did you see that Alec Baldwin roast
with like his daughter was doing it?
Yeah.
Yeah, pretty bad.
Yeah, it hit pretty hard.
That way Alec Baldwin got roasted by his daughter.
Yeah, like at a roast thing and the opening.
Oh my God, Luke's frozen in the exact same.
It's in spotting, it was just the smile.
That's insane.
Fuck.
Can you hear me?
Screenshot.
It's so cute.
What a cutie.
I hope he looks like that forever.
He will, have you seen his fucking dad?
Oh, that's so true.
Well, Efron fell off his damn old horse,
broke his big ass spine in twain.
I fucking wish.
Everett crawled inside him.
Oh, okay, let's go.
Okay, am I good?
You seem good.
Okay.
Yeah.
Can you put your arm behind your head
and smile for us really quick?
Silas Cole is on his knees with his hands behind his back
shackled by preacher-sheriff Dr. Bobby Custard
with Judge Ephraim Cortland standing right behind him,
right next to the preacher-sheriff doctor
watching as Jack Perlman, Professor Horace Green
and Everett Pace loaded the rug out of the back
of Silas Cole's wagon and then slowly unfurled the rug
after seeing shoes on one side and Everett, I believe,
reached in to the other side and felt some patchy hair,
a very thin-skinned scalp,
almost touching the skull right off the bat.
And as soon as the rug is completely unfurled,
hopping onto all four haunches, haunches?
Haunches.
You're on your own with this one.
Haunches are like, would be with your legs, right?
Hopping onto her back two haunches
with her human arms in front of her.
Are they touching the ground, the front arms?
No, she's in a two and a half point stance.
Velociraptor.
Which means she's got like one arm kind of halfway down.
The other one's on a knee, elbow on a knee.
You notice there are no fingernails on her hands
that are moving back and forth quickly
with these wild eyes.
She just slits right under them
from where her cheekbones are poking through
the thin skin on her face, blood dripping down
and she lets out a guttural scream.
Run, run, run, run.
And then we're gonna go ahead and roll
to see who she attacks.
Oh boy.
If it's a one or a two, she's gonna attack Jack Perlman.
No.
If it's a two or a three, she's gonna attack,
oh, three or four, she's gonna attack Everett Pace.
No.
Five or six, it's gonna be Professor Horse Green.
Hey Luke, can you roll a D6 for me
and tell me what you get?
Six.
Oh, that's gonna be Professor Horse Green
that she jumps directly toward.
You made him your executioner.
Hey Luke, do you wanna hurt one of your friends?
Sorry.
What does Professor Horse Green do as this human
wearing these unfathomably out of fashion clothes
with thin skin, open mouth, tongue waggling about,
jumping at you, arms first,
these fingernail-less hands going to grip
onto either side of your shoulders.
He shoots at her with his pistol.
And gets a,
And gets a what?
A hundred.
Oh no.
Oh my God.
What?
Holy shit.
You nailed it.
Oh no.
What are the chances of that?
Holy shit.
Professor Horse Green, your sidearm
is still in the holster when you reach down to grab it,
pull it out, and you flick the trigger
right there on your holster.
Go ahead and roll damage.
What's the damage on that pistol?
Ah.
That's one D10 plus two.
Holy shit.
Nice.
Six.
Professor Horse Green,
your kneecap goes right into the dirt.
Bone shards from your knee are now sticking up
out of the dirt as blood just begins spurting
a fountain of blood away from your leg
out onto this dusty ground beneath you.
How many hit points did you have total?
I was at 11.
Yeah, so I'm going to need a constitution check there
to stay conscious, buddy.
Got a 50.
And I roll an 85.
Horse Green instantly collapses unconscious
as he bleeds out on the ground.
Oh shit.
Damn.
Holy shit.
What?
I might get to play video games a little bit earlier
than I thought tonight.
Oh my God.
He's been practicing with Red Dead,
but only using the bow and arrow.
Judge F from Courtland, it is your turn.
What do you do?
From what I'm seeing, I'm busy with Silas
and I just hear a scream and I turn around
and I see her like hunched over.
So I'm like within an arm's reach of my horse.
So I grabbed my lasso off the horse
and try to get her with the lasso,
like around her arms and try to demobilize her.
Roll rope use for me.
Okay.
That is a 85 on a 40.
Oof.
Oh no.
Well, this isn't going great so far.
Oh shit, my internet just went out.
Fuck, I wasn't recording either.
Damn it.
Oops.
Yeah, we're gonna have to do it again.
Yeah, we're gonna have to do all live from the get go.
So as I hear the scream, I turn around,
grab the lasso and throw the lasso,
but I had forgotten to tie the rope into a lasso.
So I just threw the end of a rope at her.
So the end of a rope hits her in the shoulder
and it's a heavy rope and she grabs on
to the other end of the rope.
Preacher Sheriff Bobby Custard.
Oh no.
Freezes in terror.
Just failed a sanity check.
A sanity check that I forgot to have all of you roll,
which you'll need to roll now.
I'm not conscious, baby.
You are unconscious, so you are good.
Oh, I rolled a crit fail.
Oh my God.
Did you really?
Welcome to the party, baby.
I rolled a 99.
Ooh, I got a 33 on a 50.
Crit success.
There you go.
Okay, I got a normal success.
And bringing the luck back up to our side.
Oh my God.
God damn these beautiful dice that Joe gave me.
Okay, Everett Pace, you lose no sanity.
Not sure how, not sure why.
It just looks like a scared battered woman in front of me.
She's just wild with fear.
And therefore you'd lose one sanity
because the success is still losing one sanity on this one.
That is my apologies.
She's real beat up though and that's not right.
It's definitely not right.
Judge Ephraim Courtland, you're going to lose zero sanity
with the full disregard that you have for all humans.
Yeah, I've seen countless people hanging by my own hand,
so really doesn't affect me too much.
Honestly, those smashed up watermelons
made me feel worse than this.
Glad I could add some horror for Judge Ephraim Courtland
in this short arc.
Jack Perlman, you're gonna lose a D4 plus one,
except for with a crit fail,
that D4 is automatically a four,
which means that you lose five sanity,
which just happens to be enough for you
to have a short bout of insanity.
Yay. Oh, lucky.
Yeah, that sounds fun.
Yeah, it's super fun.
So this is the thing where I'm gonna have you rank,
fight, flight, or freeze from most likely to least likely.
Fight, freeze, flight, most likely fight.
If you roll a one, you're gonna run away.
If you roll a two or a three,
you're gonna freeze for one round,
and if you roll four, five, six,
you will immediately fight,
which would just be fine in this situation, seemingly.
That'll be a freeze.
Perfect.
So Jack Perlman, on your turn,
Me and Bobby, doin' the Lord's work.
You're gonna do what future Sheriff Dr. Bobby Custard
is doing, which is...
Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh.
Everett Pace, it is your turn.
Judge Courtland threw the lasso.
She grabbed onto it, so she's still holding it onto her end,
and he's holding onto his end, right?
That is correct, yes.
I wanna grab the rope anywhere that I can
to pull as hard as I can,
the purpose being to have her fall on her face.
Sounds good.
You roll, I'll roll.
Everett, you just roll strength.
Will do.
I pass a 23 on a 50.
I pass with a 46.
Fuck.
How does that...
That is an interesting question, Everett Pace.
Can we just be in a stalemate on the tug?
You know what, yeah, since we both passed,
the rope goes completely taut,
and she's looking directly at you
with these wild, wild eyes.
Roll psychology.
Son, I ain't got none of that.
A 96 on a 10.
I got natural world out the wazoo.
Would that help me?
Yeah, go ahead and roll that.
I pass that a 53 on an 80.
You've seen a feral possum.
Yeah, for sure.
These eyes, this sick combination of fear,
loathing, and pure rage of needing to survive.
And Las Vegas.
Has only ever been seen in modern day in Las Vegas,
and in the eyes of feral possums,
and I'm sure other things.
Feral mongese.
No, those are cute no matter what.
Oh, I'm sorry.
And with that...
Feral skunks.
It's Jack Perlmanster.
Oh, I get to do something. Feral spirits.
No, I just want you to tell me...
How scared I am.
Will Ferrell? Yeah, just talk to me
about what's happening in your brain.
So inside of Jack's brain,
he's been beaten down just sanity-wise
over and over and over again from the get-go,
because I think I failed every sanity roll this time.
But he's just hit the breaking point
where it's like the rubber band of stress
has been stretched too much, and it snapped.
And when it snapped, he just, he can't do anything.
He doesn't know how to put it back together
and do something that's useful right now.
Paralyzed.
I'm paralyzed with fear, baby.
He says to Everett.
Hey, Everett, I can't move.
I'm too scared right now.
And as those thoughts are going through your brain,
out of the corner of your eye,
you see Tilde be this crazed teenage girl
in a complete bout of madness in her own right,
drops the rope and lunges directly at your neck.
Unable to respond, she doesn't even try to pin you.
She just like, mouth first, goes straight to your neck.
She misses the jugular.
She goes around the side, almost behind your ear,
and bites down.
You're gonna lose four damage.
As she bites down to where her teeth, top and bottom,
touch, and then she rips her head back.
Blood begins pouring down,
and you feel the shirt on your back become wet
with thick, hot Jack Pearlman blood juice.
That's yucky.
And she begins chewing.
Judge, Courtland, it is your turn.
So the rope gets let go of
and kind of, you know, loses all of the tension.
And the opium is really starting to hit the judge right now
combined with all the whiskey he's drank.
So he- I forgot about that.
He starts to nod off a little bit
and then wakes up and just starts to coil the rope
back and then takes a swig of whiskey
and just lackadaisically starts tying it
into an actual lasso.
Okay.
Unaware of what's happening to Jack.
Yeah, completely unaware.
Horace Green is now on the ground.
Jack Pearlman is standing there
with part of his shoulder neck.
His traps are missing on one side a little bit.
And blood gushing down his shirt.
Judge Ephraim Courtland staring off into the distance,
coiling up his lasso and ever at pace,
holding on to the other end of that there rope.
Silas Cole stands up from his position, still handcuffed,
and begins making his way toward the front door of the house
and he gets up onto the porch
before it is Bobby Custard's turn, who immediately turns.
Okay, now Silas, something crazy's going on here and...
And with that notices, Tildy B takes his attention
off of Silas and is going to fire at Tildy B. Mitchell.
Strikes true with eight damage.
Nice.
Yeah.
Fires three rounds into Tildy B. Mitchell's chest,
who staggers backwards and lets out another.
Ahhh!
Fuck.
Three bullet holes in her.
Blood begins pouring down her shirt
that is clearly the cut of another time.
I don't know how many different ways I can say that.
Some kind of future cloth.
What is Forever 21?
Everett Pace, it's your turn.
I wanna take some of the watermelon out of my pocket
and throw it toward her feet.
I'm trying to bait her, so I'm saying things like,
here, here, you hungry, you hungry?
Here, here, take some of this, take some of this.
And I'm just chucking watermelon out of my pockets
onto the ground in front of her.
I thought you were going for like a banana peel effect.
Either way, either way, I'll take either way.
Boy, howdy.
Okay, I bet you don't have charm.
So let's have you roll.
Even though Everett charms all of our hearts,
every week on PTBP.
I've got farming and this is a pretty classic farming skill.
You gotta throw watermelon at the ground sometimes.
For fertilizer to get the chickens back into the coop.
And if you run into a feral possum,
it's handy to have some watermelon in your pocket
to feed it to get its attention away from you
while you get away.
Yeah, so give him like a plus 20 on that roll, Zach.
You could just do that for us real quick.
Okay, roll farming.
Are you, okay.
I pass.
It's a 41 out of 60.
This watermelon goo in the most appetizing way
you possibly could have.
Michelin star.
For an animal, oh my God.
This watermelon goop is so well plated
on this dusty, dusty ground.
As if I was planting it.
That's how well it's landed in this ground.
Jesus.
Yeah, no matter what happens,
whether I remember to or not,
the epilogue of this story is the growth
of watermelons next year.
Hey, I wanna throw that watermelon on the ground
and start getting out of there.
It's a distraction.
So I'm walking back toward the horses.
Can our next arc be like going inside one of the characters
cause he swallowed a watermelon seed
and it's gonna grow inside of him.
We gotta get it out.
Are you playing the watermelon seed?
Sure.
Yes.
Watermelon seeds.
We're food in the next arc.
Everett, go ahead and roll.
Are you trying to sneak away
or are you just kind of walking?
Just kind of walking,
hoping that I distracted her enough
that her attention is not on me.
Okay.
But I don't have stealth.
I mean, that's just not something I can do.
Yeah, no, you can walk away.
That's fine.
There wasn't a lot to hide behind anyway.
No big rocks.
I mean, if you're on stealth, big rock appear.
You roll stealth, big rock appear.
Jack Promo, what are you up to?
Oh, you know, slowly dying probably.
That's what it feels like
as I put my hand over what used to be
part of my neck and shoulder.
And now I assume it's like a donut.
Like when you take just a single or like a bagel
and it's that perfectly round bite,
but just out of the chunk of my well-toned shoulders.
Oh, Jack.
You ever fall in love with your own character?
Yep, that's exactly why.
Roll to, I want to roll to kiss Jack Pearlman.
Justin does.
Oh, I crit failed again.
Am I like kind of shocked back into reality
with the bite I'm assuming?
I'm like, whoa.
Yeah.
You were in slow-mo before.
And then as soon as she rips the muscle up out of your neck,
everything fast-forwards back in place.
Back to reality.
I want to like try and,
is she like real fast and kind of like spindly and wiry?
Yeah, she's not giving up that easy.
I would like to like,
can I like grapple her to the ground almost
and like hold her down on the ground?
You can certainly try to do that, yeah.
Okay.
Shove her face in that watermelon.
I have fighting brawl or strength, I don't know.
Fighting brawl would be the one
that I would like you to roll against me on.
Okey-dokey.
And yeah, I basically want to just like
grapple her to the ground and kind of like hold on to her,
but in a position where I cannot be bit, like.
Yes.
She succeeded with an off four.
I got a 10.
Yeah.
Yeah, that'll do.
With a success.
Hell yeah.
That'll do.
So for a pin, no damage will be dealt to her,
but you are now pinning her,
which gives her a negative and you a positive
on your next rolls and her a negative on any opposing rolls.
Okay.
You're moving forward.
However, as you have her pinned to the ground,
you look around you.
Right next to you on the ground,
you see Professor Horace Green,
who just lost another hit point this round.
Oh no.
Four.
Oh shit.
Damn.
Everett Pace, who is slowly backing away
from the entire situation.
Silas Cole, who is on the porch of the house,
heading into his home, hopefully.
Preacher Sheriff Bobby Custard,
who is gun drawn looking around.
So he seems to be a good ally here.
And Judge Ephraim Courtland,
who seems to not care so much about all this,
care far more about getting his rope
back into its upright position.
Y'all better get on over here and help me out now.
Everett.
He's walking away from me.
It's Tildy B. Mitchell's turn again
and I'm gonna go pee real quick.
Hey, I do wanna bring up for Horace's sake
that opium is a natural painkiller,
so if that can help in any way.
And he smoked some of it.
Yeah, no, he can't feel it.
You like that?
Good, good.
He can't feel that he's dying.
Can't believe I rolled a 99 and then a 10 on these guys.
High and low.
Thank God he hit that 10, though.
That gives us a moment.
I would have probably died, I think.
What happened to Horace Green?
That's when the dogs were getting here,
so I couldn't hear.
He shot his knee off.
He crit failed a gunshot.
Oh, no.
Did she attack you first and then you did it?
He said that she was going to attack him,
so he preemptively shot.
Yeah, I tried to shoot at her and just blew my knee off.
Oh, my God.
I thought she'd like crit attacked you
or something like that in success.
That's crazy.
Good old crit fail.
Always fun.
It was a hundred, too.
It was the crittest of fails.
I saw the roll, but I didn't see what led up
or what happened because of it.
Oh, right.
That's fucking wild.
Wanna hear a joke?
Yeah, go for it.
Okay, a big Texan cowboy stopped at a local restaurant
following a day of drinking and roaming around in Mexico.
While sipping his tequila,
he noticed a sizzling scrumptious looking platter
being served at the next table.
Not only did it look good, but the smell was wonderful.
He asked the waiter, what is that you just served?
The waiter replied, ah, you have excellent taste.
Those are bull testicles from the bullfight this morning.
Delicacy.
The cowboy undaunted said, what the heck?
I'm on vacation.
I'll have some.
The waiter replied, I'm so sorry.
There's only one serving per day
because there's only one bullfight each morning.
If you place your order now,
we'll be sure to save you the delicacy for tomorrow.
The cowboy placed the order and the next evening,
he was served the one and only special delicacy of the day.
After a few bites and inspecting the contents
of his platter, he called to the waiter and said,
these are delicious, but they're quite a bit smaller
than the ones I saw you serve yesterday.
The waiter shrugged his shoulders and replied,
sometimes the bull wins.
Nice.
It's a good one.
So it was like he ate the person's balls.
He ate the matador's balls.
Nice.
If only he'd been there a day earlier,
he could have gotten the bull's testicles that he wanted.
Yeah, that's actually more of a dramatic tale
that you told us.
A cowboy asked me if I could help him round up 18 cows.
I said, sure, that's 20 cows.
I like it.
Jack Perlman, roll, brawling, fight again for me.
What if I don't want to tell you what I rolled
because it's 61 on a 60.
Oh, and with the success from this unnatural teenager,
Jack Perlman is thrown at least four feet in the air
and he lands on his back.
You'll take no damage from this, but.
It's scary, but don't make me roll a sanity, please.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Roll sanity.
Okay.
Fail.
Oh, God damn it.
I've lost nine sanity so far in these episodes.
Lose one more as you're staring up at the sky,
you think about, was Perlman a religious man?
No.
He is now.
Should have been praying.
Oh my God.
Judge F from Courtland, it's your turn.
After the judge gets his rope coiled up,
he notices that Silas is not on the ground by him anymore
and catches him out of the corner of his eye
and sees him running off towards his house.
And he's going to drop the rope
and just chase after Silas.
Okay.
And if I can get to him, I want to grab him.
Let's go ahead and have you roll.
Character sheet here.
Climb for climbing stairs.
Drive wagon coach, which is what everybody in town
calls your fat ass.
I'm not seeing anything.
So I'll have your old dexterity.
Okay.
29 on a 60.
Nice.
39.
Fuck.
Damn.
Gotcha, baby.
It makes sense.
Judge F from Courtland's this big lumbering creature,
almost as horrifying as Tildy B. Mitchell.
And he makes it right up onto the stairs
as Silas Cole slams the door directly in his face.
Ephraim stops at the stairs
and just kind of like blinks hard and looks
and takes another swig of his whiskey.
Preacher Sheriff, Dr. Bobby Custard is going to...
Save us all.
Actually, let's see who's going to roll this for me.
Joe, you can roll it.
Roll a D six.
If you roll a one, two or three,
he's going to shoot Tildy B. Mitchell.
If you roll four, five or six,
he's going to start giving first aid
to Professor Horse Green.
It's a four.
Right next to his bag,
he grabs his medicine bag out of his side saddle there,
part of his tack.
Nice.
Maybe, I don't know.
And he rushes to Horse Green
and begins successfully doing first aid.
Horse Green, conscious again, you gain three hit points.
Hello.
His eyes open and he says, hello.
I don't feel a thing.
Now his eyes open and he says,
Ah!
Help me!
And your face, it's your turn.
So she's devouring this watermelon
and she's just all about the watermelon right now, right?
Like it's probably her favorite thing right now, right?
She might be looking at the watermelon.
She's scrambling over toward it.
She thinks it's part of Jack still.
Her socks have little watermelon slices on them,
so you know she's a fan.
And he's trying to get to Sheriff Bobby Custard's horse
to grab the rifle out of the side saddle there.
Smart.
Can I get there in time and shoot or do I just get there?
No, you can get there and shoot.
I'd like to shoot at Tildy B, at the scary zombie lady.
Yeah, you don't know her name.
And she screams,
Ah!
My name is Tildy B Bitcha!
So now we can all start calling her that.
Oh my God.
Oh, I can push.
So I rolled a 77.
That would be a crit fail on a 70.
I'm gonna push this roll.
I forgot about pushing.
Hey, you know what?
You can't push.
Oh, a fucking crit.
God damn it.
Oh, cool, okay.
Okay.
What?
Our dice are cursed tonight.
Fuck.
All right, yeah.
That was a crit fail with a...
Roll damage for me.
Yeah, okay.
That's a D10 plus four.
Ooh.
Four, so eight total.
Eight total?
Yeah.
Preach your sheriff, Dr. Bobby Custard, let's out a
Ew, oh, fucking shit!
Oh my gosh.
Oh, damn it.
With his own gun.
Professor Horace Green, the first thing you see actually
when you open your eyes and start screaming
once you've come back to reality a little bit,
the front of Preacher Sheriff, Dr. Bobby Custard's torso,
just on his left side, explodes through
and viscera and awful just starts kind of pouring out
the front of him.
My bad, my bad.
It's like you threw a crispy.
I criss-succeeded on my constitution check.
Hell yeah, so he instantly heals and we're all good.
Let's just keep going.
Whose turn is it now?
It is Jack Pearlman's turn as Preacher Sheriff,
Dr. Bobby Custard grabs almost the entire thing of gauze
in his pack and shoves it like a fistful
just right into his own gut.
Jack Pearlman gets his knife out.
He's going for blood.
He's going to stab Tildibee or swipe at her,
whatever, whatever works, whatever you think works.
Stab, swipe.
So you're gonna roll.
I believe it's fighting brawl.
Unless you have a knife skill that's different than that.
The knife is brawl skill.
Oh, that's cool.
Well, I failed, so 72 on a 60.
She did too, so she won't be able to use your knife
against you in any way, but you're just.
Oh, it's good to know that's up for.
Oh, always.
She takes a negative if she's already gone this round,
that's just kind of how it works.
If she was to fight against one of you guys
and you could fight back,
you'd take a negative that round as well.
So I could push though if I wanted to
since I didn't crit fail.
Yes.
But then if I do fail, I crit fail.
Yeah, that is correct. I'm going for it.
Hell yeah, don't stab yourself.
I can't roll this bad this many times.
Right guys, right?
Famous last words.
Okay, so you swing wildly as she, Neo from the Matrix,
like bends back, dodging all of your side swipes.
What are you doing to try to?
So I like to imagine he has it where it's like down,
like he's holding it and it's going down
and he's swiping like that.
And then as he misses one of his swipes,
he's going to go for like jamming it into her instead.
The American plunge.
Yes.
Well, yeah.
She succeeds with a 20.
I fail with a 91.
Oh no, what is your damage on that knife, sir?
A D4 plus two plus a D4.
So two D4 plus two.
What kind of knife was that?
Cause he has a damage bonus.
The knife has a damage bonus.
I'm very strong, so when I stab myself,
it's going to hurt really bad.
All right, do you want to roll one D4
and I'll roll the other one or do you want?
We're connected through our dice.
I rolled a two.
I rolled a one, oh, thank God.
So five?
Yeah, five.
That's still not great.
How many hit points did you have?
I had 10 and now I have five.
What did you start with?
14.
Holy shit, okay.
You had 10, now you have five.
Taking half of your current hit points in one round.
I'm going to need a constitution check for you,
Jack Perlman, and you've been doing nothing
but rolling great this entire time.
So I'm sure you'll have no issues staying conscious.
I'm gonna use one of these metal babies.
Joe.
Metal baby.
I can't believe you fucked me like this, Joe.
Oops.
Wait a minute.
No.
A 10.
Can I only roll the worst ever or super low?
Wait, what did you tell me to roll?
No, that's great.
You're still good.
I was confused on what I asked you to roll.
So you can stay conscious.
That was a constitution check in order to stay conscious.
However, your knife is directly in between
the two bones in your femur.
Nope, femur's one bone.
Tibia and fibula.
What's the bone right next to the femur?
PP bone.
It's in your PP bone.
I stabbed my PP.
Tibia and fibula.
Is that your thigh?
That might be in your arm.
No, that's your leg.
It's the lower calf.
Lower part of the leg.
I broke them bad boys.
I don't know shit about no bones.
It's in my leg.
It's in your leg and it is scratching
up against your femur.
You think that if you were to pull out your femur bone
and look at it, it would have Tildi B's initials on it.
It's completely dug in there.
And she helped guide it away from her
and right back directly into your leg.
And it is stuck there.
How could she do that chewing on watermelon?
She's a great multitasker.
Yeah, you forgot to give me my plus 40 bonus.
So from watermelon distraction.
Professor Horace Green, it's been a while.
Indeed.
Am I still losing hit points?
No longer, no.
You've been stabilized by the good preacher sheriff doctor.
Oh, good.
I'd like to shoot Tildi B.
Yes, that does make sense.
If you'd like to roll firearms.
Oh, no.
It's not a crit fail, but a 95.
I'll push it, push it real good.
Fuck it.
Yeah, I'll push it.
Oh, no.
What's a crit fail if you fail a push, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I failed.
Oh, boy.
Horace, yeah, Horace blind with pain tries to shoot again.
And what does he do, Zach?
Well, guess who's right above him.
Oh, no.
Who just got shot himself with his own rifle.
Who is just giving you first aid.
Who's right in between you and Tildi B. Mitchell.
Bubby.
Right before you can aim your gun down
to point at the unnatural creature tearing apart
Jack Pearlman with his own turns,
you fire the pistol on its way down.
Go ahead and roll damage for me.
Oh, boy.
Was it max damage?
It's 11.
Oh, my god.
I think we got it dead.
Holy shit.
Did you guys know that the gunfight at the OK Corral,
most famous, most infamous gunfight probably of the West,
happened in Tombstone in 1881?
People always think of it as this, you know,
Tombstone, right?
Big gunfight.
Wyatt Earp, Doc Holliday.
It only lasted 30 seconds, which is five rounds of this game.
And we're at the end of round three currently.
So this all adds up to me.
Yeah.
In just 20 seconds, we've literally dismantled our shot.
Could you share if Dr. Bobby Custard's head explodes
and his body flies off in a completely different direction
than where you actually shot?
Quentin Tarantino style?
Yeah, no.
He flies into the back of the wagon.
His headless body is just flung.
You Gallagher'd his head.
It's weird that that's the first Gallagher reference.
I was trying to get a Gallagher reference at the other house,
and I just couldn't work it in.
And pretty sure if Dr. Bobby Custard is fully, fully dead,
I need everyone to roll sanity for me, even me,
since I didn't see it.
No, not you.
You feel like Cotton.
Hey, I crit failed again, so.
Jesus.
My god, dude.
What is happening?
I don't know.
This has to be like our crit fails per minute
has to be a record right now.
So I lose like two sanity instead of one?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
I regular failed.
OK, you're going to lose one sanity, Everett Pace.
Jack Perlman knew it would lose two sanity.
And Professor Horace Green.
I pass.
Loses no sanity.
Totally cool with what he did to that guy.
And it blasted the wrong way, so he didn't even see it.
Exactly.
Completely blinded by the gunpowder.
Unable to see.
Here's a noise that sounds like, no, as it's happening.
And honestly, that noise is coming out
of these vocal cords that are hanging out
the top of this body, just waggling back and forth
in the arid wind.
And you assume that that noise is Tildy B. Mitchell,
the unnatural creature that you must have surely
killed just now.
However, at the top of this round,
you all see Tildy B releases the knife that
is in Jack Perlman's thigh and begins
running as fast as she can.
Away?
Away.
Oh.
She runs around the backside of the house.
And she actually runs so far in this round.
This is a six-second round.
She makes it about 75 yards.
Holy fuck.
And you could see that she is running up out of this area
in a southwesterly direction.
That's the son of a bitch what killed Dandelion.
I yell to no one in particular.
And with that is Judge Ephraim Cortland's turn.
He walks up the stairs, kicks the door as hard as he can,
and yells, Silas, get out here.
I'll burn your fucking house down.
And he is digging around in his pocket for his lighter.
Holy shit.
But I want to try to kick the door down at the same time.
Thin door.
You can certainly do that if everybody else could
take their headphones off.
Whew.
Judge Ephraim Cortland, the smell of rotten flesh
is the first thing you notice when
you kick in the front door of the coal abode.
At first, you think the stench could
be from the unattended dishes strewn
throughout this living room, the ruminants of several meals
now covered in a few buzzing flies.
But that static hum of these buzzing around flies
is so loud in your ears due to the large swarm hovering
above and about the body of Miss Kitty,
which is laying lifeless across one of the sitting chairs.
Lifeless, to be sure, because this body, the skin
is chewed up so badly that chunks are hanging off
or completely missing the dripping dark red blood pooling
below on the floor, but especially
lifeless due to the way this body is crumpled.
Her back held directly in the middle by one of the armrests
there at an unnatural angle as the top half of her torso
dangles straight down perpendicular to the floor.
Roll sanity.
A 50 on a 50.
Oh.
Make it a 49 as you lose one sanity
from this horrifying scene.
And go ahead and roll a listen check for me.
Fail.
That is all.
I'm going in.
Can I see Silas or?
No, no.
So this is a shotgun style house.
So basically front door leads to the first room
and there's one door all the way ahead of you.
Yep.
I'm going to keep going.
I want to find Silas.
And you're going to be able to make it to the next door.
Is it a closed door?
It's not like an archway.
It is a closed door.
While I'm going, I'm yelling, Silas, get your ass out here.
Awesome.
As this speedy, speedy teenage non-human
takes off into the distance, Judge Courtland
kicks in the door of the Silas home,
takes in his surroundings before you hear,
Silas, get your ass out here.
Sorry.
Who is it?
So many people on this list are dead now.
Everett.
It is Everett Pace.
I want to keep my gun now trained on the front door,
kind of given whatever kind of cover
I can if somebody comes out that front door.
But I want to be making my way to whoever
looks most injured between Jack and Horace.
I could visually tell that, couldn't I?
You would be able to visually tell which one is more injured.
Jack, what are your hit points at?
Five.
What are you at, Thomas?
Three.
Oh, shit.
I'm going to head over to Professor Horace
and try and do a little first aid on him.
That cool?
Professor Horace freaks out.
It's a crit pass, a 66 on a 70.
Yeah.
Four.
Four hit points right off the bat.
I feel like half my old self again.
Sheriff Bobby got his head blown off.
He just dropped all his medical supplies
right there on the ground.
I reached down and grabbed with one hand some gauze
and just like patted it into the knee area.
And I've done it a lot.
Living out there on the land by myself,
I had to patch up myself all the time.
So I'm real good at it.
And I keep one gun trained on the door, my rifle,
and the crook of my elbow here while I get his knee back
in tip top shape.
Perlin.
I would like to perform first aid on my leg, my thigh.
What?
My thigh.
Thigh.
Tell me about it, stud.
I want to rip off a chunk of my shirt with my teeth
and tear it up and then wrap it real tight.
It perfectly cuts like Queen Amidala.
It perfectly cuts into a cute little crop top.
Oh, yeah, I do from the tummy, not from my sleeve.
Remember that bullshit.
Yeah, I do the tummy cloth, not the arm.
I was thinking arm cloth, but I like the idea
of a long sleeve crop top.
Like a long sleeve dress shirt crop top.
Jack Perlman is a man of great fashion.
And of not weight.
Yeah, not passing.
Regular fail.
You just kind of wrap it around.
Yeah, great.
What happens if you push a first aid roll and then fail?
What's a crit, fail, first aid look like?
Slice the artery.
Do you want to find out?
I'm going to push it.
He's going to find out.
What's your first aid?
Yeah, is this worth it?
Oh, shit.
That's pretty good bad.
It's 50-50.
Pretty good, pretty bad.
Let's see what happens.
Do it for the vine, bro.
Oh, no.
Wait, hold on.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's a fail.
Yeah, I rolled the exact same fucking thing again.
What are the chances?
What is happening?
Jack Perlman, roll a D4.
Oh, a four.
That's good.
Jack, you wrap the shirt around, and it
doesn't stop the bleeding.
And so you think to yourself, well, obviously I've
got to get this knife out.
And so you grab onto the handle of your knife.
I thought she took the knife away and ran away with it.
No, she left it in there.
Oh, OK.
Did I say she ran off with it?
I think you might have.
I thought you did.
I thought you said she took it out.
OK, whatever works.
At some specific point, you did say
she dropped your knife, his knife.
I don't know if it was still in his leg when that happened or not.
In my mind, she was just holding it into his leg,
and then she let go and released it so that she could bail,
but just left it in his leg.
She doesn't need a knife.
She got chompy chompies.
So yeah, I gank that knife out.
Yeah, you pull it right out.
And as you pull it out, it nicks an artery,
and blood just starts going everywhere
as you're desperately trying to tie tighter and tighter
this shirt bottom around your leg.
And you lose four hit points.
Taking you from five to one.
So I'm going to need you to roll another constitution
check to stay conscious.
Joe?
Well, now that we know what happens
if you crit fail a first aid roll, just don't do it, Justin.
Seems pretty obvious in hindsight.
I rolled a crit success on my constitution check, a 44 on an 80.
Then you get to be awake for all this pain.
Extra awake, like super awake.
I'm so conscious during a time I wish I could pass out.
Blood is now soaking the dirt and creating
mudblood underneath the back of your knee here on the ground.
Mudblood.
And Professor Horsegreen, it is your turn.
Oh, also, Jack, your boots are ruined.
God damn it.
Blood is fully soaked into the leather
to the point of non-return.
Well, we're not in combat anymore, are we?
We are.
Oh, with Sylas.
How much mobility do I have?
Mechanically, you're going to be at a disadvantage on anything
that needs you to run or be dexterous or anything
like that.
But you can hobble.
So you're just as good as Everett Pace was always.
OK.
Well, when you put it like that, I hobble over
to where Everett is covering the door.
Is that what you did after you healed me?
I don't think I moved.
I think I just got to your position.
You're all three kind of bunched up
in this location, which I'm picturing about 10 yards away
from the front porch of the Cole home.
You guys are right out front.
Horsegreen crawls behind a wagon or a barrel
or whatever's in Sylas Cole's front yard to find some cover
and trains his pistol on the front door.
And you can very clearly hear Judge Ephraim Courtland
in the living room.
Just a reminder that he was in the first room of this house
hollering, Sylas, get your ass out here.
And the three of you can take your headphones off.
Judge Ephraim Courtland, as you are,
no, you failed your listen check.
So you're just kicking in the next door?
Yeah.
They're trying to just open it if it's open.
Oh, you're just going to open it?
If it is open.
Describe to me exactly what you do.
You know what, I'm pissed off and I'm big.
So after I'm yelling, get your ass out here,
I kick in the other door, the next door.
I need you to roll listen and spot hidden,
two separate rolls.
Listen first.
Fail the listen.
Crit success on the spot hit 33 on him.
45.
As you kick in the door, you find yourself in the bedroom.
The bed has been completely flipped over
to use as cover on the right side of this room.
And you see a small one inch in diameter metal sphere
rolling directly toward you.
What do you do?
I see the sphere, but I don't really
pay any attention to it.
Yeah, it's like a marble.
Yeah.
So I'm going to be careful not to slip on it,
but I'm going to go and just brute force grab the mattress
and throw it away to see if he's behind there.
When you grab the mattress, you just rip it away,
throw it right up against the wall to your side.
And you see Silas Cole, he's hunkered down
and he is chanting something quietly to himself.
Bob da ha ha, Bob da ha ha, Bob da ha ha, Bob da ha ha.
Can I grab him?
You can.
I just go up to him.
I put my right hand on a collar of a shirt.
My left hand, I grab one of the belts he's wearing
and I just lift him up over my head.
And as you do that, you feel a hot pinch
on the back of your neck.
And we, me and you, Luke, we see Judge Ephraim Courtland freeze.
Multiple shiny limbs extend from the small metal sphere
and slam into the wooden floor beneath you,
giving it the leverage it needs to shove down
as one of its appendages slices into the soft tissue
on the back of Judge Ephraim Courtland's neck.
Another snaps his head forward and you hear the fracture
as a third metal tendril reaches in,
gripping the top of Judge Courtland's spine
where it meets his head, the C1 vertebrae,
and it rips his entire spinal cord out of his body
in one swift motion, promptly forcing itself
into the now vacant spinal column of Judge Ephraim Courtland.
So this I'm gonna...
Judge Ephraim Courtland is now being controlled by M-A-R-Y.
Hell yeah.
So your goal is to make sure that there are no witnesses
to what has happened here on the property today.
There are a couple ways you can do this.
One, you can kill them.
You would be able to keep the body of Judge Courtland
if you wanted to do that and then control Courtland
whenever you wanted to around town.
It might be kind of tricky at this point.
M-A-R-Y typically likes to only control
like one townsperson at a time
and then other people that she can use for outside towns.
However, the judge would be a...
A pretty good one to have on their side.
So I could kill them or double agent style?
Yes. You could also, if they kill you,
that also works in your advantage,
but you typically don't want it.
You don't want someone else to be there
because then they'll know the secret,
and if they get away having known that, then you're fucked.
The third way is that Silas Cole, you know now,
that Silas Cole is chanting
and will continue to chant the spell
that after a couple rounds will open up a portal
in the floor of this room, the middle room of this house.
You know that there is a back room, which is the kitchen,
a front room, which is the living room,
and then the middle room, which is your guys' bedroom,
and the portal can be in front of both doors
on one side of the room.
And it's in the bedroom?
Yeah, so if they come in too quickly and they fail a check.
They get portaled.
This technicolor portal.
Okay, sweet.
So those are your options.
I like my options here.
Okay, and it's gonna be their turn,
so I'm gonna let them choose what happens next.
Okay, are we still doing, this is still one episode?
Oh shit, how long have we been playing?
["Get Your Head Around My Poor Little Darling"]