Did y'all know that real human people eat mushrooms?
Those weird little fuckers
that grow out of the poop or something.
Damn, and y'all thought I was nasty.
And here you are just eating dirt fungus
like it's going out of style.
I'll take a pot of day old warm cream
any day over mud fucking mushrooms.
Speaking of fucking, y'all are listening
to the radio show that fucks the most.
694.2 PTBP.
And I am your most fuckingest host, Wolf the Dog.
I'm excited to announce a new project
for our citizens of contention.
We want to write a Delta Green scenario as a community.
Over the next few months,
we'll be having prompted writing contests
to find the best meaty chunks y'all can muster.
We'll use each round's winner to inform the next prompt
until we have enough juicy morsels
to make ourselves a narrative feast.
To get in on this tub of greasy love,
head on down to reddit.com r slash pretending to be people.
Show us what you've got and vote for your favorites
to help us choose the winners.
Is 89 episodes a long time?
Are we friends now?
Would a friend throw a wolf a fucking bone
and slap those follow buttons on Twitter and the Instagrams?
Would a friend take it a step further
and spend a minute typing up a five-star review
on Apple podcasts?
If you do, I might read it on air
like I'm about to read this review
from Hello Under Dash Cerise entitled Best Wolf Ever.
They right.
Listen, y'all.
This here actual play role-playing podcast
is really creative and might just spoil you for any others.
If you don't know what Delta Green is,
you're in for a treat.
Imagine X-Files meets Lovecraft meets Night Vale,
except the agents are pretty terrible at their jobs.
But actually, really, the best part is Wolf the dog
as the intro DJ.
In the very many large, numerous amounts
of new music tracks he plays every week.
Hell yeah, baby.
Finally, some recognition for all the damn hard work I do,
especially when it comes to seeking new music out.
I don't know what all those things you listed are,
but I assume that they meant that you think
that this weird podcast is good?
I wouldn't fucking know.
Never listened to a second of it personally.
This was one of 234 tasty reviews.
And when we hit 311 on Apple Podcasts, I'll tell you what.
Every person who has typed up a sweet treat of a review
will be entered in a drawing
to win a pretended to be people t-shirt.
That's right, folks.
The merch is real.
It's just that you have to win a drawing
to get your mitts on these shits.
Until my producer figures out how the fuck
the internet works, same, honestly,
then it'll be for sale.
And remember, most of those 234 reviews weren't written.
They just hit the fifth star,
which still makes Wolfie smile.
But you must write a review to be entered into the contest.
Also, that makes each of your chances
of winning one of these sick teas that much greater.
So get in on it while the getting's good.
Do y'all remember my dog, Wolf, the dog?
Today, I found him sitting at a little desk
with a microphone and sunglasses on.
It looked like he had some kind of broadcasting kit.
What the fuck?
Where the fuck did he get sunglasses from?
Time for the most stable part of this here reality.
It is the news.
Last time, John Lee Kevin Moore the Thirth
let slip to Anne Love that he is not, in fact,
her former partner from K-Cell,
but rather he is, in fact, one of the vectors
K-Cell was tasked with destroying.
Anne then put an impossibly clean blade into John's head
and with a chant continued to move it deeper
into this cranium down into his throat
before eventually ending his life.
For a sweet, sweet moment.
In the muddy, ankle-deep, fish-infested overflow
of Bean's pond.
Clark did what he could, but it just seems like
this Anne Love is one resilient fucker.
Round and round and round she goes.
Will she stop?
Nobody knows.
There's only one thing I do know
and that's that I put my trust in kudzu with no backbone.
Quick behind the GM screen here at the top of episode 89.
Thomas, you might find this interesting.
Clark, he, oh, no, your name is Joe.
And, fuck, we're deep in it now.
We're so deep in it, my notes here for the last episode say
if Anne finds out that John is ball
she will make an excuse to walk away
to chant over her blade,
make them roll alertness to hear that
before attacking John.
Yeah, see, we're totally railroaded.
I think something in my mind was just like,
you know what, he's probably just gonna fucking tell her.
And then instead of having to make an excuse to go away
you guys are like, hey, can we have a minute?
Yeah.
Will you walk away and chant over your blade real fast?
We gotta talk.
Take all the time you need.
That was a really good Anne Love impression.
I gotta admit, both Clark and Joe were surprised
that Kevin did tell her about ball.
That popped out of nowhere.
Well, yeah, it did.
That's because I completely forgot
that we weren't telling her who I was.
That you were John, right, right, right.
Too many secrets and lies, man.
Oh, actually that's what, season two, no secrets, no lies.
No repercussions, no secrets, no lies.
We'll still fuck it up, don't worry.
Yeah.
I mean, if you guys were just truthful with everyone
right off the bat, you wouldn't have to keep track
of all your lies.
It's more or less what I was attempting there.
Radical honesty.
I gotta get this off my chest.
Well, she sure knew a lot about ball.
You know that thing, me and my, you and my dad
were sent to contention to take care of, I'm one of them.
Let's see, the note in the green box said they got
nine of 12, so I guess that's 10 of 12 now.
What the fuck, what the fuck?
I don't remember the note, I got a final note.
That was like episode five or six, I mean.
Holy shit, yeah, it was like over a year and a half ago.
And that's just in release time, not when we actually played.
It's funny, here, this is a page from back
when we first started of what my notes looked like.
Very detailed, so detailed, so many words on the page.
This was last session, and that was the entire session
was this bottom quarter of a page and then two sentences
at the top of the next.
That's fair, as you've lost sanity, you've also lost
all motivation to keep track of the events of this game.
Here was a good day, at some point I just wrote
like four notes on a page and then went to the next page
for the next session.
Here's me getting theomania, belief you are a god.
Yep, is that the last note you took?
Oh, nope, oh my god.
Oh yes, that is righteous.
That was my god phase.
Then it's back to normal notes.
My notes for last episode have a ton of stuff.
We didn't do any of it, except for that one,
the chant over her blade before attacking Jon.
I found what we'd written down, what I wrote down
for what was found in the storage lockers.
And I wrote like bricks of cocaine, a burlap sack,
lots of cash, and then it just says lots of great shit.
And then it skips down, it says three notes on a table.
I don't describe those notes.
Three notes on a table?
If you would ask me if there were three notes on a table
in that fucking green box, I'd be like, no,
there weren't just three notes sitting on a table
that we didn't like.
Do you want me to tell you what they were?
I wrote three notes on a table,
including newspaper clipping about Cole's orphanage,
which has recently been brought up,
which is kind of cool that I just read that.
Well, it keeps getting, yeah, I mean,
they did a shitty job of erasing it from history
because everybody's fucking talking about it.
Let's see, one is a note that says the cabin
is in the woods, stark west from the end of the trail,
about 2.5 miles, signed K.
Okay, so we investigated that.
But then it also says, we took care of nine of them
as well as the leader.
That's the one I didn't remember just now.
I remember it phrased like that,
didn't think they were talking about ball babies.
Yeah, there's another one that says
the work is difficult in particular,
but I've had 12 successes.
Life isn't as complex as they believe.
They are quite simple.
It will be their downfall.
And then finally, the newspaper ad from 25 years ago
for Kohl's Orphanage, new school under modern etiquette.
Which we did end up asking somebody about
and they did tell us about it a little bit.
We've talked about Kohl's a number of times with people.
Kohl's Orphanage is the orphanage
that John Lee Pettymore came from.
It also was, I believe you asked Drew
to look up information on it
and he couldn't find any information.
Right.
However, Randy Angst, the first time you talked to him,
had a distinct memory of an orphanage
existing under that name.
And then did we learn,
we learned more about it in the woods arc, right?
Certainly out of character.
That was a big part of the Ken Krenkelhoff story.
Yup, yup, yup.
Yup, yup.
Ken might be chilling in a door somewhere, even to this day.
I believe that door, along with the rest
of the cabin was set on fire.
Oh, that's right.
Yup, nevermind. Poor door boy.
Poor door boy.
Krenkelhoff door boy.
Well, do you guys want to get into this?
Yeah, let's hit it.
John Lee Pettymore the first body is like,
oh, okay, that seems about right.
Sorry.
I think Thomas might be calling me.
I'm on Do Not Disturb right now.
So I'll have to look at my phone
to see if he's actually calling me.
No, he's calling Luke.
For sure he's calling Luke.
Luke didn't pick up because he's too busy playing.
Do you have your phone set on Do Not Disturb?
Oh no, I don't.
It should be ringable.
No, it's ringing.
Hello?
Hey, follow me.
Off mic.
Oh, they're just walking away from their microphones.
They could just turn off their microphones,
but they've decided to take their headphones off
and walk away from their cameras.
Oh, I can hear them actually.
Oh, I can absolutely hear what they're talking about.
Thomas is so fucking loud, it's crazy.
He just asked Joe.
He just told Joe that he has 15 luck
and that he can spend 10 to have a vision.
And he asked Joe what would be the most
prudent information to learn.
Go lie down right there now.
Now they're back.
Oh.
I was narrating the phone call for our listeners
because you left your microphones on.
And Thomas is really loud,
so I could hear his side of the conversation.
Oh yeah, look, it's really plain and audacity.
Shit, it's like, yeah, it's totally all there.
Fuck, all right.
Well, now I'm actually gonna leave the room for a second
so you guys can just talk to each other on mic
if you wanna do that. Nice try.
He made a big show of pulling out his earphones,
but we know he's been on speaker this whole time.
The earphones aren't what's plugged in, it's his earbuds.
Those are just decoy earphones.
Did you guys have a good conversation?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Wouldn't you like to know?
Why don't you just check the track and find out?
We should have said like, fuck you, Zach, or some shit.
That would actually be really funny.
I like listening to the conversations you guys have
when I've left,
because typically in the middle of the episode,
you forget that I'm gonna listen back to him.
So when you guys just keep talking about
how much you love me and appreciate that I'm doing this,
it's like, joke's on you.
We're just trying to get you
to treat our characters well.
We know you're listening.
Well, speaking of which.
We're just trying to earn a favor.
John Lee Pettymore, the thirst body
is in a fucking waterbed grave,
and Clark is standing behind it,
and you can see the hilt of this blade
sticking up out of the water above the head.
And right ahead of that is Anne Love,
whose wry smile is just sitting
as it always seems to be underneath a single eye.
You've seen the other eye in action
when her hair gets tousled about.
Like, she has two eyes.
We're not worried about that, but.
I wasn't until now.
Yeah, why do you?
You're being really suspicious.
We're not worried about that.
About how many eyes this person has.
She's a cyclops.
Is it more or less than two?
Ooh, there's the question for anyone with bangs, honestly.
Spider Anne has as many eyes as a spider does.
It literally would have rhymed.
How many eyes do spiders have?
Luke, look that up.
All right, so.
He's having his own fun.
Yeah, but I miss him.
Oh, me too.
I mean, I get to spend time with him,
but I still miss him and his terrible, terrible internet.
Are you dating him?
Are you dating Luke?
Are you dating Luke, dude?
Don't tell my ex-girlfriend.
Are you dating?
That's not our joke.
Oh, fuck, I always forget that that's like
the stapled, good joke, Scott Ockerman.
All right, so.
Okay, nice deflection.
But for real, dude, are you dating Luke?
We're not supposed to tell anyone about it.
I fucking knew that something like this
would tear the podcast apart.
You get the five of us together
and eventually somebody's not gonna be able
to keep it in their pants.
And I'm surprised, I'm surprised at you, Zach.
Luke, I expected.
Joe, sure, Justin, of course, but you?
Taylor said she'll only let me keep doing it
if she takes Luke's spot
and plays Keith Vigna the rest of the time.
Okay, cool.
I don't know, a chick?
You don't know any?
I'd like to spend 10 luck to have a vision.
Oh, okay, cool.
What, that's crazy.
Thomas, you can spend 10 luck to get a vision?
That's nuts.
Fuck yeah, dude.
How much luck do you have?
Well, I have 15 because I spent 10 of my 25
to avoid major damage.
Hell yeah.
And I'm still hanging on with one hit point here.
You see one weak finger rise up from the pavement
from a shattered body.
It's all he can muster,
but you see life in John Lee Pettymore
as he urges you to wait a minute as he has this vision.
Okay, yeah, that seems perfect.
Joe, take off your headphones, I suppose,
unless you already know what the question
he's gonna ask is.
I don't 100%, I'll play it like that.
Take them off.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, Thomas.
Where's the book?
Your entire face is underwater
and typically your eyes would roll back
into your head during one of these,
but as you lift a finger and begin finding yourself in ball,
you seem to have the ability to reach out
into the collective unconsciousness of the entire universe
to pick out certain memories that exist
from people throughout different times.
And you see Gary Daley ushering Eunice and Jerry Bishop
into the back of the Daley Fuh,
and you see him passing this book to the bishops.
The book is covered in uncured leather
with some hairs, maybe some acne.
There's some stretch marks on the binding of this book
and he hands it to him and then reality begins
to kind of fade up and blink and turn
like you're turning channels on a television.
And then you're inside the bishop home.
And you see Eunice and Jerry,
they're talking about this book that they have
just sitting on their kitchen table
and they're sitting on either side
discussing options, seemingly.
And a young Clark Bishop walks into the room
and quickly, Jerry gets up and is like, oh, no, no, no,
and sits him in front of the TV
where Wheel of Fortune is on.
Memories kind of fade, reality blinks out again,
and you see Eunice and Jerry at the television.
It's in this entertainment center.
They move the television out of the way
and there's a false bottom of this entertainment center
and there's a safe with an alphabetical keypad entry.
And you're just watching them open it up.
What code did they punch in?
I'm not gonna give you the code.
You asked where the book is, not how to get it.
I'll fight you for it.
All right, come over here.
I could use some human touch.
That's not Luke's, I mean my wife's.
You're Luke's.
And you see them punching a code,
but the camera is just on their faces
as they're typing it in.
Oh, great.
Listen, Zach, I've seen enough below deck
to know how this is gonna go with Luke.
So you just need to end it now to keep things professional.
Otherwise we're gonna tear this whole organization apart
with sex and recriminations.
This thing was doomed the second you put two feisty,
hot 20 somethings in it like me and Luke, baby.
Yeah.
You know when we started,
Joe, Justin and I were hot 20 somethings as well.
Of course this was years ago.
In the before times.
And they placed the book in this safe
in the false bottom of this entertainment center
and they close the door and click lock
and you see them look at each other and they embrace.
And then you're back under this muddy, murky water
right outside of Bean's Pond.
And the year is whatever year it is.
2000.
I'm gonna bring Joe back.
Hi, I'm back.
Hey, Joe.
Hello.
Clark and Anne are just staring at each other
waiting for John to be done with his vision.
John is still weakly holding up his finger
and he starts to writhe in the water and
Don't you touch him, man, don't you touch him.
And Anne is looking down at him with massive eyes,
just so confused.
And he rolls over on his side.
John, John.
I know where your book is, Anne.
That's a nice try.
Okay, I guess we'll persuade.
10.
How?
Well, I'm something of a savior
and I have the second sight as part of that whole package.
He's not lying about that, Anne.
I've seen him see things before.
I can see into moments into the past
or rather moments into the not now.
And well, I saw a whole little saga of the book,
but
Tell me now.
Well, it is at Clark's parents' house,
but you'll never find it without me.
What do you want?
Well, when we find the book,
I want you to teach us the spell
to help us get through that door.
Okay, neither one of you are gonna be armed
and I'm gonna walk behind you with two guns.
No. One on each of you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Other way around maybe.
Well, why would I trust you?
After all this, you think I'm gonna trust you?
You're the one who's trading the book for your life
essentially right now.
I'm the one with a gun pointed at your head.
I reload my gun.
Just so you know, in this mud,
you've kind of turned over.
You're on your back now.
You've got a massive knife going all the way down
through your skull, touching your uvula,
and she has a gun pointed at you.
And you reach for your gun?
Yes.
Good call.
Okay, no guns.
We all leave them here.
Wow, what if we just all had guns?
This is gonna end in a bloodbath if you don't...
Can we not?
This town is full of fanatics and freaks,
and you know, you've got your magic,
but I'd rather have my gun.
You know, a lot of people are trying to find us.
I mean, you do have a knife.
We're not joking about that yet.
Okay.
It's cool that you can talk normally though.
All right, so everyone has their guns
and we'll just all be good
because we both need each other to get this done,
hopefully by the end of the episode.
Can you get your knife out of my head?
I don't know if that's a great idea.
For bleeding's sake,
I mean, I'd rather have my knife back, you know,
but it doesn't seem like you'll survive
and I now need you, unfortunately.
You're magic, but something tells me
you probably don't know any healing.
Oh, that's a good point.
No, I could do that.
Could you throw a little bit of that my way
and then you could maybe have your knife back?
It's really hard.
This is a very big knife
and it's hard to hold my head up with it.
She kind of crouches down on the ground.
There's just enough of the knife sticking out.
There's just enough of the blade sticking out at the top
to where she can wiggle her fingers in
and she begins cutting right in between two of her fingers,
just enough to get blood to start coming out.
And then she starts chanting,
Dem artai rat, dem artai rat, dem artai rat.
On the last one,
she pulls the knife all the way up out of your head.
And with a chant, the blood that comes out of her hand
forms like a jackhammer tube of coagulation
straight down into your throat
and you can taste Anne loves blood.
Both of you roll sanity.
Oh no.
Oh ho ho ho ho.
Fail, 48.
Fail, 78 on an eight.
What's your power there?
My power?
Oh, fuck me, dude.
It's a 60.
So I rolled over my power.
We were all gonna be...
This may work in our advantage.
Yeah, show her Clark's a wild card.
Fucking maybe, but this episode was gonna be fine.
It was about to happen.
Okay, you're both gonna lose a D4.
Oh, for real?
For blood magic.
One.
That puts a column of blood through the entire head.
I'm at 15.
Two.
I lose two and that puts me at my breaking point.
All right.
That means you break, right?
That means it's time for a new mania.
What a time for it.
What a time to be a fan of this podcast.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Listeners, I'm glad you're here with us right now.
This is...
We were so close.
Everything was gonna be all right.
What the...
So, it's time to roll, baby.
Oh, fuck me.
It's still time to roll, baby.
Oh boy.
Sample mania's table from Call of Cthulhu, 7th edition.
D100, three times.
94?
94 is theomania.
God damn it.
The belief that he or she is a god.
Hey, you get a second chance.
So, we meet again.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
A 62?
62 is gonna be legiro mania,
an uncontrollable compulsion to make loud or shrill noises.
No, thank you.
We don't need to roll.
I'll take that one.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Fuck you.
And the last one.
51.
51 is gonna be gymnomania.
Is that nudity?
Yes, it is indeed.
It is a compulsion with nudity.
Oh boy.
Oh, I didn't wanna take the belief in God thing
because I was so fucking bad at it before,
but I also don't wanna be taking my clothes off all the time.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Joe, what an opportunity you've been given
here at this stage.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, no, 100%.
I know that right now would be a really good time
for Clark to think that he's a god
because we are in overseer territory.
I just worry that it's hard for me to play it sometimes
because how does a god decide,
how does a god go somewhere else
when people wanna go somewhere else?
You know what I mean?
It's hard sometimes.
I'll try it, I'll try it.
That's all that anyone's asking.
No one listens to this fucking show anyway.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, I'm gonna do it.
I once again believe that I am a god.
Yes, you do.
How hard do you believe it?
Also, remember that each one of these manias,
it strips away Clark Bishop's being.
Clark is no longer who he was when he started.
He's been taken over, especially with this one.
So much of Clark's self was dictated
by his almost nonchalance.
However, I mean, you got that big overseer dick energy, dude.
Spread it around, slap it on the table.
Bring it out betwixt the robes opening.
Yeah, I got it, you got it.
But also that would be a compulsion of nudity,
so whatever.
I pick both, I pick both, I pick both.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Hey, how much did Anne Love fail me for?
Oh, let me roll.
Oh, you get a D6.
Five.
Fuck yeah.
So I'm at six.
So the thing that sent me over the edge
was seeing her cut her finger with the blade in his head.
So I'm gonna lash out at her and try and,
I want to wrestle the knife away from her.
And I'm yelling, what the fuck is that?
Fucking knife, blood magic, fucking shit.
Like rushing her now.
Okie dokie, that'll be unarmed combat.
I pass a 41 on a 70.
She passed with a 36.
Yes.
She pulls the large knife up out of John Lee Pettymore's
head as she finishes this incantation.
And before she knows it, you're just on her.
And you grab the knife out of her hand,
screaming about blood magic.
And she just jumps back and she's like,
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's literally healing.
It's my blood.
It's healing him.
What the fuck is your problem?
It's not, it's not, it's not right.
That's not, that's not something a person
should be able to do.
Too fucking bad.
Clark, I will say that personally at this moment,
I have no objections.
Are you, are you, are you you?
Are you all right?
Are you you?
It was her blood that went inside of you.
Yeah, I know.
She gave me a well, a well, a much needed transfusion.
I feel better.
I feel better, Clark.
I don't, I don't, I don't like, I don't like any of this.
This is, this is, this is,
this isn't the way it's supposed to be.
This isn't the way it's supposed to happen.
Clark, man.
None of this is the way it was supposed to happen.
No, I'm pretty sure this is exactly
the way it was supposed to happen.
Now we talked about guns, but I really,
I would appreciate the knife back,
but you seem to have a whole look in your eyes
right now.
So just by the time we get to your parents' house,
can we call it that still?
Then I would like to have that knife back
if that's possible.
I'll think about it, but I'm holding onto it for now.
That was, that was freaky.
That was freaky shit.
Does Clark have a gun?
I don't technically.
Can I fish another water?
Oh, you dropped it?
Yeah.
Yeah, and as you pick it up out of the water,
it's water-locked, so you're just kinda like.
All right, and Clark's gonna hold onto the knife
and you're gonna drop your gun here in the pond with ours.
Oh, so we are going no guns?
I thought we were going all guns.
I've, your mouth is kinda like a gun.
What?
She says spells and stuff to make people get hurt.
All right.
She's kinda got a built-in gun.
Well, it helped too.
I need pills.
I need, I need strong pills.
Do you have any of those at your house, Clark?
I mean, there's a chance I got something there,
but I could just top you up right now, right here.
Here, just come here, just come here.
What?
He crawls, he crawls a little bit towards you.
I put my hand on his head on the wound
and I try to heal him.
Clark tries to heal him.
Okay.
John Lee Pettymore starts praying.
Yeah.
It's like, no, I get it, I get it.
Through crest, all things are possible.
Is there a roll that I could make to-
Go ahead and roll unnatural.
I passed.
It's a 31 on a 49.
Whoa, I forgot we had good unnatural scores.
This game is broken wide open.
Joe?
Yeah.
Some words pop into your mind
and you know that if you can spill some blood
and say these words, that you can make it happen.
I've got the knife in my hand still.
So I take a page out of the book that I just saw
and love demonstrate for me.
And I do a little cut on the side of my thumb.
So it's kind of dripping a little bit.
And I say, damn all to year it.
Damn all to year it.
And as you finish saying the last one,
the blood just like flows out of your thumb
and goes up into the nostrils
and the mouth of John Lee Pettymore.
And you see the ooze pouring from his eyes
and his ears and his mouth
and the blood flowing on top of the ooze
into all of his orifices.
Go ahead and roll a D six.
It's a one.
Joe, every little bit helps.
And I just want to say you started this
by losing your goddamn mind over and love
cutting yourself on that knife to heal me.
And you ended it by fucking getting the courage
to do that yourself.
So I'm really proud of you, man.
Joe Clark and just Clark needs to roll sanity on this one
due to your change of pace and mindset
and your shocking ability to be able to do this yourself.
That's a fail.
And that's going to be another D four.
Fuck me, dude.
It's a 79.
It's over my power.
Fuck, and I rolled a four.
Fuck me, dude.
How much do you have left?
I got two, baby.
Oh my God.
Oh, okay.
Upon seeing that it fucking worked,
Clark's mind like starts to fracture
and he pulls the knife away and yells, it worked.
It's what I was always meant to be.
We don't need you anymore, Anne.
We don't need you anymore.
And I go right after her with the knife.
Yes!
Hey, Joe.
Yeah.
How much luck do you have?
A lot.
Do you need to know an exact number?
No, I don't, but this just seems like a good opportunity
if you wanted to literally spend all of your luck points
to determine the outcome of this fight.
You can also just spend luck points to change a roll.
You could also do that.
Don't let him, don't let him.
This is, you're talking to the devil right now.
And he's like, hey, Joe, give me all your luck.
You don't have to do that.
I'm just saying.
There's a lot of things you can do
in this fight with that luck.
Instead of having to roll against me,
who crits constantly during combat,
you could just spend all of your luck
and decide exactly how you finish off
and love in this moment.
You do only have two sanity, so.
Yeah.
And I do want to, I do kind of want to finish her off.
You know where the book is.
You told us you know where the book is, right?
Yeah, I'm going to try and finish her off.
I'm going to spend my hefty bank of 65 luck.
Holy shit.
And I'm going to call this like it is,
Clark rushes her with unnatural strength.
Oh yes, he does.
In a flash is on her and he just wants to shove,
he wants to do to her what she did to John.
He wants to bring the knife down through her head.
And that's exactly what happens.
Clark rushes her with eyes akimbo,
knowing what he has always been
and was always meant to be
and jumps up in the air with a dagger in both hands
and comes down on top of Anne Love's head,
whose eyes are so wide because she's never seen anyone
pick up any sort of unnatural ability A at all,
B that quickly or C without any sort of training whatsoever.
And you come down and pierce the top of her skull.
And as you shove the knife into the top of her head,
you see one of her eyes directly starts looking
into your eyes and the other one just fills completely
with blood and the blood begins pouring down her face.
She stops breathing and you stand back
and she wobbles forward, backward, forward.
And the knife still in her skull,
she just falls back into the overfilled beans pond.
And begins floating out into the middle
of the mushroom shaped pond.
Holy shit, Clark, that was awesome.
We should go and get that book.
Yeah, you haven't changed furniture, have you?
As a matter of fact, no, why do you ask?
Woo, okay, it'll make more sense when we get there.
I'm not gonna tell you in case you decide to and love me.
Yeah, let's go.
As Clark Bishop and John Lee Pettymore the third
trudge north through the town of contention,
heading up through the warehouse district,
pass subtropolous and all of downtown
on the west side of A plus storage
where you found the storage units G10, G11, and G12
filled with, what was the quote, cool stuff.
Lots of cool shit.
Awesome things.
Past Julie Maxwell's apartment building.
I've got a really, really dumb story.
There was a local trucking company
that had this like billboard on I-44
and it had like a picture of an electric guitar
and like a motorcycle and like a baseball bat
and in really big letters, it said cool stuff.
And in really small letters, it said trucks bring it.
But it was really hard to see the trucks bring it part.
So it just looked like a dope billboard for cool stuff.
I remember that billboard.
I totally remember it.
That's like an intimidating thing
for like a sports team called the trucks.
Trucks bring it.
Oh, the trucks is such a good name
for an American sports team.
The trucks would be so good.
Holy shit.
Oh my God, your mascot could be like a dude
inside a blow up semi.
It could literally just be a dude fucking
like tearing up your field in a tricked out like F-150.
They could bring out like a fake field to put on top.
That's how fields work, right?
Yeah, for sure, fake field.
When it rains, they pull out the fake field
at baseball games.
I was 17 years old and I was playing Ultimate Frisbee
at the park that's across the street
from our double A stadium here in Springfield
where the Springfield Cardinals play.
And it was raining and a few of us thought
to ourselves, there's a game tonight, isn't there?
So the tarps probably on the field.
And so we ran and we jumped the fence
and we ran down the third base side
and we hopped onto the field.
And I slip and slid from third base
over the mound towards first.
And then took off running and security yards chased me
for like a block, but I was more agile back when I was 17.
And it's still one of my greatest memories.
It's honestly very cool.
Yeah, Zach, that's a lot cooler
than my story about a billboard.
But also I saw that billboard and I was like,
oh, that's so cool.
And as you pass Julie Maxwell's apartment,
you look up and see a billboard that has an electric guitar
and a baseball bat.
And what else was it?
It was like a convertible and like a basketball.
I remember the basketball and the electric guitar.
I could see both of those pictured perfectly.
And for some reason, all this billboard says is
trucks bring it.
Well, yeah, we haven't talked about the local
rookie league baseball team outside of town, the trucks.
The trucks, the contention trucks.
John weakly says, trucks bring it.
He's got season tickets.
And as you're trudging through contention,
you hear screams coming from the East
and you can echo locate well enough here in contention
to know that these screams are coming from
the first church of contention as you're heading North
up towards Clark Bishop's home.
Does it sound like a lot of screams?
It sounds like a lot of screens, tens of screens.
Is it loud enough that we would stop in our tracks for it?
It's not something we're just catching a whiff of
on the air.
Off in the distance about when you hit A plus storage,
you start hearing it and it's just.
Just shit like that.
I don't want you to go there.
I just want us to feel bad about not going there.
Just enough.
Yeah.
John, I think if we stay the course,
the whole point of our mission here is that overseer
will come back and I'll save everyone.
I don't think there's anything that's going to help us
by helping them now.
If they just are released into a world full of this goo,
we need, we need me and myself.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm still pretty knife brained buddy.
So I'm in no position to run off
and save a bunch of people at this church.
I think we need all the help we can get.
All right.
And those pills, did you say you had pills?
You didn't have pills.
What was the deal with that?
I gave you, I gave you, I gave you health.
I healed you.
The one, okay.
If I took an aspirin or something.
I genuinely forgot it was just for one.
No, I healed you.
I healed you.
Good job, buddy.
Thank you.
Let's go, let's go, let's go get that book.
Let's go get that book.
Yeah, we just keep going.
Clark, your home.
How's it look?
Well, as you're approaching,
you do notice that the creek
that runs kind of behind your house, dry, completely dry.
But the home itself looks the exact same
as you left it yesterday.
Yeah, I opened the door.
That familiar smell just wafts right up through your nose.
And it's almost unseemly
because you're not the man you were who lived here.
John, welcome to my parents' house.
I guess it's mine, but is this what you need?
Is this where the book could be?
Yeah, I think so.
No drugs is what we decided.
There's no drugs here.
Joe, go ahead and roll luck.
Fuck you.
That's my favorite joke that I've done on this podcast.
That one's just for the GM.
Some of them gotta be.
Clark, not even like wine or anything?
Definitely not.
There might be a beer or two in the fridge.
Please bring me two, one, two drink
and one, two press to my head.
I do, I go to the fridge and grab a couple beers.
Okay, you need to move the TV.
Just take it off the stand.
Oh, okay.
And I go and do that.
I just, I guess, pluck it up and put it down on the ground.
Is that it, John?
You don't see a door?
Nope, the TV's on the ground now.
What do we do?
God damn it, ow.
Okay, I don't know, really try poking around in there.
Is it just a flat top where this TV's staying?
I just kinda start smacking on it.
When you start smacking on it,
it kinda like wobbles a little bit.
Two corners stay put and the other two corners kinda wobble.
Oh, I got something here, it's moving.
And you can remove the entire flat wood piece
from underneath the television.
I do so.
And underneath, there's the door of a safe
that has an alphanumerical keypad.
I think maybe the Wheel of Fortune letters
or maybe your name or some other bullshit
that meant something to your parents, I don't know.
Clark is gonna remember that his mother always told him
that I was born with the best letters.
Clark always remembers.
Yeah.
It's only three in the morning.
It's shocking you can't remember this.
Yeah, he's gonna put in R-S-T-L-N-E.
And the door unlocks.
Yeah.
And when it opens, you see a book inside
that is made out of uncured leather
and it's got like hair on it.
Some pimples, maybe a rash.
There's stretch marks on the spine.
I found my book, Jon.
I grab it and hold it up.
And as soon as you grab it.
Yeah, I was worried about that.
All right, you guys can stop recording.
Oh, you son of a bitch.
Do I really stop recording right there?
No.
Oh shit, okay.
Your eyes go blank and suddenly you're standing
in the abandoned water park, Splashylvania.
You're looking up at the two-fanged plunge.
Julie Maxwell fires a bullet
that tears through the body of Leo Piston.
You raise your firearm and immediately put lead
in the crazed Julie Maxwell's forehead.
The two bodies begin slumping down the twin slides,
leaving a trail of blood behind.
You blink.
You're standing in the suburbs in the middle of the street
in front of Dr. Marie Jacobs' house.
You see James the mill worker floating off the ground,
Aiden and Alice Little are bravely holding a vacuum
to this hovering man's feet.
But from out of the vacuum bag erupts an oily black ooze
that immediately encompasses the twin children.
And you can see them fighting violently
inside the muck that envelops them.
When you look over at Jon,
you see the same viscous sludge is dripping
from every hole in his face.
You blink.
You're staring at a gaunt young boy.
The two of you are hanging in a cage
above a deprived and debaucherous crowd.
The cage is shocking you, burning your skin
as the ceiling of this juice box lowers slowly.
You don't wanna do it.
You don't wanna push him back in,
but either one of you dies or you both die.
You push the boy's body back into the plexiglass room
just in time for the roof to come down,
squeezing the boy pulp onto the ravenous audience below.
You blink.
You're all over the CSU campus.
This one's a rapid fire montage,
murder after murder after murder,
finishing off with your own,
your own yourself ending screwdriver plunge.
You blink.
You're standing outside of Bean's pond,
an ankle deep muddy overflow,
and you know what you are capable of.
You know what you are and you scream
as you jump and bury the knife in your hands
down through the skull of Anne Love,
the woman who murdered your parents.
You blink.
You're back standing in your parents' living room.
You look down and your hands are covered in blood
and the blood begins moving,
collecting between the covers of this book
made from human skin,
and the blood begins forming pages,
each page a result of your actions.
Roll Sanity.
It's going to be a one slash one D six plus one.
Don't pass.
31 on a two.
Roll a D six.
Real quick, Joe,
did you hear how Zach just like rattled off
all the Bishop murders?
Total like basic true crime bitch.
I forgot I forgot.
I forgot to tell Thomas to take his headphones off.
Yeah, it was like,
it seems like I shouldn't be hearing this,
but I'm glad I did.
It was a trip down memory lane.
I rolled a one.
I swear it's a oneer.
So I cling, isn't there like a thing though?
Isn't it if you were at one,
it's still not good.
Well, no, it's just that the San loss for that
was a D six plus one.
Okay.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Yeah, so Clark is a,
Clark is,
he's not there.
His sanity is gone.
One of the pages flits open
and these pages that have been created
by the blood rushing from your hands form letters.
And you see these two words just repeated
over and over and over.
And in the middle is this picture of this hooded figure
with this light that is just beaming from its face.
However, in this one,
you can very clearly see your own face,
the face of a young Clark Bishop,
and you feel compelled to begin chanting,
knuckles almond, knuckles almond, knuckles almond,
knuckles almond, knuckles almond.
John Lee Pettymore, you see a flash of light
and Clark Bishop is no longer standing
in front of his entertainment center
in his living room of his parents' home.
Holy shit.
Hey Thomas.
Hey Zach.
What does John Lee Pettymore want to do?
What does he see?
Clark is just gone?
Yep.
Is the book gone too?
Does the TV turn on?
Yep.
John presses play on the VCR,
lies down on the couch,
and lets himself watch Wheel of Fortune for 20 minutes.
Clark, you're standing in a dark alleyway.
Yeah, yeah.
And walking toward you.
Is it Jim Cook?
It's Jim Cook.
Do I have any agency over this?
Do you want agency?
I mean, I know what happens.
Clark remembers.
And immediately, in the shadows,
you just pounce on him,
throw him to the ground.
And with both of your hands wrapped around his neck,
he begins struggling.
They didn't have to die.
You couldn't find it.
In your grasp, in the grip of both of your hands,
wrapped around Jim Cook's throat,
you feel his life extinguish.
Holy shit.
Oh no.
Oh my God.
What's up, what's up everybody?
It's Zach, I'm Zach.
I'm just gonna slide in here real quick
at the end of this episode to drop some pretty big news.
So Taylor and I are moving to South Korea on Thursday.
It's been our dream for years to teach English in Korea.
We're so absolutely stoked.
This long time plan is finally coming to fruition.
I know, I know you're super excited for us
and not at all wondering what is happening with the show.
Well, that's just super supportive of you.
Thank you so much.
But if you are wondering, I have some answers for you.
So first off, we've already recorded the next full arc
of season one,
and we've started recording the final arc that follows.
This campaign has enveloped my life
like a squamous viscous ooze,
and I'm not going to compromise its quality
just because I'm moving halfway around the world.
We've had a fair amount of practice recording over Zoom
at this point, so I'm not worried about anything
except that I'll have to wake up early to record now.
All MPC voices will soon become much deeper.
Next week, we'll be releasing a bonus episode
from our Patreon vault to try to coax some of you
into giving us money during a full-blown economic crisis
because we're fucking ruthless.
And the Friday after that, on August 14th,
the penultimate arc of season one
of pretending to be people begins.
I'm so gosh darn jazzed for y'all to hear it,
and I'm so pumped to play through the end of this campaign.
Ha!
Last thing, fear not.
The end of season one will not be the end
of pretending to be people.
I have delicious, insidious plans for the future.
Seriously, thank you all so much for listening.
We have such a blast making this show,
and we're so stoked y'all enjoy it.
["Get Your Head Around My Poor Little Darling"]
Get your head around the rules of howlin'
All around my poor little darlin'
I'm afraid they'll get my darlin'
["Get Your Head Around My Poor Little Darling"]
Get your head around the rules of howlin'
All around my poor little darlin'
I'm afraid they'll get my darlin'
Get your head around the rules of howlin'
All around my poor little darlin'
I'm afraid they'll get my darlin'
["Get Your Head Around My Poor Little Darling"]