Mike Smith here. Thank you again for joining us during our pledge drive this week.
You've just heard Under the Mulberry Tree with Mary Ann Kellans and we're about to get into
into a classic episode of our Smash It! Surprise, surprise Smash It!
Not everyone around here was rooting for this show but by god it's it's really
taken off. It's of course pretending to be people. An unlikely hit for 694.2
but but a hit nonetheless. I'm joined here today by Nyle Leota who...
Nyle Leota Oda. Nyle Leota I'm not gonna say the last that can't be your... Nyle Leota
Oda who who has come here and joined her. As you know me Mike Smith I've been at
this station for 35 years ever since I graduated from community college here in
contention and you know for a long time things were kind of done Mike's way but
Nyle has come in with with his uh you know his big city ideas. Listeners may
remember me from my show with my ex-wife over on KITI in the city. No one
listens to city radio. And I'm back here in contention under some interesting
circumstances but I've got a lot of great ideas to shake up the way things
we do here at 694.2 PTBP. Now you're from here right Nyle? I am yes. And you were you had a
you had a I understand a successful public radio career in the city. I did
indeed. Until you were... until I came back to contention to bring my fantastic pieces to
694.2 PTBP. You didn't you didn't have a successful marriage advice show with
your wife and then you got divorced. And then let's talk about how our listeners
can support us during this pledge drive week Mike. As as you know Nyle has
brought pretending to be people to our to our station and he's brought with it
a something called a Patreon. Patreon.com slash pretending pod. Thanks Nyle. You're
welcome Mike. You know Nyle public radio to me is it's responsible reporting
twice a day you've got your morning edition and you're all things considered
and then in between you know in a small town you got a lot of time for a
traditional Celtic music for bluegrass for jazz we didn't have a lot of you
know fancy gunplay cop shows going on in this town before you got here but then
you brought us a little something called pretending to be people and people just
love it. Yes Mike. Don't they Mike? I believe that grass should be green like the color of money
speaking of which we've got a patreon at patreon.com slash pretending pod now I
want to say some new things to bring to that patreon don't you I do there's
currently a five dollar tier there and we've got some fantastic supporters at
that five dollar tier currently called honorary police officers I'd like to
give a quick shout out to three of those honorary police officers right now
Sasha S Brian C and Jasmine J thank you all so much for listening and
contributing to making sure that we can keep making PTBP at 694.2 with
pretending to be people thank you very much to everyone who has supported the
station and will continue to support it throughout this pledge drive so the
changes let's get into those are right off the bat here first off that five
dollar tier is no longer going to be called honorary police officers at five
dollars you'll still get the bonus content on a monthly basis but the name
has changed from honorary police officers to splashylvania fastpass
holder so if I'm getting this right everyone who was currently an honorary
police officer will be a splashylvania fastpass holder isn't that fun and I'm
also here to introduce not only the $10 tier but also a $15 tier and a $30 tier
but we're not stopping there we're also adding both a 50 and even a $100 tier to
keep this sinking boat afloat you think people are gonna pay $100 for your shitty
little again this is Nile Liotta Oda at 694.2 PTBP let's go ahead and
introduce this first clip from an old classic episode of pretending to be
people as you all know during pledge drives we like to play classic episodes
of your favorite public radio content and then interrupt them incessantly to
the point where they're essentially incoherent you just get a little bit and
then ten minutes of two assholes talking maybe just one and now let's cut to a
clip from an episode the listeners voted on as their favorite episode of
pretending to be people Keith Vigna's first day the four of you the contention
the four of you the contention police officers Clark Bishop John Lee
Pettymore the fourth Barry Manstein and the fresh Keith Vigna are all standing
in a vast empty field in front of this empty husk of a cow's corpse blood and
internal organs completely missing just a future leather bag of bones and the
farmer Jedediah Blechum pokes the pile of cattle skin with his cane say they've
been around about there around about come down for a week now sir well
someone's fucking with the cows again come down about a week what was that
coming down about a week or so for about a week this is the only cow
fatality that you've had or air now and he like points his cane out Vigna Vigna
why don't you wait a couple days before you start asking questions yeah let the
uh let the vets here take over the vets like Barry Manstein you look up and
Jedediah is standing about 20 yards away from you at this point and he pokes
another one you guys did you guys see these other cows see Keith if you hadn't
been so busy yep and we would have noticed these other cows how many cows
do we see at least a baker's dozen 13 no don't fucking say that number let's
start podcast is not gonna get off the ground if you keep saying 13 and then
the the farmer and his big overalls and straw hat walks back to you guys and
points his cane up at the sky many lights we come down there in about two
hey Victor Brown to this guy's overalls are almost as big as your pants am i
right guys very very goddamn very you can always find a person's exact
weakness and just hone right in on it and then pound him that's some rookie
stuff you're gonna have to get used to it with Barry Manstein hanging around
Keith Vigna he hikes his pants up just over his belly button well I just got I
just got done with cop school in the city and uh we didn't have any bovine
crime class so I'm gonna let you guys handle this what a way to make a great
first impression as a matter of fact he that's that's brand new for us that's a
thing we've had cow mutilations around well I mean I I usually dealt with like
actual crimes in the city you know that's what actual actual crimes in the
city not like you don't think animal abuse is a crime up there in the city
vigna yeah it's a crime very bad doing me keep my business in charge if farm
you're gonna go I've been ain't no light come down there that's goddamn right
you hurt him I might as well just repeat it but I didn't because I think you
heard him very clearly vigna are you taking notes on what this guy's saying
this guy's smarter than you vigna fucking city cop I'm very smart and you
gotta get your mam and my wife and food and whatnot as you're saying this I look
at Clark and the look on my face is having no idea what this guy's saying
and I look at you for help and I take a couple steps back this is on you guys
maybe this is a learning situation you're fucking getting it everything's a
goddamn learning situation you city slick and son of a bitch I just want to
make sure that you're you're keeping your eyes on everything we do here if
there's anything you can learn from us I want you to put it down in that notebook
there how's your bigger understands what I'm saying you know you gotta get it
over there right there that's right now sir how many of your cows lie mutilated
in this field that baby doesn't jerk
so yeah nile that's that's your new show that you've brought here obviously that
is an hour of bluegrass we won't get each week that brings us down to
approximately 12 hours of bluegrass a day which I personally think is the
right amount of bluegrass for our listeners on all of the polls that we've
done yeah you haven't gone down to to Joe's coffee and ask the people there
what they're listening to in the morning the people at beans on beans know what
I'm talking about shout out to everyone down at beans on beans and my new
morning hotspot the donut hole is I haven't been downtown in 30 years since
it was revitalized as are these contention businesses these are
fantastic contention businesses with owners like Duncan Hole do you want a
laugh line there Nile pretending to public radio is a damn I'm sorry folks
public radio is a responsibility Nile it's not cheap entertainment it's not
it's not cops you know it's not America's most wanted it's jazz and
bluegrass damn it at least it isn't in this state it's okay intern if we could
get some tissues in here for Mike I'm fine I'm fine why don't you tell us
about your patreon tears absolutely I would be very excited to do that so
let's wipe away some of those te ars tears and get hyped up for some new TI
er s tears over on patreon.com slash pretending pod just to reiterate if you
are currently pledged at $5 a month the only change is your name as a
splashylvania fast pass holder you will still have access to the exclusive
monthly bonus content in the form of an audio episode what happened to the title
of honorary police officer you ask well we thought it was a better fit for the
rewards offered in our brand-new $10 tier now patrons who pledged $10 a month
become honorary police officers and will not only have access to the exclusive
monthly bonus content but they will also have the opportunity to submit the name
and description of an NPC and a location these submissions will be drawn at
random and used in the show pretending to be people well now Nile normally we
don't agree but it makes a lot of sense for the people who get to participate to
be honorary police officers and for that to move to the $10 tier instead of the
$5 tier thank you so much for saying that Mike it's maybe the one good idea
you've ever had oh that brings joy to my heart and with joy I'd like to move on
and tell you about the $15 tier at patreon.com slash pretending pod people
who pledge $15 a month will join the den of sin that sounds inappropriate now
Nile tell me what that is people who pledge at the $15 level will have access
to a monthly live stream of the pretending to be people crew recording
their patreon bonus content and that will include a hangout after for about
an hour hour and a half who knows how long it could go and they'll be playing
games answering questions it's going to be a bonafide uncanny hootenanny a
binging shindig for those of you who want a behind-the-scenes look at the
process or who'd want to kick it with the pretending to be people crew this
tier is for you again that is the $15 a month tier the den of sin quick shout
out to three more of our patrons who've been with us keeping this show going
Jack M Garth H and will G thank you all so much for pledging yes thank you will
G now back to the episode back to that episode that you all voted on is your
favorite pretending to be people episode keys first day walking through
this endless field of corn the four of you contention police officers Clark
Bishop John Lee petty more the fourth Barry Manstein and the brand-spankin new
Keith vigna you guys come across this semi truck trailer that's just sitting
in the middle of this well-planned bald spot on the head that is Jedediah
Blaschum's cornfield and he points his cane at it anybody dare to dig came down
down he's no banger and fired I hear that I hear that buddy he kind of ribs
you I rub him back vigna are you taking notes on what this guy's saying I don't
understand a single goddamn word he's saying I ran down to me he looks at
Clark Bishop man if we're gonna need you new guy fucking you're coming around
here talking shit you see how Clark's taking perfect notes on everything he
says I lean over to bury very I actually don't understand him either no
idea what the fuck this guy's saying I just want vigna to feel like shit you
hear a ting-tang-tang and Jedediah is just over at the back door of this semi
truck trailer just like banging on it with his cane he's like guys it's not
that hard to understand what this guy's saying you just look to worry banks I
think we need to go in this trailer I I go up to the back of the semi truck I
unlock it and before I open it up I hope it I open it up and then I step up
into it and go inside Jedediah takes a minute but he likes slowly is starting
to get up in and he looks back at you he's like I go over and give him a
boost and I'm getting up in there also following mm-hmm so the four of you
along with Jedediah blush and walk into this semi truck trailer and as soon as
all of you are in there the door behind you slam shut and there's a red light
that's coming from the opposite side of the trailer also this room that you're
in is square it's not the size of this in my truck trailer that you saw hold
on weren't we just in a oblong rectangle tractor trailer and now it's square what
the fuck I never encountered this kind of weirdness vigna you show up at this
goddamn job and suddenly everything goes funky well technically a ring tank
a prank take a right hey let's start yeah keep thinking I'm talking about we
got that long rectangular prism is still an oblong rectangular prism
technically a rectangle is a square I don't know ready to get a magic
Jeanette but you guys look up cool and it's completely dark in here except for
the red light coming down on all of you and Oh right above your heads you see
that there is what seems to be a gauge that is a red light slowly blinking and
each time it blinks it is lowering so it's like a battery power pack or
something that is lowering and lit in the room the only thing in this room is
a pedestal with a big red button on top and the light above you with each blink
is going okay I ripped the gauge out of the year you all remember gauging I was
at a show one time and I was standing right behind this dude who had huge
gauges and this kid just walked up with a padlock and just hooked it on this
dude's ear and ran away and the guy just chased him I will fill you in on this
they're not called gauges the gauge is the size of them yeah we all fucking know
Keith Vigna pulls out his sidearm and shoots the thing that's beeping
immediately all of your ears start ringing and nothing in the room
lightwise has changed the meter is still lowering but none of you can hear
anything as tinnitus takes over son of a bitch big no fuck don't fire your
fucking service pistol in the closed space don't you know about goddamn Rick
Shays you gave him fucking tonight I'm looking at what I just shot and I can't
hear any of this I just press the button and as soon as you press the button the
bar lights all the way back up and then continues to beep and is making its way
back down I press the button again it goes right back up to the top and
continues to go down anymore let me get onto this I push the button Barry
Manstein contingent's most decorated officer my best friend and and our
finest peer absolutely press that button thank you sir and best friend I'll
remember you forever if you promise you'll remember me forever
slap slap on that button and it goes right back up to the top continues
beeping well what if hey guys what if we let the button go down to the bottom and
instead of some of the bad happenings the door opens Jedidiah is at the
back door just trying to open it back up and he's like Jedidiah is this not your
trailer yeah so it is but you forgot okay well Clark is gonna go look at the
gauge more closely is it is it demarcated in any way is it is that the
right word demarcated does it have markings on it that indicate levels or
numbers or anything that's a great word Joe no it is simply just like just let
up the lights go back to the top and did you say it was coming out of the ceiling
yes it's coming out of the ceiling can I follow it to the top and see if it runs
to anything like a like a like a conduit go ahead and roll search it was
it was coming out of the ceiling but then I chased it in a rant fail 81 on a
20 as you're like trying to find some sort of connection between the two you
kind of trip backwards in the mostly darkness and press the button again
attaboy Clark that's what I was just trying to make sure want to make sure we
kept the button pressed that's all I was doing
Keith Vigna looks around is there anything in this trailer no it is
completely empty except for the big red button and five idiots Keith Keith you
know it's your first day why don't you go ahead and press the button yeah we'll
let you press this one but why don't you press that button press that button I
stand there button and I grab his hand and start edging it towards I don't want
to press the button but I do want to make a good impression on my new
co-workers yeah so I go up to the button and I have my hand about like a
couple inches away from it and I go and just press it a bunch of times each time
it beeps and each time light goes right back to the top Keith we said you could
press the button once can I see anything else in this room if I maybe go past the
button as you pass the button you're not sure if you walking over there triggered
this or if it just started but you feel your socks are wet and looking down you
can't quite tell if it's the red from the light or whether the liquid is red
that is slowly rising in this room and you're all stepping in a red viscous
liquid no hell welcome back welcome back to six nine four point two PT BP why
don't you think now Nile Liotta Oda I'm here with my co-host for the day Mike
Smith and we're joining I'm your host you're you're my co-host this is that's
right yeah and we're joined now by Floyd Grant our late night DJ here at six nine
four point two PT BP you're listening to the pledge drive over on patreon.com
slash pretending pod Floyd how's it going today thanks for having me Nile and
Mike it's good to see ya obviously who Floyd now it's probably a little earlier
than you're used to being here I reckon there's a whole bunch of your audience
that don't even know who I am haha yeah hey you know they tend to they
tend to they tend to hit the sack early it can get pretty lonely here being here
that late I hear you guys pitter-pattering outside the door but
nobody ever comes in to say hey we're not here when you're here I've literally
never been here oh I hear you're no easy it's very anti public radio ethos the
spirit of the effort we're all putting into this but Niles only here from nine
to five well I guess it's the janitor crew or something the janitor crew I
believe we had to cut due to costs so the trash is always empty every time I'm
in here I'll just figure that's the janitor crew and the floors are all
sopping wet and oh well you can tell they're brushing their mops against the
walls there's scratches all over the walls I try and if I see him
exterminators must have been slacking on the job or something I don't what do you
mean like a creatures getting in at night or it's here all the time you're
the only creature that gets in here at night buddy from the hours of seven to
nine obviously they do call me the creature I think you should have gotten
the memo that we do no longer have trash service you are supposed to be taking
your own trash out each night I haven't I haven't been is but it's so well it's
all family here so somebody's probably picking up your slack now why don't you
tell us about your little program you got now thank you Mike the next tier I
want to talk about is at the $30 level patrons who pledged $30 a month will
enter the circle of knowledge maintaining this pledge for six months
will unlock the reward for those in the circle of knowledge a half-hour Skype
session with the cast member of your choice from pretending to be people get
advice from Zach on running your next home game ask Joe for advice on playing
a likable PC talk to Thomas about turn-based tactical video games or
Formula One or below deck get an in-depth discussion with Justin about
anime ask Luke to help you write your new tinder bio or whatever the options
are endless in addition to all the previous tiers benefits that is an
extremely good point Mike I haven't said this yet so far but when you pledge it
any tier level you will also receive the rewards of all lower tiers again that
link is patreon.com slash pretending pod I am so delighted to announce our next
tier which is at the $50 level patrons who pledge $50 a month will join the
first Church of contention youth group after six months of maintaining this
pledge members of the first Church of contingent youth group will play in a
homebrewed Delta green one shot handled by Zach from pretending to be people on
roll 20 along with three other patrons now let's get to some shoutouts for some
of our current patrons hello there to Torin Linus B and Sam T thank you all so
much for pledging your support to PT BP 6 9 4.2 and pretending to be people yes
thank you Sam T for supporting you know this new little show that's on our our
radio station instead of every other thing we put out for you 24 hours a day
that that's got a that's got a strong sound to it I like I like that fella now
Floyd you were talking about something strange going on here in the station do
you want to elaborate on that for our listeners here well it just seems to me
we don't want Mike if you interrupt him for once do we want listeners knowing
about I think that the listeners would be very glad to know that they are every
dollar you donate to this station will go to an unhaunted radio station it's
not haunted like people are saying well we might be able to afford a janitorial
staff if we get enough money and some of these issues might be resolved you said
the floors were wet it's it's told me for a loop here that you're telling me
that the the janitors are not doing their jobs lately because they're gone
there we we had to fire them because of no money but it's not haunted but
everything is so it's like they spilled their mop buckets in some of the carpets
here and there and the floors are shiny and bright like they've been picked
clean you are a late-night DJ maybe some of your you know exuberant habits
between the hours of seven and nine
that's the tornado drill that's just the the local tornado drill sirens those
happen randomly throughout the day at all times that did not sound like a
no no no no now you see at 8 a.m. is it on top of the station they do the
tornado siren drills at Wednesdays at 8 a.m. and then also just randomly
throughout the week and now back to our classic fan favorite episode of
pretending to be people entitled can I just say before before we get back to
your nonsense it is unconscionable to suggest that the radio station is
haunted by any kind of those kinds of assumptions might be your downfall Mike
back to the episode Keith's first day
Lindsay Manstein looks down the barrel of their gun at this little green man
Ames pulls the trigger roll firearms
hell yeah that's a crit success baby no way oh shit okay roll 2d 10 for damage
the same thing you just rolled fuck off I got another another crit success 22
22 so actually we're poor damage is weirdly enough when you fire a bullet
into this tiny little green man you just obliterate him but looking out all
around the first Church of contention sanctuary you see you've got 45 more to
go exactly I look over at Keith big na big na sack up let's do this as soon as
I hear that I pull the shotgun off of my back
you fight four times yeah okay into the crowd of alien okay have Keith roll
firearms at a negative negative 40 I've got a 70 within that's a fail all right
so you just blast in and they're all like literally like jumping and four of
them that you aim at actually each time you aim at one they jump on to the top
head of the one next to them and then like the next one you aim at jumps on
top of the second one and they create this like wizard staff of small green
alien man so I had stand I hit none of them and each time they jump on top of
each other they're like and then when they're all on top they like pogo stick
away I have unloaded my shotgun and hit no one and therefore it's no longer your
turn and so yeah I take my time to put some more shotgun shells and not pay
attention to where they're going John Lee Pettymore what are you doing John
gets down on one knee oh yeah and he he takes his he takes his gun and he he
aims his service pistol at each one of those four little fucking brains on that
pogo stick and he's like die you alien scum and he pulls the trigger
firearms baby that's a crit success holy shit okay that'll take out three of
them so as they're like pogoing away from you you take out the top three and
all of their like green splatter just like falls into the baptism pool at the
top of the like sanctuary on the other side of the podium where every Sunday
pastor Adam Kane gives his sermons and with that it is all of the aliens turn
and they all start at the same time and it grows and grows and the power sends a
sound wave like a shock through all of your bodies I need everyone to roll
power I pass a 6 on a 60 oh nice I pass a 12 on a 50 well done I pass a 28 on a
65 rare I fail a 58 on a 50 medium rare you dumb dumb so in that exact moment
Lindsey Manstein you feel your brain begin to compress and like pulse you
lose let's roll of dice six damage as you feel liquid come out of your left
and right ears and you feel up there you feel up your face and there's blood just
dripping from your ears I look at Clark and I'm like Clark I don't feel so good
Clark Bishop it's your turn I want to line up a shot that takes out as many of
them in a row as I can straight through these squishy gringo I like that like
they're still stacked on top of each other not all of the room is full of
these guys yeah full of little fellas angles all right so roll intelligence to
find the right angle to shoot at first I pass a 52 on a 55 all right now roll
firearms straight up and down to take out as many of them as possible I don't
know I think it kind of added to the whole podcast
Zach that's a 22 oh my god he's not even lying about our special issue living in
some sort of weird gravity in this room like okay roll 2d 10 a 9 and a 3 holy
shit okay so 12 knock out three of them so you've got this lineup of three of
them in your sights there's like one on a pew one on the lectern and then one
hanging from a the Christian flag you know have you guys ever seen the
Christian flag I've seen the methodist flag not the Christian flag every church
that I like went to growing up had the American flag right next to the
Christian flag a very very strange choice of idols so one is hanging down
and the flag just bus and like it's almost like a like an ink package and
ink cartridge from like a money bag that you would steal a robbing and it just
banking bus this like green guck all over the flag and as soon as the flag
has been tarnished you see the stained glass at the very front of the sanctuary
just erupts into tiny tiny little particles of different colored glass all
making up some fucked up white Jesus holding a lamb and it just dissipates
into nothing as this massive version of these tiny little green men that you've
seen all over here this one stands at least two stories tall and it lowers its
head to crawl into the sanctuary of the first church of contention
welcome back to the pledge drive here on six nine four point two PTBP
contentions oldest and only radio show I am Nile Leota Oda and I am joined by my
co-host Mike Smith did you did you just I'm sorry I'm sorry Nile did you start
the whole show and we are also joined by our late night host Floyd Grant I just
wanted to thank you for having me on our intern oh someone's get into the room I
was putting in promos and the electricity went off and I heard I heard
something you look rattled your face is ghost white I've been at this station
for 30 years I heard something I I swear nothing you heard is something and does
this really need to happen right now it's an old building there's bumps
there's how it looks like an animal has been in here right there are animals in
the studio this one desperately need your support over on patreon.com shut
telling no right now if you guys aren't gonna deal with this can I take one
real quick you've actually you've proven to me over the course of this
hour that you can run this radio station Mike that means so much to me buddy
you're just an intern I've been at this radio station 30 years now you're seeing
you're here in some house you're hearing some growls you're seeing some does that
upset you does that not worry you we're the oldest radio station there's
something older than us that's in this radio station obviously listeners I do
apologize for this interruption but I couldn't be more excited to share with
all of you the $100 tier patrons who pledge at this level will become
clinkers daycare alumni the reward for sharing the same preschool as our
contention police officers well after six months of pledging at this tier
alumni of clinkers daycare will play in a delta green one shot handled by Zach
on roll 20 with the cast of pretending to be people as your fellow pcs clinkers
daycare alumni also have the option of running the game themselves ever
wondered how fun it is to handle those monsters at your own table well here's
your chance again that link is patreon.com slash pretending pod and another
reminder that when you pledge at any tier level you will also receive the
rewards of all lower tiers now I want to give the biggest shout out in the world
and all of contention even to the city and back to the almighty chuckling boy a
patron over on now you see before you came along there were none of these
chuckling boys on our station I don't I just don't understand the new style it
is patrons like chuckling boy who have blessed us and will continue to keep
this show on the air chuckling boy aka wise Mouse over on the pretending to be
people discord
did you guys that did you guys hear that that's a that's a lot closer than what
it seems like I was talking about okay all right you're the late night
DJ Mike do you not hear this it's this is just a normal vent sounds of the
studio is this in your hands Mike that's no that's that's in that's in the hall
that's in the hallway right let's there's something coming I there's
something outside the door in the hallway in that it's in the airways yeah
like it's oh god
having just revealed to you the meaning of all life in the universe the
philosopher king of the little green men extends a hand that begins to glow
and you all feel the intense urge to grasp it I reach my hand out I read that
thing grasping you all feel a warmth cover your corporeal bodies and you feel
at peace with everything a bright light bathes everything in the sanctuary and
your memories of this day are wiped clean the four of you Clark Bishop John
Lee Pettymore the fourth Lindsay Manstein and the day one Keith of Igna
all find yourselves sitting at your desks in the contention police
department the phone rings and Drew Andrews picks up Drew Andrew a
contention police department how can I help you today at that exact moment
Maggie cook your chief of police walks out of her office Maggie cook is a
strong fit woman with a dark Bob and intense eyes always in uniform she walks
over and puts a hand on Keith vigna shoulder everyone I think Keith did a
fantastic job today on his first day let's let's go around and all say one
positive thing about his performance John who tasty delicious these morsels
of moving meat writhe no more now they dwell within me they lie silent in the
never-ending darkness of my cavernous bowels I am now the one who speaks to
the masses I am filled with meat bone and joy now I'm here to tell y'all
something that will fill y'all with moist joy as our consumed talkative
friends previously mentioned there'd be a whole slew of new patreon tiers for
y'all to enjoy you can see all that we have on offer over at patreon.com slash
pretending pod also my producer who is definitely not trapped inside of my body
being digested tells me that there is going to be a twitch stream on February
11th 7 p.m. central time come on and hang out maybe you'll get into a game of
jackbox with all these boys from pretending to be people my producer also
informs me that we are gonna be doing something called howling with wolf I
guess right in and say nice things about me and I'll probably read some stuff
that y'all got to say your powers of belief make me ever stronger my babies
and now uh let me see your radio huh well I guess I need to drop some hot
slop on y'all this is contention this is six nine four point two PT BP and this
is kudzu with no backbone
you
try
oh