Welcome one, welcome all, welcome y'all, wait a minute, did I say this all before?
Have I lived this moment in another time?
It feels like I'm having one of them damn dirty deja vu moments, where you feel like
you did a thing before in an alternate reality type deal maybe, but now you're doing it in
this one for the first time, but a second time, anyway.
Speaking of endless cycles of torture that I am forced to relive every week, it's time
for Howlin' with Wolf.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf comes from Ian, who wrote a five star review of this show
like the sweet, sweet boy he is.
Hey everybody, be more like Ian, he writes.
Dear Wolf, I hope this letter finds you well.
Needless to say, I'm a huge fan of your show.
Not only for the soothing sounds you howl through the airwaves each week, your DJing
prowess and your spectacularly diverse discography, but you are hands down the most reliable source
of news that the mainstream media won't report on, those otherworldly happenings in the town
of contention.
My neighbor's got a sister in contention, and even he doesn't know what's going on.
Then again, he really hasn't been himself since last week when I returned that shiny
ball bearing he dropped out in the parking lot.
Didn't even thank me, he's usually a pretty chill guy, but the other night he woke up
half the apartment complex screaming and carrying on at two in the morning, thrashing and banging
around like we're living in college dorms again or something.
When I knocked on his door to ask what the hell he was doing, or more importantly why
he was spattered and marinara and holding what looked like a fake spinal cord, he just
said, uh, Halloween, and shut the door in my face.
It ain't even October, now he just stares at me coldly every time I pass by on my way
to the mailbox, sorry, totally got sidetracked there.
Anyway, love the show, keep on howling the good howling snapping those pearly fangs at
Mark Zuckerberg's milk toast android ass.
You're the wolf now, dawg, your friend and admirer, Ian.
P.S.
If you could do me a huge favor and dig into the deep cuts, I'd love to hear you spin something
a little different from the usual setlist.
Do you have no backbone by kudzu in your collection?
Thanks a million.
No, thank you, listener.
All-profit news stations are designed to keep you scared and coming back so they can make
that sweet, sweet cash money.
I like to keep y'all scared, but I do it for free because I'm a true radio journalist DJ
of high caliber, and, uh, it gets me off to know the power I hold, and, baby, you know
I'm always scrounging for them deepest of cuts when it comes to tunes.
I might have a little something special just for you this time.
Remember, if you want to write a message for me to read on air, tag us on Instagram or
Twitter at PretendingPod, or write a five star review on Apple Podcasts and email us
at pretendingpod at gmail dot com.
And the conglomerate of pretending to be people want me to keep shouting out that they are
taking questions for a third Q&A episode, so if you have questions for any of the mature,
most thoughtful adults who make that show, tag at PretendingPod on Twitter or Instagram.
There's also a post in the subreddit where you can comment your questions.
Or go all out, record audio of you asking a question and send that so they can use it
in the episode.
Same as the second Q&A episode, this one will be for our honorary police officers over on
Patreon who plug the holes of this sinking ship five bucks a month at a time.
The anthropomorphic corks who hold this whole thing together currently have instant access
to six exclusive bonus episodes, with more on its way, so much more.
Now if you want a question answered but you can't rationalize making room in your budget,
fear not.
There are already so many questions the PTBP crew won't be able to get to all of them.
For some of the questions missed on the recording, the boys will journey into the hardline mainframe
network and answer right there inside your phone or laptop.
They'll be all up inside them internet guts.
Speaking of crawling into other people's business, it's the news.
Clock Bishop Keith Vigna and John Lee Pettymore the fourth, in the body of John Lee Pettymore
the third, woke up in the tomb of Ari Manstein.
They had four names branded on different parts of their bodies.
On the backs Drew, on the bottom of their left foot Maggie, on the palms of their dominant
hands Tilly, and on the chests Marvin, but Marvin is crossed out.
After realizing they have the moments of the, I guess successful, raid on the glass compound,
the three former officers from contention began to understand the situation they found
themselves in.
Clark tried to summon another version of himself, looked a little too deep into his collective
unconsciousness and received a phone call from his former boss.
Taking us now to the parking lot of the city cemetery where Maggie Cook just assigned the
three dilapidated husks of humanity she once called co-workers with the task of taking
out Bruce Robin.
Ferguson Bean's former business partner is a personal favorite of mine and a brand new
single from Kudzu.
Y'all ain't never gonna guess what it is.
It's no backbone baby I fooled y'all.
I am John Lee Paddymore, doo da doo da, I am John Lee Paddymore, oh the doo da day.
We sound cool.
So you guys woke up in the tomb of Ari Manstein and then you realized like you do and you
realized that Marvin which was carved into your chest or burned into your chest rather
is crossed through with the same sort of burning all the way through which we took as a clear
indication that that was done and we have nothing to follow up on there and you didn't
talk about it at all well and then eventually leaving the tomb you ran into the old woman
making her way out of the cemetery and she was so slow oh my god and that's when you
realized that you had been here before the thing that you had been debating up until
that point she had seen us run through before exactly and then you almost ruined the entire
podcast by just standing there and waiting that's not totally off the table yeah we still
might do that and I don't understand how uh pushing you to new creative heights by thinking
outside the box is ruining the podcast I say what's ruining the podcast okay okay okay
podcast strike boys our characters sit there and wait we're out and no one's allowed to
cross us Zach just hires scabs so with us this week we've got Ali Jepson playing John
Lee Pettymore he just does all the voices himself he's like finally my dream the game
will go the way I want it to go so you guys are all standing in the parking lot Maggie
Cook has joined you she has driven up into this parking lot and has given you a job to
do which is to take out or essentially murder Bruce Robin full owner of bar Corp and the
one-time business partner of Keith vigna's brother Ferguson beans she is sitting in this
car broken down crying after having a conversation with John Lee Pettymore the third who well
there's something yeah there's something I want to add to that actually that I just kind
of realized you're allowed to you know Maggie I know this is a hard time for you reckoning
with my undeath and all but I I just realized I'm doing the same thing with you what the
fuck how are you alive and as you ask that her phone starts to ring I like I put my hand
on her hand and I'm like Maggie tell me damn it she looks at the call as Clark Bishop is
walking back over to join the group after looking at his cell phone and his car there
she looks at the phone she puts it down she's like alright I John I gotta take this just
real quick and then I'll explain okay I need Joe to roll an alertness check for me real
quick I pass 18 or 70 Joe as you walk back you actually hear a second vibration so her
phone is ringing and you hear a second buzzing at a different pitch we're from from inside
her car where she's sitting in the driver's seat and then she picks up the phone Leon oh okay Lee
Leon do you trust me and do your fucking job Leon I know it's been a while but knock the dust off
your knuckles and buckle up what controls this world Leon that's right bitch it's fire and as
soon as she's done speaking she hangs up she looks at you and she's like I never died John I
had to disappear whose body was that doesn't matter she just how did you get so cool John
I've always been this cool I think you've just been too drunk to notice and then she grabs an
envelope out of her shotgun seat and she throws it to you right out the window and she looks at
you and she's like remember I'm counting on you just Maggie just because I gave you bourbon for
Christmas doesn't mean I'm a drunk cheap shitty bourbon and then she drives off to clarify the
high-pitched buzzing that I heard she didn't acknowledge she did not got it but it sounded
just like a cell phone yes got it open that envelope so isn't that a little blur the manila
envelope has a manila folder inside labeled operation hole puncher colon bar Corp you remember the
we found that in the secret room with the Jim Cook's house in the secret room can you remind
us what we knew about it operation home I'm sorry of course we remember everything can you remind
the listeners there was a folder on the desk in that room that secret hidden room that said
operation hole puncher on the outside of it with the logo for the circle of knowledge the circle
surrounded by six circles and inside there is a list of nonprofits charities think tanks and
universities that are quote-unquote owned by the spark or knowledge oh okay where have we heard
bar Corp before that's a Fergie and Bruce Roberts Robbins beans and Robin corporation is bar Corp one
of those that's listed under companies owned by the circle of knowledge or yes it's in that list
yes okay I found where I wrote down this in my real-life notebook and I wrote down each each
company has date slash phone that phone number next to it isn't still the case so that was a
different folder than this one this one gotcha a lot of information just about bar Corp in it
whereas the other one was just a list of companies with a name and her biome got it so inside is a
full rundown of bar Corp it's two owners Ferguson beans and Bruce Robin it's three subsidiaries
Jesus Christ ministries health and rehabilitation unlimited and the Learning Center and its annual
gross profits from the last five years which has been steadily rising last year bar Corp made just
over 850 million dollars paid zero dollars in taxes and there's an estimate that this year they
will make over two billion dollars you also see that Ferguson beans is marked as deceased his
majority share in the company was split between his wife Stacy his daughter Francis and the mill
on the other side of the city this leaves the majority in the legal document that is how it's
listed in the legal documents this leaves the majority ownership to Bruce Robin there are
addresses listed for Ferguson beans home Bruce Robbins home the bar Corp headquarters and all
three subsidiaries Jesus Christ ministries health and rehabilitation unlimited and the
Learning Center is Jesus Christ ministries in contingent Jesus Christ ministries is actually
let's see it's in the city it's the one that he showed up to at the drug deal right you could
tell them in character what you know about Jesus Christ ministries that's what I know right that
you'll happen a long time ago yeah for Thomas for Thomas yeah I think maybe two nights ago
yeah oh yeah I've just recently killed Jesus Christ ministries is a church camp that is outside
the city hey Jesus Christ ministries I sold some cocaine to them you so yeah you know that cocaine
we got from the yeah from from the lockers there I sold that me I sold that to a church I didn't
know it was to a church I just heard that but my associate had a good had a good connection and it
turned out to be a very fancily dressed man well in a van that what was he wearing I remember very
very plainly the red rose pinned to his lapel Keith's face kind of drops a little bit he pulls
out his phone opens up a picture of Ferguson to him yeah that's my brother oh he was fucking
weird that makes sense so John you sold evidence cocaine to aren't we past that too I mean we've
been personally a giant ball monster like how you gonna worry about me selling a little bit of you
know contraband some good times I guess I guess we are a little past procedure but I wonder what
Fergie was doing with that did you know your brother to be a dealer I didn't really know my
brother that well towards the end anyway well he was there with a bunch of kids so maybe he was
giving it to them he had kids at the drug deal the ministry yeah he drove up in a ministry van and he
got out with a bunch of little children's and and they they dug up the cocaine that I had buried on
my property he made the kids dig up the cocaine Keith sounds like your brother sucks he sucked
how are you doing with that you know I I made the decision what do you mean I mean I can't take it
back now I'm just trying not to think about it a lot happened in the past couple days you killed
Fergie no I can say 100% with without lying to you I didn't kill him what decision did you make
Keith I will say if it wasn't for me he'd probably still be alive but I didn't kill him if I remember
right Marvin Glass mentioned all this when you and I were in his office while it was flooded
anyway I think that I know that yeah office when it flooded well yeah Keith when we were in the
office when it was all you know what we can we can talk about that later looks like we got other
stuff to focus on wait wait hold on Marvin's office flooded with you in it because the last
thing we saw was Marvin and a bunch of people bursting out of a flooded office well we had
been in the office when it was flooded and then before right after that we kind of just woke up
thrown into combat see I was a I was trying to save you and I saw your body was pressed against
a window down there and I shot it out and then all hell broke loose so what do we think happened
between then and John we were after the the room flooded I'd he Marvin grabbed a hold of me grabbed
a key showed up eventually but he he hope he opened you up he popped you open and there was
one of those one of those little silver balls was inside of you well yeah hey boys we might all be
silver balls just so you know there could be a silver ball on you right now oh yeah I mean I'm
pretty sure I am the silver ball when my Kevin father killed my my err body my first John yeah
what happened then is that I burst out of my own spine and into his because I think I'm just a
little ball that rings that rings a bell actually because I've seen those balls rip spines out of
people before and pop themselves in the place I mean I saw that when I was looking at videos
at the glass compound I saw that happen a couple times on video so well so yeah so I'm a ball and
as you can see I have the capacity to be on the side of good are you all ball I like flex and I
show off my tight pants and I'm like hell no man have you always been ball when you were first John
was that ball did I only ever know a ball I think I was a ball you were bald in I think so why don't
you remember if you were ball you'd be a ball you know you were a ball well hey man being a ball
just feels like being you or me so you're I could be ball yeah that's what I I really don't know
who's ball and who's not but a lot of us could be ball honestly Keith vigna is just looking but in
between these two having just no almost no clue what's going well you see Keith I'm a ball I'm
just like kind of nodding my head like I think I might be ball to my ball I don't I don't know I
might be ball I don't think I'm ball I don't hold on hold on hold on hold on all right I want you
all just turn around and I'm gonna give you a little John Lee petty more patented neck rub and
we're gonna see if I feel anything weird in that spot of yours what if you ball me what if I don't
what if I'm not balling you ball me I promise not to follow you just let me give you a little neck
rip and then John Lee petty more gets in there and he's like god damn it's good it's firm but
sensitive it's for the first time in days your attention leaves Clark's shoulders I'm following
your muscles and your bones perfectly and it's just like fuck you feel like a dog basically a
regular John Peters the best pet of its life and after I'm done I'm like well I'm no anatomy
expert but John Lee petty more is a back rub expert and I don't see any signs of ball from
that I have no idea how that presents in the anatomy what I've seen but thank you for letting
me lay on hands it's been in the head it's been in the skull us I sinked it in you and I saw it
having a rosemary where you saw a ball and rosemary so in the office previous when things were bad
rosemary made a move for the gun the tube gun on the desk of Marvin in his office I don't know what
her plan was but Marvin wait a minute rosemary turned against Marvin at the last minute and
Marvin flung one of those silver balls at her oh buddy I think I know why wait what happened okay
hold on what happened when he threw the silver ball crack cracked her open and took her spine
out and replaced it he threw the ball at her through the ball at her and it popped her open
like a can of soda and ripped out her spine and replaced it dang oh yeah then the ball the silver
ball now inhabiting rosemary as far as I know pulled the trigger and she disappeared did we
see rosemary as one of the corpses that came out of the the booth or whatever it was no no okay no
I didn't think so yeah all right so rosemary she was in love with Marvin's dog son yeah she was
trying to find his son the one who got gun by Tilly Marvin didn't really care but that's why
she wanted the gun Jermaine glass was she in one in love with the one who got evaporated to the
one who was turned into a fool the one who got evaporated yeah so she was trying to get that
gun to find him to get him back that's what I know about rose well I was confused at the time
and I still am about the whole business of her making a move at Marvin Marvin throwing the ball
at her like that would do like he knew it would do something but then it I don't know if it did
the thing he thought it was gonna do like she pulled the trigger either way based on all those
videos I saw Marvin knew what those balls would do Marvin does know what those balls would do and I
think he's creating or controlling them in some capacity when I was playing at juggernaut I mean
I became that from being a ball I rolled into into him and well what John Lee Pennymore sighs
a sweet nostalgic sigh he's back in his in a human body but he feels like he should be in a gigantic
metal sphere I was gonna call for a sanity check but it doesn't seem to fit your wistful not not
upset well guys I know that we just I know we just got tasked to kill Robin but before we do you do
you think he might know something about this oh I mean well yeah who knows we should definitely
interrogate anybody before we murder them but I so far I haven't seen any reason not to trust Maggie
not to murder again I mean I have but I she kind of she kind of addressed it well do you think we
should go to his house or to the wood to talk to bark or I'd lean toward going to his house
and just seeing what kind of personal files he's got do you have his number or maybe like that is
mom's number his mom is dead oh and don't ask me how I know that how do you know that I killed her
we'll get to that later what no I yeah I didn't kill my brother I you know what I'll just tell
you the story I convinced her to kill my brother and then I killed her so she couldn't tell on me
hold and there you have it let's let's let's you know what we'll cop we'll get to that no way
probably never again let's just never talk about it all cops are bastards me too I don't really
identify as a cop anymore really but uh what what why did you by proxy kill your brother
for money which I never ended up seeing you know the more I think about it the more I'm glad we
aren't cops anymore fellas you've all done some pretty you want to go sleep we can still use our
investigative skills sell some drugs that I found in the course of an investigation that's to a man
with children that is routine cop work I think a lot of drug dealers have kids they don't employ
a lot of kids I think a lot of drug dealers are kids you guys want to go sneak around his
house and see what we can find yeah I think we should do his house it's insert time here
he's probably not at home it's roughly 2 p.m. on December 6th which is a Saturday I guess
fuck he could be home or he's out partying I mean if it's home that's I mean it's a little early
honestly 2 p.m. at a Saturday is exactly when he would be home that's it that's fine though I mean
let's go it's yeah yeah we also our police still kind of we have badges I never left I've always
considered myself a cop of contention well let's go whether I be drug dealer or a giant metal ball
man I've been looking out for the people back home does he live in the city or yeah you're in
the city now boys does he live here she lives downtown perfect we don't have jurisdiction so
we can obviously commit an extra judicial killing without any paperwork yeah well at least less
paperwork I mean for us I mean let's go see what we could find out then yeah some smug city cop
looking down on the small town fuzz you guys want to take my car the only one they're hopping I get
in you hop into Clark's silver Honda Accord Honda make your dreams drive is this the Accord sport
it's a exhale II exactly Maggie gave it to me I don't know what we're in here and you guys take
off downtown to a two-story brownstone in the city when you arrive you find parking decently nearby
actually go ahead and roll for parking no I don't give a shit so you guys show up well I crit failed
and you find the number on the door is 218 but probably more important than that is that there
is police tape over the door are there any cars in the park the driveway not a driveway no driveway
for this brownstone here is it a home like a row or a large brick row house well there's other ones
that look just like it on the other side and it's really nice it's like a very very nice street that
you're on there's a park across the street well if I learned anything as a cop it's that this do
not cross tape is not very strong and I rip it and I think if you'd learned anything it as a cop
it's that do not cross does not apply to you that's true and I jiggle the handle of the door
I kind of put the tape back so no one follows this you like tie it together yeah yeah title
not in it good as new is the door unlocked ha the door is unlocked nice I rolled an 88 for the
yeah who was there last to remember to lock the door yeah I walk on it was a real kid's a big
night surprise yourself with that role you're like of course not why would it be unlocked yeah when
you guys walk in the stench is the first thing you notice like a dead body would any of you have
been in a heroin den working in the contention PD probably not in contention probably not like
you do you know what it smells like I know what a meth house smells like I've been in one of those
and it's bad it's like poop and cigarettes it smells like poop and cigarettes and heroin hmm
it is a fucking wreck there's trash everywhere most of the furnishings that should be here are
gone there's like pallets made all over the place but there's actual human fecal matter just like
strewn about seems that people were like stepping in it and tracking it all around the place smells
like piss spray-painted on one of the walls Heisenberg is eight one one eight one eight nine
five two zero one three one one eight one one one nine got it did you really I started writing
about midway I'd lost it does that have any significance to us it's on the wall is that
we said spray-painted roll again for me signals intelligence I have a zero so no don't roll
signals for me so no none of you would be able to I'm gonna put anything together I'm gonna take a
picture of it so we have it for later nice so what is it eight one etc etc and go ahead in first just
tell me what you guys are doing when you are in here like I'm just looking around for anything
that isn't just gross anything that sticks out that's not you know drugged in ask Clark is
saying hello you hear nothing except for your partners rifling through all this shit it seems
that everything that would have been in a place this nice is long gone drawers have been pulled
out of cabinets and doors are open everywhere everything is just strewn about and everything
that was once clean is no longer or not here anymore since this is such a nice place are there
any security cameras around in the house roll luck of fail no not a crit fail just to fail okay
I'd like to run up to the next floor and see if it's as decrepit and heroin II and shitty when you
get up to the second floor the hair on the back of your neck stands up and I roll an alertness
or a search you can roll search for me 19 and as your grit fail okay as you're walking through
the hallway you see there's a few rooms up here in a bathroom and there's just this heavy presence
that you've never felt before and carved into the walls in this room that is maybe had been
an office at one point in time is the same set of numbers that you saw spray-painted downstairs
eight one one eight one eight nine five two zero one three one one eight one one one nine and it
is carved over and over and over on everything in here using a simple substitution cipher with
you know one equaling a and so on do I get any new words out of this do I take a break and give
it a go fuck no just tell me yes but just I mean it's like ha ha ha ha no okay obviously that
wouldn't so I actually I'd be down to spend a few minutes looking at it I don't know we might find
fun stuff off mic though but we can bring it back I don't know take a hot piss and let's see if we
can figure it out off mic so did you guys figure it out yeah it's pretty obvious yeah I mean it's
it's very elementary once you get right into it so we can probably just breeze through that
listeners have it by now anything else in this room besides carvings on the wall besides the
obvious thing the painful easy cipher the really easy one that we figured out for sure no are there
any like closets or doors or anything did he leave a note saying where he went some of the
doors have even been taken off and the closet doors are all open and it's the same situation
and garbage yeah can I look in the bedroom and tell I don't know if it looks like it's been used
recently I'm trying to get a gauge of how long it's been like in this state it looks like what
could be like the master bedroom or at least the bedroom one of the bedrooms upstairs that's large
and has a bathroom attached the bed is gone the bed frame is gone and there are pallets all over
the place like there have been like 20 people sleeping right here can I look in the fridge
or the kitchen see what I glean from the kitchen when you go through the fridge it is sparse there
is like some rotten food but then there's also like some takeout a lot of like fast food that's
been like half eaten and stuff I want to call the city PD not like the normal number but like the
fellow cop number sure calling an office and basically I want to say like yeah this is John
Lee Pettymore out of contention we got a case about a drifter who might have committed some
property crimes down here and we might have tracked him to a drug hideout up there in the
city y'all had some police tape up around it so we didn't go inside but I was of course wondering
whatever information you had on that if you could get it to me about who was living there how long
it had been in that state as a drug squat whether or not the owner of the residence was participating
in in that squat oh yeah sure oh that's 501 east fake street so it's 218 is the address okay and
I said it wasn't as important as the police tape over the door that doesn't mean it's not important
oh 218 yeah that's Bruce Robin's home and uh he dipped out of there a few days ago seemingly and
we questioned some of the neighbors and they said that he was going absolutely crazy he was not
acting like himself and he was uh had just people coming in at all time of the day and night and
just inviting them all in and and then he just disappeared probably two days ago and they haven't
seen him since so the squat was was established already there were there were all kinds of
unstable characters coming around while Mr. Robin was still in residence seemingly for a short
amount of time but I you don't want to go in there it is absolutely disgusting they did a number on
that place in such a short amount of time I mean it was truly horrific stuff did y'all have any
leads uh about where Mr. Robin went we might want to interview him about our subject honestly you
know he's a high profile member of the community and we're just kind of putting it on the back
burner I understand uh you know cops exist to protect the capitalist superstructure under which
we we uh we serve so that's you're doing your job we looked into it and his mother died recently
and uh she hey now that's the lead his business partner is also dead oh god tragic so he seems
to have been going through some stuff and if you know mental illness is a serious issue here in
the city and really all over the world and no no no I mean not in contention we just uh we just uh
if you're not acting normal you know we either send you to a lot of church or we make you feel
alienated until you just leave or kill yourself it's the it's the small town way jesus christ
yeah his voice changes and he says jesus christ
keith can only hear one side of this conversation I'm like what the fuck
I was just like I'm just telling them about small town life well well shit but what's
our next step we came real close to doing it to you when you first came to the department I tell you
would you have sent keith vigna to church or would you have alienated him we tried to send the
boy to church we tried he didn't seem to get along too well with the pastor no one saw him show up
yeah I did like uh the all-you-can-eat buffets they had yeah I remember how you took advantage
of the lord's hospitality we got to find this guy he's obviously not here should we I mean go
to bar corp do you fellas think it's worth talking to the neighbors ourselves I was thinking about it
but if I mean since we're here I guess roll search whoever has the best search roll search for me I
ain't got it I got the baseline 20 I've got a 50 yeah yeah I have 40 so 76 all right yeah then uh
making a final pass through the home favorite uh you accidentally step in a pile of piss
you know how piss piles it's a huge stack of piss watch out for that stack of piss
hot piss no it's cold it's coagulated at this point gross it's not so uh I guess do you want
to go knock on a neighbor's door or are you Phil is thinking what I'm thinking as far as
what are you what do you think well we know about a bunch of people being destitute that's kind of
a thing we learned oh yeah we learned that Kathy was kind of running homeless people around at
various folks yeah but they weren't so much the heroin living their own shit kind of destitute
was it well they didn't smell good I think that was one thing that Keith confirmed for I mean I
was on a bus full of four of them and but you're right they weren't necessarily it was not a good
smell they weren't necessarily drug does Keith remember the smell does Keith recognize the smell
of the bus yeah could any of them have come out of the squat or is it into smell is one of the
strongest uh you know memory senses Keith vigna give me a smell roll you've been doing a fair
amount of cocaine the past few days give me a luck roll I got a six oh no a nine but still
that's lower than what my luck is this is a different smell okay I do one last big breath
in I'm like definitely not the bus uh homeless bus smell I trust your smells hey y'all I mean
why don't we just call him call robin call robin you could be like do we have his phone number in
that envelope you would have his direct number yeah it's not a bad idea Keith could call him
just checking in about his brother yeah as far as you know you don't know anything or and wanting
to commiserate about the mother yeah he lost his mother Keith lost his brother uh yeah have you met
robin no I haven't but uh you know we're both aware of each other you know I'd give him a call
you would hope a call from a good Samaritan a time of need would you both have something to relate to
it it could play yeah I give it I'll ring him you want to put that on speakerphone for us I do
obviously after we step out of this hell hole okay so back in the car I assume sure are you
guys just standing on the street should we walk around the block before we get back in the car
get the smell off just because of the smell oh yeah I thought you meant for more investigating
which is also an idea talk to the neighbors but uh I mean let's make the call in the privacy of
the car but we don't have to leave beep boop boop as you guys are walking back to the car
just a reminder of what the city looks like flowers everywhere oh yeah it's different than
contention uh the filter sickly green on the coloration yeah sickly green tint with heavy
grays the streets are covered in trash and spilled liquids and there's a scent in the air like
someone left out cheese and a colostomy bag on every corner the faces of the buildings are
slathered in billboards and the faces of the people bumbling about are bloated and lifeless
in a strange opposition to all this depressive scenery there are beautiful flowers in every shade
and shape growing in every otherwise empty alleyway and out of many cracks in the sidewalks
and roads I want to find the most lifeless looking person passing and I want to tap them
on the shoulder sorry why are you so pallid and corpse lack oh work's been pretty hard recently
I guess where do you work the corp uh bar corp yeah they gave us some days off though which is
nice so I think I've got a little bit more color to my cheeks than I did recently oh they're
positively rosy they're paying us time and a half to take like two weeks off two weeks off for a
whole massive corporation like that yeah it's crazy right why I don't know something about the
new takeover uh our new CEO Bruce Robin he's uh he's doing like some cool stuff he's like trying
to renovate everything apparently he's gonna make everyone have livable wage and benefits that are
realistically priced for all workers uh I guess we're getting better hours and yeah he's renovating
all the facilities to be up to code so we're all getting paid during the time off time and a half
but we could actually get even more if we help with the renovations do you know where he's
overseeing these renovations no I think he's just at the office but that's just an assumption he
doesn't come out to the sites very often sir what do you what do you do for bar corp in particular
what's your job data analyst and analyst I work at the office of the head office yeah I'm a data
analyst like what Thomas said that's a that's a uh soul-crushing job a great nondescript standard
office job to just throw out there samesies yeah all right well thank you thank you for your time
sir well yeah have a blessed day I remember Joe asked back when we first entered the city I asked
uh rosemary if those flowers were always there can you remind me if you said yes or no whether they
were a new thing to the city or if it's always been that way petty more asked rosemary if the
city is always this floral and she said yeah okay hey Keith what's what's barcorp do what what is
barcorp do they manufacture something other than these subsidiaries do they do something so I didn't
talk to my brother much he was rich something to do with money that's legitimately exactly how much
Keith vigna knows like the making of it or the managing of it or the financial institution or
just some comes in some goes out more comes in than than goes out though I think because they're
pretty successful I'll see they sell I assume they sell stuff I want to ask this guy that we
were just talking to hey oh hey what sorry more human connection what what does barcorp do we're
a corporation for the people do you sell something yeah I mean sure what do you sell
oh lots of things do you have anything on you pull out anything that's like in your pocket
I pull out a pen yeah we made that I look at the pen does it say barcorp roll sanity no
are you in the food business oh yeah I could call somebody and find out I have the CEO's number
okay bye I mean we could if you have like the number for Fergie at the corporation then it
might go to his secretary or something and we can have her at us to Robin or I have Robin we
have Robin's phone number oh that's right yeah we were still on our way to the car for that yeah so
you pull out your phone and dial the number for Bruce Robin and it rings hello this is Winifred
worth Bruce Robin's office hey this is uh this is Keith beans okay I was Ferguson beans was my
brother oh I am so sorry to hear about your recent loss well thank you I appreciate that I was just
hoping to get in touch with Robin I had a couple questions because I think it was under odd
circumstances that his mother and my brother both recently passed away I was hoping to speak with
him yes absolutely asking you questions away and I will relay the messages to him and he will get
back to you it was kind of hoping that I it's kind of private stuff you know I'm terribly sorry and I
understand that you're going through a real trying time right now but Bruce is unavailable is he in
the office yes but he is currently unavailable uh what what floor are you on right now well
the good one yes the best one on the best one we're on floor 17 okay well thank you know what
oh oh write down some questions and call back I was just hoping to have more of a conversation
with him but I'll think of something to ask him I guess and then give you a call back hopefully
totally and then I want to call yeah I want to call Ferguson's office number and try to talk to
his secretary Winifred Worth's office hey this is Ferguson beans I'm not dead no sorry you're the
same gentleman Keith beans you just called your Ferguson's brother why did you say that no I'm
Ferguson and she is old it sounds like so she doesn't remember what Ferguson sounds like he's
my brother we sound very similar I'm whip-crack smart and you sound like an idiot now is this
some sort of prank on Bruce tell the DM what's going on I try what I really liked was when we
played with a different DM this past weekend who was not Zach and you tried and he was just like
I hang up I hang up I'm like damn I thought that would definitely work
Winifred Worth is good at her job she fucking keeps it locked down we found out where Bruce
is I mean he's there right now we could I mean once we get up to the 17th floor and bust in with
some fucking cop uniforms on you know some yeah some uh she doesn't know what I look like breakers
with some initials on the back yeah if we just go up there it's just police business I mean there's
no reason they can't stop yeah I mean I would like to see Winifred Worth try to stop us after
hearing that phone call on speaker we were just talking to that fella and it sounds like Bruce
is maybe doing some good for this city as well that's what they told the workers that's true
maybe things has changed nothing going on in this city that was good so I'll believe it when I see
it but I say we go try to confront him see what we can get out of him then his business partner
was a man who bought cocaine in a van full of children how do we think that Robin is any better
but according to this guy it's because he's now CEO he said a bunch of changes were coming and
that they were positive all I mean is that he's the kind of guy who got into business with Ferguson
in the first place and is his heart that full of gold and someone that we trust wants us to kill
him yeah you're right we gotta I say we go I say we go I mean we go talk to him if we if we find
out some better information we could change her mind but I trust her that she's telling us these
things will stop this thing so I'm gonna do these things to stop the thing I don't know yeah I don't
know if I do trust this new well it was pretty cool I'll she faked her own death that was right
I mean I said earlier if you if you trust her I trust you not to mention the circle of knowledge
is what I've gleaned so far has been around for a while and seems to have been doing good being
keeping keeping with this awful thing was at bay let's go talk to Bruce just get some info yeah
maybe find out what other stuff the circle in the lodge has been up to
the only one trying to