hello friends one and all it is your host with the most wolf the dog coming at you live from 694.2
PTBP my babies i just want y'all to know though it has felt like we've been at this thing for weeks
now it is only december 3rd here in contention that's right y'all all this shit went down in two
damn days that is 48 hours not even enough time to get a good stool going and now we got a little
news for y'all once again now you know those boys went to julie maxwell's and saw a whole mess of
taxidermy i even heard they got a couple souvenirs from the joint now when they went looking around
they found a circled yellow pages ad for dr marie jacobs them boys also found a receipt from
forgotten treasures everyone's favorite flea market in contention and they found out the
camera julie maxwell purchased was from mildred mitchell's booth well then those boys decided to
go to mildred's house that old kooky pothead you know i love me some mildred and then wouldn't you
know it her damn granddaughter done disappeared into thin air now just a reminder for y'all we
got a new segment called howlin with wolf we need to have y'all screenshot those five-star reviews
by the way and submit them to pretending pod at gmail.com you can also make a post and tag us on
instagram facebook or twitter you can find us on instagram and twitter username at pretending pod
or look up pretending to be people on facebook you better watch your back mark zuckerberg now each
time you do one of these little favors for us we're gonna put your name in a bowl and each week me
or one of my pups will draw a name and that person will be able to write an announcement
to be read by your local canine dj wolf the dog damn y'all i just can't stop thinking about how
that girl disappeared out of thin air but you know who's not disappearing anytime soon it's kudzu with
no backbone
so
i think tilde might be wrapped up in some some weird stuff that's been going around in town
can you give her a call uh mildred uh pulls out her phone and calls and you hear a
um
coming from upstairs uh john you would you would hear it like in the same room as you
there's some kind of huge bee in this room uh i what kind of phone does she have iphone
full stop all right is it locked yeah does she have any pictures of herself in the room
yeah all right i try to unlock it with a picture of her uh yeah you can unlock it hell yeah
um hey i hey i just answer and i'm like whoa she looks at keith and she's like
oh she answered she's right upstairs no mildred it's me it's john lee peter pennymore
i can't keep revealing my terrible secret
so she's gone i'm sorry to say mildred it seems like she is when will she be back we don't
rightly know i think around now is when clark starts to regain some of his faculties and he
goes over to mildred and said uh mildred uh yeah i don't i don't know where she went but you know
we're gonna find her we always find people we're looking for do you find john peters
that was yesterday we're working on it we actually are coming pretty close we think
uh she like reaches over to her ashtray relights that spliff and starts walking upstairs uh so in
until this room i want to do a couple things a has the camera reacted to being in here at all no
okay uh now that i've unlocked her phone i want to check her texts her facebook like messenger
anything i want to look at her communication see who she's talking to you know is she in a
facebook messenger group called like freaky death cult uh yeah she's in a freaky death cult no
basically what you would garner is that
i'm sorry there's so much tube technology
in this world
she was a pretty standoffish kid from what you can tell she clearly grew up maybe not clearly but she
grew up in this house with her grandma her parents are gone she's had a weird home life uh her
grandma raised her but was always stoned you would gather from her phone that she probably has uh
dabbled in in smoking some pot herself and uh you know normal kid stuff she's into tv shows and
you know movies and music and other things that people find uh enjoyable as hobbies looking
through her phone she seems like your typical teenager i don't know how she came across like
watching tv shows and movies and your typical enjoyable things yeah the kind of things that
people like wow how old a girl is she uh
mildred is sitting on her bed i feel like we were asking you and not mildred yeah
oh i definitely we saw her uh early high school freshman or sophomore probably cool probably
sophomore actually we'll go with sophomore she has a car hell yeah so she's pretty cool she's pretty
cool i'll do cash till he has a driver's license we should grab that we should grab that gun
before we forget okay so it seems like a troubled teen uh sneaking around her neighbor's abandoned
house find some spooky shit but i do you think she knew she would disappear or was she trying
to harm you she pointed it at you that's what i'm trying to say is i don't think she knew what this
was so she was gonna shoot me for entering her room she was gonna kill me somebody might have
gotten to her about having those things somebody besides julie maxwell purchased other items maybe
we should go back and find out who purchased those other items if there's a security footage
or anything like that if she said it was in the past week or so they might still have some that's
not a bad idea keith see if we can find some people snooping around that booth we've just
entered the room of like the mastermind of all of this and we're like she's a poor teeny and you're
like you'll never catch me alive did clark not mention that she said she twirled her mustache
it all happened real quick but she looks scared as all get out pointing that gun at me was it the
fear of a little girl about to shoot a police officer or a fear of a girl about to do something
metaphysical i think i think we i think we probably got both but i i would suspect that
she learned some things about what she had in her possession i think we should go back
to the metaphysical store hidden treasures forgotten treasures
i know they're closed but not for us uh they are closed but you see the same woman inside
she's like sweeping up give her a friendly way from outside and point to the door
i'm sorry um we're closed oh yeah man we're not here to shop we had some more questions related
to uh booth 504 oh oh okay i i guess come on in thank you man what what can i what can i assist
you with officers we were specifically wondering if you had any more records uh or receipts from
that booth you see that big book that she was going through and uh she looks at it walks over
and starts flipping through it well second question do you have any security cameras in here
yeah but they don't rightly work with they're mostly just the show the kids
yeah yeah and oh hey i want to come through on that roll it up uh 96 can i human her too
yeah let's not so um so yeah you you believe what you want to believe the truth is out there zack
and this old lady is a lying two-faced fuck she does have a face on the back of her head
as she's flipping through the through the big book gosh uh there were three items recently
bought from booth 504 there was a camera that was bought with a check and uh that was from
and she's done through julie julie maxwell another item was uh put on uh the tab uh by
marie jacobs marie marie has a tab uh yeah she come in here pretty often i'd say so what sort
of things does she usually buy well what was that item on the tab it's a radio yeah it says a radio
and then uh there was another item uh uh a helmet that was uh it was put on a credit card you have
a name on that card man it's uh the first church of contention this might be a strange question do
you remember all of these items being tubed um i didn't sell all of them i don't rightly remember
that's fine do you remember who from the church purchased that helmet i i wasn't here for that
but who would be purchasing things on the who has a credit card to the church do you think do you
know clark who would have that you religious clark probably not i don't think john lee is
but i think he definitely would have spent time around a church growing up what is the first
church of contention baptist Scientologist it's uh we're not it's just the first church of
contention we're not gonna call it one denomination is more evil than the other they're all pretty
equally dog methodists are all right methodists don't give a fuck they're chill
was there anything else uh no that was it hey well i think we got i wish we
would have followed up with this with you on this on our first visit but uh thank you for
i figured you would i was kind of surprised you didn't to recap ma'am we had a camera that went to
julie maxwell a radio that went to marie jacobs and a helmet that went to the first church of
contention do you know anything about that helmet is it a bike helmet it just says helmet okay did
anybody else come in asking about these did julie maxwell maybe ask you about who had bought some
more of these things um no just inside i only asked because we found the uh dr marie jacobs
oh that's right what was her name on in julie's apartment uh it was in the yellow pages just
circled uh i think we know our next stop yeah well thank you very much ma'am go ahead and if
who has the highest human intelligence human i have 80 go ahead and roll it for me 74
when she says no that no one asked her about these items she seems scared are you sure nobody
did um i put my hand on my gun i grab her by the collar roll firearms
so um i do just to intimidate her though oh god also i'm in a wheelchair so i don't know if she
can see me do it that's that's why i grabbed her by the collar and i forced her to like vision over
to where you have your hand on a gun why don't you start talking you two-faced shit sandwich
oh i have no idea but you won't he was the one who saw that she was saying something yeah he
just was asking yeah and he went for his gun i trust my colleague's instincts i didn't pull it
out i just i'm doing this no i don't know he said who's he i don't know who he was he was very mean
he was very tall and he smelled like alcohol he was absolutely vile what was he wearing
i don't i don't remember i'm sorry i've got him did he maybe drive out of here in a white Toyota
i don't know what he was driving can you please i i'm honestly scared we're here for you ma'am
if you're here for us here's what's gonna have to happen your life and contention is over you have
to go into witness contention protection immediately you have to go into witness
contention that's the alternate that's like contention five miles down the road
for people who've witnessed spooky shit in contention you guys might want to visit there
we can really yeah drill i say ma'am ma'am it's okay uh we just need you to be honest with us
here uh you said he was vile was he was he saying cuss words at you yeah he threatened me what was
he threatening about he wanted those items or he wanted to know where they went yeah he wanted to
know where they went were you able to tell him anything at that time i told him i told him what
i told you he told me not to tell anyone else that's okay we're a police officer you can tell us
well i already did but thank you and that's why you're doing a real good job you're doing you're
helping you're helping maybe save lives here now can you can you remember anything else about him
something maybe maybe something on his face or he had bad teeth okay that works and um
you know he had he had gin blossoms all over his nose and under his eyes love that man and he had
whiskey blossoms all over his tongue and he had he was a real floral fella i understand it did
he smell like very very quite blemish you're telling us he had terrible skin it was so scary
did you get a sense of maybe any of his interest or hobbies or when he left did he leave away get
in contact with him do you want you to follow up with him ever said he'd be watching
turn around he's standing right there
it's a tall man with bad teeth and whiskey uh clark charles when you saw him was he a tall man
he was real tall he smelled bad and he had gym blossom blemishes this guy sounds like the same
guy that came to see me okay i think we should go what i'm thinking we gotta find charles but
i'm thinking we need to go talk to uh what's the physician's name marie jacobs yeah what time is
it right now uh it's like six six thirty somewhere in there all right let's should
we roll over to her we should probably eat how can you eat at a time like this
my dehydration it's been a long day yeah you guys are gonna die if you don't eat some food
you guys all lose a hit point per hour this point forward roll constitution i'm trying to role
play excellently we would all be very hungry yeah um no let's go let's go see marie as you guys walk
out the door of forgotten treasures you see a white toyota in the road and it peels off
i throw on my taxidermy hat and get my cruiser and take off after it
okay for uh what what are your dexterity's the three of you
ruffle ruffle ruffle yeah uh mine is uh 65 i got a 60 oh uh it's 12 times 5 60 size 60
quick math quick math important okay john lee pettymore you run and get in your cruiser with
your taxidermy hat on i've got it i've got it held low and tight and it's it's it's business
what was it again dude it's been two months do you remember what it was
i think it was like we haven't gotten to hear that episode so i have no idea like faces like
together or something we'll find out later something crazy so it bumps the top of the
cruiser like you didn't have to set it on the seat uh clark what do you do i'm already running
toward my car not even that's the reaction absolutely i'm wheeling over there uh are you
with me help me throw this into your trunk and i hop out of my wheelchair i run back around grab
the wheelchair and throw it in the like the back seat and i get in the i get in the passenger seat
and say i hit the roof of the car did you hear that yeah it worked really well luke just slapped
the top of his head john lee pettymore roll me a drive check oh god damn it 82 on a 70 amazing
all right the hat gets in my eyes and i have a really hard time getting the car started clark
uh roll a drive check as well 42 on a 50 nice so as you guys go off you see the white toyota
as it peeled off it actually ran a bit off the road up onto the curb and had to back up as to
like to avoid hitting a sign on the side of the road and then gets back on the road and as it
is going north on the road from forgotten treasures clark you are in position right
behind the white toyota and john lee pettymore you are taking up the rear right behind clark bishop
as you are driving there's an intersection approaching and the white toyota is going
to drive straight through the red light clark what do you do real fast my assessment of the
situation can i see if is there more than one person in the car roll me in a search
fail 61 i also wonder that i pass a 34 on a 40 uh keith you see there is one person in the driver's
seat of the white toyota cool clark how are you handling the situation from a driving perspective
there is traffic going horizontally i do it like a ambulance would so lights on siren on and just
cautiously but still trying to maintain as much speed as i can but still seeing how safe i can be
about the oncoming traffic if i'm if they're stopping i'm going but if they're don't look
like they're stopping i'm not going through okay yeah he is going to go through the intersection
and john lee pettymart full speed i peel around him and i'm not really looking okay i need you
both to roll another drive check for me fail on mine if i roll 70 on a 70 is that a fail no that
is a great success okay cool it's a really really quite good success very lucky the white toyota
swerves out of the way of the traffic as he goes through the intersection nimbly dodging a car
clark bishop you are about to hit a car coming in from the right too hot didn't see your sirens
didn't uh didn't hear you so you have to like hit the brakes yeah in order to uh avoid a collision
there as john lee petty more just like slides like through the intersection and flies through
it on the tail of the white toyota keith what do you want to do i'm gonna flash my gun at the
person that almost just hit us and point out and then i nod my head and i go yeah yeah then i say
hit it i do okay so now the pursuit is still heading north on that same road the white toyota
is going like 60 65 miles an hour on a 45 and gaining speed john lee petty morn it is up to you
what you want to do next i'm just still in hot pursuit you're basically right behind this white
toyota so what maneuvers are you going to take i assume my police cruiser has more power so i'm
just going to try to get ahead of him and make him stop or run off the road how close is he to
the white toyota how close are we to the white toyota i would say john lee petty more is roughly
10 yards 15 yards behind the white toyota and you guys are 20 yards behind his cruiser you
can just call him a channel okay i see that john has the lead on this one so i'm whatever he does
even if he does manage to get to the side or around it i'm gonna still kind of be taking up
the rear in case that car goes off i think we should try to get up close too because i can get
the shotgun out of the back and try to take out his tires okay because i got pretty good firearms
okay i'll do that i'll get a little closer if you can pull up to the side i'll try to get up
to the back and i'll be like cop loudspeaker just like pull over stop the vehicle okay six so i'm
going to roll okay so here's what happens john as you pull behind this uh this white toyota you see
a hand go out the driver's side window with a something that is on fire in the hand and he
throws a bottle molotov cocktail awesome and it is flying through the air i need you to
roll against his throw on a drive check in order to avoid the molotov cocktail heading straight
for your windshield five as you swerve you manage to avoid the cocktail hitting your windshield
exactly but it does catch the the back corner of your car and and you're not sure whether or not
a fire has started or whether or not just the exterior of your car is on fire currently clark
you and keith see a small explosion in the back right of john's car and glass seems to just
shatter off in in that direction as you guys are pulling up closer this is the most alive
john has felt since his racing days holy shit did that guy just throw a molotov cocktail
i think he did dude we gotta take this guy out i already have reached back and picked up the
shotgun and i'm waiting to roll my window down until we can get close enough to him because i
don't want no fire in this car okay i think he had to slow down enough and john clearly like
swerved to the left and you guys pulled up right next to him so the two of you are side by side
with the white toyota right in between you right ahead of you clark is there anything you want to
do maneuver wise while you're driving or are you just trying to i mean always getting closer into
maybe his right side there's a passenger side now okay awesome so let's go ahead and do another
drive roll off all both of you and i'll roll for for the white toyota as well fuck 89 on a 50 90
on a 70 okay the white toyota failed his check as well so you're still in the same positions moving
forward but you are heading directly for a t so there's no straight there's only right or left
coming up and the white toyota is going to whip it to the right so as you guys hit this turn
let's do one more check to see if anything changes if he's with jostling and i was already on the
right can i try and t-bone him or i don't know if it'd be a t-bone but maybe like half pit maneuver
to hit his back side to get him spinning yeah absolutely i want to try to shoot out his front
right tire as well okay and how are you doing that hanging out the passenger seat with the
shotgun and just awesome okay so let's get those drive rolls a two on a 50 nice 63 on a 70 63 and
what are you trying to do i guess as we come up to that t and i see him turning right i'm just
going to try to do some late braking and pass him on the turn basically awesome roll the firearms
please keith 21 on a 70 awesome and you were aiming for a tire front right tire yeah as he
takes this right turn clark you try to fishtail him you make connection however he turns into it
and begins to avoid the fishtail maneuver however keith vigna blows his front right tire as he's
doing so which would pull him harder right hard right yeah so that is going to complete the fish
tail and make that a success and john you can yeah has i mean has this pretty much brought him
to a stop uh he's gonna be sideways here in a second yeah and probably just like right in the
middle of the street okay once we stop i'm gonna jump out have my shotgun trained on him and stand
there until you guys can move to get him out because i'm not trying to pop around so john
what are you doing where's your car going i'll just go around to the rear of his car since you
guys are in a position to go like to block him from the front we can just get them blocked in
basically yeah are are you picturing our car i'm picturing me my car and his car parallel facing
opposite directions oh okay i was picturing you okay then i'll get in front of him yeah and you
guys get behind him or whatever yeah that's good so i've got shotgun trained as soon as you get out
of the car you've got a shotgun in your hands and he is going to begin firing at you okay are you
going to attempt to take cover or fire back so if i was coming up to his passenger side i'm gonna
jump towards the back of his car so that he doesn't have a good aim on me and try to like get
by the trunk of his car and kind of take cover and try to i want to get a good shot on him but i'm not
i don't want to like shoot at him yet i don't want to try to kill him but i want to get at a good
angle where he can't hit me but i could if i had to get him absolutely so he he fires a few shots
breaks out the glass of his uh the on the passenger side of the white toyota and then
in the passenger backseat side he shoots out that glass too as he's trying to get at you
i believe that would make it john's turn john tries to remember his training like officers
are under fire so cops would just be like wasting this dude for sure yeah but but we we need him
yeah that's why i didn't just immediately blow his fucking head off can we uh can we tell from
the shots or see what kind of gun he's using is it just a pistol it's a pistol yeah so how many
shots has he fired off at this point four couple i'll pop out of my cruiser and keep talking to him
through the intercom put down your weapon we just want to talk maybe you know about this goo can i
from my angle see if i know this guy have i seen him before i know that this is charles's car
do it can i tell it's charles yeah okay it looks like charles i'm gonna be on my intercom using
his name charles come on settle come on what was that voice come on hey hey charles big
old thing of helium right before charles stop shooting at him stop shooting at him
all right t what do you do okay i want to try to get around to the like passenger side of the
trunk and see is he still in inside of his car yeah with all the doors closed yeah if i like
pop up pop up over the trunk and look and see inside of his car through the back window is his
arm still out like trying to shoot or like what can i see looking inside i mean yeah he's in the
front he's in the driver's seat he is looking your direction he's kind of looking all around
but he just fired back through there and so he's panicky how would you feel if i was him bad
probably probably not good probably like a shouldn't have broken the law
um can i try to like open up the well shit that's stupid what do you do no that's what do you do i
fire off a warning shot of the shotgun to where maybe like a couple pellets hit like the side of
his ear or his head the rest just go like like a like a like a but not right at him okay so
you're firing away from him into the car yeah but you're not firing across his face bow i'm
not trying to like shoot directly into his head okay but like if a little spray gets on him
okay roll firearms for me i fail
and you had a shotgun so go ahead and
uh let's see is that essentially a called shot like yeah like near it like not trying to hit
someone is just as hard as hitting someone exactly where you want to also i am thinking this is like
buckshot not like a slug yeah yeah he just wanted to grace his face right with a couple pellets not
all the pain refreshing spray mist of pellets yeah wake him up a little bit it's so good
yeah so go ahead and roll 2d6 for me
shit okay um
so you uh you blast into this car you were trying to shoot to the right of him
but you really you just fired directly into the back of his seat there is a mist of red
going all over the front of the car as the horn begins to blare and the slumped body of charles
is leaning directly into the steering wheel his face making the horn incessant
john lee pettimore lets off a couple of panic shots towards the van when he sees all that
happen as the as the windshield just like turns red all of a sudden he just a couple and where
did they go into me oh no crit fail 77 oh fuck you fire off and uh you hear the the distinctive
pop of a tire as you shoot out clark's front right tire on his cruiser sorry clark i'm taking cover
ricochets are going on as you take cover i think you saw
what happened and then heard more shots coming your way what do you want to do open fire back
uh welcome to the last episode
as i duck recover whoa whoa he's dead he's dead guys did i get him i think i think keith did
you you almost got me though guys fuck i did not mean to do that i'm i'm coming around to
the driver's side yeah you just wanted to graze him i get it the horn is still blaring is he
still slumped oh yeah i open the door and i pull him back how much is left of him as you open up
the door you see he is bleeding out all sorts of crazy basically from his nipples to his uh
seat belt is just shredded confetti person nipples a seat belt whoo you know that's bad hate to see
that uh but is he alive yeah i yell over at him did i did i kill him do you want to roll uh first
aid please this would be to see if he i mean i'd take it you're not you know i don't know what
you're trying to do but 28 on a 30 oh well done you grab at his i don't know pulse one of them
which pulse do you want to grab his intestines you get right up in his butt hole just reaches
right into the cavity that one of his chest as you put your fingers around his still beating
i got you buddy and i manually beat his heart for him
it's all canon uh as you reach for his pulse you're not finding it but you think you know
where you are you think you you know your way around a wrist or a neck however no pulse is
being felt by you as i as i'm looking for the pulse i'm using my radio to call in an ambulance
and then i want to do a flashlight in his eyes do i get any response no he's dead damn yeah
i'm gonna use 30 points of luck to no no oh shit do you guys all want to throw in 10 points of luck
to revive this guy and interview him i kind of would avoid death is 30 yeah 10 points each oh
so that's for you personally we can't do that to other people on other people you know that's not
what it says on the car in here in dnd there's a spell that you can talk to the dead i'm gonna
use that let's see that one yeah i'm gonna get out my dnd rulebook real quick holy shit that
would be hell has anybody ever done that like four four different role-playing like mechanics
all together that'd be interesting let's start it now or a fucking nightmare oh for sure you'd
have to be real intimate with all of them that'd be wild though i'm i'm barely i'm barely intimate
with this one so okay well yeah i pop up out of the side kill the guy boys he's he's dead
he's he's real dead ah fucking i hate paperwork can we cover this up maybe just make it look like
a road accident or something let's search his car yeah i want to search him to pat him down
check his pockets in the middle of the street a crowd begins to gather around you all i fire a
couple more shots into the air and tell them to disperse roll firearms what are we around up up
here 59 on a 60 how big of a crowd are we talking here it's not there's like like three hundreds of
people gathered there's like four people who stopped what they're doing to watch and a couple
cars like two cars have pulled over and they're just sitting there staring phones out do they
take off when i shoot in the air do you actually shoot yeah oh then yeah they leave okay uh-huh
one of the people just gets into somebody else's car and they they're nice enough to take them out
of this scary situation that's how you maintain law and order i cast obliviate on them so they
forget what they just saw harry potter universe canon now okay so as you guys are looking through
this car you see there's a there's a handgun in his hand in the seat next to him there's a
different handgun does it have any crazy um features no they both look relatively normal
handguns uh there's also a mag light sitting in the shotgun seat and in the back seat there's a
rifle a burner phone a wallet and some keys all in the back seat all in the back seat i want to
look at that burner phone too what numbers are stored in there i'm gonna grab the wallet as you
look through the burner phone everything has been deleted off of it there's literally no information
on it whatsoever and as you open up the wallet there's an army id for a billy harrison he's a
pretty nondescript dude pretty young he doesn't look like charles he's bald no it's not charles
pretty fit dude bald guy young guy probably in his uh late 20s early 30s wouldn't it say on the id
he's got shut up he's got pretty intense eyes he is 29. anything uh interesting about the keys
particularly if they have a storage unit it's a key ring with one car key on it does it seem like
this toyota was his can i check the glove box the keys to the toyota are still in the toyota
what is in the glove box there is almost nothing in the glove box there's like the manual for the
there's not like any interest no there's no registration on the one key on the one key ring
is there a make of the car did we check the trunk yet did we check the trunk yet it's a van right
are we checking trunk yet an suv what is it toyota toyota i think i was picturing a white carola
for some reason i was picturing like a tundra i actually just pictured us chasing a ford bronco
this whole time if i did it by charles the guy just killed him we'll say dodge why not dodge
how about dodge on the key ring john lee pettymore i want to check the trunk too since i'm already
back here okay so as you pop open the trunk there is a man is completely unconscious is it billy
harrison he looks exactly like billy harrison he is alive though yeah he's unconscious he's
unconscious and he is wearing a black t-shirt and jeans is there anything else yeah underneath him
also in the trunk is a police uniform a set of scrubs and a black suit this guy likes costume
parties can i try to wake him up is he tied up or is he just stuck back there conscious his hands
are bound with a chain spooky uh i want to try to wake him up shake him shake him up clark as you
are going over charles he has id on him named charles donovan he is from the city he's got a
burner phone on him and he has a piece of paper two addresses on the piece of paper you recognize
them both immediately one is john peter's house and the other is the piston pig farm
the keys that are in the ignition of the white toyota include a key to a room at the motel my
motel the one that keith vigna is staying at and there is a key fob for dirty dog grooming
charles donovan also has scratches all over his arms legs and face do they look like
scratches from a dog or a human those are the only two or like brushes brush if he was running
oh yeah are they claw marks i think that would be easy they're not claw marks okay i like what
you're thinking uh but no yeah his skin is definitely uh red and irritable looking as if
it has been scratched repeatedly in multiple places but not not breaking the skin like
they're not wounds a couple seem to have bled but mostly not and no discernible pattern no so
it doesn't look like he got scratched up by brush or something not really okay no well now what
there's a lot we could do actually uh let me look at the burner phone in his pocket
there is nothing on it yeah no it's it's wiped clean
shit not even like a recent calls list what was the last selfie he took
holding the molotov you should show it to his family no he wouldn't have any recent calls
there he would have deleted him by now keith you are slapping this bald man
in the back of the trunk and he's not waking up your slapping is not helping guys look what i
found who i found could we do a search rule to like more intensely search the vehicle sure
one holy shit 13 on a 20 i get it also not as good as him okay he starts the fuck out of this
car though maybe a tantalizing piece of information that might have escaped his lips before his chest
was exploded john as you are looking over the stuff you decide to pull out dump them all on the
ground yeah you dump it all out in the middle of the road the police uniform that he has matches
the police uniform that the three of you wear here in contention okay and he has a badge on there
a real badge you would know that it's not but it looks and no other identification like it says
officer kissel is it a contention badge yeah is it pretty good yeah no this is like a pretty good
fake the set of scrubs has an id that says dr zebrowski and the black suit inside one of the
pockets has fbi credentials for an agent parks does the do the scrubs have a name of a hospital
on them no good question what do we have in contention just like a clinic correct and then
the city has a hospital oh also with your search role sorry because you critically succeeded
as you're looking over charles's body helping clark discern the scratches that are all over him
you see that the scratches are in the pattern of of hands and it looks like a human human's hands
made all these scratches all over charles okay so i guess i would like to get drew looking up
all these credentials to see if there actually is a dr zebrowski somewhere in state following up on
the fbi credentials for agent parks see if that's a real person and then uh john is gonna go over
and start changing the tire on clark's cruiser nice it feels bad about that the ambulance arrives
on the scene before they get to either body i'm gonna have them take a look at my foot
you got anything for this yeah does this count as a hospital visit
can you roll to get some foot hit points back
yeah i like that go ahead and roll d4 or that's a d6
that's what you get uh they throw a band-aid at you now they um they have a splint with them that
you can throw on and it'll make walking much easier charles is dead so i'd like to direct
them to um trying to wake up billy yeah they attempt to bring billy harrison to consciousness
and do not succeed and immediately they're like we got to get him help they throw him on a stretcher
and put him in the back of the ambulance i'm gonna go with him in the ambulance just in case
he's a bad guy or if he's a good guy i can ask him too perfect i grab keith don't kill this one man
i'm not a murderer not this one uh keith go ahead and roll sanity for me real quick for murdering
charles 18 on a 40 nice
justified police action in the line of duty i mean this is is this the first time i've
killed someone i would think so i think yeah this is my first murder by cop how many people
have we killed in this podcast so far you killed one i killed you and i've killed one
and you haven't killed anybody yet pussy that's surprising yeah
all right so keith hops in the ambulance as it goes away a little notepad out of my back pocket
make a tick mark and shut it back yes he's pulling away keep keep him
how are you
out of hearing
heaven I'm drowning out
hollow noise
If nobody knows
Yeah nobody knows
Fight fight
street me down
takes me back
to where you're from
don't stop
a dime of
devotion
to only one
If nobody knows
Yeah nobody knows
Tell me you love us