Salutations, my fellow interdimensional friends.
It's your time and space traveling trash sommelier,
Wolf the dog.
And I'm live from somewhere, some time,
but probably still from 694.2, maybe?
Listen, I don't know where the fuck I am right now.
It's somehow both dark and bright
and there is everything and nothing all at once.
There's also a possum wearing a cowboy hat.
His name is Jeremy.
Uh, anyway, this week's Howlin' with Wolf
is from Newman's Necromorium Funeral Home.
Who got Wolf here reading an ad copy
all because they tweeted about the show
and tagged at Pretending Pod,
a smart business decision in this cutthroat business
of dead folk parlors?
They right.
Ever wondered what to do with your dead friends and family?
Here at Newman's Necromorium Funeral Home,
we take the wonder out of death.
For an astronomical and non-negotiable
price of our choosing,
you won't have to worry about the finer details.
Still not sure?
Meet Stu.
Stu says, the dead make great listeners.
Except Lewis.
That guy keeps screaming that he just wants to go home
and there's been a terrible mistake.
Classic Lewis, now that you sold on the idea,
let us handle you dead.
We'll even wear gloves.
Well damn, thanks Newman.
I would advise you to not listen
to the screams of Classic Lewis.
Every Lewis I've ever known has been a lie and a cheat.
This one is probably no exception.
And every Lewis is also a rat bastard.
But especially a Lewis named Classic Lewis.
Remember, if you want to write up something
for your wolf to howl, tag at Pretending Pod
on Twitter or Instagram.
Or write up a five star review on the Apple Podcasts.
Huge shout out to a concerned observer,
Lobster Memories and Huge Earn for writing reviews.
It makes this interdimensional traveling little wolfie
so gosh darn happy.
And if you want to meet other listeners,
AKA super rad weirdos like yourself,
check out the link to Discord
and the subreddit in the show notes.
Our community isn't big enough yet to be toxic
and it's a real good time to hang out.
Honestly, I'm just there for the memes and pet pics.
But there's a good amount of role play chat as well.
Or maybe you want to put together a one shot
with a group of other listeners.
Bubble gum tree my babies.
The links, as always, are in the damn show notes.
And not to be weird about it,
but if you've listened to the entire first season
of Pretending to be People
and you've been considering joining the Patreon
but you've never done it,
the link to the Patreon's in the show notes.
It's worth it.
And apologies to the PTBP crew
for letting you in on this little secret.
But you can actually sign up for like five bucks.
Then listen to all the bonus episodes in a matter of days.
Then delete your pledge.
They can't stop you.
Is it cooler to just let it ride
and support the creative dreams of some small town weirdos
that you really like to listen to?
No, it's obviously cooler to rip these dumb idiots off.
But you do whatever feels right.
I heard they just finished up another arc
of a 13 episode long mostly homebrew campaign.
And the 26th episode is a session zero
for the upcoming run of Control Copy,
a Delta Green scenario by Dennis Detwiller
chosen by a poll over on patreon.com slash pretending pod.
The link's in the show notes as I have mentioned many times
but you can probably remember it.
It's just patreon.com slash pretending pod.
Sign up for the Circle of Knowledge shirt club
before Halloween and you can receive an exclusive shirt
a whole month sooner.
And check out the YouTube channel.
The composer, some freak named Justin,
continues to slowly upload tracks from the show
onto the ultimate TTRPG playlist.
Guess what that damn link is, you freaks?
Also in the show notes, you can find a link
to a music video for this hot new track.
It's Kudzu with no backbone.
So.
It's Q&A time.
Hell yeah.
Whoa.
The season is done.
The season is over
and it's time to answer questions about the season.
Now we get to find out what happened.
Yeah, in some ways,
I like to think that most of the questions
as far as what actually happened have been answered.
Although, I understand
that that's not the case
and that's okay.
Dude, today a coworker of mine asked me for my phone number
so that they could send me a playlist.
And what are the seven,
not 10 numbers that you told me?
No, I won't be saying that.
He sent me this playlist.
Oh, hell yes.
And it had,
what's the band that sings Radioactive?
Oh, is that Imagine Dragons?
Imagine Dragon Deez Nuts Across Your Face.
Oh, no.
I kept wanting to tell it,
but I was like, wait until we're recording.
We've been hanging out for a while
and I'm not sure I've ever been more proud of you
that you held onto that.
I feel like I got hit by a train.
I did get,
I got Joe with a-
He got me before we started recording
with such a genuine one.
I was like-
It was really good and I was like,
oh, you should have saved it for the pod.
I didn't even see that coming.
I had another one.
I straight up don't,
I don't know if I was in here,
if I wasn't listening.
You were not.
But it was a,
dude,
I just like,
it was like both of us looking at our phones.
I was like,
dude, did you see that thing about the article
about Cho Ken today?
And I went,
Cho Ken?
Oh my God.
Yeah, Cho Ken on Deez Nuts.
Jesus.
I was so genuinely,
I have not heard about this.
Please tell me.
You're like, who's Cho Ken?
My
God.
Anyway,
that was good.
Yeah.
Proud of you.
I think that's enough.
We have enough questions for that to be
our jumping off point.
So let's dive into these.
I'm gonna go ahead and start
with a question here from me.
I'm Zach and I have a question.
We asked for questions,
comments or compliments on Twitter and Reddit and
Zach felt he didn't get enough compliments.
So.
So I'm gonna start this thing off
by complimenting myself.
Zach,
I don't say this a lot,
but
you actually finished a thing.
Good job, man.
That's huge, dude.
Yeah.
All right.
That was genuine.
And I didn't expect to
negate my horrible self-talk to myself,
but here we are.
And so I do have a compliment right off the bat
for the three of you,
each of you.
Joe,
I'll start with you as it's-
Oh, literally individually.
Do you also have one for the group?
I literally didn't plan this at all.
I am not looking at anything.
I didn't have these planned,
but I have a compliment for each of you.
Joe,
having you as a player makes my job
as a GM more fun.
Dope, dude.
Legitimately watching your reactions
to things that happen
and how stoked you get
and how into the story you are at all times
makes me,
oh, I was gonna say horny,
but I'm being genuine.
No, you can say it.
That's so nice, dude.
At first, I thought it was just
a veiled jab at Luke and I.
But no, it makes it more fun as a player at the table.
Yeah, it totally does.
So moving on from the compliments.
End of praise.
No, moving on to Luke.
Luke, you are without a doubt
the most fun and spontaneous person
I've ever like hung out with even.
You are extremely enjoyable to be around
due to your ability to take any situation
and find the levity in it.
I appreciate that so much.
And I specifically within the realm of role-playing,
anytime that I feel you grab the reins out of my hands,
I'm nothing but overjoyed.
Hell yeah.
Thank you.
And back to the questions.
I can't do the same joke again.
And Tom.
You could.
I thought, I almost thought you were just gonna go
into the question, so I was like, I was fine with it.
Thank you.
Thomas, you make jokes that are literally standing
on the precipice of like in and out of game
in a way that, in my opinion,
speaks to the soul of like how we role-play.
Your ability to constantly have one hand in hot water
and one hand in cold water is like absolutely excellent.
Also, I respect you and any opinion that you bring
to the table, regardless of how opposite
of what I've just said is.
Basically, you.
You are one of the only people whose opinion I trust.
Thank you.
Also, the earliest stuff about me being the voice
of a role-playing generation, I wonder if you said yes.
Agreed.
Legitimately though, I have a hard time taking
anyone else's opinion.
I'm very controlling.
I think we all know this and I respect that a lot of you
and I think you're a great dude.
Thanks, bro.
Same, please.
I love you guys so much
and you have changed my life for the better.
Same.
Back at you, man.
I like you so much.
I like barely, I barely remember a time with you.
I love so much about you.
I like don't remember a time in my life
not playing this, even though it's only been.
Yeah, I've blacked out all memories of life.
Even though it's been more.
Yeah, we've been doing it for like 10 years.
No, I love you too.
We love you too.
Fuck all that.
Shut up.
All right, we've got a question from.
Oh, wait, no, no.
You said you had a question for us.
We have to jerk each other off real quick.
To finish.
All right, so the question that I have is actually
a question that I will ask at the top of the next episode,
the next Q&A episode.
I have a personal question for you guys.
It's a teaser for next week.
We could say you can expect to hear Justin
on that next episode.
That's right, that's right.
Justin will be here for next week's Q&A.
Check back in at 8.30.
Justin's busy right now.
All right, let's dive in here.
We've got a question from.
It was all a snow globe.
They say, I hope it's okay to ask a few.
It is.
That was a classic reference to that one show.
I was gonna say, do you millennials get that reference?
Yeah, it's the thing where Chris O'Dowd
dropped the snow globe in Travel Man.
Okay.
It's Saint something, right?
Oh, okay.
Saint Elmo.
It's a spoiler no matter what.
Once I'm a very drunk mom.
Be careful.
Oh yeah, just in case anybody's trying to watch
Men in Black.
That hospital show or whatever.
They were in a marble and the marble had fake snow in it.
Was it Saint Elsewhere?
Saint Elsewhere, yeah.
Okay, so real quick.
Once I'm a very drunk mom in a bar in Colorado.
It could be so much quicker.
Once I'm a very drunk mom in a bar in Colorado
asked me how old I was and I was like 29 at the time
and I said 29 and she goes,
oh, you're just like my son.
You're a millennium.
I am.
I'm a millennium.
That's really good.
Yeah.
Okay, that's perfect.
They asked, it was all snow globe, asks,
who was the person in the woods in episode six?
Charles Donovan.
Okay.
I should have asked who you thought it was
but that would just belabor the whole part.
Moving on.
I would say, oh.
Next question.
Who is the ambiguously British man
in the circle of white powder?
I believe they are talking about the person
that Lindsay's character talks to
in the contention woods arc.
That was an agent of Pisces.
Delta Green has a British wing of its existence
and they are called Pisces.
And I believe that man had a tattoo somewhere
and I believe, I did not look this up,
but I think that I made that tattoo a reference
to the fact that he was in Pisces.
It might've even been a fish.
Like it straight up might've been a fish tattoo.
So, okay.
So if any of us had run into him,
we would have known right away.
Yes.
Next question.
Fish, Pisces.
So that's deep lore for somebody
who knows Delta Green lore.
Oh, that's some real deep lore.
That wasn't for us.
No.
Zach, yeah.
Speaking of like your own deep lore,
I totally thought you were like,
oh yeah, that was Pisces.
They were competing against Myriad.
You never really ran into them,
but they were there the whole time.
You guys literally never ran into anyone from Pisces.
My cool fish men brigade.
Actual company behind, was it Bar Corp?
Bar Corp owned by Pisces.
No.
So next question.
What does Joe smell like?
What flavor vape do you have?
Yeah.
I got some strawberry milk tonight.
Oh, that is an answer.
All right.
That's pretty much what he smells like just in general.
I've known him since middle school.
Joe, middle school.
You've got the option.
Chocolate, vanilla.
Is it called vanilla milk?
Regular.
2%.
Chocolate, milk, or strawberry?
Strawberry.
Oh, all right.
And moving on, what was the asylum all about?
Specifically the Satan plot line
that apparently got dropped.
Yeah, because I did mention at one point
that the Satan, somebody asked about it mid-game.
And I was like, yeah, like as an NPC,
I think I said, you guys didn't look into that very much,
so we didn't worry about it.
I thought that you guys were gonna try to follow
the agents, the dead president's cell,
Kennedy, McKinley, and Harrison
back to wherever they came from,
or at least try to hitch more of a ride on what they had.
But as we were role-playing,
it just felt right to kind of leave you out in the cold.
I could use that sentence for all role-playing.
Yeah, that's your go-to instinct as a GM.
And I'm trying to get better at it, all right?
We're all growing.
That's one thing that I'm gonna work on.
No, it's fun and it leads to, I don't know.
But if we do wanna not go 113 episodes again.
Yeah, exactly.
We go to the mill.
So what was the asylum all about?
So basically there's a woman there named,
code name Satan, not actually birth name Satan.
And she was in charge of running these different teams
of essentially what Delta Green Lore would call cowboys.
So your A through Z cells.
But I decided instead of the modern day
using A through Z cells,
they would have gotten rid of it by then
and come up with some fun alternatives.
So I thought dead presidents was a fun combo of things.
So I went with that.
But that is also where K cell was run out of,
because they originally started with the alphabet cells
as cowboys, essentially fighting against
the unnatural threat to the world,
not with government oversight.
And so that is what the asylum is specifically all about.
The woman who runs it, she's a black and white character.
She's got a lot going on.
She lives in the middle.
Yeah, I don't know.
Everyone's got like a middling agenda.
In Delta Green, from what I can tell,
there aren't a lot of like specifically good
or specifically bad people.
Some people get turned bad by circumstance,
but everyone's kind of like trying to do their best
with the hand they've been dealt.
I don't know.
So that's what was happening at the asylum.
If somebody else asks a question about it later,
which I bet they do, I might add to that.
And that part of Delta Green,
it just really stresses me out when we're playing it,
because it's not like real life where you know right away,
like, oh, do they believe in Jesus?
They're good or bad.
You can just know, and all the uncertainty
and like the grayness, it gives me a headache.
Yeah.
No, thank you.
Hey, why don't you just ask the NPCs if they believe in Jesus?
Are you a good person or a bad person?
So they finish it out.
Snow Globe finishes it out by saying,
thank you all for everything.
This is by far my favorite podcast,
which is just a very nice thing.
Thanks, us too.
It's a nice thing to say.
It is ours as well.
Ain't on a no, no, no.
Is that how you say it?
Which is No Way Hang On.
That's one of our beautiful mods
over on the subreddit and the discord.
We've got a question.
What's y'all's favorite karaoke jam?
Soak Up The Sun by Shirl Crow.
That's good.
Soak Up The Sun is real good.
I just do Beatles songs,
cause I know the words already.
Yep.
And what are Beatles songs?
It's this band that I've been into lately.
They're kind of coming up.
And Thomas, do you do karaoke?
I actually never have.
Really?
Really.
Wait, when we did karaoke at my house, did you not sing?
Oh, I probably did.
But like drunk, living room karaoke.
I've never been in a bar full of people,
like strangers, selected a song and sang that song.
Yeah.
Thomas, you were actually there though
for my birthday a couple of years ago.
After the ball game.
Yeah, you got me tickets to a Cardinals game
for my birthday.
That was a surprise, which was fucking rad.
We went and hung out and watched a day game in St. Louis
that I didn't know was happening.
Yeah, I got you those tickets,
not your wife and my partner.
You know what?
It actually makes more sense
that it was my wife who got me those tickets.
And then after the ball game, we like-
There's a chance I totally pitched in.
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know, man.
Who knows?
But I would bet.
I was just willing to give you full credit here
on the recording.
Oh yeah, just like if either of the other people
involved heard that, they would probably be like, what?
Oh, they're not listening.
They're not listening to this?
That's fair.
And so I sing my go-to karaoke jam,
which we have posted a video of me singing
on Instagram and Twitter.
You can find it there.
And that is me singing-
Oh baby, baby.
How was I supposed to know?
My go-to is Hit Me Baby One More Time by Britney Spears,
specifically because it is just out of my range.
Zach, I was actually going through my Instagram
story archives the other day and came across those videos.
And do you remember the guy who sung After You?
No, I was on a high.
He was very red and drunk.
Oh yeah, classic.
Like karaoke.
The Cardinals colors.
Well, that's Neil.
Looked like yellow teeth, red face.
It looked like most of the guys at a Cardinals game,
like meaning like late forties, a polo.
And they love the polos.
He was shit-faced, but passionate.
And he was singing Closing Time at like 3 p.m. I bet.
I love that song.
Compliment from ainonanonono.
Nice cock, bro.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Wouldn't you like to know?
All right, and a question from ainonanonono.
I remember Zach delivering some well-deserved praise
to Dirk Gently's Holistic Detective Agency,
which shares some fun elements with season one of PTBP.
What other foundational media or artists
have influenced y'all in this season
as handler and players?
Anyone have an inspiration to you as a player
or just to give you like a head space
of what this game we're playing was?
I just do whatever I want.
Yeah, there, yeah, yeah.
The most truthful answer.
Yeah, Wild West Arc was all Deadwood in my brain.
Yeah.
Deadwood was what I would reference in my brain.
Mine was Red Dead Redemption.
In general, just all police media.
Yeah, like that pop culture is inundated with
so just lots of cop stereotypes
and then the actual place we live for.
Yeah, for sure.
The actual place we live and like going hiking
or just visiting other small towns around
and getting a feel for what life is like in a smaller town.
I actually drove through Mountain Grove.
I mean, literally just passed it.
You literally drove through.
I literally drove through.
You're the one who drove through Mountain Grove.
I drove through.
You drove through the downtown just like
Mountain Grove.
Blues Brothers style like that mall.
Hung out for a little bit, just drove around.
That's the small town that I stole the map from
for contention.
Oh, nice.
Oh, really?
I stole the map from Mountain Grove, Missouri.
The layout of the roads and things.
Yeah, I did.
I dated someone and grew up there
and when I was like 19 and we drove out there a few times
to hang out with her parents.
And it was, it's very small.
It's really small, yeah.
You've been to contention then.
Yeah, you've been to contention.
All right, yeah, Dirk Gently's Holistic Detective Agency
and like-
Anything ever Delta Green or not Delta Green,
but like Lovecraft.
I've literally never like read Lovecraft.
I've seen some movies.
It's good.
I don't read, but read Dirk Gently's
Holistic Detective Agency.
I took a lot from that.
Compliment, thanks for making me laugh so hard.
I cried a few times.
Wow.
I'm glad we did it to you
because we did it to ourselves a lot.
Oh yeah.
We had more fun making it than you did listening to it.
Oh, 100%.
And I'm glad our podcast made you so hard, you cried.
L-Elephant, L-Elephant, L-Elephant, L-Elephant.
L-Elephant, L-Elephant, L-Elephant.
I think it's just L-Elephant.
L-Elephant, L-Elephant.
Like their name is probably L.
Congrats on finishing the first season.
Thanks.
Thank you.
There have been a lot of little Easter eggs
for people paying a lot of attention.
There was, quote, no backbone being,
oh, by the way, we're doing spoilers.
Yeah, big time.
We might need Dog to say that.
Yeah, well.
Who's Dog?
We'll have Dog.
Joe's on a first, last name basis.
Last name basis, yeah.
We know each other pretty well.
Joe's on a last name basis with Dog.
No, he has to call him Mr. Dog.
Over the years, we've gotten to know each other
pretty well.
I think I can call him Dog.
No backbone being a more relevant song than first thought.
Yes, classic.
The Wizard of Oznod with what everyone lost
slash was searching for in the raid
on Marvin Glass's compound.
I think at one point you named some corpses
after the last podcast on the left crew.
Actually, those were the costumes that Billy Harrison
was tied up in the back of Charles Donovan's trunk
and also in Charles Donovan's trunk
was Charles Donovan's extra disguises
in which he used the last podcast on the left crew
as covers.
Oh, what are some of your favorite Easter eggs
no one has mentioned yet?
What's an anagram?
Am I thinking of the right?
Whether it's all mixed up.
It's all mixed up, yes.
Okay, so Tildy B. Mitchell is an anagram.
Oh, fuck, what's it for though?
I refuse to look for anagrams in every name you give us.
I'm looking up anagram solver.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not gonna give it to you because it's like half baked.
It's like lit B.
It's lit.
How do you spell Tildy?
Oh, T-I-L-D-E B as B
and then Mitchell, M-I-T-C-H-E-L-L.
But lit is part of it?
It's lit.
Fucking good, dude.
Meet Bill Ted.
Wait, are you for real?
Good anagram, bro.
What, Bill Ted?
Yeah, like Bill and Ted because they time travel.
So you had the time travel and the fact that she was
zombie-ish or undead-ish from that early on
that you just named her.
Holy fuck, that's cool.
I thought that came later.
I thought those revelations came later.
That is what Keith might name his meat monster.
Lich meet Bill Ted.
Nice, good one.
But that was her name.
Tildy B. Mitchell.
Yeah, like exactly.
Like from birth, right?
Yeah.
I guess that.
She was destined.
That was just fun for Zach.
That's just a fun detail outside of the canon.
Yeah, that doesn't mean anything.
It's an Easter egg.
That's just a Zach fun time.
What's another Easter egg?
There's one that a fan found that you definitely put in,
none of us caught was the Mary Coles Institute
or whatever it was.
It was an acronym for consume, was it?
Consume, yeah.
The Coles Orphanage colon new school under modern etiquette.
Somebody pointed that out on Twitter and it blew my mind.
I thought that I made it so stilted
that you guys would be like, why is it that?
Every time you do that, I'm just like,
I'm not gonna make Zach feel bad about his English.
Well, now you know to make fun of me
and reveal my hidden secrets,
but also it might hurt my feelings.
So, you know, it's a time when we're like,
that must be one of your weird things, right?
And you're just like, no, no, no, no, Thomas.
Anyway, so that's one.
Consume is definitely one that I really liked.
Oh, this one's dumb.
This one's so dumb, but Oz Mayhem Wolf,
his brother was Elby, E-L-B-Y, which is not a name.
But like pounds or?
Yeah, L-B and ounces.
That's good, that's a good one.
I like that.
That was real stupid.
That's real good.
Did we ever meet Elby?
No, he just talked about him.
He mentioned him, yeah.
Oh, okay.
He mentioned him once.
Keith Vigna, Vigna is a type of bean or something.
Yeah, Vigna is a genus, I think, of bean.
It's a science version of a bean.
It's a sciency bean.
It's a science bean.
John Lee Pettymore is named from the song,
Copperhead Road by Steve Earle.
We kind of made his dad something else,
but I guess Kevin is literally the character
in Copperhead Road.
Exactly.
Clark was born with a tail.
Just a little Easter egg for you.
And never got it removed.
He had it the whole campaign.
The whole time.
If you just looked at his back,
you would have seen it wagging every now and then.
If you'd done an alertness check,
you actually had detailed emotional responses for the tail.
I had rolls I could have made.
For those of you who are gonna go back
and listen through the campaign,
you'll find a slight whooshing sound.
I do remember one last Easter egg.
Right before we started this whole thing,
Zach was like, okay, your character is God.
This is all a dream that he's created
for the other characters.
So just remember that at the end.
I was like, okay, yeah, for sure.
I wrote it down.
The only thing in my notes.
You're God.
What are you looking at?
Trying to find my cheat sheet.
Just show you guys my cheat sheet
where I had listed like.
There was, I was frantically reading as fast as I could.
Was trying to consume all the little nuggets
as it went by.
There was a bunch of stuff in there, man.
I was on top of a lot of stuff that was happening
on certain time restraints for a while.
Yeah, that was a weird time when you guys were like
at the end of your time in contention
when all the moving parts were happening.
And I was trying to keep track of it.
All right, let's move on.
Hope it's okay to do two questions.
It is, we'll keep going.
A little while ago,
I had an idea about a connection to Martin Cupertino
being an influential person wanting to create cube
during the calm comfy campground arc
and the contention boys chasing down the origins
of what they called ball.
I get that Martin was a Steve Jobs stand in,
but was the cube versus ball connection intentional
or am I grasping at straws?
I'm gonna turn this one over to Thomas for the answer.
Unfortunately, grasping at straws cube
was just a parody of the original iMac.
And then like the crazy promises about cube
were just like Zombocom style like nonsense
and over promising like tech world.
Like this will solve every problem anybody's ever had.
It's the normal stuff.
It's a very, very, very simple broad parody of Steve Jobs.
We got to think about our pace.
Cause I think we have 50 total in three.
Yeah, we're on page one of nine.
The reason it was called, we are 30 minutes in.
The reason it was called cube
is cause the iMac is like a cube shape kind of.
Nice.
Soren Ash asks.
Oh yeah, you guys keep going, I'm gonna go pee.
Oh, I didn't know you were peeing right now.
This isn't one we can answer.
We could try.
I'll read it and we'll try.
Okay, so the things I've racked up over time.
How did Marvin get removed from the myriad hive mind?
That's a question I've had myself.
Yeah, so here's my best guess.
Marvin, he just didn't want to be in it anymore.
That was my, exactly what I was gonna say.
He just wanted it more.
Like kind of the odd, but he like he wanted out and he did.
I can't remember if I said this on the podcast
or if it was after a session one time,
but I wondered if he was some link in an evolution
between Tildy and what we know as myriad,
whether he was in the middle
or he was an evolved beyond myriad.
I think he was just like a funny guy.
He's just a wild and crazy dude.
Next question.
Yeah, were Marvin's sons his biological sons?
Yes.
Was the glass syndicate just a puppet
for some greater organization?
Yes, next question.
Yeah, yes and yes.
What was Stan and Nancy's agenda
and by extension that of the city asylum?
Zach never knew.
He didn't actually have.
And yes, he did just keep forgetting her name.
He wanted, they were actually,
the city asylum was trying to research the brown note.
Right, yeah.
Okay, we've covered the first few.
Yeah, we got it all Zach, pretty thoroughly.
Do you guys have any questions?
Should I add in anything?
I was wondering how did Marvin get removed
from myriad hive mind?
How did Marvin remove himself?
Smart question, Joe.
Yeah, good question.
Okay, so Marvin was like the fallen angel essentially
of these creatures
and that's all I ever really thought about it.
I like it though, that's also cool.
Well, that would also be a great campaign,
a mini campaign.
Yeah, it really, I honestly had a certain thought
as we were recording from 100 on.
I was like, I could do at least three or four more spin-offs.
Like we could do this theoretically forever.
Yeah, oh yeah, Jesus Christ Ministries
could have easily had its own one shot,
which I was planning for a while
and then abandoned at a certain point.
Well, that was Fergie's thing, right?
Yeah.
Fergie's whole crime organization.
With all those little kids that were all like androids.
Yeah, oh, we could play Android orphans.
Yeah, like that would be very fun.
So that's all I really ever had for Marvin.
Oh, were his sons biological?
No, they were not.
What was their deal?
Were they created?
No, he was dealing in trafficking
and so he took two of the strongest ones
from the Den of Sin and made them his sons.
Gotcha, so they know they're not his sons.
They have been, they had been like brainwashed
to basically just like the Glass family was their family.
They were Glass boys like through and through,
but one of them had their mind melted
before the season started
and the other one got sent to the dark place.
So they were not role played through very thoroughly
just because of their circumstances.
Another question here, biological sons.
Was the Glass syndicate just a puppet
for some greater organization?
The Glass syndicate was not a puppet.
The Glass syndicate was held strong by Marvin Glass
who definitely held his own against Myriad.
That's interesting, so that's, we disagree on that.
Okay, that's fair.
What was your guys' answer?
We said yes.
And who was the hand?
We said yes, next question.
Next question, what was Man Stan Steen's agenda
and by extension that of the city asylum?
Okay, so these are two very different questions
specifically because the city asylum
was holding Stan Man Steen as a prisoner at the time.
He was let out only to go to his daughter's funeral
as a courtesy and he used that time
to get the fuck out of existence
which was his goal due to his ability to see.
He was living the same kind of life where you guys were
where his idea of the world kept changing.
Every single time something unnatural happened,
I changed the town of contention slightly
and the main clue of that change
was the name of your fourth police officer in contention
and small other changes happened
but the only one that we really stumbled across in game
was Randy Angst.
Those were like set about as little things
that could pop up if the right questions were asked
which I should have, again,
just learning how to be a better GM
pushed that theme forward.
But Stan was always aware of these changes like we were.
He very much was.
I thought they felt weird.
Yep, and so he fucked off and when he fucked off,
he landed himself in a heap of trouble
and then eventually got a hold of a phone
and needed some help from the future pulp hero overseer.
Yeah, at the end there.
So that would be a fun thing to look into.
I would love that story.
Okay, so yeah, he only showed up twice
but I thought of him as just another person
who is dealing with the same thing
where he saw what was happening in the world.
There were some other people like that as well.
Mildred Mitchell being one of them.
If you guys had talked about your fourth officer around her,
she would have gotten the name wrong like you guys had.
Were K cell and the FBI agents working for the same group?
Yes, but in different time periods.
Given that in the ending,
the FBI agents were answering to the lady
that got dubbed Satan,
it seems as though there was another pernicious element
at play and that K cell was likely opposed to them.
To clarify, my working theory is that the FBI agents
working for Satan are an M-A-R-Y-esque threat
with some evil agenda in mind.
Yes, I mean, they are as much a threat
as the group of cowboys are a threat
in traditional Delta Green lore,
which, you know, Delta Green agents are a threat, man.
That's just kind of how it happens.
Their goal is to-
Mr. Steal Your Girl.
Yeah, exactly.
And so that is the reason why the father of Maggie Cook,
I almost said Tim Cook,
well, it was Jim Cook, which is why I called him that,
is Jim Cook, he worked for Satan
and that's why he had a reference to Satan in his house.
But by the end of his time,
he was working against her machinations.
So moving on, what was up with all the numbers plague deal?
What was up with the numbers plague deal?
What was the overseer's original motivation
for setting it off?
Also, it seemed like the overseer considered that run
a quote, success, despite everyone dying on that go round.
Why?
Did we know that Joe set that off, Luke?
I have, I don't think so.
It seemed like it'd be fun.
Get the fuck out of our house.
They got into you.
That was cool.
Answer the question, Joe.
I don't have an answer.
You set off that, you were the overseer at that point.
I had not become the overseer yet.
So basically the overseer got a hold of someone
with good intentions from the other side.
I had it so that the overseer would make lots of mistakes
throughout his time because in Delta Green,
the characters traditionally 60% of the time
succeed on stuff.
And so I kept that in mind as I worked
through the overseer's plan.
And his plan for CSU and for Bar Corp was,
he did not plan for CSU to become a crazy suicide haven.
That was not his plan at all.
His plan was to give this woman, this activist,
on CSU's campus, the ability to change the mind
of Bruce Robin, the leader of Bar Corp,
and make him a better leader as the head
of the biggest corporation in the city.
And so he failed in that.
And accidentally set off a whole thing
where basically the spell went cattywampus
and the cleanup needed to happen.
It was almost working though
because didn't we run into people saying
that he's had a change of heart
and has been doing things better lately?
Exactly. That's cool.
It was so close to working, but something was off,
which is just kind of a constant in Delta Green
is that, yeah, you can use the unnatural
and sometimes the unnatural can do good things,
but overwhelmingly, if you try to use the unnatural
for good, it's not gonna work out.
And so that was my thought for that whole arc.
Dope.
I can tell you why the overseer considered it
a success.
That giant is for sure the thing
that was on his mind the whole time.
Defeating that was his most solid of a goal,
at least when I got ahold of him.
So anything that doesn't hurt that effort is a success.
Yeah.
Exactly.
A wild gazebo asks, I think that story arc,
oh, they were adding on to what was said by Soren Ash.
They said, I think that story arc needs
the most explaining.
I love how just wild everything got,
but they didn't really investigate
and find out any of the plot points there.
Yeah, they were a little preoccupied
with all the shit that I was throwing at them constantly.
Wouldn't change that because it's a great in a way
to see it all go missed.
I just wanna know what any of that is about
and exactly how high did that girl end up going.
And ShamWow Chameleon, I can tell you,
got real, real high.
Did she grab a passing helicopter at some point?
She did, she got ahold of a passing helicopter,
got even higher and then in my mind,
into the rotors.
I think she probably just convinced
the helicopter pilot to keep going up and up and up.
That's what I like to think.
Got a thing from Jake Medrano, 911 says,
always love your stuff.
Hey, that's a big always.
Thanks.
What about this?
Blip, blip, blip, blip, blip, blip, blip, blip, blip.
Blip, blip, blip, blip, blip.
You love that?
Testing your boundaries.
He did say always and boy, we're still living in it.
My God.
Anyway.
Yeah, they say Sean McCoy,
who is the creator of Mothership,
which is a RPG game,
recently did an AMA where he mentioned
he loved your podcast and hope you eventually
did a adventure campaign of Mothership.
I've been looking for a good actual play
and would love to see you guys cover that.
Hope this finds you well.
I'm found well.
Same.
Yeah, Thomas, you found well?
Yeah.
This is the question that Thomas was gonna lead us
through the answer of.
Because it is asking about Mothership and Sean McCoy.
And we are-
I don't know fucking shit about it.
He just asked me to look him up
and see if it was problematic.
As far as I can tell, no.
All right.
And as far as he can tell, no.
And that is a good thing.
So we are, with that being said,
we are super interested.
We would love to play Mothership.
It's, as far as I understand, a space RPG,
which we've all been talking about
if you wanna play a space thing sometime.
Yeah, we would love to play it.
Yeah, hey, Sean.
Take us to your GM.
Hey, Sean, hit us up.
That was a robot, but it was an alien.
Banstu says, for Thomas, Luke, Joe, and Justin,
uh-oh, I will-
Shut up, Zach.
Let us read it.
For Thomas, Luke, Joe, and Justin,
can you tell us what happened in season one?
Zach, how would you describe it?
Oh, this is a, all right.
So we're gonna cut to-
An hour each of recaps from all of us.
I think it would take even longer.
We're gonna skip this one.
My dude, it would not take me longer and an hour
to describe what happened in the season of this podcast.
I think as far as Keith goes,
what you saw was what was going on.
Wow, great answer from Luke.
Luke, what you heard is what you got.
Keith, he didn't like his brother, you know,
and then fast forward, Keith tension.
Justin doesn't need to be here.
That answer applies to all of us, but Joe.
I mean, did you guys expect the goo to when it grabs you
and slams you in the ground?
I didn't expect anything ever.
Did you?
Did you think that it killed you?
Yes.
I had a hunch that it was doing something
because we kept getting pictures from a place
that had no goo.
Yeah, no, it seemed like there was another goo place.
Yeah. Yeah.
But not at all formed like it was.
No.
It seemed way cooler to be honest.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's how it works.
Should have killed you before we got there.
Bansu also says,
can you go into a little bit of the goals of each faction
at the start of season one
and how those changed as things evolved?
One of the big changes that I decided to make happen
each time something unnatural occurred in the world
was that I would make Maggie Cook more aggressive,
angrier at her father,
and more dedicated to taking over the world
every single time something fucked up happened.
And so the Maggie Cook that you guys knew
would be different than the Maggie Cook that you talked to
anytime you ran into her for the rest of the time.
And that was attempted to be shown
through her setting up her own fake death,
where someone said like,
oh, she didn't stand up.
She didn't like hold herself the way that Maggie Cook would.
Like someone else was trying to,
Gary Daley was trying to throw like a slight hint there,
which you guys picked up on and were like,
okay, so it might not have been her.
If you guys had actually run dental through Randy Anx
with her teeth files on file,
you would have found out that the corpse was not the same,
did not have the same dental records as Chief Maggie Cook.
Gotcha.
And then when you ran into her
after your time at the Sydney Mausoleum,
you all kind of talked about how aggressive she was
and how angry she was,
which is different than we had talked about
her as a character being previous.
Right, which I was like,
yeah, the real Maggie Cook died
and this is a fake Maggie Cook.
Exactly, but essentially it was just that
each time something wild happened in this world,
you guys were the ones who were kind of split off
along with Stan Manstein, Mildred Mitchell,
certain people who continued on this specific timeline,
trajectory of contention,
as other people continued on the same path of contention
that they were on.
I forgot we were microdosing a lot
when you were writing this campaign.
Yeah.
Zach, were the time loops always planned?
No, did that come about due to the condition
the characters were in by that point?
Yes.
And the microdosing.
Also, Zach, I know you mentioned the possibility
if there was enough interest of writing up a setting guide.
So I wanna say I'd be interested in that
and TD underscore Woogie says seconded.
Hey guys, that is a goal that we are considering
putting up on the Patreon
if we're gonna put up a poll soon for patrons
to kind of let us know what they're wanting
from pretending to be people moving forward
and that will certainly be one of the options
of things that we should focus on
is writing up a campaign setting for contention,
which I think would be really fun
and also would take an astronomical amount of my time
and I would love to do that
if enough people were interested.
Edgeworth08 says, how different was episode 100 on
from what you initially thought the ending would come to?
How off the rails did it get?
Right on course.
Yeah, that's exactly what I planned.
No, we kind of talked a little bit.
We could talk about it with Justin
when he's on next episode about how I told you guys
I was trying to kill Don D. Pettymore
and it just didn't happen.
Yeah, when you guys were fighting against that rabid ball,
I really wanted to kill Don on the catwalks.
Yeah, that was the one role I ever lied about
and I feel pretty shitty about it,
but I don't actually because it got us, Justin,
through to the end, so.
But I fudged an unnatural success
because I didn't, I don't know why even.
I'm a weak man.
Oh, I wish that could have been the end of the episode,
but we have to get through more.
Okay, oh, so the answer is that it was very different
than I expected.
I wrote what was gonna happen in the next session
after we played the previous session.
I had literally nothing planned
and I planned as we played
through the end of the entire campaign.
Nice.
Yeah, that's honestly,
if you wanna know how I plan the entire fucking thing
and always have, I plan it based on what happened
the last session every time
because you can't just prep a bunch of stuff
and expect it to work
because it never does.
Nice.
What was the biggest takeaway you got
from making this podcast
and what did you learn to prepare for season two?
Shit's easy, make it up as you go.
Yep.
So more of that coming.
Yeah, the answer you just said from the previous question.
Yeah, but also for sure on season two,
gonna take your guys' advice.
I really liked the idea of, Thomas mentioned,
recapping what you learned from an NPC
after your interactions with them.
We love recaps around here.
I do that with combat, I realized,
where I kind of recap each round what happened in combat
and then thankfully later we had characters do it in game.
But yeah, I really liked the idea
of recapping what you guys get from NPCs.
Characters who would have never been there
if I hadn't heroically lied
while Zach tried to murder us on those catwalks.
Murder Justin on those catwalks.
Right guys?
Biggest takeaway from making the podcast?
Shit's easy.
Shit's easy, just make it up as you go.
Make it up as you go.
It was fun for me.
Editing is really hard and takes a long time.
Yeah.
And is really important.
Finally, I just wanted to say
that when I finally saw your faces,
I had a completely different image
from what you sounded like, except for Luke.
I thought, quote, yeah, that's about right.
It's, yeah, it's true.
I mean, we sound like normal people,
but we're all devastatingly attractive except for Luke.
No, they just could tell from my voice.
They're like that guy.
They say great stuff, guys.
What confidence that man has.
And I look forward to more content.
Tall idiot Milky Way at ShadowWorldVivo.
Oh, we're on Twitter.
It must have hashtag PTBPQ.
Love the podcast.
I've listened through all of it twice.
That's hundreds of hours.
Double hundreds.
Double, double.
What did the myriads mean at the end
when they were saying, quote, for your own safety,
please remain here?
Did they think shutting down Overseer and Ball
was a safe choice?
I was curious about this one too,
because on the re-listen,
you really hit home with that a bunch of times.
Was there a hint there that we didn't pick up on?
No, it was simply the thing that I kept hammering home
is that it's really fucking dangerous
for you guys to try to go back into the world
that Myriad was about to shut down,
was kind of the vibe that I was trying to give you.
Basically, find another option,
which you did in the weirdest way that I was not expecting.
But yeah, I was saying like,
if you go back to contention,
I am going to make you blip out of existence
because Myriad will erase your entire plane,
which includes all iterations of contention.
Sure.
I guess I assumed at the time
that also meant the place we were in, right?
The same.
Okay, I did too.
I thought for your own safety, please remain here.
We'll wipe you all out.
I was like, you're lying.
I thought it was a threat.
Nope, they were definitely gonna just leave you there.
Okay.
In my head, that's what I had planned.
That we could have lived in existence there.
Yep. Gotcha.
You definitely could have lived in existence there.
A great fun one.
So yeah, they were basically just saying,
for your own safety,
because jumping to a new plane is really hard.
And we kind of talked about that
after we recorded a couple of times where it was like,
what would have happened
if you guys would have tried to jump planes?
And I had a table that you would have rolled on
and the options were mostly bad.
Yeah.
My favorite that I was really pulling for
was going to be a very luscious, verdant, green jungle
that then you all would have slowly died
of radiation poisoning and maybe at the jaws of dinosaurs.
So yeah, there were different places.
Well, that's not my favorite.
That you could have ended up
if you had to try to leave.
Gazebo, a wild gazebo says,
I for one look forward to our new lives under Keith's rule.
I'm sure he'll be a kind and a holy empathetic leader.
All hail Keith's, hallowed be thy name.
Hallowed be thy name.
Looks like the Keiths myriad
have taken over some Twitter accounts
and are spreading some disinfo.
Bless you, my son.
Lynn is spooky at Jet Sedette says,
shout out to the handsome boy, Luke.
Hashtag HZKMP, hashtag PTBPQ, smiley face.
Keep it up.
Another Keith on Twitter.
Who is that really, Keith?
I don't know who that is.
Sasha Snow, one of our fantastic mods,
at MariexLupin says,
so when y'all releasing the hot dog cut of No Backbone.
Amazing job on season one.
I can't wait for the next season to kick off.
We can't either.
We're excited for everything
that's coming down the pipeline.
Super stoked, super stoked.
I'll release the hot dog cut of No Backbone
with the permission of Kudzu on Patreon.
I'll actually, that's a great question.
I'll hit up Seth, who's the lead singer of Kudzu,
and see if he's cool with me releasing the hot dog cut,
which he will not know what I'm talking about.
So I'll send it to him and then we'll,
thankfully the season's over, so he can't pull out now.
Kyanite fuck cars at 1312 Kyanite asks,
do y'all have a secret to not getting burnt out
on the same story, adventure, system, et cetera,
other than reasonable and restful breaks?
Those are for babies and I am no baby.
I am a baby, I took a break.
We took big breaks.
We took a big break, yeah.
We took a couple of big breaks.
We started recording this season in contention
a full year before we started releasing,
we've said a few times.
So I mean, there were many breaks in there,
but I'm curious, did you guys ever feel burnt out
on the story?
No, because it just changed.
It was a consistent thread,
but so many other things where it's like.
We had the luxury of those mini arcs also
to break it all up.
Actually, yeah, by the time we got to the numbers
and everything without a lot of even hints
about what was actually going on.
Yeah, that arc was, I mean, like about that
in the world in general.
Though I don't know if you guys had more than I did
at that point with your characters.
I didn't know anything.
Joe is definitely learning that he was the overseer
during that arc.
And so that was a very Joe centric.
There was also a moment where the entire story
could have changed because Leon wanted to take me elsewhere
and I had some kind of role that I succeeded
and or failed on.
He said, you know what, let's not do that yet
and let's do the city campus first.
If I had gone to the other place,
I guess we're in spoiler territory.
He wanted to take me straight to Comcomfy Campground
and meet up with Maggie.
Meet up with Maggie who was waiting for you on the shore
with a heavy metal box that would have summoned
the Gigantum Barpithecus into the world of contention
and her plan was alongside the overseer, you,
was to hold the world hostage
and literally take control of a one world government.
You guys could have had a very different overseer.
Yeah, I mean, obviously I love the story that we crafted
but that's way better.
So secret to not getting burnt out, I guess,
is just to keep the story fresh and moving
in different directions constantly.
That makes me remember that also even after the fact,
when I came back from one of the loops,
I was trying to convince them to go to Comcomfy Campground.
We had another chance to have done that.
I was also planning on that happening, yeah, for a while.
Spine Bazinglingter at Putnam Puppeteer says,
it seemed that there was an uneasy truce
between the Circle of Knowledge, Coq, Myriad
and the majority of factions in the series
with the possible exception of the Glass Syndicate.
Was this unity an allied powers-esque counter
to MARY's agenda?
No, MARY was the allies and everybody else was the ISIS.
Yeah.
I like to think that Myriad and the Circle of Knowledge,
Bar Corp, they were all kind of working together.
You had an NPC kind of say that one time
that they're all moving in different ways
toward the same goal.
Yeah, and Love was talking to you guys about that
outside of Beans Pond and that is true.
MARY was not a part of that agenda.
Everyone was pretty confused about the balls
and how they work and no one had a grasp on it
was my thought process.
There are a couple other balls that are out there
in this world that were never found
and I never wrote anything for them
because I didn't. Make it up right now.
Didn't think I needed to.
They're out there, baby.
Yeah, they're fucking out there though.
If you do the math, there were a certain amount
of successes, Kacelle knocked out a certain number of them,
John was one of them and yeah, the math doesn't quite add up
there's one or two I think that are left out.
Nice.
And so they're still doing this stuff.
Take some time to feel your spine right now.
Also, keep in mind if you're stoned
and you're listening to this and it's late at night
and it's dark and you're in your house by yourself,
don't look out the window
because there's someone looking at you.
Yeah, and your ball.
That's right, Derek.
There's someone looking at you through the window.
Also, Tyler, shut your door right now, then lock it.
Xylopia or, well, no, it's gotta be that, right?
Xylopia maybe?
Oh yeah, probably.
Xylopia.
Question, what can you tell us about season two?
Nothing.
Nothing, but we are talking about it.
Who the fuck told you that?
I'll tell you about season two.
How do you know about that?
How do you know about season two?
That wasn't supposed to leave this room.
Codename season two.
I think it's worth saying
that you've done a lot of work on it already.
Yeah, it is.
It's worth saying that I remembered a couple months ago,
contention in the main story and everything,
like with the NPCs that would be moving parts
were all written out well before we started recording.
And I was like, oh shit, I gotta get on this.
So I've had the idea rumbling around in my head
for season two since, I would say,
when we were recording episode 12.
Nice.
And I've kind of fine-tuned it.
Taylor has worked as my story supervisor
to basically me talking out loud
and her being like, that doesn't make sense.
Let's fix that.
And so. Nice.
Yeah, I'm really, really fucking excited about it.
So that's what we can tell you.
What were you watching a lot of at that point in time?
Oh, that's a good question.
What was I watching?
Gilligan's Island.
Fucking one show you were so into.
Whoa.
The magic thing.
Oh. Who?
Mr. Strange, wait, what was it?
Jonathan Norrell?
Jonathan Strange and Mr. Norrell.
Yeah.
It's pretty good.
Yeah, I think it's really fun.
There's a Faye, and I'm not really super into Faye lore,
but I really like that story.
And the acting is really solid in it.
Yeah, definitely.
Dirk Gilligan had a lot to do with season one.
John dies at the end, had a lot to do with season one.
A lot of stuff.
Anytime I'm watching media or listening to media,
I'm stealing.
Question, would you guys ever consider playing a season
of Scum and Villainy or some other spacey flavor
of tabletop role-playing?
C Mothership.
Yeah, C colon Mothership.
Yeah, for sure.
I've heard Scum and Villainy is dope.
Is Scum and Villainy the Star Wars one specifically?
Yeah, I think it is not name brand,
but it is essentially, do you want to role play Star Wars?
This is a way to do it.
Cool.
And I would, you know what I would call it
the whole time we were playing it?
What?
Scum and Villainy.
Oh, okay.
Zach, oh, okay.
Compliment, this is one of my favorite podcasts.
PTBP is my only Patreon subscription at the moment.
Hey, thank you.
We encourage you to divest as much if you're welcome
as you can from other sources
and invest it all in PTBP.
It's going up and up and up and up, baby.
Diamond hands on PTBP.
That's right, you hold.
It only goes up.
1KL, oh no.
1KL Island.
No, 1K Island.
Oh, 1000 Island Stare, 1000 Island Stare.
Yep, 1K Island Stare.
Come town joke.
Says, what was Maggie Cook's agenda?
What was the schism in the circle of knowledge?
Really all about.
Her relationship with her father depreciated in value
every single time something unnatural happened
and that is what led her to come up with the idea
to dethrone him and take over the circle of knowledge.
So there were unnatural things happening
before we blipped into existence as characters.
That is correct.
Because we found a bunch of notes about that schism
happening previous to us.
Gotcha, cool.
Yeah.
Modern Cannabis asks,
what was the deal with Joe's parents?
Why did they get the book?
What was the deal with their hinting him
about letters slash Wheel of Fortune?
I may just have spaced something.
What happened the day Joe was in the library?
I don't know what the deal with Clark's parents is,
but what's the deal with Joe's parents?
Like Joe's parents, it's a whole ass episode.
Yeah, we would need some time.
You'll have to ask why they got the book
or answer why they got the book.
I can tell you what I think of as the day in the library
was Clark Old, the overseer, protecting young Clark
and knowing that that was a timeline
that needed to continue.
And that's why he chained the doors closed
and created a distraction, a diversion
to get the myriad away from those doors.
Oh my God, dude, that was so cool.
I just threw the vague back to Luke and mid answer,
Joe just like snagged it out of the air one handed
and then handed it to Luke and continued answering
until we couldn't hold it in anymore.
That was good, because it was like,
really good answer though.
And the deal with Joe's parents is just simply,
they had the book, don't fucking worry about it.
It's called the McGuffins.
Yeah, exactly.
My own thoughts on the way that his story,
that Clark and the overseer storyline ended
is that he was gonna go back and put the pieces in place
that then set them in motion to end up where they ended up.
So the book had to end up with Joe's parents.
Is that a TV trope?
With Clark's parents.
And yes, you're 100% right about the day
that Clark was in the library as a child.
That is exactly what the overseer was there to do.
But the overseer was always being chased by myriad.
So let me hit the ATM.
A great user name, says, well done guys.
Thank you.
Thanks.
It's been a fun ride.
Thank you.
Thanks.
My question is, what, if any,
meaning did the actual vocal portion of the spells
throughout the show have?
Like, were they a specific language?
Did they mean something aside from the spell?
And the answer is slightly.
Yeah, I used a Google translate to take words
that I thought were meaningful to the spell.
And then I Google translated them into fucking Swedish
and then Arabic and then French and then Spanish
and then Indonesian and then Dutch.
And just like somewhere along the line,
pulled out a syllable or two that I liked
and then did it with the next word
that also worked toward that spell.
So if it was like time backwards,
then I would do it with those two words
and then put those combination of syllables together.
And that's how I came up with the spell.
Yeah.
So that's how we used hyper geometry in season one.
And I've been working on my magic engine for season two.
And I'm pretty stoked about it.
So.
And I did the same with to do hakanu.
Bacon Monkey says, listener from Thailand here.
Thank you.
Whoa.
That's awesome.
Very cool.
And I love season one and congratulations
on finishing it on such a high note.
Thank you.
My question is a bit more pertaining
to the behind the scenes stuff,
but I wanted to know how you guys approach
the various topics or directions
that the characters will go through.
I know a lot of the twists were surprises
and I was wondering if you guys had to talk beforehand
regarding what topics to avoid
or if certain subjects were too sensitive for some people,
or if a player didn't like a certain direction
that the handler took their character down
because it seemed like everyone took all the surprises
in stride and strove to continue the story with them.
And that really stood out to me.
Excuse my shitty English, which.
Your English was great.
Your English was phenomenal.
Alc underscore the underscore missed also added
your English is fine.
Thanks for popping in there to reassure
this poster. Thanks.
Yeah, for sure.
So let's hit some of these points in here.
We do talk about some stuff before,
like, do we want to, like,
we discuss some content beforehand,
not necessarily like surprises that are going to happen
to the characters that keeps that from us,
but like we have pretty like serious
and thoughtful discussions about what we do
and don't want on the show.
Yeah.
We definitely have one-on-ones with Zach too
that are like, hey, here's what I'm thinking.
Exactly.
He'll do that.
Like I want to kind of do this with your character maybe
or whatever.
Yeah.
Which even pre-recording,
I specifically remember one day at work,
I was, I texted all three of you when I was working
the shitty job and I took my lunch break so seriously.
And I would, I was at the time,
I was just spending my lunch breaks,
reading every post on the R slash Call of Cthulhu
and R slash Delta Green subreddits.
I went to top all time.
And I read for like 10 pages on both of those,
just consuming as much content as I could
to try to try to get more info on how to be good at this.
But I texted you guys something about your characters
and Joe texted me back immediately.
And then we literally started like role-playing
like a solo thing with his character over text message
on my lunch break to prepare for like the next session
that was happening.
So sick.
Yeah, okay, you guys sexted, that's good brag.
There's also a part of the question that says,
if a player didn't like a certain direction
that the handler was taking their character down,
I never felt that way, but I also always felt comfortable
if I needed to, to tell you that.
I think you were receptive to anything we said.
And I think there have been a couple of moments
where we're like, I don't,
I can't think of anything in particular,
but it does feel like maybe we've done that.
Yeah, I feel like at least before we recorded,
there might've even been a couple of times
where just mid campaign,
you might come up to me and be like, hey.
I'm Irish now.
Meaning to talk more about it in character,
if you could kind of prompt it in the role-playing.
Like Joe said, that's my hope obviously,
is that you guys feel comfortable coming to me
with any concerns that you have.
There's nothing so sacred that I would feel
like I couldn't say, hey,
I don't know if this is what I want.
I hope you feel comfortable coming to me,
Zach lustily texted Joe.
Luke and Thomas read Joe and Zach's sex ASMR style.
Yeah, that's the ultimate Patreon goal.
Yeah.
And then as far as like hot topics go,
we've been friends for a long time and like-
We all know kind of.
Yeah, we know our boundaries, I think.
Oh yeah, we also wouldn't be friends
if we didn't have like the same general values.
Yeah.
I like respect you guys as people.
And I wouldn't, if you were gonna joke about stuff
that I wasn't comfortable with.
Yeah, for sure.
All people as people.
Exactly, which is-
It's a really, really basic concept.
It's like so simple.
It's just like really, really easy and super cool to do.
Jacob pegging, nope.
I see where you're going for there.
Jacob pepping.
Pepping, Jacob pepping just says,
love the show, only actual play to really grab me
and drag me down into the ooze and never let me go.
Thank you.
Erotic.
Yeah, that's great.
If everyone had to pick a moment from the show,
what would it be?
Coolest, funniest, most memorable, or just most nuts?
There's tons.
Most recently.
Yeah, man.
The Keith turn.
I think the Keith turn had us all like dying.
It was incredible.
That was nuts.
Yeah, that was so fucking insane.
That was a really, that was a really good one.
The death of Anne Love.
I was gonna say that for me, for sure.
Really important, the way that that all went down
and the fight with John and Clark,
like the roles just happened the way that told a fun story.
Yeah.
I really loved the robot fight we had.
I was like, dude, this is sick.
That was one of the most intense things, I think,
like as a player that I felt like-
Are you talking about in the house?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Where I was like, oh, we're gonna die.
Like this is-
Yeah, yeah, right, totally.
I don't know how to fight this robot.
Your guys' eyes, like each of your eyes,
when I described the top half of that robot
breaking off from the bottom half,
probably like put another plus five years
of role-playing for Zach, like.
Yep.
I'm chasing those eyes.
I saw the look in their eyes
and I've been chasing that feeling ever since.
And you gave us just an old man
shitting himself the whole time, too?
Yeah.
Not the plan I had for Randy Angst.
You guys were so aggressive about the guns with him.
That seems like so long ago.
It was so long ago we did that, but that was dope.
Thomas, is there like a moment
from the season one of pretending to be people
that when you think about the show,
like reaches out to you as a particular moment?
No, I'm way more into the later seasons.
Well, for me, for you as a role player,
I can think of two specifically.
One, Martin Cupertino, trying to convince the group
that he was in the right about where to go
when you guys were in the woods
and looking for the door.
And you had a much lower skill in survival
than the alternative,
which was the archeologist played by Joe.
Whose name was?
I don't remember his name.
I don't either.
And it was not Angela.
Angie, Angie, Angie.
Which that cracked me up when I was like,
hey, can I name your wife, Angela?
And you're like, yeah, whatever, whatever you want to do.
And then I was like, ha ha ha.
It's Anne Love, motherfucker, mommy fucker.
If I remember right, did that reveal happen
off the podcast, didn't it?
To me.
Oh, I think it might've.
I think it might've.
I think I wasn't recording when you put two and two together.
Gloating three AMS, by the way, idiot.
Idiot.
Shouldn't have let me name your wife.
And then the other one for Thomas is,
when you decided that,
when you passed a sanity check in the Old West Arc
and you said, no, I don't want to be sane,
and then just grabbed the head of the preacher,
chair of Dr. Bobby Custard,
and started moving his mouth and talking through his head.
That was another.
Thanks.
And then additionally, I'll throw up one more
just because we're on the topic and I'm thinking of it.
When you threw Drew Andrews against the wall,
when it was just me and you,
and you threatened his life.
Oh, yeah.
If he fucked you over on the cocaine deal,
that was really intense.
By the way, Drew-
I just thought about what I would do to you, Zach,
if you tried to screw me out of our cocaine deal.
Drew was not adamant,
but he did throw out the idea top of like,
okay, so this much money split four ways.
And Thomas was like, no.
Two ways, Drew.
Drew was definitely, in my head,
like I thought I was going to be able to rope all of you
into being the worst fucking cops.
Oh, which you did on your own for the most part.
Keith would have probably been in,
but then when we found Fergie Beans,
it might've just instantly gone to gunfire.
Oh, that would have been-
That would have been really cool.
That was the reveal that I was hoping for
is the four of you out there for a drug deal
and then Keith's fucking brother shows up
with a van full of android kids.
At the same time, imagine the Keith that we know
is essentially the villain of this whole story.
Definitely the villain of this whole story.
Getting like a million dollars and some change
to fund those dreams earlier than, you know,
then he might've otherwise realized them.
I don't think it's a, it wouldn't be prudent.
It wouldn't be prudent.
To quote a relevant and popular sketch
from a relevant and popular show.
A highlight of Keith was being Silas Cole.
Yes, that was super fucking fun.
The orchestration of his brother's murder.
Yeah, that was really fucking good.
Your Wild West character was also fantastic.
Ephraim Corland and then the turn that Ephraim
got to take where you got got first
and then were able to take them down
is another key role-playing moment that-
That was great.
That actually is like, I was like,
oh my fucking God, I'm such a goddamn idiot.
I'm the dumbest man alive.
Man, being a player is fucking hard.
Come on guys, come on in and look at this.
Like in D&D, you literally played the hero of the story
and you know that like the story is on your side.
Right, in Delta Green, you're not like supposed to win.
No, anything you do.
This is why DMs like it so much
because it's literally like, yeah, like maybe they'll win,
but it's still gonna let you get
your sick little rocks off.
That's why he brought bringing us back.
He still gets to tell the man, really do it somehow.
It's like, I killed him, yes.
Oh no, what have I done?
Post kill clarity.
I gotta bring him back, I gotta bring him back.
Load up the mausoleum.
So thank you all so much for listening
through this first Q&A.
We're gonna do one more to finish out
the rest of these questions that everybody asked.
I think we got through exactly half of them.
Yeah, hell yeah, we got through exactly half
and we'll come back with Justin next week
to answer the remaining questions that you all have
and thank you.
Thanks for listening.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
If you've listened this far, whoa.
Whoa.
Yeah, whoa and also do tune in next week
with the exciting conclusion
of the question Zach was gonna ask us.
Oh yeah, I haven't been teased it.
By the way, I've been meaning to ask you guys.
I'm gonna eat a woman, a woman.
Sorry, sorry."
I know you really can't.
Another one, there's a scene where you videos
pace game sort of tennis cinematography.
That's different from competing to competing.
It would be insane if we missed several videos
with some contradictoryuns.
I thought that was just funny to me too.
That's right, we got O Edge on theMoment.
What do you think about O Edge?
O Edge, the moment of that edict Jesse
or whatever your point is,
where'd the audience go?
How am I the only one trying to fool all?
How can you have enough drowning out of the notes?
There's no point in going.
No point going.
Fly to fly to stream.