Hello, good friends of the podcast called Pretending To Be People.
It is the wolf, the dog, w-wolf the dog, with a special announcement this fine morn-vening.
You may have noticed that this here episode is not episode 26 of season 2.
In fact, it ain't even part of this here campaign.
We'll be back in a couple weeks to pick up where we left off with the very precarious
situations we last left Julius Beck and Cal.
But for now, it's a b-b-b-b-bonus episode from over on P-P-P-P-P-P-Patreon.
In this premium, exclusive content from our contention-confidential feed is the episode
one of a six-part series that Thomas has entitled, The Lost Treasure of John Lee Pettymore.
That's right, Thomas is the GM, and he's running a story set in the holler outside of contention
following the events of season one of Pretending To Be People.
So if you haven't listened to season one, my delectable listeners, now is the time to
go back to where it all started, because there's, uh, spoilers and such in this ish.
Now if you have listened through season one, then boy oh boy, you are ready for what we've
been calling the Oops All Pettymores campaign, because Joe, Luke, and Zatch are all playing
members of the extended Pettymore family, and let me tell y'all the what, it's been
so got darn fun.
Just five dollars over at patreon.com slash pretending pod will unlock the saga that follows,
as well as the 30-something bonus episodes that came before.
Now I'm not saying you need the bonus content, but I am saying that if you did need all this
bonus content, it's just five bucks to get what you need, and fittingly, Wolf is here
to provide an all-new, all-banging theme, provided by one of Joe's dad's bands.
It's the Morels with Get What You Need.
I need a boat.
I need a plane.
I need a car.
I need a train.
I need a pill.
I need a drink.
I need a smoke.
I need an eight-foot couch and a four-foot screen.
A big vacation and a dog that's mean.
I need a four-wheel drive and a three-piece suit.
A nine-millimeter that I know I can shoot.
In the USA, it's not a question of greed.
Cause everybody who is anybody agrees.
For followers the ones who lead.
You get what you need.
Brad's Monkey.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Five, four, three, two.
Brad's Monkey!
The Funky Monkey!
Brad's Monkey Monkey!
Blam!
Welcome to the Danov Show!
For episode 39 of the Patreon, which is a very fucking special episode.
Is it not, Luke?
It is.
The title of this one is, remind me, Thomas?
The Hunt.
No.
The Lost Treasure of John Lee Treasuremore.
The Lost Treasure of John Lee Pettymore.
Episode 1, Bad Blood.
Where we will be all playing Pettymore cousins or uncles or brothers or whatever it is.
You're all cousins to somebody.
The working title in all of my notes is Oops All Pettymores.
Oops All Pettymores.
Exactly.
So I think the Pettymores cousins are going to go on a treasure hunt.
But see, it's Thomas' job now, thank God, it's not my job for this one.
It's Thomas' job to make it serious and call episodes bad blood.
And it's up to us to say, Oops All Pettymores!
Well, I did want to say, while tonight we'll be searching for treasure, you can find treasure,
especially for the holiday season, at Target.
Target is the best destination for treasure.
That bit hasn't come out yet.
It hasn't come out yet.
You're right, this is a sneak peek.
It's a preview bit.
And it's real too.
So guys, go shop at Target.
That is what you get here in the Dennis Inn.
That's a bit from an episode we recorded yesterday, last night.
So it's some pretty fresh stuff for you.
Some pretty hot sauce.
Bleeding edge.
Right off the lips of Luke.
We asked for some sins in the chat.
And I saw one that, it's already scrolled past now, but I had to mention it.
I think it was Zach said, that's a different Zach.
What did I say?
A different Zach.
Zach with a K.
Said that he accidentally put laxative in his boss's coffee.
I think that might take a week.
Whoa!
Accidentally?
What were they putting in their box's coffee?
An accident isn't a sin unless you don't apologize.
What if you don't need to apologize?
Like this one?
Because what's he going to do?
Apologize?
You make fun of him.
There's a lot to take into account here.
How much does your boss hate shitting?
How much do you need your job?
How much do you personally value honesty as an individual?
How much is that going to eat you up?
Are you the kind of person who, if you know you have to lie to your boss
about the fact that you made him shit his pants?
Every day for the rest of your life until you die
because there won't be retirement for us.
Exactly.
Is that going to fuck with you?
One day you guys are sharing what the worst thing that ever happened to you was
and he was like, it was probably that time I shit my pants at work.
What about you?
That's when you tell him.
Honestly, it was the day that I accidentally gave you laxative
and then I saw you shit your pants at work.
So if that would eat you up, just get it over with.
Get it over with?
Were there any other good...
I was setting this up.
I read the Brad's Monkey thing and then I kind of missed all of it.
There's somebody talking about that they found this cheap beer
called Montucky Cold Snacks
and just the name alone makes me want to taste it.
Have you not had it?
Totoro's Bang Bus has been recruiting people for a year
to drink it because it makes really good Brad's Monkeys.
Brad's Monkey.
That funky monkey.
Montucky Cold Snacks is well distributed here in our hometown of Springfield, Missouri.
I feel like it's at every bar.
Every bar?
Is it in a grocery store where I've seen the cans before?
I don't go to that section.
It's like blue with a horse on it.
I haven't seen it, I don't think.
It looks like a retro NBA jersey.
I'll pick some up next time.
It does.
What else?
It looks like if they made Outrun Horse Show.
Uh huh.
What's an Outrun Horse Show?
Come on down!
See if you can outrun this horse!
No, it's like Knight Rider, but a horse.
The horse always wins.
Yeah, every time!
Who's faster than a horse?
It's Knight Rider, but it's a talking horse.
Back in the day, they used to do
radio plays that had Superman
racing the Flash
And what I understand, Superman always won
and I always think that that sucks because
he does all the other things
The Flash has one thing and it's to be fast
And he's still not the best.
And if he loses to Superman, that's just sad.
That's such a bummer for him.
Man, if you had that kind of power, wouldn't you become
I don't know, an authoritarian fascist
or just indifferent?
That might be interesting to explore.
That kind of Superman.
Has anybody ever done a bad Superman?
Who would try to put him down like some sort of
opposite?
It's probably going to have to be another group of
pretty shrewdly realized superhero
parodies.
No, Rorschach's not pretty.
Wait, what?
Who are we talking about?
Well, a number of different IPs.
What was that recent one that came out, Bright Something?
Bright?
Where he's a kid?
It was not great, but I liked it.
I haven't seen it, but I remember the whole thing was that
it was bad Superman.
Oh, Hancock.
No.
Yes.
Yeah.
He's right, Joe.
That's hilarious. Brightburn.
Brightburn.
I liked it.
Because it's like, oh, Superman, he's bad,
but what are you going to do?
Evil.
He's a kid and he's bad.
Oh, and he can do crazy stuff.
What are you going to do?
Brightburn.
Yeah, I've got Brightburn.
I'm sorry to hear that, dude.
What are they going to do, though?
You're a kid.
It Brightburns when I pee.
What do we do?
Like, neon.
What are you asking?
What do we do?
Yeah, what do we do to get the fire back
within our loins?
They've got pills for that.
An uncle.
LMFAO. Put it on right now.
Loins burning.
It's strange.
They're not that far apart
in age. It's not that weird.
Thomas. Yeah.
Almost ready. I'm ready.
I'm rearing to go.
I'm ready to play a pettymore
for the nth time.
I've never played a pettymore.
Are you excited? Yeah.
How do you get into the mindset of playing a pettymore?
It's a page-long introduction.
Yeah, I saw how long it was.
You wouldn't let me read it, though.
No, of course not.
Of course not. There's secrets in here
that I don't think you can handle.
I've got my intro in mind, but
unless the story reads it, I think I should go first
so that the more thought-out ones
can go after me.
Yeah, that's why you're going to go second
after Zach.
Actually, we might sandwich Zach.
Luke can go first.
Joe, you told me you literally had dreams
about rehearsing yours.
It's not a page-long, is all.
Okay, Luke can go first
and give Zach time to write his.
I'm just looking up the questions you sent.
I don't know if you're
trying to be me as vengeance
or if we are the same person.
Look on me, look on me.
If it's vengeance, I get it. If it's just you,
then...
Welcome to my life.
Did you get it?
Is that how we're kicking off?
Are we kicking off with all of this?
No, there's some stuff.
Should we get some good intro stuff
about the episode for the Patreon?
Let's get some intro stuff about the episode
for the Patreon.
For them audio listeners.
Hello audio listeners.
You guys have missed so much
that we talked about before
in the Patreon.
So go ahead and up those Patreons.
Did you know Chris D'Elia died?
I saw that, dude.
We didn't talk about that on the stream, did we?
No, you gotta explain why you said that
though, because
Joe's over here scrolling
on his phone.
I got the update, I got the CNN update
that Kirstie Alley had passed away
and I said that aloud.
And I really loudly was like
aww.
Which confused Zach.
Because I thought he said that Chris D'Elia died
and then Thomas goes, aww,
oh no.
But like genuinely?
Like someone you cared about
or like cared that they died
and died? Well, you know, when I was younger
I watched that pervert episode of Workaholics
all the time before I went to bed.
No, I did watch Cheers like all the time
because it was just on like the nightbox
as I was going
to bed as a young one.
I'm going to rip Kirstie Alley
who will be long dead and decayed
by the time you hear this episode edited
as a Patreon listener.
Okay, so what we're doing here tonight
is episode one
of The Lost Treasure of John Lee Pettymore.
It's called Bad Blood.
Bad Blood.
Cause baby now we got
bad blood.
And everybody made me mad.
Got it.
Check.
Nailed it. Nailed it.
And what this is is a
an oops all Pettymore arc where
all the boys are going to be playing
family members of
my character John Lee Pettymore
from season one. And we kind of
established during that season that he has a very big
extended family who are
kind of as crazy and wild as him.
Big old wild family out there in contention.
Big old blunts. In the surrounding
areas. Huge
smoking big doinks in Amish.
Big smoking big doinks
in contention.
But we won't be in contention listeners
because some of you might remember
what happened at the end of season one.
Spoilers. Spoilers. Spoilers.
Which is Keith put a big old dome over everything.
And I
after seeing
the beautifully round shape
off riding into the sunset
of Planet Juggernaut
he looked at that shape and said
I like that.
Now you know it has deeper roots than that right?
Oh. I thought you did this
intentionally but I don't know.
I was like damn I respect the fuck out of
Luke when I listen to like episode
15 or 16 and
Keith literally says like I'd like to
put a giant
dome over the whole city.
I think it's just something
I think about a lot.
That's just the Luke
preoccupation that you brought into
the character.
Which is a great
no it's the who shot Mr. Burns episode.
Oh. Did they do it in the movie too?
I think they did. It was like the whole
point of the movie.
Oh they do a dome in the movie who shot
Mr. Burns he just builds a giant thing
that blocks out the sun.
If you want to block out
any one of us your three sons
during this episode you can put up your hand
like that in a particular way
in front of that camera that can block
one of us from sight. Yeah.
That's me. I'm gone now.
I was trying to block you all.
That's all of us.
Okay my three sons.
You're all going to be playing Betty Morris.
I cannot wait.
And times are a little tough for the
Betty Morris.
They are not at their full power as you might say.
You all are friends of
Jon in the way that cousins
often are. Some of you
are a little older. One of you is
pretty much right at Jon's age.
But he's been missing for a year at this point.
He's not the only
anymore missing.
Don D. Pettymore is gone.
Jimmy Sanders is gone.
There's some talk about
Aloysius
and Edward. Some sort
of foul play that might have happened involving
Jon but nobody really knows. You've only
heard rumors. And
when you were all growing up you would come
to Pettymore Holler at least
every year if you didn't actually
live there for the big family cookout.
A huge Pettymore reunion.
And it's been five or six years since
that's actually been put on.
But this year everybody gets
a call or an email
or a handwritten note from Ma
Pettymore, the family matriarch.
We can work
out family trees and stuff later.
I think even though some of you are older
it's plausible you're all
within the same generation of cousins
of Jon. So we're going to say
she's your great-great-grandmother.
We have them young. Yeah, she's like
67.
Wow.
The math on that
is horrible. It sucks.
She's like 77.
97.
She's turning 70.
That's what I wrote
on the Patreon is that it was her 70th birthday.
She's turning 70.
Great-great.
Great-great-grandmother. Okay, she's your great-grandmother.
Okay, that helps
a little bit.
Put in a second grade. Make it weird.
No.
She's your great-grandmother and she's called you all here
today for the first Pettymore
cookout, hoedown, get-together,
hootenanny
family reunion that you've had in
five years. And usually this is at
her place. This is at Ma
Pettymore's house, kind of the heart
of all the family property
in Pettymore Haller, which is where
John lives on the edge of.
And the unusual thing about her letter this year is
that it mentions this is going to be at John's
place. She says, it's not just
a birthday celebration. This is
about family, remembering,
and our future. And so
in one way or the other, you all make your way from
wherever it is you live to
John Lee Pettymore's house on the outside
of contention. And it's not
really the same as you remember
getting there last time. The Haller itself
is located in between,
um, I've actually got something written
for this. I could just start reading.
Yeah, you should do that.
Do a good voice.
Like Liz.
Welcome to
the puddle.
Do a baby voice.
The home and property of John Lee Pettymore.
The home and property of
John Lee Pettymore sits just above the cleavage
that separates the two local prominences
known as big and little beans
teat.
A cleavage that, for as long as
anyone can remember, has borne your family's
name. Pettymore Haller.
Generations of Pettymores have lived and died
between the teats, tending to the land,
themselves, and generally honoring
the bounty the good Lord has seen fit to bless them
with. That's at least how the Pettymore tells it.
But God doesn't make bras big enough
for mountains.
And you know as well as every outsider
within 50 miles that the Haller
has never truly contained your rowdy,
wild, and extremely prolific
clan. You're all driving.
There's one way into contention, pretty much.
The highway. And
you're driving down some familiar farm
farmland, wide
open spaces. As you get closer to
contention, the land becomes more treed
and hillier. And about 10 miles outside
of town, there is a massive
construction barricade across
the highway, diverting you onto
Farm Road 67.
Damn. Too way.
Just wait.
As you get to that
construction
detour, roll an alertness
check for me.
Ooh. Already rolling.
Right off the bat.
Mine's a fail. Fail.
I pass. 18 on a 50.
Okay, you two grumble a little bit and take the detour.
But Luke, you
would notice, and we'll get to who you are
in just a second, but you would notice that
pretty much as far as you can see past the
barricades, you don't see any
signs of construction. There's no
equipment. There's no
upturned earth. It just seems like
abandoned highway for as long
as you can see until it disappears kind of
behind the bend and some hills. And
you think that's odd, but you've read about
it being a pretty extensive
project, so maybe it's just further on down
closer to contention itself.
And you all take Farm Road 60
in your own ways.
Through these woody hills,
beautiful picturesque dreams,
gorgeous oaks, mighty
pines, stout
sycamores.
Everything the Ozarks
has to offer, all the natural beauty you
grew up with, or at least spent time
around as children, like to some extent.
And you're actually, you're gonna pass through
Pettymore Hauler itself, on the back way
to John's pretty much. Give me just a second.
I'm liking it. I'm there.
I'm in the hauler. I'm there. I'm a drone right
now. I'm a drone in some cleavage.
In between the teats. I'm a titty fucking
hauler. Hell yeah.
Hey Keith, you're
named after the pair of tits?
No, it's named after me.
You come to the
crossroads of Farm Road 67
and Jiminy Road, which sits
pretty much directly at this
small unincorporated
community known as Jiminy Station.
There's a little gas station
and bed and breakfast there
and a couple of like abandoned
mid-century commercial buildings.
You would know that, you know,
if 50 people lived in Jiminy Station
in the 70s, maybe less than
two dozen do now. You take Jiminy
Road past Farm Road 68
to Farm Road 69.
Which leads to the heart of
Pettymore Hauler.
And you see, you see all the ancestral
fiefdom. You see
Ma Pettymore's house.
You see some frankly
less well camped properties.
Sites you're pretty familiar with though.
A lot of pettymoors don't like to get rid of things.
They like to keep them around in case they need them.
So if you prefer that to a yard, you know,
whose business is that but yours?
And when you get to
the gates of John's Farm, you see
the front field is
completely packed with parked
cars. And there's already
a pretty broad gathering.
Dozens and dozens of pettymoors
all around these tables and
Bunch of ladies. Ladies.
Guys. Broad gathering.
Kids. Got it. Oh, broad gathering.
Boom. It's a real broad city.
BC, you see your
whole family there. For the first time in years.
Relatives you haven't seen
since you were small. Some you might have
seen more recently. But everyone is
so happy. Luke, we're gonna do
you first. Okay.
Tell me and then I'll go.
As your character
pulls in to this cookout, you park
and you get out of your car. And who
gets out? Who are you? Where are you from?
Well, why are you here?
Many creatures
are born in and roam the
hollers near contention. Bears,
coyotes, bobcats, and pettymoors live their
entire lives there until they're eaten,
shot, or hit with a truck. The latter two
spell the end of Bernie Pettymore but only
after he fathered his first and only son
Peter Bernard Pettymore. Peter Bernard
Pettymore, known around the hollers as
PDB, was raised by his
was raised by his now single
mother along with plenty of help from
the rest of the Pettymore clan. Upon
graduating high school, a relatively uncommon
accomplishment in his neck of the woods,
Petey left the comfort of the
holler to pursue his dream. Flying.
Peter packed up the few belongings
he had, hitchhiked his way to Colorado,
and joined the United States Air Force
Academy. After four long years of
intensive study and training, Pete joined the
Air Force and at long last took to the
skies. Although a handful of Pettymoors
had taken trips in planes and even more
had conquered the land and sea,
Petey was the first of his name to make a home
in the wild blue yonder. After
fulfilling his duty to the United States military,
Peter set his sights on the final
frontier, Florida. Petey accepted
a position at NASA honing his scientific
skills and offering his perfected
piloting prowess for the furtherance of
humanity and safety of the planet.
Pete successfully manned many missions,
retiring with full benefits and the knowledge
that he made a measurable difference.
The stories Pete's friends and family hear about
his tenure at NASA seem exaggerated,
outlandish, and often completely
fabricated. But Petey knows
the truth and that's all that matters to him.
I flew a
secret rocket ship to shoot a missile
bomb at a giant accumulation
of space trash that was headed right
for Kilimanjaro.
Would have wiped out the whole eastern hemisphere
but we nailed that sucker and blew
it back to Alpha Centauri.
What was some poor alien's fucker's problem
now? When we got home,
I cracked open a little intergalactic
pale ale, which is the secret beer we
brew at NASA. Yep,
that was the best beer I ever had.
What about you? Petey Pettymore takes
a long sip from his Miller Lite and size,
looking over at his conversation partner,
a young disheveled Pettymore boy concentrating
on his Game Boy. Without waiting for a response,
Petey chugs his beer, stands up,
and crushes the beer under his black combat
boots. The camera pans up from the
crushed can and we see a blue jumper
adorned with a NASA patch, an American
flag, and an embroidered
name tag that reads Commander
Petey B. Peteymore. The top of the jumper is
unzipped, revealing a black graphic t-shirt
emblazoned with a cartoon astronaut eating
a peach and the text that says
Eat NASA.
Laughter
Petey runs his hands through his
slick-backed red hair, the sides
still shaven in the military fashion,
but the top long enough to
slick back and settle on his back a few
inches below the shoulders. His piercing
green eyes dart around, searching for a familiar
face in the curious sea of
Pettymores. It's good to be home,
Petey BP says as he turns his
gaze to the sky.
At least for now.
Hey Petey.
Hey there. Hey, it's your
Uncle Ron. Ron, of course.
You remember me? And you
see a very, very
almost impossibly skinny old
man who kind of just comes hobbling
over to you and he's wearing
a camo fatigue vest
and he's got a Vietnam veteran's
cap and he just grins
at you with these yellow teeth
that are, you know, what's left of him and
this huge, huge tobacco-stained
white beard. And he says, Petey, I've been
really wanting to talk to you about
your experiences at NASA.
Yeah, Ron, I haven't seen you
since I went to space.
Well, since you've seen me, I've been to
space too, my friend.
Really? More than once or twice have the
grays abducted me.
I'd like to pick your brain a little bit about what's
been going on up, you know, up in the
government because they don't answer my letters none.
Well, you know, I'm retired now so I
can mostly just tell you about blowing stuff
up in space as far as the
government's concerned. I never saw any aliens.
Yeah, the official story is
you blew up a ball of trash in space.
But who put it there, man? The aliens!
I don't, well, how
about we circle back to this
later. Okay, I will catch
up with you later because I, well, have you heard
from, have you heard from Trey?
Trey wants to talk to you and
some of the others. I haven't seen him yet
but I think you're done with your government work.
You ain't afraid of making a little money,
are you? Well, no, that's, I mean
one reason I tried to move back around here
was, you know, make a little
money and have a little fun. That's good to
hear, that's good to hear because I think we can do both.
Okay, well. Trey's gonna fill you
in on more. Okay, I'll go find him.
It was really good to see you, Beatty.
I'm gonna get you to talk. I'm gonna
get you to tell me about them grays.
Ron, we'll talk about it. So, yeah, Ron
hobbles off to refill his beer.
You wander off to go mingle with the rest of the party
and Joe, you pull up next.
There's a man already kind of
standing by the keg
and he's got a red solo cup full
and he has a cigarette in his other hand
and he's got a mullet.
It's a gray mullet and the front
of the mullet is feathered out
kind of Rod Stewart style mullet.
Hell yes. And he's wearing these
kind of gaudy big glasses
with a gold rim
around the edges. Maybe little circles
embroidering the arms of the
sunglasses. And he's wearing
a cowboy shirt
and it's a white cowboy shirt with white
pearl snaps and the filigree on it is
embroidered white. So it's
kind of shimmers in the sun and catches shadows
and it's cut off at the sleeves
and he's got no shirt underneath. It's open.
He's got a big
beer belly hanging out the front
but his legs are like in
skinny jeans. He's kind of
like a rooster looking almost
with his big belly and his swoop
back hair and his rooster legs
is actually a highly desired
trait in a petty more man.
If you can
get them jeans that tight and that.
He's been cultivating the look for a while.
Probably nailed it a long time
ago and stuck with it.
You're
I love you're describing like so
many guys that we used to see at
your dad's shows.
So
the camera kind of zooms in on him and
he's already talking to somebody and he's
saying it's me.
It's Arlo Pettymore.
I don't blame it. It's been years. I kind of keep to
myself anyways. I'm back there in the
laboratory. I mean yes
it's my shed of course but it's my
laboratory. You probably sampled my
Saturday morning cartoon.
You probably had
a taste of that SMC. That's what the kids
were calling these days. People think it's called
that because it makes you see Looney Tunes.
That's not what it's called that.
It's about the ingredients. That's what I make
it out of. I make it out of
it's frosted corn flakes and milk.
And then there's a little gasoline
in there of course. You got to give yourself
a little kick or something there.
I don't mind telling you the recipe
because it's all about the proportions of
them chemicals. That's kind of the whole thing.
Use chemicals. I use chemicals.
Use all chemicals. It's just a matter of the
proportions of them chemicals. It's just something I've always
been able to tell in a person is the chemical makeups
of them. Some people say I'm a genius.
I don't say about myself much though.
But yeah that's that Saturday morning cartoons.
It'll fuck you up for sure. It's real good.
Hey I'm just kind of cooped up in that lab
back there. It's got a cot. It's got a real
nice cot. It's one of my favorite cots.
I bought it myself. Well I didn't
buy myself. Ma bought it for me. But it's mine.
She said it's all mine.
You having a
good day? Camera pans down.
It's the same kid that he was
talking to. Yeah that's the game boy.
It's a little kid.
Well I'm going to go see who else
is here today. Okay yeah.
Well it sounds like you really got a lot
going on and I feel like there's a lot of
people here and kids are really
more into like TikToks and
streaming content. I don't think it's like
cartoons have to strictly be on like a
Saturday morning anymore. You can
kind of watch it at your own schedule.
But it didn't really sound like you were talking about cartoons.
My mom
said I should meet you. I got to meet all my
else's but I hope you
enjoy talking to someone else. Yeah
of course and if you ever want a free sample you
come on back. Okay bye. And that
brings us. The little boy wanders
through the party with his game boy.
And he's
been told to meet people
as much as he can but he's basically relying
on them to shout out to him.
Pretty game boy focused otherwise.
And he runs straight into the legs
of... Well he'd run into
some bedazzled jeans that might do
that boy some harm because they are
shiny these jeans.
And above them a big old
belt buckle. White tank top
tight and tucked in
under a pearl snapped unbuttoned
cowboy shirt. Joni
Pettymore the first is
wearing some high top Nikes
to bottom out that whole situation
clothing wise.
She's got a bleached
blonde perm
with super dark roots. And her
eye shadow gives
raccoon. Oh it's giving raccoon?
Oh it's totally giving raccoon.
And immediately
upon this kid
bumping into her she just pushes
him away from her.
He looks up from his game boy and he's like Mom
I'm not your mother.
Do you hear me? Oh I'm sorry
Go on get running then.
Okay okay bye.
Joni Pettymore the first
is a
fucking wreck.
Flash back to
you see her
in the exact same outfit
climbing out of a second story
window and like
kind of reaching out for the drain
pipe on the left side
and she just kind of makes
a jump for it and as she's shimmying
down someone's hollering
from out the window. You
get back here Joni.
Zips on down. She's like
What do you fucking know? Come on down
here. How about that? And she
dips off running off into
the distance. We flash back
previous to that. You see
her she's going through the
metal detector to get into
high school and then immediately
heads to the bathroom
goes into one of the stalls. She's
wearing the exact same outfit that I
described before but she is
six years younger ish
and she opens up her
backpack pulls out a
ziplock bag that has
like a is it dehydrated urine
she shoves a straw into
it and starts
pulling on this straw like it's
her job sucking down liquid
in this bag and then
giving it that kind of
breath like she's just
barrel proof whiskey through that
ziplock bag.
She puts it back in the backpack
and heads back into
the high school there
and as she walks through the hallway
she runs into her boyfriend
Jared Krinklehoff
wearing a
letterman's jacket and
Thomas just gave me
big eyes. I was
preparing. Okay.
He's wearing a letterman's
jacket and immediately he puts
his arm around her and he's like
Joni hey Joni how's it going?
She's like don't do that
voice don't do it.
Immediately is like transformed
by the presence of this young man
and the little love that
they have and it flash forwards to her
slamming a screen door
closed and is like I say
that Joni is yours for
the weekend I gotta go to
a family function and based on
the way you acted last time
you're not allowed so you're gonna be
here alright and she
walks out the door and as she's walking out she's
eyeing the muscle car that's
half renovated that's what they
call renovated for cars
in the driveway and she pulls
out a little butterfly knife
and she just runs it
down the whole side of the car
as she heads out with
a screech.
She cracked your key into the
side.
And then yeah she's on
the way out to the Pettymore Holler today
by herself in a car
that you are considerably
worried about how it's running
and whether it would pass an inspection
and she goes into a
gas station and
she steals
a water bottle and as
she uh. Empty or full? A full
water bottle that's
theft. Oh right
yes.
Yes. She goes in to
steal a water bottle but as
she's heading out.
Roll to steal the water bottle? Yeah okay.
on a criminology
of 80.
Oh yeah she's bad.
She's bad. Oh look at
Joanie she's bad. And as she's on her way
out she actually catches a glimpse
up at the front of
the register.
There are these prepackaged
bags of whiskey
being sold right there at the register.
When did this start?
We've had them in for
six or so months now they seem pretty popular.
Would you like a bag?
No.
I think I just
want a pack of smokes.
Yellows. Okay. And when he turns
around she's gonna grab
a bag of whiskey.
Actually you know what
I gotta quit. I gotta quit.
I keep telling myself I gotta quit. Lord's gonna help me
this time. I gotta go. Well bless
you much ma'am and good luck in
your journey. 36 that's it.
Hey didn't I
have five bags
of whiskey? He says as the door closes
on him.
Go on then run.
And then she goes to the party?
Yeah that was me flashing back to the kid.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Oh okay I thought maybe I was your
kid but you established that you left
your kid at home. You must just
a lot of the women here look like you.
I'll
go find my mom.
Thank you for talking with me.
Goodbye. Oh I'm sorry I'm sorry
we got off to a wrong start. You gave me a scare there
cause I didn't know you were gonna be in front of me when
you were walking backwards. You best expect
me to be everywhere. Oh that's fun.
Yeah I'm a pettymore same as you.
Okay I like that spirit.
I like that spirit. God damn right you do.
And he kicks your shin really hard and he runs off.
The
pettymore way. That's how you say
bye in pettymore.
As you've all arrived
you see Arlo around the drink
table. Joni I assume you might be heading
in there too. A lot of pettymores are actually
the first stop traditionally. You gotta get
your lubrication, get your libations
and then you can talk to your god damn family
right?
Cause that's what family's for.
You see Ma kind of deep in conversation
like on the other side of the party with some older
older relatives you haven't seen in years
and immediately around you
you notice a few people. It's all
kind of mysterious
what exactly is going on
here. Why did Ma call everybody?
Kind of, you know, you've left the
hauler, you've gone on to different sort of lives
it kind of seems like maybe we're leaving this whole thing
behind. Maybe we had finally stopped
killing and dying for this way of life.
Killing ourselves trying to
wring a way of life out of this hauler.
I've been prepared a way for you to meet each other.
Is that Joni I see over there?
Oh hey Arlo how's it going?
It's been a minute. Joni's been here.
You still up to all the mess?
Just making a living. Doing what I can.
Guys I'm here too. You got all ten fingers?
The camera pans down to the five foot three
uh
PDP
Hi. Hey
Petey. Hey Petey. Petey this man
I don't want to see you. I was just going to pick your brain about
something. You reckon there's a way I could get a
hold of some of that rocket fuel?
I mean, yeah.
I'd be willing to, you know,
cut you in mate, let's say five
percent of the SMC.
I mean how much you need cause uh, who's to say
I didn't take any with me? Oh it just takes
a drop per batch. We can
send this shit into orbit right
here. It's been so long since I've tried
some of your, what are you calling it again?
It's uh, it's Saturday morning
cartoons. Saturday morning cartoons. There was a kid
earlier who told me that they don't do that anymore.
So I'm maybe thinking about a new name for it.
Well SMT, it's been a while since I had
some of your SMT but if I can
I'll do any, I got some. I took
a gallon with me. Hell yeah.
We in business. Well I've just been sitting out
there just waiting for some kind of
use and here we found it I think.
Arlo spits in his hand and holds it out to you.
Petey does the same and
sticks it there. Match made in heaven.
Pleasure doing business with you. Well I
cannot wait. Anyway
Joni was up. Where them rugrats
yours? Junior? I left
her uh, back with um,
you know, Jared. I was talking
to some kid who I thought could be yours
but I guess it's not. Oh yeah
they thought they were mine.
Who's kid is that? Well I don't know that
kid's about as, he's about
as old as long as I've seen you so I figured
who knows, probably Joni popping one out.
No.
This old thing? That kid?
As she does
the uh, like full blown
throws both of her karate
chop hands down
to the groin. You can't tell if it's the
same kid or not but a
small slender toe headed child pops
out from underneath the tablecloth on
like the keg table
and just runs out holding
a comical amount of
solo cups full of beer
and disappears
off into a group of other kids
who all just start cheering.
You did it! You did it!
Run Luke! Just run!
Remember back when we were kids
and we used to play Tipsy?
I recognize
you sent me down a path.
Well I'm a good one cause you're
look, you're making deals for rocket fuel.
Hell yes! Damn.
What about you Joni? As far as what?
Making deals, rocket fuel
going to outer space like me.
I mean I'm curious about learning more
from each and every one of you
I guess but you know I think there's
a lot of skills that I'm bringing to the table
these days that could be of use
to you as well. You know you're talking about
maybe losing some
rocket fuel you know if you need to lose
something from something where you don't have
the sort of connection where you can get
in there I might be the kind of gal who
could acquire such situations.
Heck I reckon if I didn't have to buy
any of them frosted flakes anymore
bring that cost of goods
way to hell. You know why they call me jungle style?
They call you jungle style?
Yes I remember that.
Cause I'm in and out.
Is that that? Is that that?
Did I do it? They called you
the flying detriment as far as I remember.
So at that moment this woman with
the crazy like bleached blonde
perm and electric
like acid wash denim vest
full like tiger leggings
she runs
up and she says oh my goodness
hello y'all it's so good to see
all of you. It's been years since we've
been together. Isn't it kind of strange though?
John not being here we're on his land.
We're as hell. I mean what's
the deal with that? You know he'd shoot us all.
He'd shoot us all in a heartbeat. He'd shoot every last
one of us. He was a shooting
son of a bitch. He sure
was. He sure was. Catch a stray
an hour later falling from the sky.
You can still see his shooting tree right
back there.
That's an actual season
one callback. That is
a bonafide season one callback right there.
Bonafide callback. I'm
sorry sometimes I don't make any sense when I'm
grieving. Somebody told me that he
shot just would go out in public and
shoot his gun in the air when he was a police
officer. Grieving? But now hey I
I mean he's gone. So many
of our boys are gone.
I ain't wearing black you ain't wrapped up.
Oh Johnny we've talked
about this before. Six months.
I mean how many times has a petty moor
boy ran off though? I think it's been closer to a year.
No it's weird to
be weird about it after six months.
I don't remember how much time exactly though.
More than six months and that's strange
to me. It just feels like no one's
heard a word and. Well
what about the other petty moors I heard gone
missing? Sounds like they got out.
I mean I guess they still
their Facebooks haven't been posted on.
Nobody's heard from them in the family
group texts or via mail.
But we hold I guess we got to hold out hope that's right
that's right. I don't know if I want to hold
out hope for John though because have you
heard about well have you heard about his
good fortune? I mean if you believe
them tales I guess I don't know if I do. You really
think it's out there somewhere? The tales
are he was a very rich man.
I think that it's talking out of school. I will
say that uh. I haven't
been to school in a very long time Joni.
That's why you're few years older than you.
It's more like school's your butt talking
out of it. I will say that Gregy's boy
said he knew that
his cousin Freddie was
at the thing. At what thing?
When things went down.
I heard they loaded it all into
a trash truck and they drove
that trash truck all the way across
the country but it got blown up.
I heard that petty moors for as long as
they've been around have been telling
stories about lost treasures to keep
themselves busy and not minding
their actual capitalistic ventures.
Huh. Hmm. Well
I mean but it is a good story Joni.
Why are you such a downer? This is
a cookout. Why are you being so so
odd about all this?
No reason mom.
I don't know.
I just you know
you could call me more
baby. Yeah I could. Oh hell do you
need a drink? Yes I will have what I'm
having. Which is?
And she points to the table
which has a water bottle filled
with whiskey.
Joni just like
your grandmother.
She gives you a huge hug.
And she goes
just like grandma and she stabs
just like a tiny pencil sized hole
on the top of it and then squeeze bottles
into her mouth.
Wait did you bring more of those girls?
Do you have
one for your mother? I probably got a spare in the
car I guess. I could go get it.
Yeah. Alright. Cause you know there are
some missing boys which means there's some
wait. Never mind. That joke
doesn't work.
There's a couple missing
girls too of my generation
which means there's some
you know eligible bachelors here. Oh.
This again. Great. Well
honey it's been five years since
Steven died and I
just think you know it's time for your mom to
get out there. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Well Arlo, Peter
it was wonderful to see you all. Honey do please
call me more. I'm sure I'll see you around the party.
Well what about the treasure
though? You know she's probably right.
There's no treasure. Where are people saying it is?
You know. Like if there was
one like. Oh honey
some people say it's in the barn.
Some people say it's buried under the floorboard.
Some people say it's at the bottom of the ocean.
Others say it's deep deep deep
in the woods. I heard it got blown up in a
trash truck is what I heard. A number of people
are pressing the trash truck
theory yes. Which I do
admit has a ring of truth to it.
It's so oddly specific. More
thing about it more trash truck makes sense.
Blown up a trash truck. I lean over
to Arlo and hey I heard
Trey might know something about this or
he's got a secret. A secret? Have you
seen Trey? I ain't seen him. Johnny.
You seen Trey?
What are you two whispering about?
Oh we were wondering where cousin Trey was
I just hadn't seen him since I went to space.
She steps on your foot.
Nobody's seen Trey. I mean you know
he's always late to these things. Oh yeah
okay. I'm sure he'll be here if he wants
to. And um she excuses herself
she sees um what was the name of your
husband? Jared. She sees like his
uncle. Whoa whoa why the fuck is he
there? Because his uh. He's married in?
Yeah he married in but
he's ex married in. He's here for the kids.
Nice. She runs up and goes uh
did I say what his name was? No.
Hi Sylvester.
Hey how's it going?
What a god.
Hey how you look? You look lovely
today. Hey. It's been so
long since I've seen you Dawn. Thank you for noticing
I do look lovely. She's gone.
You can't hear this. Not a day
over 40.
Ha! You!
Yeah so
you know that it's gonna be maybe
30 minutes before y'all sit down to eat so you
can continue to mingle. As soon as she walks
away Joni looks at the two of them and she's
like you two are the kind of people that I was hoping
to talk to about all this maybe without
the addition of more people who make
the cut smaller. Oh I like
where this is going. Ron. Uncle
Ron you remember him? Yeah.
He told me that Trey was looking
for me. He might be planning something.
If you guys are thinking about
getting in on something with Trey I'd like to
get along. Oh yeah.
The more the merrier and only this
case and no more.
That's right we're keeping it to
four. We'll keep it well Trey's
gotta tell us and then we'll try to kick out
whoever he's already talked to. That's smart. At that
moment Uncle Ron hobbles up.
Hey! Oh wait no I sounded like this
didn't I? Hey
it's good to see that you ran into these two
cause they're exactly the folks that Trey's looking
to help you up with. Where's Trey at?
Don't know he's learning late he should be here
soon. Gotta go bye. Bye.
Aliens
are real.
What? What?
That's all you get for now I'll tell you after.
Come flab it.
So yeah
you've got an opportunity now to
look around the property maybe poke around
if you want to get a little frisky but
you could also talk to some more people here.
There's a few interesting
characters that you might see around
you. Maybe they're highlighted if this was a video
game. Maybe it seems like there's some more
conversation options with them.
Peter remembers the last time that he was
at John's house. John
was like starting his DVD
collection and so he wants
to go snoop around and see how
big John got that collection.
Yeah well did he have all of prison
break break break that we
need to take right now. Everyone we're gonna
take a break real quick.
Stand up
stretch your legs go to the bathroom
grab another seltzer water
do whatever you need to do for
life and stuff.
And we're back
we're back
Everyone give a big
fucking shout out
a throaty congratulations
and a happy
thank you to Thomas who's
fucking killing it right now. Hell yeah.
Hoot and holler.
Why aren't throaty? Why don't you all
give a throaty
phlegmy wet
congratulations
to all the boys here who are
killing it and Zach who's graciously playing
graciously
graciously playing graciously
stepped down gave me the podcast
graciously pettymore
episode comes out on Friday yeah
okay we'll see
we'll see
we might be moving to a more relaxed
schedule
keep that in mind
that was a joke
their episode will be out on Friday
we'll see
Maxine your mother
Don yeah Don
Don Maxine Pettymore
my parents Don and Han
Don and Han
a woman who may or may not have been your mother
I named Maxine
moments before I invented her
but then we ran with the fact that she was your mom
I like
yeah Don Maxine
Don Maxine Pettymore
she's run off to go
to go to court
and
Uncle Ron just confirmed
you were the three that Trey wanted to see
Trey you would all know
he's the cool
pettymore
Joe and Luke
Trey is a little bit younger
than you guys he's right in between
John who was
26 at the time of his disappearance
and your generation so he's in like
his late 30s he was a
he was maybe a rough kid to love
depending on who you were if
you were the object of like
his charm and his magnetism
he lit up the whole world
it sounds like Jesus everybody loves this kid
it does sound like Jesus
so far it's Jesus
don't spoil my Christ narrative
everything's a Christ
narrative some of you
if maybe you got in the way of something
that Trey wanted you might have seen a different
side of him and he left
the family pretty early he was not around
for the long slow
decline of Pettymore Holler
he in fact is one of the original
exedees he left
out on his own into the world
short of it is Trey does his own thing
you don't know when he's going to show up
you know when he does it'll probably be pretty loud
you know when he do it's going to be loud
you know when he do it's going to be loud and that's Trey
but Luke what's your character's name?
Petey Petey had just asked to go see
inside the house to check on
John's DVD collection
so you walk in through the front door
and there's a lot of Pettymores
in the kitchen cooking food and
getting things ready there's a lot of hustle and bustle
and you get caught up for a minute as people are saying
oh hi Lexel hello
I haven't seen you in years what are you doing?
how you been? oh my god
what's your spice?
I'm crying I'm crying I'm actually
crying it's the three of you
you brush past all that
you get into the living room
which is eerily quiet considering
the size of this party nobody really
wants to hang out in the
house besides the kitchen because
it's exactly as John left it
in the living room you see the DVD collection
the shelf that they're on
looks like it was broken and half repaired
at one point all of them are there but
Petey the first time you saw it
you were amazed it was the most organized
thing in John's house and now you see
it's kind of been hastily shoved back on
you know Smokey 3 before Smokey 2
it wasn't
what? that's embarrassing
sacrilege
one of the reasons nobody's really sitting anywhere
is that you can see
a lot of bullet holes in the ceiling
and the couch
is covered in drywall debris
and some foam insulation
from the attic that's wafted down through the bullet holes
while he's looking at the DVD collection
Petey sorry sorry real
quick sorry not insulation
popcorn actual popcorn
you can see some
leaking out of a little plastic
bag and you remember that
John used to take home
the huge plastic bags of
popcorn that they stocked concession stands
with at the Raceway and he
he filled his attic with that
to use as insulation
and it's cold in here because the squirrels
have eaten most of his popcorn
Petey
is looking at the
DVD collection and is
just a little sad looking at it
thinking about John but also just sad
that it's not as perfect as he remembered
but he kind of
fixes it up a little bit and then from
the inside of his jumper pulls out a signed
he has signed a copy of
Space Cowboys
and then
slips it in alphabetically
where it should go
so in between Space Cowboys and
Space Cowboys director cut
so now he's got one
one regular Space Cowboys
one Space Cowboys signed by an
astronaut right very cool
Peter you probably would have been
someone you wish John had looked up to
I think you probably tried to put him on the straight and narrow
a little bit or at least you know show him that
with hard work and dedication you can
join the Air Force get through Air Force Academy
go to the become an astronaut
and John thought it was cool that
you were an astronaut but he thought it was
a lot cooler that Trey had a dope car
yeah Petey is content
in the fact knowing that John
also wore blue though
just like Pete
I always picture them wearing kind of a tan
it's funny I did too
well the cop in the
season one thing is wearing blue but
even if they didn't wear blue you know
they're wearing blue
I actually pictured you wearing blue
because then when Clark changed into
the 70's CPD uniform
and it was tan
so yeah they both wore blue
also I pictured Keith wearing that light
blue shirt so you know he's like
not his cop
even though he was probably the most cop of all
them
but yeah he's
sticks it in there looks back and is thinking
like you know
maybe if we find him we can
set him set him straight
somewhere perhaps through like the rustling
wind through the bullet holes in the attic
you just hear a it sounds like a comforting
sigh and you think
maybe somewhere John would like
what I just did with his DVDs
Pete feels good are you fucking with John's DVDs
over there Petey I was just fixing them they're
all messed up which is unlike
John we'll write that one down as
maybe he did go missing and
didn't run away
you guys look back and Joni's
not there because while Jon
is family Joni's a thief
and right now she's
very much interested in one
thing and that is getting
an undershirt of John's
that has that manly manly
smell on it that she can
put in her car to piss
off Jared later
Joni as
you head back to the bedroom
to the bad room
that's what
John always called it
depends
on what time of day it is sometimes
after a night
a night of Miller lights and beer
pretzels the bathroom's the bad room
you know what I'm saying
got to do some bad things
like a good thick one
Joni you would see in the hallway on the way to the
bedroom a number of
framed pictures of John and
lots of your family but you see
a few of you and John
he was about three years older
than you so like just
in that sweet spot
for cousin friends
but older enough to be cool
and influential you guys were pretty close
I tried to drive a cool car cause he did but I
can't afford a cool car
dated a guy with a cool car cause he had a cool car
when you say you want a cool car
the picture falls off the wall
she catches it
ooh can I catch it
you can roll to catch it
what should I roll
dexterity or athletics
that's a 40 on an 85
dexterity you catch it
it says my distinguishing feature is wiry
like a live wire
wire like a live wire
you can feel the back of the frame feels a little weird
it's kind of bulging out like
there's something stuck back there
she immediately is going to go for the bulge
looking back in the picture
there's something stuck between the picture itself
and the backing
she does all the little clips
around the back edge of it
which is easy cause only two of them are holding
the whole thing on and she kind of slides it out
what's back there
there's a little note and it says
hey Joni
she smiles
big
it's your old cousin Jon Jon
I thought you might be one of the ones who could
seek out some of these clues that I've left behind
here's the deal Joni
I came into a treasure
and I don't know if I'm going to be able to enjoy it
in this life
so I want my family
at least whoever in my family deserves it
and aside from my clues
it might be you
and you know any team you might assemble ocean style
to aid you in this process
oceans 12
oh yeah she's folding up this note
is there a clue at the bottom?
there's more
I was like that is a shit first clue unless there's
like some coded message in here
yeah or it's the world's greatest clue
I buried the treasure
at these coordinates
man
alright I just got to figure out
what coordinates are
I always did like
you Joni you reminded me of myself
she's in the bathroom at the door shut
there were certain things
she sits on the toilet that's not actually
one of the sentences I'm riffing this all
uh
there was one thing
in particular we loved
about Smokey and the bandit
one thing find that thing
and you'll find your next clue
and you remember you guys always just talked about how
fucking sweet it would be to have the uh
77 black Trans Am
his dad's car
Jon's dad's car? yeah
is that a thing? yeah
of course it is I'm Jon talking to you in this letter
I know what car my dad drives stupid
it was in the flashback to
when they went and stole
the baby uh fuck yeah
in the back of that 77
anyway Joni
I really hope it's you
or your team again if you have assembled one
who finds my treasure
absolutely not just me
me and me alone can do this
the next clue is somewhere
on this property the clue after that
is gonna be harder good luck
and there's a little winky smiley face
and if you look down the line of pictures on the wall
you see actually a lot of them are bulging
oh I grab those
I grab all of those
they're not coming off
uh fuck
unnatural yeah that's a fail 92
your cousin Jon was apparently
Peter naturally good
at attaching pictures to walls
it looks like it's just
should be just a simple wire
but try as you might you can't get
any of the other pictures to come off
the wall and you see one um
Peter these are Peter naturally
put on the wall do you think you can
handle it? what the fuck are you talking
about? and you
see Petey's fumbling
around with a DVD he's
decided that it would be a good ambiance to have
smoking the bandit on in the background
what? if you come into the
hallway and if Arlo follows
Arlo let's go see what she's screaming about
back there Jon are you down there taking
she shoved the note in her pocket
Jon are you down there taking a
trip down memory lane?
let me see some of them photos
what you got over there? while they're on their way real quick
take a
sanity roll for me
I rolled a 76 on a
45 it's not right
it ain't right it's not right
it ain't right it ain't right Jon was good
but nobody's better than Joni
no fucking wall is gonna keep
these pictures on here if you want them
so why can this wall not
give you it's picture? Arlo try to take that
try to take that picture off this wall look at this
look at this and she's like grabbing onto
it and she's gonna try to like put her feet
up on the wall
to show that it's really
stuck on there
as Arlo and Peter walk in
and look at this
a picture actually of all three of you and Jon
like on a float trip
plops off the wall
and it's also bulging
can I try to catch it?
yeah
what am I rolling?
athletics or dexterity
it's what I was hanging onto right?
I got an 88 on a 70
the picture shatters
it bounces down the hallway into the
fireplace
the picture shatters?
you know the glass shatters
fuck it was a really nice frame it's broken
fuck and Peter
the glass is poked right through your face
my face?
ruining forever as far as you
know the only copy of a
pretty nice picture of the four of you
oh through my face of the picture
yeah and you cut
I thought you made my real face
and you slice your finger take a D4 of damage
god dammit look at what you've done
Petey
you took a
I slice from like
pointer finger down to below my
wrist
oh fuck
blood splatters the ceiling
can I try to first aid myself?
well cook has canceled
I'll get you to the hospital
more like cook I just started
fuck does anyone know first aid?
nope I got you I got you
I got you Petey you know that's the thing
ew ew ew
37 on a 50 for first aid
I cannot do blood
oh fuck dude hang on a second here
give me a second he pulls out a bandana
out of his back pocket and just wraps it around there real tight
he knows where to stomps the bleeding
just right that's not gonna feel good
for a while but you'll be alright
man what the
what's that? is there anything
amongst the shattered glass?
there's blood everywhere but um
but Arlo is able before
it just gets like
fire hosed with your blood spray
to nimbly grab a note that's in there
and it's essentially the exact same
note as before it says hey
Arlo, Peter, and Joni
I feel so much
less special now
do I lose any
grip or? yeah you're gonna have to take a
you're gonna have to take a little grip roll for
what do I lose? uh just one
just one I only lose one
you lose one nice
welcome to the hunt for my
lost treasure
fuck dude
it comes out at the bottom like
Joni is this what you're talking about?
yeah I guess so
right about now Joni you're probably feeling
pretty unspecial
but if this picture came off the wall
it means all of you are here god dammit
I couldn't happen to know who might
stumble into my house or why
I figured you might try to rob me
hell I figured all three of you might try to rob me
yup but the fact of the matter
is you're some of the only petty mores who have
the smarts, know how, gumption
and the character
to deserve my treasure
hell yeah hell yeah
remember when we all used to watch Smokey and the Bandit
together? oh I love that car
remember how cool that car was
didn't his daddy have one of those?
yeah daddy drove one right up until the day he
disappeared and then that car went missing
shortly thereafter
he rebuilt the son of bitch from the ground up too
well what's the rest of this note here say?
yada yada yada
treasure treasure treasure treasure
series of clues
oh hey we gotta find that
car I think
good luck to y'all I love you lots
Arlo looks up into the sky
but it's a couple bullet holes
looking at popcorn
love you too John
there's a breeze of warm loving air
through those holes
that's what she said
hey Arlo you know there's nothing up there but stars right?
I just farted
was that Johnny saying that? yup
uh
I've been up there
Arlo there's nothing
so you know you know you pass right through heaven
and Peter thinks about the time
spent piloting jets and stuff
and that was heaven
you can probably smell it now
punched a hole right through that thing
well shit boys and Joni
we gotta do something let's go
yeah we gotta find the car 77
you know where you said it got lost
stolen something? what do I remember
about the car? I bet Ma knows
I bet she does
I didn't remember that John's dad had that car
it's pretty cool
it is pretty cool that he did
somebody
somebody else
I'm not talking about my dad's car
I thought of literally saying that
not my dad's car
well if that car got stolen
you flip the note over
I bet you chuckle
folks were thinking of my dad's car
by the way I know my dad had a cherry
trans amp
but that's not the car I'm thinking of
his was black
I'm sorry I was misremembering
his daddy had a black one
the one from the show
was cherry
is that right? no it sure ain't
and is it a movie?
little Joni
I thought somebody would teach you more about cars
cherry just means it was real nice
right
I haven't seen it
looking at my phone
probably not timeline wise
I was looking at my phone
I was looking at the phone on the wall
waiting for Jared to call
there you go
can I go over and look at the DVD's
and search that
little area over there
17 on
a 40 for search
yeah you know that there's
no clue in the DVD's
you open them up and they're all smashed
except one does have
a note that says go back to the
hallway
guys I found something
it says go back to the hallway
what do you think is going to happen there?
you want to edit?
do you have an ending spot
coming down the line?
I mean we're like 20 minutes from it
I don't care for that as much
ok
well, tough titties
I'm the DM
this episode will be out in January
not December
yeah you go back to the hallway
you pick one of those letters back up
you keep reading the back it says
I'm not talking about my dad's cherry trans am
I'm talking about a sprint car that I was building in my garage
with a sweet
smokey and the bandit paint job
well shit guys
why don't you go take a look at it
after Ma's speech
cut to
Ma's speech
you hear a dinner bell
a big loud dinner bell
and Ma Pettymore
you hear a voice in the distance say
come on y'all
it's time to eat
yeah
Pete runs
you all take your seats
wherever the fuck you want to sit do you sit together
yeah I think so
Joni just has a cigarette hanging out of her mouth
unlit
normally Arlo sits at the kids table
he's done it all his life
and he doesn't know where else to sit
this time he's kind of
like you're gonna go sit over there
Joni who's 24
and just started sitting at the adults table
no didn't even sit at the adults table
the last time she was here
five years ago
he feels so much injustice
Arlo
you reckon I could sit with y'all
yeah I guess I could do that
I've got a little flow chart here
and if at the start of this
whole cookout you had decided not to
mingle or investigate Jon's place
and instead just be dicks
you would have been sent to the kitty table
and
we would have heard mom's speech about
45 minutes ago
well we weren't dickheads
we searched the house
I didn't want you to be but there were contingencies
contingencies
here you go Arlo and I pulled the chair out for him
much obliged
everybody's
everybody's sitting down too
there are two huge
long tables that stretch
almost as wide as
Jon's barn which they're in front of
and Ma, it's her 70th birthday
she kind of comes out
from the kitchen wearing a
long white dress
and she's beaming
she's smiling to everyone
she shakes some hands
she hugs the little children
and two or three of them follow her
as she goes and sits down
at the table
and she raises a glass
and she says please, please, everyone, everyone
be seated
and as everyone sits down
do we all roll for our anti
yeah roll to see if you can sit
what were you saying before?
anti-authoritarian
we were told to do something?
yeah, if you get told by
we can make this a mechanic actually
if you get told by a person
in authority to do something
even
even if you want to do it, you're going to have to roll
against your oppositional defiance
which we're going to say
means Joni
you're going to have to beat a 40 or above
on all oppositional defiance
I have to roll above?
you have to roll 40 or below
I don't know how you want to do it
you've got a 60% chance
of not doing it
I have a 60% chance of not doing it
yes, you two have a 60% chance
of doing it
but there is an exception in every
Pettymore's heart
for Ma, who is not
thank god
man's authority, she is
as far as you're all concerned
a direct agent of the Lord
like, this is
this is the mouthpiece of
the universe
as far as you guys are mostly raised to be concerned
and she's currently beaming
and she's tapping her glass
thank you, thank you all so much
thank you all so much for coming
here today, for joining me here today
on my birthday
happy birthday Ma
she clinks her glass
thank you, thank you, quiet down
it's been so long
it's been so long since
we were all here today as a family
together as a family I mean
we're here today obviously, listen to this old lady
but it
touches me to see
see all my Pettymore's
and I know you're not all Pettymore's
you know, we got the extended families here
boo
laughing
laughing or leaving
the Pettymore's, the Pettybones
the Kenmore's, the Bradleys
the Sanders
the Joneses, the Joneses Pettymore's
the Pettymore Joneses
no matter what your last name is
I'm thankful you came out for my birthday
you see the Krinklehoff uncle just kind of like
bow his head
laughing
what did we say his name was?
Sylvester
I see you Sylvester
you know our families may have had some problems at one time
but Krinklehoff is
well there's worse things in this world than the Krinklehoff
am I right?
clearly
but I'm also
I'm also sad y'all
because it didn't used to be so hard
to get this family together
it didn't used to be so hard to get the
Pettymore's to have a party in Pettymore
Holler woo woo
times have changed
the outside world is creeping in
and I understand in some ways so many of our
cherished young ones
they leave a Holler for a better life
they think they deserve and they'll find out there
but others, others have been
cruelly taken from us
where is our John Lee?
where is our Don?
our Edward?
Aloysius? Where is our Samuel?
somebody goes
I'm right here Ma
she says shut your damn mouth Sammy
I was talking
about your cousin
Burt you keep your boy in line
sorry Ma
now I'm asking you
who took our boys?
who took Ma's boys?
I glance over at Ron
laughter
she says well it's no great mystery
is it? it doesn't take Dick Tracy
to solve this one it's as plain
as the straps on a skunk
the pernicious parasites
who live on the other side of our teat
have broken the peace
boo
who took our boys?
you know who I'm talking about
and every petty more screams
the McRibs
I want them to never return
laughter
we had peace between
the Hollers for nearly 20 years
Beauregarde McRib
has shattered that peace
with no provocation
boo boo boo
Ben microscopic
alright
quiet down there
she's like
she's like Stuart
a jokeful comment is fine
but it has to land
laughter
also sweetheart
I'm in the middle of something
keep your good boy
in line
laughter
who took our boys?
McRibs
we had peace for 20 years with the McRibs
the Beauregard shattered that peace
what do you think?
think we wouldn't notice?
he wouldn't think?
we'd notice our son's missing
Ma's son's missing
he thought that we'd let the loss of our kin
go unanswered?
he thought the Pettimores would just let him spill our blood?
no
no way
where is John Lee Pettimore?
the McRibs got him
where is Don D. Pettimore?
who killed Aloysius?
the McRibs
who killed Edward?
who killed Samuel?
the McRibs did it all
everybody but Joni
give me an alertness roll
oh my god I pass
I fail
a 6 on a 20 because I don't have alertness
you know there's been rumors about
Edward and Aloysius
some of the cousins said they were up to something with John
you're not really sure
but their bodies were found in a shallow grave
not too far from here
just outside the borders of the Hauler
Edward and Aloysius' brother
whose name is Jonathan
when she says who kills Aloysius
who kills Edward
he kind of kicks the ground and spits
but Ma goes on
Noor Guard, Beauregard, that's what they call him
did he forget his history?
Pettimores have
the
Pettimores have licked the McRibs
time and time again
I see why they call him Noor Guard
because he has forgotten
but his hubris won't save him
he's taking on one hell of a debt
and it's a debt that cannot be repaid
in treasure
it must be paid in blood
everyone knows you won't want to be in debt to a Pettimore
everybody knows you don't want to be in debt to Ma
you know what we say
gas, grass, or ass
no one rides for free
Big Bo wants to ride your ass for free
no free rides
I say let his hubris
be his downfall
let it be the downfall of his whole godforsaken
clan
Big Bo may have started this feud again
but Ma is gonna end it
for good
who's with me
I'm fucking in
I'm in
that's
everybody's murmuring and then shouting
yes Ma we're with you
we're with you
fuck the McRibs
no free rides
fuck Mark Zuckerberg
and in that moment you hear
booming up the driveway
the powerful engine
of a 77 black
Pontiac Transam Firebird
which rolls to a stop
in the driveway
right in front of John's house
and you'll see who gets out next week
I bet it's Trey
I think we found
our clue
weirdly a letter
falls from the sky
delivered by an owl
an owl swoops
down and it's got another scribbled note
in John's handwriting
and it says
I couldn't
I tried to prepare for every contingency
with my animal friends
contingency
and one of those
contingencies was me forgetting that my daddy
drove the kind of car that I was talking about
Trey drives one it's also not the clue
again it's the sprint car
in my shed
why don't you go check it out next month
hell yeah dude
hell yeah man
fuck yeah
I cannot wait to fight some fucking McRibs
bring on the McRibs
them sweet and tangy bastards
I said I did not
want to spoil that joke for you guys
so when the McRib came back for that farewell weekend
I was like we should maybe go get a picture
of us eating it for social media right
and you guys were like
fuck no
we should go get some McRibs
never
that probably doesn't have anything to do with anything
we talked about the fish fillet for like 10 minutes
yeah we did
oh I'd go for a fish fillet
oh man it's not cheddar is it
oh it's not cheddar is it
it's not
I need a pill
I need a drink
I need a smoke
I need an eight foot couch
and a four foot screen
a big vacation
and a dog that's mean
I need a four wheel drive
and a three piece suit
a nine millimeter
that I know I can shoot
in the USA
it's not a question of greed
cause everybody
who is anybody
agrees
a borrower's the one to lead
you get what you need
I need a girl
I need a gal
I need a friend
I need a pal
I need a car
I need a screen
I need some coffee
I need some cream
I need a lovesick slave
with six foot legs
a liberated woman
and a dog that begs
I need the will to live
and a place to die
don't wanna know how
but I gotta know why
in the USA
it's not a question of greed
cause everybody
who is anybody
agrees
a borrower's the one to lead
you get what you need
guitar solo
I need a nurse
I need a dog
I need a mouth
I need a claw
I need a bush
I need a shovel
I need a hand
I need a glove
I need a sunburned sager
and some hot top shoes
a new straw hat
I'm the king of the blues
I need a whole wheat meal
with saturated fat
a ding-dong daddy
and I like it like that
in the USA
it's not a question of greed
cause everybody
who is anybody
agrees
a borrower's the one to lead
you get what you need
guitar solo