This is yet another introduction to the radio show known as 694.2 PTBP,
the galaxy's only radio station that is technically also maybe a toxic waste site.
You all know me, and if you don't, my name's DJ Wolf the dog,
here to howl out some things at y'all before something else starts happening right after I stop talking.
Have I ever stuck around even one second after my segment ends?
Damn, you know I haven't.
I clock out and skitter as fast as my limbs can skitter out to the municipal dump.
It's all you can eat every day, baby.
And speaking of howling, and skittering, and me, Wolf the dog,
it's time to skitter on over to a new howling with Wolf.
Howl
This show's howling with Wolf is from Gwenivere in Greenville, North Carolina,
who tweeted about the show and tagged at Pretending Pod.
What's that? You haven't tweeted about the show and tagged at Pretending Pod?
That's so weird.
You should be more like Gwenivere in Greenville, North Carolina,
and tweet about the show and tag at Pretending Pod.
Gwenivere in Greenville, North Carolina, writes,
Greetings, Wolf.
I'm writing you from some weird liminal dimension I stumbled into while cleaning carpets in some old church.
Overall, it isn't too bad.
I just wish they had more food than these strange bits of jerky with hair on them,
and wine that tastes more like pennies than wine.
I want to give a shout out to my best friend Ash and girlfriend Kaylee,
as well as everyone who works on this podcast.
Y'all have got me through more hard times than I can count and made me laugh just as many.
Damn.
Well, I hope you can turn that liminal dimension into a liminalade dimension, you know what I'm saying?
And if you could, uh, email me some of them jerky bits,
I would be mighty delighted to partake in whatever or whoever it is.
Now, if you want to write up something for your wolf to howl, tag at Pretending Pod on Twitter,
fuck the musk, tag at Pretending Pod on Instagram, fuck the zuck,
or tag pretending to be people on Facebook, fuck the zuck double time.
Or write us up a five-star review on the podcast app of your choice,
and make sure it gets in front of my dang eyeballs.
And fuck whoever owns podcasts.
And if you happen to have forgotten, the links are in the show notes.
That's right.
Whether you want to give us money in exchange for bonus content on Patreon,
or cop some new drip at the merch store,
or join the listener communities on Discord and Reddit,
or vibe to a selection of tracks from the PTBPOST on YouTube,
you can find those links in the show notes.
And now, for our top ten shortest news segments, it's the news.
Last time, the gang went to the Zeitgeist,
the abandoned and very unimpressive city Space Needle,
and then Dr. Brock Hargrave,
no, no way, this can't be right,
says here, Dr. Hargrave brought a couple of sedated folks on leashes
up to the spot he'd been digging, smoked some meth,
plunged a syringe in the dude, stuck a finger in his own ear
and then promptly into his own mouth,
and then that very zonked-out dude
just climbed into the abdomen of Dr. Brock Hargrave
and disappeared?
Also making a disappearance for the final time,
it's Hudson Freeman with muscles all sprees.
You are now listening to the final episode
of our four-episode series, Fuck Me.
Oh, do you want to take that one again?
Do you want to do that?
What a gentleman.
Holy cow farms, leave it in.
Oh, right, no, we now know that burps are not only important
but life-changing to our listeners,
so we got to leave them in.
Also, we're sponsored by Aldi and those burps,
brought to you by Aldi Generic Sparkling Water.
It's Bell V Sparkling Water Tangerine by Pure Aqua.
Hey, Zach, I'm sorry, but you have a dozen cases of those
in your house and you don't know what the fuck it's called
without looking at the can.
It's because you have the koozie.
That's exactly right, I'm covering it up constantly.
24-7 koozied up.
And he knows how to read, for sure.
I just think it's weird to not use a koozie
and touch a cold can, like that's fucked up to me.
I have so many koozies in a drawer of my house
and I've never once used any of them.
Same, Zach and his wife have the same drawer
but they use them all the time and it's pretty great,
honestly, they're always like handing you one
when you have a cold beverage at their house.
It's a nice touch.
You're making me question my koozie behavior.
Yeah, I mean, you've got them.
Keep them in the drawer, that's where mine are.
You don't fuse, you're gonna lose.
That's exactly right.
That's what they always say.
I forgot how to say the word.
That's what Taylor's back tattoo says.
Right above Richard Nixon.
It was supposed to be a cover up
but it just looks cooler now.
Sweet, does your wife really have a tattoo
of Richard Nixon on her back?
No, Roger Stone does.
Oh, right.
What happened last week?
Wolf already told us, let's dive into this shit.
Oh yeah, thanks Wolf.
I think maybe we need to go talk to him or get him,
but I am not leaving here without dropping this
in the hole.
You say as you roll grip,
as you all see this dude disappear into the torso
of Dr. Brock Hargrave.
I pass.
Shelly passes also.
I've opened enough people to, you know.
Same.
The hook passes as well.
Okay, everyone is going to lose one grip still.
This is strange enough that it stops you all in your tracks
and you're left just watching.
Just checking.
Did you guys also see that guy roll up his belly
like it was a carpet and put another man inside?
We sure did.
How does a man fit in another man like that?
He just walked right in.
He absolutely devoured him like my career.
It was like he went into a tiny set of stairs,
like there was a vanishing point
and he got smaller as he walked towards the belly,
but it didn't make any sense.
It was kind of amusing.
We got to go save that woman before she walks
into his belly.
There's only one quick way down.
I made hook.
I know what you're thinking.
I think we got to ride the Bigfoot.
Well, okay.
That's not what's going to happen.
I'm sorry, you're going to die.
If you try that.
With a Bigfoot landing.
I would like to pry open the elevator doors.
Oh, fuck yeah.
And look down the shaft
and see if my good old buddy elevator cable is still there.
Go ahead and roll criminology.
Nope.
Okay, so you get these elevator doors pried open
and you're looking at the shaft,
the empty shaft ahead of you.
And you see that the cables that go all the way
down the bottom are like frayed to the point
to where you think if you were to like jump on
and try to shimmy down, it might break.
Dang, my usual method of going downstairs
is out of adequate question.
It's okay.
I'm sure we'll encounter a sewer very soon.
Fellas, any ideas about how to save that woman's life?
We got to check the toilets.
Maybe there's a cow toilet.
See if we can get flushed down.
Yes, maybe there's a cow toilet in the restaurant.
We don't know how fresh their beef was.
Is there a giant cow-sized toilet
to get flushed down on this level?
All right, let me roll now.
Meat hook in this line of work,
sometimes the person gets eaten.
You all don't even care.
You look so complacent.
Isn't this your dude, Shelly?
Why is he doing that?
It's not that we don't care.
It's just that stopping him is our only option here.
And right now we've got to find a way to stop him.
We also don't know that they're not perfectly fine in there.
We can also take this out on our children
or wives or whatever later.
Specifically for that we've written down.
Yeah, like subtracting from your bonds.
Something like that, yeah.
Metaphorically.
Is there a door to where the old observation deck
used to be even though I know the deck fell off?
That is correct, there is a door
and it's got tape like over it
trying to warn people to not go in this general area
as it is dangerous as the door is not there.
It's just the open wind, the summer wind coming through
and the smell of the parking lot.
Does it happen to be right over the holes?
Oh yeah, of course it is.
I can't get open.
Do something, throw something at him.
Hey, take this and we'll do it at the same time
and I give her the small Bigfoot
and I dangle the Bigfoot over the hole
which he happens to be close to, right?
On the count of three we're gonna clap
which requires both hands which will make us drop these.
I see exactly what you're going for and I'm in.
One, two, three.
Go ahead and roll.
The foot's full.
What are we rolling for?
I think you can either roll dexterity or athletics here.
Or Bigfoot.
Or Bigfoot obviously, dropping Bigfoot
if that's a craft skill.
Yeah, I got a 46, that's a pass.
Nice.
I didn't hear any of the things that you said
to go for. What did you roll?
25.
Oh, what is your dexterity or athletics?
More than that.
Yes it is and with that,
describe these two bigfoots falling please.
It's just like a long beard
and a kind of Neanderthal face with a hairy body
but it's got, it's like a plastic troll doll underneath
so it's pretty hard when it's coming at speed.
Oh yeah.
Flung.
It's companion, same thing, much larger
and I said it was stuffed, it's not.
It's also got the big, hard troll body.
And they're somersaulting through the air
as if they're in a beautiful ballet in the sky.
It's stuffed with trolls.
Exactly, and the truth.
I'm aiming for the dude.
I wanna distract him so that he comes after us
and we can save this woman's life.
Fantastic.
I'm aiming for the hole.
Okay, one bigfoot, large one?
I had the large one, yes.
Goes directly, perfect hit, dude perfect
from the top of the zeitgeist into the bottom of this hole
and as it hits the bottom.
Vincenti braces to be teleported back to non-existence.
It bounces and then lands softly, lifelessly
like a stuffed bigfoot that you might get at a carnival
at the bottom of a dirt pit.
And the other bigfoot knocks Dr. Brock Hargrave
right in the hand as he pulls out a syringe, shatters it.
I rolled combat for the woman who he was going for
and Luke, what did I roll?
You rolled what I assume is a critical success with a 22.
And then I rolled damage for when she grabs the shovel.
Right, she grabbed a shovel which I assume is a D8.
So he rolled a D8 and he got an eight.
Even up from like from up here, we can see it glistens.
And the sharp tip goes directly in to the soft belly.
That's where all the people are.
Of Dr. Brock Hargrave.
The extra soft belly.
He falls to his knees.
You see blood splattering out onto the ground.
I need everyone to roll grip again for violence.
Can Shelley celebrate?
18.
A custom.
I am happy at this violence.
Vincente goes, fucking excellent shot kid.
And then he throws up.
Lose one grip.
For failing?
For failing.
Shelley lost.
Lose one grip for failing as you also have
just like a stomach turning reaction.
That should have been me.
Don't worry doc, there's a lot of professional rivals
you might one day get to kill.
I believe Jimmy Corrigan is.
I thought he was adapted.
That was actually a different character.
So I rolled and passed which makes sense.
Cause he's seen a lot of death.
Seen a lot of death, seen a lot of blood.
It continues to just ooze out
and you see one of his intestines falls out of the hole
onto the ground, dripping.
And he's just kind of shaking violently on his knees
and then he falls.
I feel like we should go down there.
But if Meadhope glances around the top of this observatory
real quick, is there anything else of interest up here?
What are you looking for?
What about a length of rope that they used to hang aliens
off the side of during the parties?
Or perhaps a banner?
A banner is good.
Rush hour two style.
Okay, we've had a couple of bad experiences
but I think we're all getting pretty lazy.
I think we can handle the stairs.
Vincent has his eyes closed.
I rolled a hundred.
Oh, wait, I'm gonna use my, wait, what this word?
That's a one.
Ooh, he found a loophole.
I'm gonna use my luck.
He can make it a one?
Yeah.
Boom.
Luck spent.
Ooh, I like it.
You only have half a luck, take mine.
Vincent grabs half of a luck,
forms it with his own half luck, spins it to...
You almost fall head first into a closet, but then...
Look at this industrial strength rope with climbing gear.
Yeah, with a crit success,
you just find like a fireman's ladder
that's used for exactly this purpose.
Yeah, it's in the closet.
It's just in the back of the closet.
You move some stuff out of the way.
You have to clown fireman's ladder
so it's shoved in there, but when you get it out.
It goes to the ground, there's a hole in the ground.
Yeah, because ladders are easier to go down than stairs.
Everybody knows that.
Right, less dangerous, more stable.
Oh, you guys don't have to roll for a fireman's ladder.
He does the, he presses the extendo release button
on the fireman's ladder and it just shoots down
to the bottom and I look at Mead Hook
and say, get scuttling, kid.
I scuttle.
When I's told to scuttle, I scuttle.
A tear forms in Jimmy's eyes and he's like,
he didn't say shimmy.
I need everyone shimmying down to roll.
I'm taking the stairs.
Alertness or dexterity.
And if you're taking the stairs, do the same.
Just an eight, a definite success.
Success in here.
Finally able to go up and or down.
Something fashion to do just that.
We get to use your hands and your feet on this one,
so it's easier.
I pass my scuttle.
Scuttle.
I pass my stairs, but I fail my alertness,
which makes sense because I'm the only one
going down the stairwell.
I failed.
Dead silent.
Oh, I didn't roll alertness.
Fail alert.
Not alert.
I'm focusing on safely scuttling.
I pass alertness.
Okay, as the four of you are heading down
to the base of the zeitgeist,
Jimmy Corrigan and the stairs all alone meet Hook
and Vincent D'Bori focusing deeply
on making their way down the pole.
Scuttle, scuttle, scuttle.
And Shelly St. Blythe, who is lively going down
and you notice that there's a window actually
out this side, just like a thin window
going all the way down.
So you've got a clear view as you head down
this fireman's pole for not a single fireman in sight.
And you see this woman just shaking,
her hands covered in blood,
and she kicks the body of Dr. Brock Hargrave
into one of the holes and begins covering it
with the mound of dirt that's next to it
as fast as she can.
Wait, we'll help you.
We saw everything.
What?
You're all right.
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No one could have seen that.
No one could have known.
We're the good guys.
Who the fuck are you?
My name's Brandy.
You're a fine girl.
If you were worried about being incriminated,
now I got more information.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Brandy, it's okay.
I'm just trying to teach you a little bit about the world
as my dads did for me.
Brandy, how'd this guy find you?
We were just, we were just at a bar.
Oh shit, shit, shit, where, where's, where's.
Which bar did he find you at?
The Iliad.
Fuck, fuck, where's Brandon?
Where's Brandon?
Jimmy sighs deeply and he's like,
your boyfriend's name is Brandon.
Oh shit, my name's Brandy.
Okay, I see, I hear it now.
You never heard it before?
Nobody ever thought that was weird?
You're just now getting this.
I didn't, no, it's not the time.
It's not the time, but I also wanna say,
Brandy, we don't know for sure
that if you hadn't gutted that man,
we couldn't have gotten Brandon safely out of there.
Out of where?
Yeah, he's in his stomach.
We might as well try.
And he brushes away some of the dirt
and tries to open the stomach.
Do you hop down into the?
No, I peer in.
Okay, so you're gonna have to like lay down
on the ground to like. Sure.
Okay, so you lay down on the ground
with your arms outstretched down to the bottom of this pit.
You're like pulling at the wound?
Yeah, at the wound, I guess, yeah.
Or like trying to, did I see him belly button pull?
I mean, now there's a gash there
where she stabbed him with the shovel.
So it's really easy to do now.
Yeah, I use that opening.
Roll grip, because that's fucking gross.
It is.
40 on a 40.
Damn.
With his success, you lose no grip on reality
as you have done this kind of shit before.
And everyone kind of notices the like steady sure hand
that Vincentibori is taking as he pulls apart the abdomen
of Dr. Brock Hargrave inside of this pit.
I worked at the old man's meat shop.
I done it a hundred times, except on like animals, but.
Intestines begin falling out.
Blood is just covering your hands now, Vincenti.
And you see there's a kidney's spleen.
It's just like all just in your hands as you're reaching in.
Yeah, there's no, there's no Brandon in here.
What?
She just throws up all over the ground.
I thought he was just there.
Starts crying.
It's okay, Brandon.
You kind of fucked this whole thing up for us, Brandy.
I'm gonna touch her hair to calm her.
It's okay.
I seen people do this.
Hey doctor, do you know anything
about what's in that syringe?
I'm almost there.
Give me a moment.
He's coming down the last few rungs.
What did I miss?
Oh, doc.
Vincenti.
They're not in his intestines.
Eviscerated somebody.
I see.
It's okay though.
He went to work in his old man's meat shop.
I guess the intestines
were already out. I did.
So there was that.
And I suppose you did not find the man inside there.
No, Brandon, this is Brandy.
Hey Brandy.
And her boyfriend's name was Brandon.
Yee-hoo!
Brandy and Brandon, huh, yes.
We all saw him go in there though.
There's gotta be a trap door to this belly or something.
I do wanna pick up that syringe and take a look at it.
I've got 40 forensics.
Is that something that would cover?
It wouldn't, no.
I've also got, oh no, I don't have-
Oh, I have pharmacy.
Yeah.
Pharmacy will do it.
Hold on.
I've seen a syringe or two in my day.
Let me take a look-see.
Thank you, laughter.
That's a 17.
That'll do.
Ooh.
What does that mean?
What's in the syringe?
You kind of squirt some out the tip of the syringe
and smell it and you know that it is
some sort of a tranquilizer, like a horse tranquilizer,
some like ketamine adjacent.
So nothing supernatural.
No.
Hey, Rowan, are you still up in that tower?
Yes, I am.
Thank you for asking.
God, why are you just the worst?
So unambitious.
Do you know anything about what's happening here?
Rowan is just shaking their head vigorously,
just back and forth.
No, no, no.
We could put it in him and see what it does
and then he won't talk anymore.
No.
And you see that the face of Rowan kind of disappears
as they walk backwards.
Once you say an idea, we gotta do it.
She shoves the needle in her hand, broken or not,
into his arm.
As he slides down the pole.
Rowan walks up to the group and you shove the syringe
into their arm and they're just like completely
not ready for it.
Completely caught off guard.
It's all right.
I'm a raptor.
Nobody panic.
I don't think they're actually a raptor.
I feel like a raptor.
Okay.
And Rowan is just like laughing, giggling,
and then they just kind of go quiet, staring at the ground.
I think he's just regular high.
This is a Christian podcast,
so we don't know what that's like.
So you imagine you're a dinosaur, right?
No, I mean, the only time I've done ketamine, the...
You were a raptor?
One of the people in the room thought he was a raptor,
started jumping up on all the furniture
with a couple of claws out, just kind of being a goober.
That didn't have anything to do with the ketamine.
That guy was probably just a raptor.
With my arms, it's still inside Dr. Prock.
So what the fuck do we do now?
Well.
This was the guy we were looking for.
I mean, I guess we could just tell Ruth Moses Esther
that we found him.
It seems like mission accomplished, yes.
I'm gonna give her a call.
Oh, I don't have a cell phone, though.
I like, yeah, I like kind of like nod my head to-
Turn your head to the side like you just did.
Yeah, nod my head to like where my back pocket,
where my cell phone is.
That's weird.
I'm laying down on the ground with blood all over my hands.
I grab the phone.
I give her a ring.
Ring, ring, ring, ring.
Vincenzi, Vincenzi, what's going on?
Hello, it is me, Meat Hook, on the telephone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Great phone etiquette, kid.
Yeah, so Meat Hook, is Vincenzi okay?
Is everyone okay?
Have you figured it out?
Have you found Dr. Prock?
We found him.
Everyone is not okay.
Dr. Hargrave's guts are outside his body.
And, well, do you know anything about supernaturally
putting people inside yourself?
No, did you see anything like that occur?
Or I assume that you could get inside.
Do you know how it's done?
Did he tell you?
Well, we can't get any information
because he was murdered before we arrived here.
Hold on, let me check his pulse.
And I just kind of, don't move my hand for a little bit.
Is there, do I feel a pulse?
The blood has stopped like splooshing
like at a heartbeats rate.
Yeah, no, we can't ask him anything right now.
He's dead, he's dead, he's dead.
So how, did you take him out?
We met someone named Brandy.
She's wearing club wear.
And she's just, it was kind of self-defense.
Brandy, are you there?
Let me give her the phone.
Oh shit.
Cool, I enjoy talking to your own NBC.
I like that he paused.
So you wanted to rip off comedy bang bang, right?
Until, all until you.
Completely forgot.
He paused to wait for a response.
Was the deal.
I would have to answer that.
Let's see how it's done.
Did you see anything strange or out of the ordinary
throughout the process?
She's useless, take her out.
Like that's why they call it a handler.
Take her out, out.
Yeah, casualties are acceptable on this mission.
If I didn't tell you that before,
I think you should know by now.
Hey, Meat Hook, I think it's time you prove yourself.
No, I don't want to kill her.
Good, you proved yourself.
Ruth, how should we proceed?
I mean, we found the target.
I guess you bring her back here, I guess.
And did you learn what he was trying to figure out?
No.
Shelly kind of walks up.
Does lost in the fungus mean anything to you?
To the fungus.
I mean, yeah, I've heard people going missing,
people talk about people getting lost in the fungus.
Disappear.
That's just an expression?
It's common between the cowboys.
It's an old city expression, yeah.
Lazarus, you seem a bit agitated.
You seem a bit agitated.
No, everything is so clear now.
You seem a bit more manic than when we last spoke.
Manic because I'm on the right path
doing all the right things.
Is this the path that our mutual friends have set you on
or is this a path of self-discovery?
What's the difference?
You take your directions from me
because I am the handler, I'm in charge.
It's possible she's become a raptor,
if you know what I mean.
I'm getting big raptor energy here.
Hey, we never asked and we should have.
Why did your place reek of cat piss when there were no cats?
I've been trying to, I've been having to stay up,
I've been having to stay up to take care of this mission.
What does that have to do with cat piss?
Oh, you've been buying from the strummers.
Or producing.
Okay, okay, oh, oh, oh, I'm all high and mighty.
I've never done anything weird or bad
that the dare officer would disapprove of in my life.
I'm a fucking piece of shit square.
Okay, like that's, we got to do with the things
that the commission makes us have to do
because I had to stay awake and I had to find the numbers
and I had to figure it out and it's 836, 836.
It's around holy cow farms and it's, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, 836, we found holes that say that.
I don't know if we should give her any more information.
Yes, I feel that she may be compromised.
That's what time we were supposed to meet.
At the Bible study.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Holy shit.
That's right, that's right.
That's some fucking good note taking.
Hey, this is something that's not come up as players ever.
What do you do when your Delta Green handler is insane?
Who do you call?
I mean, not the obvious answer to that question.
Yeah, just the cops.
The cops.
I don't know what to do.
Meat Hook, could you take her off speakerphone
for just a second?
Yeah.
Don't take me off speakerphone.
I'm sorry, Lazarus, Ruth, we need to have a sidebar.
I already hung up on her.
So I think we got to, I get up off the ground.
I stopped playing with his guts.
Wet hands.
Maybe she knows something about the numbers though.
Maybe that's a bigger clue.
Eight, three, six.
I don't know.
Do you think there's anything to be learned
at Trigate Supply?
I guess not until the morning.
Well, she wanted us to bring his body back,
but that feels very incriminating.
I mean, we didn't even kill him.
Also, you should probably get all that blood
off your hands, Vincente.
He is also already in a hole.
A whole lot of trouble.
Usually I just do what she asked me to do
and it's proven to be the best choice so far.
So, I mean, I think we just-
Vincente, you heard her.
She's not the same person
who was making those calls before.
She's gone.
She's not gone.
We can help, maybe we can help her.
Now that the mission's over.
Maybe we have to eliminate her.
Kill Ruth?
She basically said it herself.
This wasn't a mission, it's something she gave us.
But she's the handler, the guys, the lizard people,
whoever give it to her. Who handles the handler.
I never asked and I never really cared.
I think we take the body to her,
we find out she probably knows about the numbers.
What if enabling her enables something much worse?
I'm not here to discern that.
I'm here to do a job.
Then we have to rethink this whole parenthood situation.
What do you think, Shelly?
Shelly's been kinda staring down in the hole at the body
and he wants to jump down into the hole.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Look in the ear,
cause he stuck his finger in his ear
and then into his mouth.
I wanna see if he got anything out of there.
You smell it first when you kinda get down close
to look inside.
It's like a salty, horrible earwax smell
mixed with like the ocean,
mixed with like an earthy.
Is it perhaps fungus-like?
I mean, when something earthy
is like mixed with the wet and the saline
for long enough.
Those are the conditions there, too.
It's almost as if something might be growing.
Comrades, down here please for your attention.
There seems to be a growth of sorts in Hargrave's ear.
I believe I found the aforementioned fungus
that one gets lost in.
Is it in his fucking brain?
Be very careful, doctor.
I can't tell how deep it goes,
but it does look as though it's cultivated here.
Can you get a sample?
I will attempt to do so now.
Do I need to roll?
No.
I think he pulls just a pin out of his pocket.
No, just touch it.
Yeah, just touch it, you fucking idiot.
Use the little puppet hands.
They'll fit right in there.
I whip out Craig Mile.
Craig Mile, I know this isn't your normal job.
I need you now.
You put a little lab coat and goggles on.
Tiny little rubber gloves on the ends.
And he maneuvers Craig Mile's hand in there
and makes it do a perfect scooping motion.
And pulls it out.
And then he grabs a sandwich bag that he always has on him
from after lunch.
Yeah, of course.
And scoops it into the bag.
After lunch is my favorite of the before trilogy.
Can we do a little experiment with that?
What do you think?
Hey, Rowan.
Rowan looks up at you, bags so deep under the eyes,
falling even heavier, seemingly,
as these dead eyes look at you.
It's time for a snack.
I pass the bag up to Meat Hook here.
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
There you go, Meat Hook.
I do believe it is time for science.
Okay.
Shelly's also starting to get out of the hole
and on his way out, he spits on the body of Hargrave.
He steps on his nose.
I'm gonna, when you're picking up dog poop
and you put your hand on the outside of the plastic bag,
but don't touch what's inside, but reversed.
And I'm gonna put just a little bit into his mouth.
Okay.
Hey, Becca.
Thanks.
Meat Hook is the closest
to Rowan when this happens.
And as the substance that was in the ear
of Dr. Brock Hargrave touches the mouth
and goes into the esophagus of Rowan Fitzpatrick.
Meat Hook, you are overcome with a need,
a feverish, rabid desire to get in the belly
of Rowan Fitzpatrick by any means necessary.
I need you to roll power at a negative 40
to fight against this.
Oof, get in my belly.
Yeah, I'm gonna get in that belly.
Kid, don't do it.
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna get in.
It's my creep now.
It is really.
My dads highly advise you against getting in that belly.
Okay, so I rolled a 35.
My power is a 60.
But you needed me to roll a 20 or below.
I did.
Oh, man.
So I just start digging in that belly button
to make a little spot, a little basement nest,
if you will, for a rat curl.
I can't lose another daughter.
We've got a basement nest for you here.
Basement creep now.
Remember how repulsed you were by this person earlier.
So we are going to go into combat order here,
which is in order of dexterity.
So call out your dexterity, please.
70.
50.
65.
Okay, so it's gonna start with Meat Hook,
go to Vincenty, and then because we're already
going that way, we'll go Shelly and then Jimmy.
And with that, Meat Hook,
you are fighting tooth and nail
to get inside Rowan Fitzpatrick.
Hell yes, I am.
This is the answer I've been waiting for all my life.
Who would have ever thought Rowan Fitzpatrick
would hold it?
But now I need to know what's in there.
And I just try and rip it open.
Yeah, and because you did the syringe, there's no contest.
So if you succeed, you succeed.
I rolled a 77 and I needed a 50, so that's a crit fail.
Oh, shit.
So is that, that might be good for us.
I don't know.
That depends on your goal.
It definitely depends on your goal.
With a critical failure, as you are desperately
trying to crawl into the stomach area of Rowan Fitzpatrick,
you slip and one of, your hand reaches out
and just goes directly soft through,
like you're putting your hand into a bowl of jello,
just like into the middle of Rowan Fitzpatrick.
And you hold on, and I need you to roll a grip
as you hold on to this weird kind of like bouncy,
synthetic feeling substance on the other side.
Zach is in grip to me in grip.
88 would be a crit fail.
Holy shit, wow.
All right, okay.
So two crit fails in a row.
No.
Oh, that means you get slimed.
Click the button.
It's not working.
So I need you to, well, I was gonna have you roll a D8
and add one for your grip loss, but when you crit fail,
you just take the maximum.
So that's nine.
Okay.
So you lose nine grip in one fell swoop,
which means that you are on a temporary loss
of yourself from reality.
We weren't there already?
Okay.
I just start humming Mamma Mia.
And is it because you have three dads now?
Yeah, exactly.
Yes, exactly.
Genius.
You feel a hand reach out and grab your wrist.
Holy shit.
Oh, my friend, you found me.
Brandon, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
And now it is the turn of Vincenty Bory.
You've got Meat Hook up to one elbow in Rowan Fitzpatrick,
a normal role-playing sentence.
Vincenty's thinking when Hargrave died,
his portal belly went away.
She's how far in?
Just an arm?
Elbow, yep, single elbow.
Meat Hook, I'm so fucking sorry.
And I pull my revolver out
and I want to shoot Rowan in the face.
You have good firearms?
I got good firearms.
Okay.
What?
Strong choice.
Go ahead and roll firearms.
I do not pass my firearms.
85 on a 50.
You didn't have good firearms.
50's like I went to college
and got a doctorate in firearms.
No.
According to the rules.
I think according to the rule book,
a 50 would be above a college degree in something.
It's firearms.
I forgot to load my fucking revolver
in this particular chamber.
That's an out that doesn't kill Meat Hook.
And your turn's over.
And we move on to Shelly Seamblithe.
Shelly sees that Meat Hook is going in
so he wants to grab a leg.
He's pulling back the other way.
Tug of war.
Yep, tug of war time.
That's a way more logical move.
As you roll strength.
My basement creep, you're coming with us.
I rolled an eight.
Oh, that is good if it wasn't in a contest.
Yep, hold on.
Yeah, I did that math right.
Okay, I've got an 80 firearms and an 85 strength.
So I'm going to join Shelly.
I was going to say, I just passed with a 24.
So you can add your success onto the eight
to try to beat a 24.
It's a 96.
Oh no.
Doesn't an eight beat a 24?
It's got to be.
Not in a contest.
Yeah, if it's a contest,
you have to roll higher under the score.
The worst critical thing.
Higher under?
Your rules are nutty.
It's blackjack rules.
That's what Thomas keeps saying.
Yeah, I don't like them either.
But they're not our rules.
Because you're telling the dice to roll low.
You know, you can't tell the dice two things.
I know, exactly.
You got to tell the dice to roll as high as possible
while still being a success.
But it makes sense because if you have a higher level skill,
you can roll a higher number and still win.
Yeah, but it feels weird.
You're not wrong.
I've been on Zach's side this whole time.
But holy shit, that's not good.
So yeah, Thomas did the crit-est of crit fails
in our own rules.
Yeah, I didn't roll a 69.
I rolled a 96 trying to pull you out with.
Not nice.
That's like two angry people
that don't even want to look at each other.
Yeah, they're not pleasuring each other orally.
They're farting on each other with their backs turned.
Yeah, they're sleeping in fetal positions
in opposite directions.
One's upside down.
Angry in it, opposite end of the bed.
Meat Hook is gonna-
I'm gonna turn my back to you.
Grab onto this hand that she found inside the belly.
I kind of want to try and pull the hand out,
but I'm wondering if the need to go inside the belly
has changed at all.
Or if my crit fail means I'm just jumping on it.
I love the pulling at the hand.
Yeah, that's fun.
Hold on, what's in here?
What grip did you have and what was your breaking point?
Oh.
I'm not at the breaking point yet.
That's right, but you rolled over five.
So we're gonna actually go-
I'm sorry, I completely missed that.
Basically at this point what we do-
I'll be the DM for a minute.
Thank you.
At this point, we roll a D6
and we put in order fight, flight, or freeze.
And so if you think that Meat Hook
would be most likely to fight,
you put that at the top and that would be four, five, and six.
You text flight to fight to four, five, six.
Four, two, oh, six, nine, six, nine.
And if you think it's second-
Wait, no, it only gets two numbers.
Five and six.
And then the second most likely that you think
if you roll a two or a three,
then you do that one.
And then the last one that you think is the least likely
is just a one.
You mean given my insanity what's most and least likely?
That is correct.
Okay, well flight means crawling in this belly.
So that's the most likely.
Okay.
Fight is probably her natural inclination.
So that's next.
And then freeze, yeah, that's the least likely.
Okay, that's perfect.
Oh no. It's a five.
Five is flight.
We jump on it.
I take the hand and I let the hand pull me
as I just relax my body.
Yeah.
You all see Meat Hook fully engulfed
by the midriff of Rowan Fitzpatrick.
I need you all to roll grip.
Completely inside?
As she disappears from view entirely.
You see a steel-tipped boot
with a lot of extra studs and spikes stuck out of it.
Kind of get caught on the edge of the skull buckle
and then before going in.
I am not okay with seeing our new adoptive child
sucked up into that man's belly.
This is fish face all over again.
Did I mention I'm 27?
It's okay though.
I failed.
How old were you when your parents
dropped you off at the place?
Seven.
Oh, okay.
20 years in the hole.
So that's where I'm stuck mentally, you know?
So then fish face is still very problematic.
Oh yeah.
Well, no one ever debated that.
Joe, how did Shelly St. Blythe do that?
I passed.
Okay, so the single pass here on the grip.
You only lose one with the disappearance of Meat Hook.
The other two of you, I need you to roll a D6 and add one.
So when, fuck.
That's an eight for me.
Puts me past, well past my breaking point.
How could it be A is D6 plus one?
You said plus two, I thought.
Oh, sure.
He did not.
Oh, well a seven still puts me past my breaking point.
And a temporary grip loss.
Teacher, didn't we have a quiz?
No, I never fucking said we had a quiz.
When Corrigan failed his, Extreme failed
his strength check, I think he fell backwards
and it knocked me off.
I was gonna say, yeah, we didn't ever resolve that.
Cause I was still holding on to her leg,
but we'll say that I am not now.
No, you definitely fell back.
Along with the critical failure there.
I lost four grip, but I'm still well above
my breaking point.
Okay, and with four, you don't need to fight
flight or freeze, however.
I'm going fight, fight, freeze.
You said D6 plus one?
Yes, I did.
So I lost five.
And you're gonna do the same.
Freeze.
Fincenzi Bori freezes in his tracks, unable to move.
Lost in thought.
Jimmy Corrigan fights, he fucking thrusts
both arms into the belly of Rowan.
And as you do so, I need you to roll a D4 minus one
for damage.
That made a cool noise.
Two.
Two minus one?
Two minus one is one?
No, no, no.
And so with a two hit point loss,
you just punch with both fists into the stomach.
The abs you feel just like, oh,
you get a slight response out of Rowan for the first time.
And then it's just, and then just continues
to just dead eyes look at the ground.
Where's that ear fungus?
Give me that fucking ear fungus.
Is the bag that had the fungus lying anywhere?
That would be on the ground.
I'll use my luck to have dropped it.
Yeah, no, I think you could have dropped it.
I like that, I like that.
We'll let it ride.
So you've dropped it on the ground there,
but I actually at this point need a roll.
I need a con roll from Meat Hook.
Oh.
Oh, pass, 49 under 50.
What wonders is she going to see in there?
You're not sure about anything that's been happening
so far, Jimmy Corrigan, but you do know that
when you punch the stomach of Rowan Fitzpatrick,
they explode like in half.
Exactly where you punch, just like right at the midriff,
exactly where Meat Hook just went in.
They just, something like as if the building
was being dropped, but all the detonation spots
were like halfway through.
It just boom, and then the top half just kind of falls
a little bit, slump, slop on slop, human inside
on human inside.
And the top half falls, and then the knees fall,
just like when you shot people in the dick in GoldenEye.
Do I need to roll a grip for that?
Yeah.
Uh, that's a fail.
I need grip checks from the other two of you as well.
Jesus.
I pass.
One grip loss with a pass.
I'm going to death of a thousand cuts, lose my mind.
Again, 1d4 plus one.
I crit failed.
That's five again.
Awesome.
I also, five.
Jesus.
Absolutely meltdown.
So what Jimmy Corrigan does is-
I hit a breaking point again.
He grabs the syringe of ketamine,
and he's going to try to inject it into the nearest person.
Okay, let's roll and see who the nearest person is.
It is just three other people standing here now.
It is Vincenzi Bori, Shelly St. Blythe, and-
Brandy.
Oh, Brandy's still here?
What the fuck?
Oh my God.
I thought we were going to have to kill one of the dads
to save the child, but unfortunately I-
She runs off into the woods.
I athletics, I run after her.
As you tackle her into the ground
and you're doing what now?
Injecting that ketamine.
Yep.
You do so, and she like almost immediately
just like falls unconscious.
It's okay.
Where you're going is probably a better place.
We're not going to punch you.
We're not going to make you explode,
but we got to get our daughter back.
And well, you know, sorry.
And he walks back to the ear fungus and eats a little bit.
Wait.
Well, before he does that, he-
Too late.
Oh my God.
He said it.
He just fucking said it.
Well, wait a minute.
I mean, one of us has to eat some to get in there, right?
We can't-
No.
You think we can feed it to her?
If it goes in her mouth.
Have we seen anybody open a portal?
Oh, we did.
That's what this whole thing is.
That's what just happened.
Well, I'm insane.
I feel like once you say a thing,
the thing can't be unsaid.
He walks away from her.
He kind of eats her and then eats the whole thing himself.
I thought that's how it worked.
I mean, that is what Dr. Brock Hargrave did.
Exactly.
So if your goal is to open yourself up,
perhaps that would be the way of doing it.
Yeah.
He eats it and he says,
save our baby girl.
And he looks at you too.
That doesn't make sense, does it?
Should we just rerecord me feeding it to her?
That's why it's funny.
I think it makes sense
because you don't have all your wits about you.
Yeah, I think it absolutely makes sense
that you're walking back to them
as you put it in your mouth.
Vincenty also does not have his wits about him.
With that-
I give you the ketamine, I take the earwax.
And I need a power roll at a negative 40
from Vincenty Bory.
I've got a pretty good chance here.
A 20 on a five.
It's like a primal urge.
It's like a hunger deep within you.
You feel just like completely drawn without hesitation.
Vincenty gets in like the-
Let me be clear,
to crawl into the stomach of Jimmy Corrigan
is what you feel like doing.
Vincenty gets in position like you would
at the beginning of a track race.
And takes off sprinting
and is gonna try to just dive head first into the stomach.
Jimmy Corrigan, how are you responding to this?
I like make myself a bigger target
and I say, you go get our girl.
Holy shit.
Oh yeah, I need a con check from Jimmy Corrigan.
Like a really important one.
Pass.
That's good.
Vincenty takes off
and as his feet leave the ground
and his head is heading towards the stomach,
he just says, I'm not real anyway,
so it don't fucking matter.
I'm coming.
And through the torso of Jimmy Corrigan,
Vincenty Bory just disappears.
I'm pulling that out
and using it for all the previous ones.
You're welcome.
Jimmy Corrigan, you are completely gripless.
In Seattle.
Should I say Blythe?
We are at the Space Needle.
Go ahead and roll a grip for me.
Hey, I passed that one.
Okay, so you just lose one again.
It's all good here.
I'm just nodding enthusiastically.
I'm like, Shelley, we're gonna get our daughter back.
I need to know what the two of you
who have just left yourselves alone.
There is one dead body in a hole in the ground
that is like not covered up.
There is a exploded kid on the ground halved
and then there's an unconscious woman off to the side
down the path heading back to the parking lot
and the two of you are just looking at each other.
How does it feel?
I mean, a little jiggly, I guess.
I really thought stabbing her with ketamine
would do something else.
Oh, I could tell.
I thought maybe you got mixed up on who was who.
I got mixed up, I got mixed up.
I thought she was one of the dads.
I understand.
Luke and Joe, could you guys take off
your headphones real quick?
Yeah.
Hey, Thomas, Jimmy's never felt anything like that ever
and it was like the coolest, best feeling
that you've ever had.
Oh no.
I'm just saying.
Okay, yeah.
Should we bird him?
Yeah, they can be birded.
Love the bird.
Wait, unbird, I'm sorry.
D-bird.
D-bird, D-bird.
D-bird, D-bird, D-bird.
If I eat more, he will want to come into my belly.
Oh, you've lost enough grip now.
Yeah, you're pretty sure how this works now.
So basically when you eat the substance,
the person closest to you seemingly
wants to get in your belly.
Okay, okay, okay.
So yeah, bird, bird.
That's not the bird.
I'm doing it quickly and I have dice in my hands.
I wonder why he just went thumbs like that.
Shelley, how does it feel?
It feels fantastic to be a family.
And you notice he's starting to like nibble
a little bit more out of the plastic bag.
It's time that you joined us.
Joe, just looking at Zach like, help me.
I've never seen such a help me look ever.
I didn't know if my sanity loss makes me want to do this.
I think with the passing,
I'm going to let you keep your wits about you enough.
But I mean, obviously this is chipping away
your ability to sense reality.
Okay, I eat a little more.
No, I'm not hungry, sorry.
No, no, Shelley, you don't have to eat any.
But aren't you hungry for family?
I mean, I miss Meat Hook, of course.
And Chedi, I didn't know him terribly well,
but he seemed nice.
But no, I don't want to go inside of you to find them.
That's where our little basement troll is.
They haven't returned and I don't know if I will return.
I firmly placed my hands on his shoulders.
You want to get in there.
I don't want to get inside of you, Jimmy.
It's so cool in here, doctor.
My belly button like whistles.
But also you just hear that in your head.
She's calling for you, doc.
That's the real Bigfoot.
Basement creep, basement creep, is that you?
It's me.
They've got so many types of rocks in here.
Rocks.
There's a lot of rocks in here, doc.
Igneous, the, limestone.
Limestone.
I mean, it's your head telling you this,
so it's rattling off all the rocks that you love most.
Igneous, limestone.
The.
Stand back, cannon ball.
So, yeah.
Jimmy opens his arm wide again
and just like has a huge grin on his face.
And it's almost like he's reaching for like an embrace,
but he's just inviting you to jump in.
I get a running start and go in feet first.
Knees tucked to chest.
I don't have to roll for you.
You do have to roll a constitution.
Oh, I know that look.
That's the look of deciding whether or not he wants to lie.
It is.
It's just, I have a cool thing to do.
You better do it quick.
Would have failed, Gibby.
You, as Shelley St. Blythe dives feet first,
like he's going down a water slide
at fucking Splashylvania, two fanged plunge in there.
You look down at the ground
and see the split in half body of Rowan Fitzpatrick.
And you feel like,
hmm, what happened to Rowan
is gonna happen to you any second now.
You can feel it.
What do you do with your last thoughts?
Get inside your own stomach.
Shut up, Luke.
That's my whole deal.
I get inside my own stomach.
Knowing I'm a ticking time bomb,
I watched like the last long white hair
breezing by of Shelley get in me.
And I just try to shove my head in there after him.
As you get your head close, you feel like.
While munching on some fungus.
You shove the last little bit of it into your mouth,
shove your face and hands into your own stomach.
It just falls away.
And just so you feel this like warm wetness.
It's like, you smell saline in the air
and you hear this like weird noise
as your hands go through
and you feel the grip of friends hands,
family's hands on the other side, pulling you through.
You made it.
It's like in the labyrinth
when she goes down the tunnel.
Just as I'm ecstatic about those hands on mine,
I remember my wife and children.
We're your family now.
Yeah, my family's in me.
The four of you on the other side
of Jimmy Corrigan's unnatural stomach.
Plus Brandon.
Right?
Oh, hey.
And the coworker.
Co-workers nowhere to be seen,
but you're all-
Further on in the territory.
Looking at a sprawling town park
straight out of the 1950s idea of the future.
Perfectly manicured trees
like enormous emerald cake pops line,
a colorful synthetic walkway
that you've been pulled up onto
in this slightly bouncy, comfortable sidewalk
would take you all the way around
this gigantic green area around you
where on the far side,
maybe, I don't know, 124.3 meters away or so,
people in yellow and green uniforms are running around
and all the way across this park.
So monumental, they are clear from here.
There are two statues of men,
each about 26.3 meters tall,
made of green rock.
Yeah, dude.
They stand in front of a gorgeous building
seemingly made of glass and grass
and a woman in judge's robes
and a powdered wig wearing electric blue heels
looks at you and says,
or very quickly we need to get you inside and hidden.
Quick, everyone, before anyone sees.
And that is the end of Holy Cow Farms.
Thank you so much.
Holy, holy shit.
Okay.
Yeah.
First you tell Becca what happened.
Oh my, I knew it.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
I just want to go to this place.
That's a place that's in another part of our podcast.
This is the easiest way to say all that.
It's very nice here.
Yeah, it seems that way, huh?
It's growing.
It's Grover's Gorge, which is like,
Oh!
Which is like if Walmart had a city
that all its employees lived in.
Oh yeah, actually they do have one of those
and they've got some pretty good concerts.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
Becca, Scott, thank you so much for coming on
and joining us for this four episode run
here in season two.
Thank you so much.
But also this was so much fun.
The series.
Such a blast to play with you.
Aw.
Thomas, Joe, Luke.
Nailed it.
Thank you for having me.
Oh, we're in the mind palace now.
And also the MVP was Dylan.
Absolutely.
The straight ass dude.
Do it.
Shout out to him.
Zeitgeist is so cool.
Zeitgeist, for the win.
For the win?
For the win, dude.
Epic.
I love some cosmic horror that ends up
in everybody dying and little explained.
That's my way to roll play.
So thank you so much for letting me be a part.
Yeah.
This was actually a fate worse than death, I think.
Which is fun.
Sometimes when a belly opens up,
you just need to either dive right in or cannonball.
Yeah.
Cannonball.
That's the only mystic advice my dad gave me about dating.
Oh yeah.
I've never used it, but I've wondered what it meant.
When I was in sixth grade,
my dad told me that you have to make the woman come first.
That was inappropriate for me.
Yeah, that's true.
Really sage advice.
But he's a Christian, so we don't listen to him.
Good job, dad.
All right.
And, Becca, do you want to give the people
like a shout out for where they can find you
on the internet?
Look into the cameras, tell the people
what you got going on.
Besides the show notes, which there will be a link
to your website and your Twitter account.
Or anything else you want.
Or whatever you want.
Look at them show notes.
There's a bunch of backlog of me running
Call of Cthulhu games on my YouTube channel,
Good Time Society.
You can find me on the internet at the Becca Scott.
So go do it.
Do it.
Absolutely do it.
I'm going to do it right now.
Go learn how to play a game
because she does the coolest tutorials on board games.
That's how I've learned how to play a game.
Thank you.
I do do that.
Joe was so fucking excited when I said Becca Scott
was going to be on.
I'm a big fan.
I'm a very big fan.
Doo doo.
Thank you so much for coming.
Yeah, and doo doo to you listeners.
Doo doo all around.
Doo doo unto you.
Oh my God.
Yeah, that was fucking tight.
Well thanks, Francis.
Thank you so much.
That was awesome.
I lost audio at 70 minutes.
No shit.
Are you for real?
How long was it supposed to be?
Oh, well I have an hour 17.
So you lost the last seven.
I think that was just some bullshit.
Yeah, and also I have a recording of us.
Through that, yeah.
Through OBS.
We'll be fine.
So we'll be fine.
Oh, thank God.
That was scary.
Did you write down?
Yeah, I wrote down everything.
I need a second.
You've got to run the calculations to see.
836.
Which Bible verse is that?
Oh, you don't know?
I know.
We're not a Christian podcast.
Thou shalt climb in the belly of your brethren
and be with him internally inside his own guts.
That sounds right, yeah.
Yeah, and also if your brother dies, you marry his wife.
If it's some consolation
It's a lie
I was thinking the same thing
I am now mechanization
All my muscles work like swings
It's like a primal urge.
It's like a hunger deep within you.
It's like a paranoia.
Looking over my back.
It's like a whirlwind.
It's Linkin Park.
And it's all my fault.
Thanks for watching!