Hello, my ever-present fan base.
It's your time jumping, dimension bumping,
grease pumping baby wolf the dog.
And I'm here to slurp up all the information of the worlds
and regurgitate it back into all y'all's mouths
like the baby birds y'all are.
Chirp, chirp, my hungry little chickadees.
Mama Wolf is bringing that good slop fresh out of her gullet.
Oh yeah.
We're also live from 694.2 PTBP or something, I guess.
And now speaking of sustenance,
this week's Howlin' with Wolf is from at Bagel Boy,
who tweeted about the show and tagged at Pretending Pod,
which is the third quickest way to make wolf salivate.
Bagel Boy writes, howdy wolf.
Just wanted to send some good vibes your way
and to tell you to stay greasy.
I'm new to the big city
and although everything right now is new and unfamiliar,
I'm glad I got good old wolf to grace my hearing holes.
The city seems nice so far.
Aside from the fact that I've been mugged
four damn times this week,
I haven't seen a single damn police officer
since I got here.
Though I'll admit it does make me oddly feel
like I'm right back home in sleepy, quiet contention.
Anywho, keep up the good work over there
and I'll keep on tuning in over here.
Oh, and stay safe out here in the concrete jungle.
I wouldn't want to see my good friend wolf
on the evening news.
Thanks for writing into the show, boy of bagels.
I'm glad we got some listeners buzzing in
from old sleepy and quiet contention.
Never anything exciting or dimension altering
ever happened over there.
No sir, redo.
Nothing to see over there, that's for dang sure.
Ha, ha, ha.
If you want to write up something for your wolf to howl,
tag at pretending pod on Twitter or Instagram,
tag pretending to be people on Facebook,
or write up a five star review
on the podcast app of your choice.
Screenshot that stunning missive
and get it in front of old wolfy's eye holes
so I can say, hey, thanks.
Now raise your hands in the air
if you support this show on Patreon.
Wave them around, get weird with it.
Fuck everybody else because you, my delicious listener,
are keeping the proverbial lights metaphorically on
in this quote unquote studio.
In the ephemeral words of Dame Alyssa Arnett Elliott,
get your freak on.
In the words of Cal Colorado,
blah, blah, whatever, something about the news.
Last time, the field team for the City Action News
began in a familiar place, the CAN Conference Room.
But without Ty Frailand at the head of the table,
lead anchor Isabel Acaya took on the role
of handing out assignments and sent Cal Colorado and co
off on a wild goose chase to a mysterious drop pen
for exclusive coverage of a secret town
run by the Godel Company.
They were joined by Stevie, a production assistant
with a wall of dark wavy hair that covered all of her face
except a pierced bottom lip.
And the four members of City Action News drove and drove
further and further off the grid.
All the road signs told them to turn back,
but they carried on until the CAN van
approached a perspective engulfing wall
made of tree-lined vines and kudzu,
taking us now to the other side of this foresty facade,
this biennial barrier, the dam of detritus.
It's Altagirl with My Life is Great and It's All My Fault.
It's all my fault
Cause my life is great
And it's all mine
And it's all my fault
Were you at his house that said that?
I didn't say it was disgusting, but I was like
Well, you meant it
You are
I don't think it's disgusting.
I think it's thoroughly emasculating
Do you feel emasculating when I burp you?
To be burped like a baby
Well, so I don't think about being emasculating
because I don't think in terms like that, you know?
I don't feel like a father when I do it, if that helps
When I think of myself, I don't really think of myself
Yeah, you're more like a sexually dominant, like
Always
I don't really ever think of myself as a man
I'm like a boy that has to shave
I don't have a beard
Do you have to shave?
I thought you were saying, I don't have to
No, I don't have a beard, but I have to shave
Dude, literally, I shaved this morning
Yesterday at Ethan's house, Jake Herron was over there
and he's like
Shout out to Jake's Vegan Burgers
Are we recording?
I had the taco meat tonight
Oh, nice
Jake was on season one of the podcast
and on our Patreon
I hung out with Jake last night
Go listen to the, we were fighting the devil in Hawaii
or something
Yeah, a church group fighting the devil in Hawaii
He was like, dude, Luke, I've never seen you with facial hair
and I'm like, yeah, it's a mistake
I don't have facial hair
and this is something that I don't know that I've brought up
with you guys before, but I follow a Reddit
about what I have and they say, tell your friends
Have you ever noticed me picking at my face?
No
I have trichotillomania, which I pull my hair out
and it's like, I enjoy doing that
but it's like, you shouldn't do that
Specifically your face?
I should probably stop pulling hair out of your face, too
Wait, but the subreddit says that you should
tell all your friends
It's a callback from the last episode
It is, that's not make damn sure, is it?
No, I mean, it's by taking it
I know it's taking back Sunday, I just don't know
Anyway, some people it's like on their head
Some people it's like random parts of the body
So when I grow my facial hair out, it's only here and here
and it's because I literally just pick all the hair out of my cheeks
and I'm trying really hard to stop it
So if you see me doing that, tell me not to
So is it like a support group on Reddit kind of thing?
Yeah, it's like a join this so that you can think about doing it
so you stop doing it
Interesting
Should we get a spray bottle?
Yeah, just spray me when I do it
Literally, I can grow hair on my cheeks
Also, if you look at my middle fingernail
Did you just do it?
It's literally like
Luke, don't
It's like worn down because I pick like that
My thumb and middle fingernails have like indents
Is there a support group for grown adults who need to be burped like babies on Reddit?
See, that's a thing that I don't want to give up
And hey, here's the thing
And I'm not far enough, it's not a fetish yet
Luke, you let me know when it is
Yeah
But
Dude
I don't know, hopefully this isn't recorded
Or maybe it is
Maybe it is and you're out there and you have trichotillomania
It is recorded, is that okay?
That's fine because literally I would love to grow a beard
And the only thing stopping me from doing that is me picking the hairs out of my face
Just so you guys know
Spray me, baby
If we hit a certain Patreon goal, we're gonna get Luke a Hannibal Lecter mask
So he can't touch his face
I think it'd be more to just like glue oven mitts on my hands for a while
So I can't do it
Glue them
Glue them on me
Why not both?
Fuck day
Glue oven mitts to my face like a Hannibal Lecter
And then all your hair gets ripped out when we take it off
Solved
Look how long his beard was
And then I was gonna make like a ripping your pubes joke out but that's a real thing
Yeah, ouchie, ouchie
Ouchie, ouchie
So
We saw some cool shit at the end of the last episode
It was like fucking cool, dude
What do you remember? What is the vision in your mind of what you saw at the end of the last episode?
Crazy ravine where no ravine should be behind a crazy wall where no wall should be
With a train where no train should be leading over a gigantic fucking bridge where no bridge should be
Well said
During our break I was just like googling Blaine the Mono which is like the scary train from the Dark Tower series
Okay
I've got three opened up here, scroll through them, but that's what I was imagining
Oh, duh, these look like evil trains, dudes
Yeah, straight up evil trains, bro
Train one had kind of tentacles or something underneath it
Well
No tentacles on this one
I didn't think there were but it seems Cthulhu-y to have tentacles
Cthulhu-onian
But also
If you guys haven't listened to, I say listened to the Dark Tower series because I read the first book and the last book
And I listened to all the rest of them
Listen to the Dark Tower series, it's really good
If you like Delta Green, holy shit, bro
If you like Delta Green, don't fucking listen to the Dark Tower
Listen to Pretending to Be People
Season one
Scary, very scary
Also, his name is Blaine the Mono because Blaine the Train I guess is too stupid
It all seems pretty stupid
I don't know, you do a bunch of coke and write a whole series
Okay
Challenge accepted, yeah
No, like the little faces on the train are so dumb
Like the mean eyes
None of those are like
I'm Blaine the Mono, don't call me Blaine the Train
I'm evil
That's why I'm angry
Everybody keeps calling me Blaine the Train
Um, the train I guess isn't sentient though
No, it's pretty simple looking
Aw, damn
Oh, I thought you meant Blaine
Oh, Blaine is sentient for sure, bro
He's definitely sentient
I wanted to clarify, is this bridge that is extending outward from us across the ravine, first of all?
Yes
And you said 100 meters long, does that mean we can see the other side?
Okay, what's on the other side?
The same thing that's on your side
Which is?
A train station and a wall
And a wall
Fuck that
That's creepy
And so the fog is all settled in the ravine below us
You said a deep foggy ravine
Yep, the fog is settled in the ravine below you
Cool
I need everyone to roll grip, as this is a deeply unnatural sight
I pass a 20 out of 75
If you fail, you're just going to lose one grip
I was going to say, I pass enough that I don't even have to look up what mine is
Rolled a 3
I rolled an 87, which is a failure
Which is a failure
So you're going to lose one grip, and with that, as you guys are looking around this area, Cal is...
You don't know this about me, or maybe you do, but I happen to be an avid student of local geography
And this ravine should not be here
This ravine can't be here
Well, I mean, we're looking right at it, dude, it's right there
I know it's here, but it shouldn't be
Are you getting this? Are you getting shots of this?
Beck definitely is
We're 87 minutes away from my home, and there could be one, I don't know
This ravine would be a national park, if it was natural
Does it look natural, or is it smooth walled or something weird?
Go ahead and roll if you have any sort of science, or I'll take intelligence at a negative 20
Any of us, or him?
Any of you
Oh my god, at a negative 20, that makes my intelligence 50?
I got a 51
Oh, I can roll on intelligence?
Mine is 20, yeah
Oh, I pass with flying freaking colors, bro
At a negative 20, I'm also a 50, and I rolled a 50
Nice, we got a success there, and we got a success from Julius Summers
Julius Summers is the only one who really notices
And I only say that because Cal Colorado is dealing with
Yeah, loss of grip, and on top of the loss of grip, just the itchiest face, hands, and arms that he's felt since he was a boy
Not to touch my face
Oh, you fell face forward, sir
Critical fail
I didn't realize that Cal's money maker was
Oh, it's gonna be a time frame situation at this point
With the crit fail, I think all your clothes came off real quick, you rolled around in it, and then they all flew back on
Yeah
Yeah, no, you are working on a time crunch to your face not being camera ready
Stevie, do you have any concealer? Do you have any
Yeah, and she's right on it, and she's getting into her makeup bag and coming at your face
Stevie, you're practically a Marvin, you don't know what that means, but
Julius feels deeply insulted by that comment
Julius is far too busy staring at the deeply unnatural sides of this rock
You can't quite put your finger on it, but it's nothing that you've ever seen before, this is not a natural occurrence, I need you to roll grip
Haha
And yeah, I like what Joe said earlier, let's say it's really smooth
Yeah
Cool, I like that
I'm unaffected with a five
Amazing, so you know that this is not normal, it may not have ever happened before, but
No, not but, but so
It's a kick ass
Julius pulls his phone out, goes to TikTok, thinks it's the perfect time for the calzone
Cal, could you stand next
It's much better Mr. Colorado now, it's much better
Julius points his phone at Cal and looks at his phone to see like how good he looks on his screen
Sure
Does it look good
Yes
Is he made up
Yeah and honestly it's
Maybe you slide over to a filter
Oh for sure, yeah
Well one of the things that Julius did on the way here was, because he didn't have to drive, was make a can filter
Specifically made for Cal, Colorado
A calcan?
The calcan, the calcam for the calzone
The calcam for the calzone
And it perfectly matches his skin tone or something
No, it's just like any blemishes or anything are kind of like smoothed over a little bit
Okay so you need to get this poison oak faced, elderly, older statesman of anchors to dance like a monkey for your TikTok
While he's just lost grip
We are not dancing for this calzone
Look at where we are, this is insane dude
I'm saying this to the DM
Cal
Julius
Get next to the edge and we're gonna do a calzone
You want me to go on right now?
You want me to be on?
Well you don't have to be on, we can practice it, it's a TikTok
You can practice a TikTok?
We don't even have to record the first time
I've spent 30 years on air living on the razor jads of live TV
Have you ever thought about acting?
I'm mostly thinking about itching
Well they're from what I've heard one and the same
I'll make a note of that
Right now I'm acting very hard
Well then let's not make you act too hard
And he just starts recording just video that way he can upload it to TikTok later
I'm here in front of an unholy monstrosity
The god old corporation in their avarice has torn a trench into mother earth
Make it fun
It's very deep and broad
Like the dance that you're gonna do
Cal just looks at the camera and like bewilderment and confusion
Who could dance at a moment like this?
Not this reporter
Julius cuts it off right after like not this reporter
And he's like okay, perfect, I got this
And then he just starts editing the can talk together
Hey man, we have like TikTok quotas or whatever
But like maybe we wait to post that
My uncle told me to do TikToks
Yeah, for sure
I just don't know if like we like we're kind of in the middle of like figuring out what this is
Like what if it's like, you know a nuclear test site
We don't want people like rushing out here to see it
Understandable
He continues editing the TikTok
Cool man, I'm glad you heard me
Beck, anytime you want to talk to me, I'm here to listen
That means a lot dude, thanks
Yeah, and then he finishes editing the TikTok
And he doesn't post it, but he sends it to his uncle
Interesting
So looking at this simple train car in this simple train station
All seemingly made out of steel
All built for this one single car
You see that there are lockers adjacent on the exterior wall of the station
And above it the sign of course says, welcome to Grover's Gorge
Founded by Frank Godel in 1945 by necessity not choice
I know it was founded by Frank Godel, but what if it was founded by Grover from Sesame Street
Let's just all take a moment to imagine that
I actually saw that What If episode
Is What If a show?
Are you thinking of What Would You Do?
What If with John Quiñones
With John Quiñones
What?
What Would You Do with John Quiñones?
John Quiñones
Yeah, Quiñones
Quiñones
You've never seen What Would You Do?
The whole premise of the show is like
We get actors to do really shitty things in public
And then we see what the public does
What Would You Do?
What would you do if a guy beat up a little kid?
What would you do if he was at home
Sixteen seasons
February 26, 2008, the present
I've never even heard of this show
The thing that kills me, Thomas, is that you're not alone in that
There's a lot of people who haven't seen it
But for some reason
I've seen like every episode
Everybody on the show that ends up being on the show
They go, oh my god, it's John Quiñones
As if they all know him and he's a big celebrity
It was created by Chris Whipple
Which is a very fun name
That is a very fun name
Chris Whipple
Not a fun show, really, though
Zach, I don't want to harp on this ravine
But I just realized we didn't ask what was down left or right
Like, how far can we see? How far does this ravine go?
So you can actually even really see how deep the ravine is
Or how far left or right it is
Because it's so foggy
You can see to the other side
That a hundred meters across
But the fog is just filling up this ravine
And then the fog kind of
Takes over the land far down on the left and far down on the right
So you can't even see the end of these walls
Of massive plant life
If there were another bridge like the one we're looking at
Would you be able to see it?
If there was one
You would be able to see it
If it was within about a hundred meters of you on either side
Okay, and we don't see anything
Beck, could I borrow a mic clip?
Sure, of course, dude
Hey, Stevie, would you grab a mic clip out of there?
Yeah, of course, yeah
Here you go, sir
Julius grabs the mic clip
And he shows it to Beck
He's like, can you get audio from this?
Yeah, oh yeah, for sure
Hang on a second
He wires it up to the receiver
Could you do it unwired?
Do what unwired?
Bluetooth, perhaps?
What are you getting at, man?
I'm gonna throw it
Oh no, we can't afford to lose a whole mic, dude
This is your first serious error as a producer
The network will not be pleased to hear about how you wanted to use their equipment
And unfortunately, Beck and I are duty bound to report it
I will say Beck did
Beck did say we have so many of those
Yeah, it's for like, you know, miking up people
But like, we're not gonna like toss them over ravines
Sometimes you have to interview a group of school children
Or perhaps a church choir
Can I roll to see if this is Bluetooth or wired?
It's wired for sure
Wired for sound
So yeah, Julius throws the mic with the mic clip over the side
But then it just like six feet later stops
Cause it's wired in
What can you hear, Julius?
Not what I want to do
And Stevie's walking up and noticing your headphones
Beck and she's like, Mr. Wilder, those are some sweet cans
Dude, thanks!
And I knuckle, Stevie
Knuckle
Cal Colorado gets like a chill down his spine
As if he's heard that voice from someone else in a past life
Another faithful
That was smart, I am smart
Hey, Julius, like if you're trying to like get a sense of like the depth here
We could just do the old fashion way
And Beck finds a rock
Dosses it over the edge to listen for the sound
And you listen
As if you threw a rock off of a cliff
9.82 meters per second squared, right?
Uh huh
You're asking the right people
Down about somewhere like 836 feet
Like basically 80 stories
And then you hear just
Of a rock hitting water
It sounds like it's about 80 stories down
Uh, there's water down there
I don't even think we'd be able to hear that
No, but once I started talking
I was like, well, fuck
No, I heard it
Cause the mic
I know I heard it
The mic's hanging over the edge there
And I picked it up on my headphones
Good work, Julius
On this simple single train car
You see two steel doors
One toward the rear
One toward the front
And they both slide open
Without obstructing the large lettering
Laid out under the train car's windows
It says
My uncle didn't tell me
That this is what we would be looking at
But I think if we go in
I can impress my uncle
If I recall correctly
Your uncle didn't tell you anything
You haven't been in contact with him
Julius goes in
And acts like he doesn't hear this
Given that assignment by
Julius walks right into the train
The woman who took my job
And actively
Actively doesn't hear this
Looking out over the bridge
Is it also enveloped in fog
Or can we see, like, the center clearly
You can see the center of the bridge clearly
Is there anything distinguishing, like
This is a Thomas question, not a Cal question
Okay
This is a Zach answer
Does it look like a train is blinking out of existence
In the middle of the bridge or something
Like there's evidence of, like, cartoonish
Burn patterns or something
If Thomas is asking no
Cal's looking at the center of the bridge
It doesn't look like anything weird
Is gonna happen in the middle
I think if we get in this train
We'll just pass uneventfully
To the other station
Perhaps that's where this gate is
Julius walks into the train
And finds the snack cart
Stevie's, uh
Gathering up all the equipment
And dragging it up into the back
And the seating in this train car
Is similar to the types of train cars
That have a narrow aisle
Running down the middle of the car
With two seats on either side
Oh you mean
All trains
So with five rows
There's enough space here
For
Magic
20 passengers
Oh
Sitting
20 sitting passengers
Magical schooler
There are some cabinets
In which Julius finds
Some light refreshments
Energy drink
And pretzels
I like to think that energy drink
Is made by the Godel Corporation
Is just a plain, like, aluminum
Unpainted can with energy drink
Painted in the same green
That, like, the
That was on the wall outside
It's perfect
And yeah, you find some energy drinks
There
And there are large windows
On either side of this steel train car
Which kind of looks like a giant can of energy drink
Which does
And the lettering is green
So it matches
Is this the can tram?
This is the can tram
Fuck yeah
Cal steps on and says
Now it's the cal tram
And there's TV screens
Mounted in both the front and the rear
The modern flat screens
Flicker to life
As you all enter
And you see a blank
White sound stage
With a white stool
On the screens
Oh if your stool is white
You should probably get that checked out
Yeah, definitely
Like some like
Sun dried dog poop
Yeah, that's
That is not natural
You don't see much of that
You said stool
So we thought
Poop, white poop
A man walks into frame
Sits on the stool
Oh no
Stool, you said it again
And smiles
Joe, when he says stool
What do you think of?
No, I think of a seat with four legs
What are you guys?
Oh, I think a big poopy
Actually, stool
It's medical
I think of a very gross poopy
When we start calling it stool
There's a reason it's been collected
And it can't be good
A man walks into the frame
Sits on the stool
And smiles at the viewer
Well hello there
Cal says hello
I'm Fred Godel
And you see the Fred Godel
He's a soft looking man
In his later 60s
With a loose plumpness
And glasses
That consistently look like
They're about to fall off of his nose
With black pants and shoes
Fred's green shirt
Is the only pop of color in the shot
Welcome to Godel's Gate
To Grover's Gorge
I'm overjoyed that you're here to join me
On a tour of the future
Before we begin
Please leave all outside food and beverages
In the complimentary lockers
On the outside of this here
Simple steel single train car sized train station
Fred Godel points his finger into the air
And a purple light comes on
This one means there's still
Outside food or beverages in the car
He moves his hand a bit over
And a green light comes on
This one means you're good to go
So which light stays on?
Definitely the purple
With Stevie's huge bag of awesome snacks
Yeah
And Stevie kind of looks at the screen
With this like anger
As she goes down to the bag
And is like ugh
Guys I think I got to get rid of all these snacks
I'm sorry the cooler
But did you finish the coke in that energy drink
That I brought you?
Yeah but hang on a sec
And Beck is getting into her bag
And finding energy drinks
And is chugging
Like at least one if you guys want to get in on this
Julius does not
I've got a thought
Maybe leave one of those for last
And see if the light stays purple
Yeah of course Cal
Let me just get
Topped up here real quick
Hang on
Do you need to be burped?
While this is happening
Julius is going to wander up there
And see if he can't just like
Turn the light off or something
Yeah it's just kind of these like
Colored bulbs over the top
Of where the light is
And just the bulb on the outside
Is the coloration that's making it
So Julius's hand
Over the light doesn't
As Julius puts his hand
Over the purple light
His hand kind of turns
Purplish
Right like
I'm not saying that it's going to change
I'm saying like just if it's covered up
Like
There's nobody else on the train right?
They're not going to know
But the train knows Julius
Exactly
Julius
Continues to hold his hand over the light
Just to see
It's not doing anything
Still doesn't
I let Stevie go ahead and finish
Putting the bag outside the train car
Whatever she was doing
I've gotten my fill
And we are keeping one
Energy drink with us to see
Okay so
I got rid of all of the snacks and drinks
That we brought except for
And she flicks a finger
At the one in Beck's hand
And then we look to the light
And the light is still purple
We actually got rid of
All the drinks
And then he
And then he looks at the light
Are you trying to fool the light with a lie?
Julius looks at you and goes
No
As he nods his head up and down
I don't know what kind of detection system
They have for this outside food or drink
But I don't think it's based on your word
Have you ever been in an autonomous train
That knows whether you have a drink or not?
No but I've been on a roller coaster
And they just ask you there
But this light seems more insistent
Exactly
Now that you mentioned it Cal
How do they know though?
Like
And then Beck wants to see if there's a camera
Or anything in here that he can spot
Every single part of this wall is cameras and sensors
Yeah go ahead and roll search
Or you can roll computer science
I got a 48
Which is good for my computer science
So you know where to look
Which is behind this kind of like
Black sheen plastic
The top middle
The front of this train cabin
Above the TV
Sheen
Very ethical corporation
And you see if you walk real close up to it
You see that there's a
A red blinking light on it
Did anyone else succeed?
I did succeed at search
Bro
Yeah so the two of you noticed
That there are sensors of some sort
On the doors
And the entrances
On the front and back
Entrances of this train car
What do you see there Beck?
Yeah I guess like
Smile dudes
We're on candid camera
And I'm no tech wizard like you
But it appears to be
There are some sensors on this door
Food sensors
Cal
Dude
Good work
You're right man
Those are sensors
You're getting the hang of this tech stuff my man
Cal is like
Openly blushing a little bit behind the makeup
It might just be the flush of like a
Poison oaked face
But he really like
Nothing gets his old heart
Glatter than a young person saying
He did something right with technology
Julius takes his hands off the light
And he walks up to Beck
And Beck I think
If you want that
You better drink it
Dude waste not want not
Wow he drank that really fast
Beck is wired
That was the sound of Joe actually drinking an energy drink
Did Beck have his camera recording already?
Oh yeah
It hasn't stopped
After his third energy drink in three minutes
He's a little wired and just like
Pointed his camera right at the camera
I see you
The watcher sees the watchman man
So
You can play that game
Train go
Well so we've now downed the can
And I guess I'll throw the can out the door
As soon as the can flies out the door
I say train go
Zach asks you all a question
In the same way that you guys ask me these kinds of questions
Did you try to sneak any additional food or bev?
We're not going to pull out like
Oh by the way I still
Actually I had peanuts in your pocket and your light's fucking dumb
Idiot
You didn't
I didn't say Simon said didn't have any food
So Simon says the light turns green
The door shuts
Hey guys I do have like six hamburgers in my pocket
Oh yeah I've got a bunch of wet lasagna
Just leaking down from my hand pockets
Dude I have to pee and poop
As the simple steel train car begins making its way down the track
It does so at a quick clip
The flat screens show an animation that follows along with a serious voiceover
In 1945
The world defeated men with evil in their hearts
Later that year
Evil itself was extinguished
Out of the windows
You see a palm sweat inducing drop
As the velocity of this train
Has whipped up enough of this fog
That it's moving up out of the ravine
And towards the clouds
And you can see deep 836 feet down
Almost 80 stories which would make this
The 21st tallest bridge in the world
The only thing that kept Frank Godel fighting those years
Was the thought of coming back home
And marrying his sweetheart
But Frank, freshly back from stamping out evil overseas
Returned only to find evil at his doorstep
Threatening his future
Looking back at the cliffside you just stood at
You can all see just how smooth and strange this wall face is
Like nothing you've ever seen before
The fight between Frank Godel and this evil
Lasted for 13 hours and 56 minutes
And the final blow to defeat evil caused this massive crevice
Frank fought the fucking ball-rog?
On the left hand side of the train
The fog in this absurdly deep canyon clears out even more
And you see a church building
Still mostly intact
But completely upside down
Awkwardly stabilized by jutting rocks from both sides
The steeple reaches out for the water below
But the house of God is well stuck
Frank Godel stood tall and victorious after this contest
You can see on your left hand side
The church did not
In its place, the Godel Company cared for Grover's Gorge
And kept its residents fed, clothed, housed and safe
The screen quickly cuts back to Fred Godel
Sitting in his green shirt on his white stool
And the Godel Company has continued that practice
Into these modern times
So open your heart, open your eyes
And open your mind
Let me show you a future without hunger, without pain
Welcome to Grover's Gorge
Holy shit dude, this is dope as fuck
Oh damn
And as the simple steel train car stops, you're on the other side
Strangely, it feels identical
That's not so strange, you look exactly the same
That's right, if everyone could roll heavy machinery, architecture, or search
Whichever you'd like
I passed search with a 14
I also passed search with a 19
Whatever it is, I passed it with a teen something
Uh, what were you rolling on?
Search
Okay, so you all rolled search, so
It was heavy machinery and what was the other one?
Heavy machinery, architecture, or search
Gotcha, yep
Which I only have one of those
So with the success there, you kind of match up
Where the door was on the original side
Like how far away it was from the station
And you can pretty quickly make your way over and find the door through the plant matter
On this side as well
And there's so much plant matter growing on the door
However, it seems to wrap itself in a way in which you can open this door
Without needing to like, cut through any of this shit
Can I, now that you mentioned the overgrowth, can I retroactively real quick mention
Looking around in the train to see its level of decrepitness
Like, was it dusty even, or was it feeling brand new in there?
How did, I mean like the whole setup really, the station, the lockers
Clean, sterile, spartan
But like, maintained?
Simply due to its cleanliness, you would assume that it is wiped down a decent amount
Yeah, okay
Used much, or?
Used much much?
Okay, let me rephrase
Without a heavy machinery roll, you're gonna be hard pressed to figure that one out
Okay, I don't have any in that, so I won't do it
But we rolled search successfully, you
Yeah, you rolled to find the door
Is there like a path that's been followed through this
Or does it seem like we might be one of the few that have used this station?
There is not a well-trod path here
I tricked him, I tricked him
I didn't have any heavy machinery, but I got him to tell me with
You used logic in a good way, I like that, good job Luke
Can I get a pointy look?
Do you have luck already?
Nah, I have luck already
Okay, nevermind
Joe, you can't have any
Damn it
God damn, I drank all those energy drinks there dude
With all that being said, I would like to open the Spongebob door
And emerge from the other side
Yeah, you guys pack up all your shit and kind of
Who lives in a church in the bottom of the ravine?
Frankie Godall
Battled evil for 13 hours did he
Were there lockers on the other side also?
Cause the lockers at the first side was to kind of leave our shit in
Yeah, that's a great fucking question
There are lockers on this side, it is exactly identical
Aw, lame
Aw, dip
We should have looked in those lockers back there and seen if they were something
I mean Stevie did, she put the food in the lockers right?
Oh yeah
Stevie, did you see anything in those lockers?
Oh, I didn't open up a bunch of them
I just kind of opened up one and she holds up a key
There was already keys in them so I just locked it and I guess this is our key
Why don't you like check if it works on one of these over here?
And then she walks over and she's holding up a key that is number 5
And she's like, oh these are alphabetical on this side it looks like
Oh cool
Try F
Wait, E
Try L7
Try E
She walks up and there are keys in all of the doors on this side
Drats
Except for
There's keys in all of the doors?
There's keys in all of the lockers so they're all ready to be used except for one
The A locker is locked
Stevie, will you try that one real quick?
Yeah I guess
And she tries to put her key into it and it just kind of jams
She's like, ah it doesn't fit
Interesting
This is so fucking cool
I want to open B
You open B, it is empty
C, D, E
Empty, empty, empty
Z
There's only 20
I put my pocket lasagna in B
You almost had me for a second
What happens as I open up the hatch
Oh okay I thought you were going to say the 20th letter of the alphabet
No that's obviously 6
You guys head on over and Stevie's kind of pack mewling all of your gear over to where this door is
And she's like, alright I've got the key here in my pocket so don't let me forget it
Stevie, don't forget the key in your pocket
Oh sorry guys, Luke just shits pants
That was Julius opening up the hatch
It opens in the exact same way, this time it opens in toward you
And on the other side of this enormous and lush impediment
Is a vast opening with plenty to unpack
You're looking at a sprawling town park straight out of the 1950's idea of the future
Perfectly manicured trees like enormous emerald cake pops
Lying a colorful synthetic walkway
This slightly bouncy comfortable sidewalk would take you all the way around this gigantic green area ahead of you
It's like a big square and the path is a big square going around it
And on the far side of this green space
Maybe about 255 meters away or so
So really far, these people are really tiny, you see tiny people in the distance
People wearing like yellow and green uniforms
And from all the way across this park, so monumental that they're clear from here
There are two statues of men
Each about 26.3 meters tall
Made of green rock
And they stand tall in front of a gorgeous building
Seemingly made of glass and grass
Or ass
There might be ass making it, nobody rides the Godel train for free
So it's a big square, you're on one side, the statues are on the other
There's a massive square park green space in the middle
The trees outline the green space
And on the side that you're on, behind you, there's just this enormous wall of plant life
You can go left or right
To follow the path
And you would assume that based on what you can see in the park that it would lead you in a big square around
Is there what's in the middle? Is it just green space? Literally just green space?
Yep, it's a lot of places where people are playing, people are hanging out, picnicking, throwing frisbees
Are they all wearing green or yellow uniforms?
They're all wearing some sort of green or yellow flair on their clothing
You said the pathway was synthetic, colorful, and bouncy?
Yeah, I did say that
Fuck yeah
Cal puts a foot out on it and then gives a few steps out and starts springing a little bit on it
Yeah, it looks like even Cal could go for a jog and it wouldn't hurt his knees
I haven't felt like this in years
Everyone roll grip
You are in a completely, seemingly unnatural to you location
I failed, 86, Cal starts to think, I haven't felt like this in years
As the other two pass, you're both just looking at, is that okay?
He stops bouncing on the pathway
Stevie, is anything okay?
This is weird, huh?
This is weird, huh? Beck, you're filming, right?
Beck is not only filming, but he's zooming in to try and see if there's anything on the closest uniform
If there's any kind of logos or names or anything
Yeah, so no logos, everyone seems to be wearing a name tag
Does it look like anybody's noticed us?
As you're now looking at the people who are walking, people are walking on this pathway
And they're all kind of side-eyeing you as they're passing, but no one has approached
You see that everyone is wearing nice clothes, they're like very well made
Everyone who is walking on the pathway is wearing grey-scale joggers and athleisure
But then with a flare of green or a flare of yellow
And everyone who's sitting nicely casually, having a picnic, is dressed
Everyone's sitting nicely
That's the call and response I used when I taught children in Korea
I was gonna say they're all in Oakland Acor
Green and yellow
Oh yeah, so it's either green or yellow
No one is wearing both that you've seen so far, but everyone is wearing something
The people who are sitting at like picnics, the men are wearing like nice black shorts
With a green or a yellow polo
The women are wearing like a green or a yellow sundress
The people who are playing a sport of any kind are
Everyone is wearing clothes that are specifically built for what they're doing
And everyone has like nice, what you would call like upper shelf athleisure
Uh, Cal?
Julius
You're a pro, right?
Julius, I am the pro
Beck, from what I know, you're a pro?
Yeah dude
Let's find out where we are
We're in Grover's Gorge, the secret Godel company town
Hidden behind a giant mysterious ravine
That apparently Frank Godel created in a fight with evil itself
Julius has already stopped listening and he's going to find somebody to interview
But Cal is nodding vehemently while rolling on Cal
Did you call me Ba-Cal?
Ma-Cal? What did I say?
You said Ma-Cal
Rolling on Ba-Beck, Ba-Beck, Ba-Beck
The way you were saying that sounded so perfectly angry that Beck instinctively was filming you as you said it
We're standing here
I've always just had this voice
Julius just walks up to the first person he sees and says
Uh, would you like to be on TV?
Yeah, you look up across this absolutely gorgeous, like stunning park
So just like clean and glimmering in the sunshine
And there's a woman who's mid-twenties, blonde ponytail bobbing up and down as she's jogging
Wearing her like lovely, there are no apples in sight
She's not bobbing for apples
But her ponytail is bobbing up and down as she's jogging
For apples?
Towards you
Are you glad?
Yeah, it would have been sad if he didn't do it again
And she kind of like slows her jog as she's kind of approaching you with a quizzical smile on her face
Confused, but also curious
Cal like kind of turns to face her and reaches out his hand and like puts on a big broad smile and says
Cal Colorado, City Action News
May we have a moment of your time?
Oh yes, of course, yeah, absolutely
And she puts out her hand and says
Jennifer, it's extremely nice to meet you, welcome
Welcome to Grover's Gorge, I see that you're not from here
No Jennifer, we're not, we've come here to learn more about your fine town
Well welcome, welcome all, again I'm Jennifer and she puts out her hand
Speck and Julius
Hi Beck, hi Julius, and what's your name?
And Stevie puts out their hand and
Stevie
Yeah, it's nice to meet you Stevie
I mean, is this your first time I would assume at Grover's Gorge?
Yeah, never made it out here before
Welcome, welcome, welcome, oh the Godel Company has treated us so well, woo
Go GEs
That's actually what brought us out here
Could we ask you a few questions about the Godel Company and the gorge?
Yeah, absolutely, absolutely, I mean I'm in the middle of a jog, do you mind if I run in place?
Yeah, I mean I don't, unfortunately that doesn't play on the camera
And she's running in place like, and she's doing high knees now and she's like high knees, high knees, high knees
Beck is getting into the camera bag to get out of lapel mic and he's trying to attach it to her and it's kind of difficult because she's jumping up and down in place
Uh oh, hey, could you maybe just hang on for just a sec, let me get this attached
She slows her roll a little bit, stares you straight into the eyes and is like, I'm doing calf raises
Yeah, you are, those are good calf raises, can I have you like say and spell your name for me real quick?
Yeah, it's Jennifer, J-E-N-N-I-F-E-R, Jennifer
And what's that last name?
Um, Lang
She gets kind of a quizzical look on her face and she's like, can we actually not do a last name, it's just Jennifer
Yeah, that's fine, it's just how we're going to credit you on the news, I just wanted to make sure that we get it accurate
Jennifer from Grover's Gorge, uh, Godel Company, uh, G-E, woo
Jennifer from Grover's Gorge, Godel Corporation, G-E
The Godel Company, gotta get it right, T-C-G, woo, T-G-C, woo
Gotta get it right, The Godel Company, Jennifer, how long have you worked for The Godel Company?
Well, worked I guess, um, you know, a few years now, but
And how long have you lived in Grover's Gorge?
Oh, I've lived here since I was born, born and raised, Grover's Gorge, woo, go G-E's, woo, hungry for points
Did you always hope to work for The Godel Company?
Sure, yeah, I guess hope is a weird word, I knew I was going to work for The Godel Company
What do you mean?
Well, I was born here and raised here and everyone works for The Godel Company here in Grover's Gorge
No one grows up to leave and become a doctor or an astronaut?
Oh, I guess, yeah, if people want to leave they can, but I knew I was going to stay, I like it here
Has anyone to your knowledge ever left?
Yeah
Many people?
Mmm, like, not a ton, maybe like two or three a year maybe?
I see, and Jennifer, you've enthusiastically shouted G-E a couple of times
Woo, go G-E's!
Yes, go G-E's
Thanks for asking about that
What is G-E?
Oh, that means I'm a great employee, woo, go G-E's, hungry for points, woo
I'm a G-E of TGC, I'm a G-E TGC
Yes, yes, Jennifer, hungry for points, what are these points?
Forget about it, cuh, I gotta have my points
Like I said, we hungry, trying to get these points
Cal is like desperately looking to Beck and Julius and he's like, is that a TikTok thing?
I mean, not that I know of, it could be new
Looks at Julius
Julius shakes his head, he doesn't know
Jennifer, is that a TikTok thing?
Oh, I don't think so
Asked and answered
Ask if there's any B-E's, bad employees
Jennifer, perhaps a difficult subject
Mmm
You are a great employee
Yeah, I am, ha
Are there any bad employees?
Oh, I see what you did there, no
None of the people who left were bad employees
Oh, no, they just left
Everyone performs adequately at their job, no one is ever fired or let go or disciplined in any way
Well, no, I don't see why they would be, no, no, no, everyone works like
We have a really good job here and a really good life here, so I don't see why anyone would not want to work well
Does that make sense?
That makes sense to Cal
And now the corner of each of your eyes, all of your eyes, each and every one of them, you all see
How did you know about all my eyes?
I read your character sheet
Goals, get rid of all these eyes
Get rid of all these fucking eyes
I didn't fill out my eye, uh
Oh, dude, if you don't put at least two, you're fucked
Too late now, baby
Out of the corner of your eyes, you
That's a compelling story, the blind television producer who can never see his own segments
But still longs to struggle in the industry, or succeed in the industry
Longs to struggle in the industry
Does struggle in the industry, longs to succeed
My taste is so good, though, that I can
Oh, yeah, you're actual
My taste is with my tongue
I thought you meant you had like Daredevil vision, but for reality television
No, I can taste anything
Your taste is great, and so is your vision, which means that you can see out of the corner of your eye
All of them?
A jackalope
Wait, is a jackalope the rabbit with antlers?
It's the mythical creature with antlers, yeah
It's a rabbit with antlers
A rabbit with antlers
And it's got a yellow ribbon tied around its head
Around its head?
Yeah, like
Around its antlers, or?
Yeah
Cal's jaw drops
Julius immediately starts filming it on his phone
Beck whips around to it and says out loud
You guys got a jackalope?
Jennifer, what is that?
Are we recording?
The people love this
They love what?
They love the roid talk
You just said what now?
I have my first Aldi hemorrhoid
No, it doesn't hurt, it's fine
It's just a firm little guy
I need 30 seconds of silence
Fun little guy
Firm
He's just a, hey, you should get to know him
He's just a fun little guy
He's just a silly little guy
He's just popping out to say hello
He's a lot like you, Zach
Bald little head poking out of your asshole
And it's all my fault
Thanks for watching!