Greetings.
Introduction.
Transition.
694.2 PTBP.
The good numbers.
The radio station is... somewhere.
Wolf the dog is... here.
There is nothing to fear.
Maybe.
We have fans.
They shouted us from the void.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Bundad Elliot,
who tweeted about the show and tagged at Pretending Pod.
Which you should also do.
Bundad Elliot writes,
Wolf, I need your help.
You travel through myriad realms and unknown plains
and maybe you know how I might escape.
The bunnies that were once my pets
now hold me within a liminal space.
Doors folding in upon themselves.
The eldritch forms of these furry fiends
have been revealed to me.
They keep me fed and clothed,
but I am captive nonetheless.
All because I wouldn't give them banana chips.
I have slipped this message through a crack in the wall.
I hope you find it.
P.S. Please send banana chips.
Oh damn, you met those guys?
Tell those fun buns ol' Wolfie says hello.
Enjoy your stay.
I'm sure they won't be keeping you there for too long.
Humans live what, a couple hundred years or so?
Ah, you'll be fine.
I will not be sending you banana chips
because I do not believe in them.
I will not conform and I shall not obey.
If you wanna write up something for your wolf
tag at pretending pod on Instagram fuck Mark Zuckerberg
at pretending pod on Twitter fuck Jack Dorsey
fuck Elon Musk or pretending to be people on Facebook.
Another fuck Mark Zuckerberg.
And if you wanna be the very best,
like no one ever was,
go ahead and write up a five star review
on the podcast app of your choice
and let us know.
We love that shit.
But if you're keeping your love of 694.2 PTBP
a dirty little secret from your online friends and family,
you don't wanna post about how much you love this show.
You don't wanna wear our six shirts, hats, and fanny packs.
You don't wanna dry off with a towel from Splashylvania.
Well, that's all fine.
You can confidentially support us
at patreon.com slash pretending pod
and for even $5 per month,
you'll get access to 33 bonus episodes.
And what's that?
I'm hearing there is more on the way.
What more can I say?
The links are in the show notes.
All right, I got through what I needed to.
And now it's time for me to read the news.
Last time Beck Wilder was impaled by a DIY Jackalope
with a yellow ribbon tying the mundane antlers
to the standard rabbit to create the mythological beast.
While watching Stevie witness Fox God'll twitch
and convulse at the side of headphones,
Cal realized that she was very likely Faith Godell,
the oldest child of Fred Godell
disguised as the production assistant.
The medical staff at Grover's Gorge
showed up in a bullpen car
to pick up the Gord camera operator.
And on the way to the lab,
the group saw another makeshift Jackalope.
This one with a purple ribbon, Fox Godell,
who Stevie says went by Greg before,
quickly grabbed the ribbon, popped it in his pocket
and promptly fucked off back to his Godell innovation zone
or jizz, if you'd like, and I do.
In the lab, the medical staff says
they can treat Beck's wound here in the same room
as the interview with the mayor.
The mayor, an old beat up damp box turtle
called Sandro.
Taking us now to this quirky and riveting news story.
It's Altagirl with My Life is Great and It's All My Fault.
My life is great and it's all my fault
Cause my life is great and it's all mine
Cause my life is great and it's all my fault
On the tree subreddit right now it was like,
I joined thinking this was actually about trees.
Where's the real tree sub?
And I knew that the one about trees
is called marijuana enthusiasts,
but I didn't, there's some other ones that I didn't know.
World politics is anime titties
and anime titties is world politics.
And John Cena is about potato salad
and potato salad is about John Cena.
Oh my God, nice.
Oh, also I knew this one, but Super Bowl
is actually about superb owls.
So I didn't know this one.
There's an Amish subreddit.
It has 175,000 members and no posts.
I fell on a jackalope.
Oh, good call dude.
Holy shit.
Whoa, look out.
Fell on a jackalope.
Damn, I remember watching those videos for the first time
when I was like probably in the sixth grade.
I have no idea what you're referencing.
Guy on a buffalo.
Whoa, look out.
I still have no idea what you're referencing.
I haven't seen Guy on a Buffalo.
I guess I haven't seen Guy on a Buffalo.
Is it one of those like two girls, one cups kind of videos?
Cause I haven't seen any of those.
The guy fucks a buffalo.
Yeah.
Like donkey man.
Donkey man.
We've already done this.
Mr. Hands.
Donkey man.
Let's not do this.
Okay.
Thanks.
We'll do it afterwards though, for sure.
No, we'll forget.
So yeah, we're talking to a turtle.
We were, yeah.
So what are we doing?
So we're talking to a turtle?
So we're talking to the turtle.
Can news get a big old scoop with the mayor of this town?
Turns out, turtle.
Sandro.
Sandro the turtle.
I put a microphone on the turtle's shell and...
Cal, pat your back and he's like,
way to step up for a back buddy.
Mr. Mayor, could you spell your first and last name?
The makeup artist is kind of like laughing
and she looks up and is like, you got him?
And then she kind of walks away and heads out the door.
Says you got him to us?
To Julius, who's standing there.
Cal leans into Stevie again.
So does turtle, can it talk?
Exhales real big, looks you dead in the eyes.
Kinda.
What do you mean kinda?
Beck did not expect the word kinda.
It's a whole thing, okay.
Like two taps for yes, one for no.
And one of the medical people kinda,
we're gonna be right back with the equipment that we need
to take care of this.
Should only take a couple minutes.
And they head out to the front door.
Word, no hurry.
And as they head out the door,
you see a 58 year old man standing there.
He's got bright blue eyes and a face lined by the sun,
which is topped by a flat top of salt and pepper hair.
He's Uncle Strong.
Like he could bench 250 pounds,
but he gets winded.
Oh, that's not his name.
I thought.
He's Uncle Strong.
I was like, okay, is he a turtle's uncle?
He just looks like he could bench 250 pounds,
but he also looks like he gets winded
going up a flight of stairs.
This is Chuck Bidwell.
He says, as he introduces himself.
Hey, how's it going there?
It's Chuck Bidwell.
It's nice to meet each and every one of you.
I'm the mayor.
Well, I'm not the mayor.
I'm kind of the mayor.
Shout out to Anthony from Bristol, UK for Chuck Bidwell.
Anthony is one of our $10 or up subscribers on Patreon.
Thanks, Anthony.
Or up.
Yeah, Chuck Bidwell.
It's a pleasure to meet each and every one of you.
Oh, it looks like you've had a bit of a rough and tumble
goal of it so far, Mr. Camerman, sir.
Fell on a jackalope.
As he looks at you, guess what happens?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, Zach, Zach.
I think I can guess.
He's wearing a green dry fit polo
tucked in kind of over his belly.
Hog?
Yes.
And he kind of zones out for a moment
and you see into Chuck Bidwell's deepest, saddest soul
of a face and then with just a half a second,
he's right back to normal.
Hey, how's it going?
Chuck Bidwell, yeah.
What's your name?
Julius Summers.
Julius, Mr. Summers.
Nice to meet you.
And you, sir?
Hey, Beck, it's Beck Wilder.
Beck Wilder, what happened to you, son?
I fell on a jackalope.
I fell on a jackalope and I don't think I survived.
Oh, oh, he pats you on the shoulder
and he's like, he looks at the other two.
Did he kill it?
No, no, I'm sure it's fine.
And what is your name, sir?
Chuck Bidwell here.
Cal Colorado, City Action News.
Pleased to meet you, Mr. Bidwell.
Oh, right, you're the Cal Colorado
who has come to do all the wonderful interviews
and show off Grover's Gorge for the beautiful town
that it is, that's right, okay.
Well, we've got you set up over here, of course.
You know, with the mayor, Sandro, if you met Sandro,
I'm not the mayor, I happened to lose.
I lost the election there.
Oh, so Sandro was able to participate in an election?
Well, yeah, but he does get elected every time.
How long has he been the mayor?
He's been the mayor since almost the beginning, yeah,
since the founding of Grover's Gorge.
And he'll always be the mayor?
Well, seemingly, seemingly for sure.
I mean, I lost by 836 votes.
What is the voting age here?
Voting age is 18, like everyone else.
We're in America, aren't we?
Well, that's an interesting question.
You were the mayor, perhaps?
Well, I'm not the mayor, I wish I was the mayor.
I mean, the only two votes I even got
were from me and my wife, Barbara,
kind of honestly, if I'm being completely honest,
she pushed me into running.
I'm being totally straight with you.
Yes, you're not the mayor in title,
and yet you have all the responsibilities of the mayor.
Is that correct?
Yeah, speaking of those responsibilities,
them responsibilities is why I was so late.
I'm so sorry that I didn't greet you at the gate.
That is my deepest and searest apologies.
I'm so sorry.
Isn't it funny that a turtle is running for mayor?
Oh, I like this kid, you don't have him on camera yet.
Oh, you writing the jokes for this old man over here?
That is very funny, I'm going to say that.
It's all yours, Cal.
The turtle is a turtle.
Right.
At this point, you've walked away from the turtle.
No, I think we're standing right by it.
I've got my eye on it, it's not really going anywhere.
Okay, we're all kind of bunched up
in the same area then right up the front.
The medical staff comes in and starts treating Beck
while you guys are having this conversation.
Hey there, whoa, precious cargo now.
They have some sort of machinery
that you haven't seen in a hospital before,
and they begin attaching it to Beck's backside
and upper thigh.
I instinctively say, Beck, get a shot of that.
But then I realized.
But Beck is trying to,
whatever weird positions they put him in,
he's holding the camera,
trying to get footage of this new machine.
You still have the camera?
Yeah.
When he does that, Julius, yeah, grabs the camera,
trying to still keep the shot.
You feel some resistance.
Everybody roll alertness for me real quick.
I'm going to burn my dice, if that's cool with you.
I got a 27, I pass.
And you're at a negative 20, Cal.
Yeah, doesn't matter, 73 fail.
Got an 87 fail.
Julius, as you've walked away,
you actually notice that similarly to the way
that the glass kind of rose from the grass below
on the first floor, letting you through the entrance
into this building, the glass on this room, the window,
opens in a similar fashion.
Chuck sees that you notice and you look down
and see that he's got a little clicker in his hand.
Oh, I thought it'd be nice that way
there's no glass behind the shot.
We get a beautiful, perfect view
of the city park right behind.
Oh, like a remote.
I thought you meant like he's clicking
to see how many times I noticed things.
I'm like, what the fuck, man?
I was like, I'm taking that away from him.
You're like, what's the count?
I see.
Chuck, that's, thank you, incredible.
I wouldn't have even thought to ask.
Yeah.
Can you do it to, I mean, you don't need to,
but can you do that to all the windows in this building?
Yeah, isn't that amazing?
It's an absolutely incredible laboratory that we have here.
It's beautiful.
And that controls all the doors as well.
Yeah, I mean, the door is the window,
the window is the door, am I right?
You'll see here, and he points behind him
that there aren't really any doors inside here.
There's just kind of open doorways.
Julius is going to bookmark that information
and definitely gonna try to steal that at some point.
How's the machine, what's it doing to me now?
They've got a machine that kind of wraps around.
It's almost like a heating pad, but on the inside of it,
there is some sort of technology
that you haven't seen before.
It kind of looks like a light almost,
but they can fold this piece of machinery around you.
It's easily foldable around the back of your leg.
And when it's on, you just kind of feel this sort of heat,
a nice vibration, you get hard.
You guys gotta try this.
Beckworth, you're at work.
Do you remember those old school machine things
that would do this for weight loss?
Oh yeah, just kind of like pulsate your muscles.
It was a band around.
No, it was like a band that just went like,
okay, it's wrapped around you.
Like just putting his hand at the side
and then waving them wildly.
I know, in my mind, this makes sense.
Anyway.
I'm kind of talking to a medic person near me.
I've never seen this before.
Is this like some like new medical issue thing?
You tell me and they pull it off and you look behind you
and you basically don't have wounds anymore.
Beck is making wide,
like he's looking at where the wounds were
and then looking at Cal and then looking at Julius
and then looking down at the leg that is now healed.
Yeah, and you feel like there's some slight cuts, right?
Where the holes were not even sutured back together,
but where they came back together,
they're not completely healed.
One of them goes, oh, it didn't actually,
didn't work all the way, but that's okay.
It should heal up naturally from here
and you should be able to walk
and they kind of hold your hand and lift you up out
and you do, you feel much better
as you gain back two hit points.
You're only one away from full health
and you can walk on this leg pretty easily now.
Doctors, is that gaudal technology?
So with everyone paying attention
to the gaudal technology here.
Yeah, the turtle's dead or something, right?
Yeah, for sure.
They help Beck up out of the bed.
Oh no.
Well, it's okay, they can just put him in the thing.
Go ahead and roll alertness at a negative 40.
The turtle's gonna fall out the window.
Yeah, I've failed miserably.
I mean, I have 40 alertness, so I'd-
Oh yeah, ouchy, ouchy.
Cal is still looking at his in astonishment
at the healed wounds.
The camera looks behind this group
staring at this incredible technology
as this turtle is swaying back and forth on its stool.
I just wanna say right now,
we did not put that turtle on that fucking stool.
This is a gaudal company mistake.
Teeter, totter, teeter, whoop, teeter totter turtle die.
Chuck Bidwell looks up and goes, oh my God.
And you see the turtle going over the side
along with the stool, boom, off the side of this building.
The open window door thing.
Oh, fuck.
None of this is on us.
From the quick glimpse we got,
did it look like the turtle was doing that on purpose?
Because you weren't able to get a quick glimpse,
you're completely unable to roll.
Human, animal, turtle-ant?
Turd-ant.
Yeah, we just hear the cries of the onlookers.
Literally, suddenly you hear a squoosh.
From your second tier in the lab.
And then you just hear this, oh my God.
Oh no, holy shit, oh my God.
Sandro, no, Sandro.
Sandro, where's Sandro?
Our town is leaderless.
Why do animals keep dying around me?
Everyone roll.
Beck, you were much farther away from this turtle.
I'm not even joking, I'm not using these dice anymore.
That's an 88.
Again.
Oh my God, dude.
Have you rolled an 88 or did?
Yeah, I rolled an 88 earlier.
I don't think I've rolled under a 70 something all night.
Wow, that would be great
if we were playing some different game.
I got a 21.
Beck, you know what, it's a critical fail,
so you're gonna lose four grip, the full D4.
Oof-da.
What are you at and what's your breaking point?
I'm at 68 with a breaking point of 60.
Luckily, grip was what Beck was good at, so.
Nice.
He's taking a lot of hits though.
Yeah.
This is not a normal day for him.
You've said that a couple times now, I think.
This is not a normal day.
I don't know if it's a human roller
just looking at their faces,
but Howard's like, I assume Chuck has his own reasons
for whatever his reaction is,
but just a normal medical staff,
seeing the mayor throw themselves off the thing.
Why are you entertaining this?
They placed a turtle on a stool
in front of an open fucking window.
But I mean, are they like in tears
like their great leader has died
or are they just like, oh shit.
No, they're mostly super, super confused
and they are at a loss for what to do now.
I need you all to roll grip.
Failed.
Pass.
This might be why you said to do this,
but Julius for sure was still had that clicker in mind
and was like, oh fuck, he did this.
Interesting.
Joe.
97 baby with brand new dice, sir.
Joe's rolling bad tonight.
Thomas, go ahead and remove your headphones real quick.
I need you both to roll a D8 and add one.
An eight plus one is nine.
Holy shit, dude.
That's a four, so a five.
So you're gonna lose five.
Holy shit.
Beck wild there.
Julius Summers, you lose nine grip.
And that puts me past my breaking point.
As you both see a wet energy erupt from the spot
where the turtle just teeter tottered to its doom
and this wet energy flings itself
into the body of Chuck Bidwell,
throwing him back through the wall
on the far side of this room.
And it is a glass wall and it shatters.
Holy shit.
Holy shit, Zach.
Now, if you don't mind,
if I could talk to you each one at a time, Luke first.
This wet energy that you see just for a glimpse,
you just catch enough of it to get some semblance
of like what it looks like, what it moves like,
how it reacts to things around it.
Like very short split second as this thing flies past you.
So I'm gonna let you ask three yes or no questions
to kind of try to decipher what this thing is like.
Okay, everything has a shape,
but did it have like a, not like human shape,
but like what, there's a word I'm looking for here.
Humanoid?
Humanoid, sure.
Yes, it has a humanoid shape.
Did it make a sound?
Yes.
Question two, part A.
Like a buzzing sound or like what?
It was weird.
It's like you could hear a man's voice,
but it was not.
But like not actual words or anything?
Er-yem-hoth-floo-hah-maw-hah-maw.
But it's just like whispering through,
almost like it's this enormous noise
that's billowing from out of this thing,
but almost distant with inside of it.
Gotcha.
Whoa.
Okay, third question.
Maybe you only get two.
What did it taste like?
We got away from yes, no questions,
and that's fine, because this is more fun.
And as it kind of went by you,
you get this like just saltiness in your nose
and on your tongue, like as it whips by you.
Okay.
Very scary.
Hey, thanks.
I rubbed my ear so much,
I think I gave myself dizziness.
I was kind of sick.
I'm sorry.
Let's make you sicker.
This wet energy, you kind of get a glimpse of it
as it just flies past you.
To the body of Chuck Bidwell, throwing him back.
So I'm going to let you ask three questions.
And I think the first two have to be yes or no questions.
And then the last one doesn't have to be a yes or no question
based on what I did with Luke,
in order to get an idea of like what it looks like,
what it seems like, what it's doing, like how it moves,
like anything you want to ask
about what you might be able to perceive.
Okay.
My first question is, you said wet.
Did it splash against Chuck Bidwell
or did it get absorbed by Chuck Bidwell?
Yes to the second one.
Okay. That's what I hoped.
Is there a reason that I saw it?
No, wait.
Yes or no questions. Sorry.
Is there a reason?
Is a yes or no?
Doesn't help me though.
I did elaborate when Luke asked his second
yes or no question, so we can do this.
Well, I just wanted to clarify,
was it just because I happened to be looking
in the right direction?
Or did it seem, I don't know how to ask this.
Yeah, no, it's a good question.
You think that like,
no matter what was going through your head,
because you were looking in the right direction,
you fucking saw this thing.
Because I was looking in the right direction,
I saw this thing. Okay.
For my third question then, you've said wet energy.
How fast was it?
Fucking wildly fast.
Like lightning strike fast
or like somebody's shooting a super soaker out of the air.
Super soaker. Okay.
Good question.
Tommy, Tommy come play.
We're bringing Thomas back with the bird here.
Oh wow, what the fuck?
Thomas, that reaction comes from seeing all of a sudden,
Chuck Bidwell has exploded through the far side wall
on the opposite side from the open wall.
He slams backward through glass, exploding everywhere,
10 meters from where he just stood a second ago
when you saw him.
You lose one grip as you have no idea how the fuck
that just happened.
No, it's pretty obviously that the ghost of the turtle
that Charles Bidwell tried to assassinate
or successfully assassinated,
came back and like super scienced his ass through the window
into like a last act of spiritual vengeance.
You said explodes through the glass,
but his body didn't explode, did it?
No, his body did not explode.
It's the glass around him that exploded.
The glass around him explodes, yeah.
And you hear him just like, oh, fucking shit.
Oh my God.
You hear the blabered breathing of Chuck Bidwell.
Oh, oh my God.
And then you hear nothing coming from the room
that is now part of your room.
Partition gone, glass wall down,
shattered into a million little pieces.
The footage from Beck's camera maybe had seen the,
it's shown like an empty stool tipped over
and nothingness just, you know, there, there.
And then you heard a big crash off camera
and Beck was so shocked that he is now pointed
to the ground with the camera.
Yeah, that's perfect.
And then after the thing had settled,
yeah, so it goes from like your wound healed
to an empty stool across the room
to just like chaos having already erupted.
Yeah, exactly.
Okay, very cool.
Luke.
Yeah.
Let's talk.
How, what are we doing with breaking points this season?
What do you guys want to do?
Do we want to come up with like a phobia or mania together?
Do we want to do it just one-on-one
or do we want to roll on the table like we did last time?
I would do any of the above.
I don't think we should do it together
just cause it's fun to have that as a secret or not,
you know, rolling is fun,
but I think it makes more sense to have something related
to what happened to make you break.
Here's a pitch that's half your idea
and half the opposite of your idea.
Joe and I come up with your mania related to,
related to your current situation.
That's interesting.
I don't hate it.
That's kind of fun.
And you know, vice versa all the way around.
Yeah, I like that.
Okay.
All right, cool.
I'm in.
Okay, so let's talk about it.
Well, he's never going to see a turtle
without shit in his pants.
I'll tell you that.
I was going to say, I'll listen, but I'll just not talk.
Hang on though, the bad thing about this is that
Thomas and his character don't know
what it actually was that made him lose his career.
It doesn't really work.
Yeah, okay.
That's fair.
I have no fucking clue.
Okay, Joe and Thomas,
take off your headphones real quick, please.
Do you have any ideas right off the top of your head?
So initially I was like, well, it's boring,
but like afraid of heights.
But the thing that fucked me up
wasn't the turtle falling out the window.
It was the fucking wet ghost energy thing.
Yeah, it was the wet energy.
So...
I would say let's go water.
Just hydrophobia?
Yeah, let's go.
Oh fuck, okay.
But let's say it's a specific kind where you can...
Like running water or like a stream or a faucet or a shower.
But still water is fine.
I'm not going to die.
And obviously we're not going to tell them
until it comes up.
Exactly.
Rock and roll.
Hell yeah, dude.
Welcome back, boys.
Hey.
I'm afraid of having a huge penis.
And so I start screaming.
Yeah, man.
And I look back and I remember that he has a huge penis
and it scares the shit out of me.
And I haven't seen cows yet, but I imagine it's big too.
We cannot get you around those statues.
Yeah, so Julius kind of, he comes to and...
I mean, you're in Fight, Flight or Freezer at this point.
Freeze.
Well, I'm going to go freeze.
Freeze will be four, five, six.
Fight, flight.
Okay, flight is one, fight is two or three.
Go ahead and roll a D six.
That's a three.
So you're going to fight.
Fight, yeah.
Fight.
Well, no, yeah, fight.
Fight is going to be your response here.
So I'm going to just...
Fucking attack a doctor.
Yep.
Go ahead and roll.
Are you using your hands or are you going to grab something
and utilize a weapon of some sort?
There's broken glass everywhere.
It's too far away from you to grab.
Yeah, it's 10 meters across the room.
What's close to me?
There's a whole like medical bay.
It just doesn't slide across grass floors
like it might on something.
Oh yeah.
Exactly.
There's a whole medical cart like right in front of you.
Yeah, I'm going to grab the blood pressure monitor.
Just start swinging.
Okay, awesome.
Go ahead and roll a melee weapons.
He's got a 90 in that.
I don't mind.
I got a 59 on a 50.
Oh shit, it's a higher skill than I would have guessed.
I'm athletic.
You fling your arms wildly at this medical professional
who just helped your friend and they're backing up
and they are really, really confused.
And they see the crazed look in your eye.
Okay, we're leaving.
And they grabbed the medical cart
and kind of wheel it backwards away from you.
Julius is screaming,
you fucking magicked my friend back and then the turtle,
you got the turtle energy.
The two look at each other and they look back at you
and then they look at each other and then they dip.
Probably the best solution.
Beck is looking at Julius and hearing him saying that
and he's nodding vigorously to whoever is in the room still.
It is literally just the three of you
and the body of Chuck in the other room at this point.
So Cal this whole time has been like watching everything.
He was furiously taking notes while
Julius was fighting with the doctors.
And as soon as he senses that like the audio is right,
he motions to Beck to roll and he says,
tonight, you're a little yeeted.
Turtle mayor of Godel Gulag assassinated
and the chief suspect,
his political rival is an unknown condition.
Tune in to Can Action News for more.
Stevie is standing there with eyes,
absolutely as wide as eyes can be.
Yeah, I didn't think this would happen.
Did you get that?
And then Beck is pulling down the camera
and is looking at the viewfinder
and realizes he didn't really get much
and his face kind of slacks.
Fuck.
There's no proof.
Oh shit.
How's Julius feeling at this point?
I would say absolutely enraged
and about to like punch Beck.
You like wanna break glass.
Julius stomps over to Chuck's body and is yelling,
Sandro, Sandro.
Cal kind of like cautiously walks up behind you
and he puts out an arm on your shoulder
and he just says, Julius.
Julius whips around and his like teeth gritted
and like fucking spit coming out of his mouth
and fucking hit.
Cal puts both hands on your shoulders
and he says, you're Julius Summers, City Action News
and we're here to do a job.
Beck has the camera up and is catching this.
The turtle's in him.
The turtle?
I don't know.
Sent who?
The turtle's in him.
Oh, is in who?
You look down and you see the body of Chuck Bidwell
just absolutely covered in like cuts and blood
and is covered in sweat, just like drenched clothes
and not lifeless, he's breathing.
You can tell like his dry fit green polo
is kind of bobbing slowly up and down.
Is that medical wrap still lying on the ground?
Like, no, but sure.
We're gonna take this everywhere
and heal all our wounds all the time.
Yeah, no, the medical staff took that with them.
The only thing that you guys still have
is the blood pressure monitor.
Which I slap on him to see if he's got any.
No.
Yeah, you can tell that he's breathing.
Is he like bleeding really, really bad
or just like kind of minor cuts and stuff?
It's not good.
There's a pool of blood beneath him and you see-
Nobody's ever almost died
from falling through a glass window, have they?
You can't, yeah, you can't like lose blood, right?
Yeah, no, probably not.
You definitely can't have an 18 inch long piece of glass
stuck in your upper thigh, butt area
and then lose a third of your blood
and have two blood transfusions on the operating table and-
Yeah, not never have your penis work right again.
You know, just like-
It works, it just doesn't work right.
I was describing my shotgun blast to you the other day,
right?
Yeah.
Oh, wait, yeah.
Yeah, you said-
Is that from that?
No.
No cilia in your pee hole.
That's right, there's no cilia in my pee hole.
No cilia in your pee hole,
which we all are helpful helpers.
I burnt it all out, vaping through my dick.
Oh, that sounds rad.
How is that the response?
I don't know.
Well, how did we get to this?
Oh yeah, he's cut up and you almost died.
Ding.
And you all actually see coming up
the synthetic bouncy walkway up to the second floor,
you see through the glass wall
on the east side of the room you're currently in,
this pencil-like woman with the spiky hair
you know as Barbara Bidwell, the wife of Chuck Bidwell,
is absolutely losing her mind
as she's running into this room going,
oh my God, oh my God, no, no, Chuck, Chuck,
what's this, what happened?
What happened here, what did you do?
Barbara, try to stay sharp.
No, I will not, I refuse to stay sharp.
Well done.
Your husband killed the turtle.
Wait, what?
Well-
The mayor's dead.
Yes.
And your husband might be too soon.
And for a brief moment,
I think your husband was the mayor, officially.
She's down on the ground now.
That's nice, that's if that's any consolation.
Hands and knees in glass shards.
Now her hands are bleeding, her knees are bleeding
and she's, you know, just, it's okay.
It's okay, Chucky, it'll be okay.
And she's kind of like slapping his face
and it's like, wake up, wake up, wake up.
Medical, medical!
Barbara, Barbara,
do you have one of those communicator devices?
They're on their way.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
I don't know that they are on their way
because they were like on their not way a minute ago.
Yes, many of them were already here
and then they fled in terror.
You might want to try to call them again.
It's like they didn't want to help.
They didn't want to help?
No, that doesn't make any sense.
Okay, and she pulls out one of the same-
Full disclosure, Julius beat some of them away
with a monitor.
As she's pulling out her radio device,
she looks at you and she's like,
well, that's probably why they left.
Medical, medical, yeah.
We need a medical up to the second floor of the lab.
Yeah, right by the entrance.
Yes, boys, come immediately.
I mean, I know this is a crisis moment for her,
but she's got a very sultry voice.
As soon as Cal says my name
and describes what I did to the doctors,
I kind of like come do more.
And I'm like, that's fucking, that's ridiculous.
So he kind of like sets the blood pressure thing down
and he looks at Beck and does the rolling signal
and then like tries without asking permission
to mic up Barbara.
We constantly do this.
We're constantly looking back to see if Beck is rolling,
even though it's completely unnecessary.
It's always, he is always.
It's just Joe nodding.
He is, he is.
What are you doing?
No, I'm not being interviewed right now.
Medical, medical.
She swats your hand away
and the medical staff tentatively, oh.
Like kind of dip toe in.
Inches towards you
and they're keeping their distance away from Julius.
Julius backs away and puts his hands up.
And they are just confusedly looking across at him
while moving to do their job,
which is to get Chuck Bidwell up onto this bulletin carriage.
Wow.
Bulletin carriage?
He means bull pin cart.
That was incredible.
Oh my God.
Okay, do you not know what bullpen means
or what bulletin means?
Because only one is Squamous.
Let's get him up on this bulletin carriage.
Let's get him on the bulletin carriage.
Holy shit, I didn't know that's what it looked like.
It's a big hat.
It's a big helmet.
It's a baseball wearing a hat.
Yeah.
They all look a little different, but the best ones.
Wow, that rips.
They were really popular in like the late 70s and 80s.
And now I'm gonna Google bulletin carriage.
Yeah, that's what I thought you were looking up.
No, that'll be the dolly image we posted.
I'll do it right now.
You guys still like that meme, right?
Yeah.
Of course you do.
We're gonna do it enough that it's our meme.
Beck is kind of now saying like pass the camera
toward the belabored breathing body of Chuck.
Dude, you're gonna be fine.
Like I had holes in my legs and now I don't, dude.
You're gonna be okay.
You see a little lung come out.
Chuck, you're gonna be fine.
Or is it Sandro?
What are you doing?
He's not awake.
What are you?
And they're moving him into this cart
and they begin to kind of cart him out of this room.
The medical staff don't want to be around you three at all.
Specifically Julius.
Makes sense.
So they're trying to get him out.
And of course Barbara is just at the side
of her husband, Chuck.
As the group walks out.
So are we now being left in this room by ourselves?
Yep.
Interesting.
I want to look around for interesting things.
I would like to perhaps roll the search.
Yeah, so this is kind of the first time
you guys have looked around here.
Go ahead and roll that search.
You were previously in a conference room
that overlooked this area.
So there's a big table off to the side
where you guys kind of weren't.
Hey, I finally passed a roll.
Oh nice.
It's a 38 on a 40.
I got a 34 and a 60.
I got a 42 on a 70.
Okay, so success is all around.
Success is all around.
Wait, did you say 32?
42.
Oh, I thought you said 32
and then we all would have had 30s
and that would have been full out.
That's crazy.
So the room that Chuck busted into was an office.
It was an empty office.
No one was working in there today,
but it just has kind of a spartan desk
and anything cool on that desk.
Like a key card or secret villain plan.
Oh yeah, there's a secret villain plan for sure.
As you've seen so far,
that you might not need a key card in this whole place
as doors don't seem to be too much of an issue.
Walls might need a clicker.
Yeah, which I see and grab.
Yeah, sure.
How about that?
You grab a clicker,
which will be able to open up any doors or walls
that you come across while you were here in Grover's Gorge.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Excellent.
Congratulations.
Along with that.
I'm the mayor now.
You all hear murmuring
and it's coming from out front of the lab
kind of by the statues
and it's almost like you can hear a crowd gathering.
Is it like where the turtle is?
It would be exactly where the turtle was.
Maybe we should get out there amongst the mob
instead of being directly opposite the mob.
If we're inside it filming, getting interviews and stuff,
they're less likely to turn on us for killing their mayor.
Very true.
Also, we don't tell them.
Dude, but like, they're gonna pin it on me.
I'm already an animal killer here.
No, no, no, Beck, Beck.
There's no proof of it anymore.
He looks at his leg.
Yeah, I mean, people saw it.
If you guys don't think they're gonna turn on me,
I'll go with you, of course.
Now, Beck, I know this might seem harsh and even unpleasant,
but if they start to turn on you,
all you have to do is show them your headphones.
Good, good point, dude.
They all seem really freaked out by my headphones.
That should buy us some time.
The trauma of getting godled seems to pause the psyche.
Yeah, yeah, man, I like it.
I mean, I don't like it.
It's awful and it sounds like these people
are maybe being subjected to inhumane things,
but I like it for our purposes now.
Beck looks at Stevie at this point.
Yeah.
I mean, it seems like we could have been more prepared
to enter this scenario.
Well, I didn't want you guys to blow my cover,
so I didn't want to really give too much away,
if that makes sense.
I guess now that that's done, it doesn't matter anymore,
but I would say we're kind of all in the same
fucked situation at this point.
Stevie, I understand your reasoning,
though if you had told us your identity,
it would have allowed us to prepare
a more comprehensive infiltration.
You make a really good point,
and then next time that I do this, I'll let you know.
That's all I ask.
Okay.
When we infiltrate the secret company town
on your mom's side of the family.
Perhaps give us a couple of weeks to prepare.
She laughs and then you see genuine laughter and joy
come across her face for the first time.
She's been really nervous this whole time.
What do you think the chances of us going out there
and being apprehended and sent to, I saw the judge,
I assumed, god-old jail for killing an animal
and maybe the mayor?
Hang on, real fast, just so we're all on the same page.
We had nothing to do with the turtle,
and we're not even lying.
Yes, true.
I mean, it was quite old, and it needed a lot of makeup.
None of us were anywhere near it, right?
No.
No. No.
Can I human that?
Yeah, sure.
84.
Yeah, seems.
Let's get a shot of the crowd from above
before we join, at least.
Yeah, that kind of creeps to the edge.
He doesn't want to pull focus up to himself up there,
so he's maybe holding the camera out a little bit,
using the viewfinder at an angle.
Oh yeah, this has to be incognito and stealthy.
Otherwise, it's just the three of us standing over
at the fucking balcony where they're pointing down.
Yeah.
Can you guys do that for the shot, though?
That one is sobbing.
Film her.
Yeah, I'm gonna need the videographer roll here.
74 on an 80.
Ooh.
Very nice.
You were able to slyly put this in a position
where you know that in the ceiling above,
there's a pattern to where if most people
are looking up toward you, the camera kind of blends in
with what would be behind it.
Smart man.
Nice.
The ceiling is just a tesseract of a camera.
Yeah, it sounds like a pretty cool ceiling.
No, literally, there's just thousands of cameras
filming your every move while you're in Donald Gorge.
Hey, let me tell you something right now.
There's definitely not.
Also, to prove our innocence.
If you can fucking kill a balrog
and make a ravine in a magic town,
you probably aren't scared of shit.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Why would I have a security camera?
I killed a balrog.
I can't remember, were you saying the stuff
about blending into the crowd and character?
An excellent idea.
Yeah, I'll film interviews and we'll just look like
we were doing what we were doing,
which is just doing interviews for City Action News.
That's what we do.
Tell them the truth.
That's what we do and that's what we did
and that's all that we were doing.
Yeah.
All right.
That's all we saw and that's all we saw.
Can crew on three.
And he puts his hand up.
One, two, three, can crew.
And then we reservoir dogs like out of the building
all on a line, all very confidently like,
I got a tripod over her shoulder.
Cal just walks up right to the first crying person.
Cal Colorado here on a sad day.
Sir, where were you when you heard the mayor had died?
The crowd is all staring at you as you come out.
You walk past the dried up corpse of Sandra the turtle,
put a microphone in the first person's face
and the crowd immediately parts and standing there,
you see a rail thin man with a balding,
mostly already balded head.
Is this another pencil person?
He's wearing a tattered three piece double breasted suit.
Turtle, turtle.
But his skin that you can see is bruised and scratched
and seems to cover his entire body.
But the suit covers most of that.
And he is rabid, almost foaming at the mouth.
And he drags a long thin cane against the ground
as he approaches you.
Holy shit.
Well now then boys,
I do believe that you are under arrest
for the murder of our mayor,
Sandra the turtle.
I believe in fact, no such thing will happen.
We had no part in your mayor's death.
He was placed carelessly.
Roll dodge or fight back.
Just Cal who's talking right to him
cause he's walking right up to Cal as he drags that cane.
Well, Cal rolls a 92
and probably gets smacked in the face with it.
In the middle of you talking, you're just slapped.
Not even for damage.
It literally does no hit points of damage to you.
It is to shut you up and put you in your place.
And he says, now then.
Cal doesn't like that because he was telling the truth.
Beck just saw Cal get hit with a cane
and his reaction is not to stand out.
His friend just got hit.
Whoa, hey, bro.
You can't just go around hitting people with canes.
Immediately the tip of his cane is in your face.
A guy comes running up.
He can, he can, he can.
He did, didn't you see it?
When he sits back, it's like when Beck saw Cal get hit.
Excuse me, but this man is an employee of City Action News.
We were invited here to cover your community.
He's going to punch you in the nose.
If you want to try to dodge.
I mean, I'm going to try to like, yeah, I want to actually,
I guess if he's throwing punches, we're going to fight.
I pass with a 14.
Well, then I beat you with a 32.
Oh, absolutely you do.
So he goes to throw a punch and?
Cal catches it and then knocks it aside.
Sir, are you not interested in hearing the truth?
While he's talking,
Julius is going to try to pin a microphone on his.
He's distracted.
He was trying to fight Cal.
You know, this is one of those let it happen moments.
Cool.
You're just going up and he's literally, he loves it.
He looks down and he's like,
yes, these words need to be heard, of course.
You will know your place, good sir.
Now I'm of course, Cal, Colorado city action news.
First things first for the viewers
who we are streaming live to at this moment.
And he wants to like persuade or fluff that guy.
Could you please state your name clearly?
So go ahead and roll.
He's going to roll a human against your persuade.
He succeeds with a critical success.
Oh shit.
I also succeed.
I thought you were going to say
with a higher critical success,
I quit with a 33 and he looks at the camera
and he smirks and he looks back at you.
Oh yes, of course.
My name is the landlord Vernon Covington.
And when he says the landlord,
you can feel the chill run down the spine
of all in attendance of this crowd.
Sucks the air right out of this beautiful sunny day.
How did you say he was dressed?
In a tattered three piece double-breasted suit
that mostly covers the bruises and scratches
that are all over his body.
Beck wants to twiddle his headphones just to try,
like as though trying to tempt a dog with a treat.
And as you do so,
you see that nothing about his suit adds up.
It's not nice, which everyone's clothes here are nice.
And it's also all over the place color wise.
I mean, it probably looks like it's out of the forties,
right?
Or fifties.
Eh, it's just like old shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not like...
I mean, style wise.
Oh, style wise, yeah.
It's just kind of like a big boxy cut.
It might even be like eighties or some shit.
I love an eighties cut.
David Byrne.
Do I see the body of the turtle laying anywhere?
Oh yeah, they left it out.
I think Luke was on the same page as me.
I thought this was the personification of the turtle.
Yeah, for sure.
So at least it's not the body thereof
and his name isn't Sandro.
So I don't know if this is the case or not.
I just thought Luke was expressing his mania
about seeing turtle bodies fly into other people.
Is that the shit you fucking saw?
You gonna talk about it in character
or you gonna talk about it out of character?
I'm asking my friend, Luke.
Will you please let us have a conversation, Zach?
No, Vernon Covington is making it very difficult
for you all to have a conversation
as he is doing his best to keep you quiet and in your place.
Yeah, this guy sucks.
Yeah.
Cal pulls out a gun and shoots him.
By God, if I'm going to be found guilty of murder,
I better damn well be guilty.
What authority do you have to place us under arrest?
He looks back and in the back of the crowd,
you see the judge wearing the powdered wig
and the judge's robes.
And he looks back and he says,
oh, I do believe that the authority is here with us now
in order to make a decision.
And then he's going to start prodding you
like a farmer poking cattle
to kind of get you guys to stand all together in one spot.
Cal stands right where he is and he says,
you're insinuating that the judge over there,
that's your authority, but what is their authority?
None of you are agents of the state
or the federal government.
You are vigilantes.
You have no right to put us on trial
for a crime we did not commit.
And I feel, you know, we did not commit this.
The judge walks up to the front
as you've been making your plea
and Vernon Covington looks down at you,
smiles really big and starts laughing.
Oh my.
Where are your courts?
Where are your police officers?
Where is your law now?
You perhaps misunderstand me.
I do not dispute that you could do anything
to us you might want, but you do not do it
with the grace of the law that you spit on
and they will come for you.
Maybe not today, maybe not tomorrow,
but the name Cal Colorado means something in this town
and he will not be sacrificed for some fucking turtle.
Vernon Covington has been smiling the entire time.
He looks at Beck Wilder and Julius Summers
and he says, any squawking from the other two?
Looks over at Stevie.
And you down there?
Anything from you?
When he looks at Julius, he pokes him with his cane
and Julius wants to try to grab it
and snap it over his huge fucking thighs.
Awesome.
He's gotta get a bonus for the size of his thighs.
I'm gonna use my luck and that's a nine.
Wait, was that a contested roll?
I'm gonna tell you to not use your luck.
Yeah. Okay, yeah.
I'm gonna be nice and tell you,
no, I think that just seems super fair.
I rolled a 77.
Oh, so, fail I hope?
Nope.
That is a critical cane success.
Okay, I got a 90.
For Vernon Covington.
What is it? Is it a nine?
Yeah, that's a nine.
What the fuck?
How many hit points do you have right now?
10.
What?
Why does a cane-
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Like six shots to the face all at the exact same time.
Blood starts spurting everywhere
and you hit the ground unconscious immediately.
What the fuck?
Roll constitution to see if you can actually
stay conscious at this point in time.
As Vernon Covington stands over your body.
Cal screams, Julius, no!
But then also looks back to see if Beck is filming.
He is.
Yeah, Julius, I pass my con check.
So Julius is on the ground, face bloodied,
and also looking blood.
And also looking back to make sure he's filming.
He's like on the ground, reaching out,
and making the like little roll motion.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
Fuck, dude.
What the fuck?
I'm almost dead.
I don't like this guy.
Vernon Covington stands over the body of Julius Summers
and looks out to the crowd and says,
are there any witnesses?
The two medical workers in the crowd
kind of raise their hand and one of them speaks up
and says, uh, yeah, that one?
And points at Julius.
That one chased us and tried to hurt us.
Vernon Covington puts his hands in the air.
Do you not see what kind of men these men are, judge?
Men are, judge.
So Cal is looking over at Stevie.
Do you really think she'll protect you?
And there's a glimmer of hope in Stevie's eyes.
But as you're staring into those hope-filled eyes,
you hear from behind.
These men deserve the proper punishment.
They should be stoned to death.
Fuck.
I'll say that one more time.
They should be stoned to death.
Hell yeah.
As soon as I said fuck, I was like, wait, no.
It's all my fault.
The sun's reflection off the ocean water amplifies
the heat and steam rises, crawling up the wooden boards
of a small ship.
And as the flag unfurls from the top of the highest mast,
the fog dissipates and reveals text that reads,
North Atlantic Ocean, Northeast of the Greater Antilles,
20th of August, 1694.
And then the credits start to come up on the screen
for like, you know, before the movie actually starts,
but the names of everyone are coming up.
And it says, Luke Gensman,
Joe Terry,
Thomas Cox,
Zach Reeves,
and Beth May.
Teeter totter turtle die.