Due to a very special guest, we may have us some first-time listeners.
And those first-time listeners might be worried that this is the ninth episode of the second
season.
But I assure you, first-time listener, you are in the right place.
You do not need any prior knowledge to listen to this episode.
This is the first of a four-episode prequel story.
It was actually recorded before anything else for season two, and season two is not
a continuation of season one.
So no need to worry about those 115 episodes for now.
Just sit back, relax, and enjoy how nervous Zach is, while Beth May from Dungeons & Daddies
gets on our audio show.
Let's go to the intro.
Welcome, listeners, new and old, bashful and bold.
All are welcome in Mother Wolf's warm and damp embrace.
For I am Wolf the Dog, and I am cherishing you all live from 694.2 PTBP, the only radio
station that exists here in August 20th, 1694, the Golden Age of Piracy.
You know we got it locked down here in the greater Antilles.
Sometimes we get fan mail, and sometimes I read it.
And by sometimes, I mean, like, every episode.
It's time for a new Howlin' with Wolf, baby.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Eula in Bochum, Germany, who tagged that pretending
pod in an Instagram story, an Uber guile thing to do.
Eula writes, please give this message to Klara and Robin, who hate things like this.
Without you, the world turns black and white, because your eyes take the color with them
when you leave.
Happy birthday.
Look at me keeping a secret, and give a kiss to Luisa, who is responsible for all three
of us listening to this show.
I hope I'm making tea for you right now.
As we say in Germany, brüder muss los.
Thank you, Eula.
This writing you wrote makes me feel happy, for the people in your life.
It's great.
But, um, can't help but notice you didn't really say anything about me, Wolf, the dog,
in this wonderful letter, but I'm definitely okay with the fact that I wasn't mentioned
a single time during this entire letter.
It doesn't bother me one bit.
I definitely am not going to cry into my pillow tonight when thinking about this wonderful
fan mail where my name is not uttered in a singular instance.
If you want to write up something for your mother, Wolf the Hal, tag at PretendingPod
on Twitter or Instagram, tag PretendingToBePeople on Facebook, or write up a five-star review
on your podcast app of choice, and send us that receipt.
If you tell your friends about the show, I'll say pretty much whatever you want me
to say.
That's how this works, my babies.
If you want to shoot the shit with other listeners of this fine show, join our Discord and subreddit.
If you want to see pictures of our faces and sick fan art, follow us at PretendingPod.
If you want to give us money, we'll give you bonus episodes and or merchandise.
If you want to find links to all that slop and more, the links are in the show notes.
Click them, you goblin, and get your peepers perusing.
Got a pirate problem?
I be the modern solution.
Time to gyrate.
It's R.I.
P.E.T.E.R.
with Cruisin'!
Welcome, everyone.
We are doing another short story here with PretendingToBePeople.
I'm really excited.
Joe, are you excited?
I am so excited.
Thomas, how do you feel right now?
I'm pretty stoked.
We've got one of our favorite role-playing podcasters.
She's a playwright.
She's a screenwriter.
She's a poet.
She's a comedian.
She's Ron Stampler and Scary Marlowe on my personal favorite actual play podcast, Dungeons
and Daddies.
It's Beth May!
It's Beth May.
Beth May's at the house.
Oh my gosh, what an intro.
Wow.
Welcome to PretendingToBePeople.
It came off of 30 seconds of deeply serious room noise where you guys are like, we need
30 seconds of silence for, and I thought you were about to say the name of a departed friend
or loved one, and I was getting ready for it, but no, to come from the energy of silence
into that lovely intro was so wonderful and welcoming.
Thank you for having me here.
Thank you so much for being here.
Why are you on our show?
Yeah.
Do you actually want to know something like really funny that is funny?
Are you laughing with us or at us?
Kind of like both.
I'm so sorry, but I did.
I did agree to come on the show because I thought that you were a friend of my friend
and then I found out that you weren't, but then you seemed chill, so it was all okay.
Beth, our podcast is actually good.
You're so lucky.
I know.
I feel lucky.
Yeah, I feel like I really lucked out.
That's kind of rare in the role playing podcast world.
Should we shout out that podcast that you thought you were coming on?
No, I just literally thought that one of my friends knew you for some reason, and then
I was like, Travis, I'm going on your friend's podcast, and he's like, what, I've never heard
of that.
He's like, who the fuck is that?
Zach has a good friend named Travis.
I do.
There's more overlap.
They must pretend.
Yeah.
That's exactly what we do.
That's the whole point of the show.
Zach, you never asked Luke how he felt.
Luke, are your socks wet?
Are my socks wet?
How do you feel about having Beth on the show?
Neutral plus, I would say.
Okay.
He just started listening to the day, Beth.
I'm sorry.
He doesn't really know.
No, I totally understand.
No, I'm stoked because I know a lot of people listen to you, so that's good for me.
Yeah.
He thought that it was a friend of his that was coming on the show.
I love Beth.
She's great.
And then you showed up.
I was like, wait.
Oh, damn.
Luke, she's really good.
It's chill.
I don't know why you're saying really good.
I'm like notoriously the worst D&D role player actually ever.
I can't believe you guys wanted me on here.
No, no, no.
We don't.
That works out really well.
We don't play D&D.
We don't play D&D at all.
We also don't play the game we play either.
Okay.
That's fabulous.
It's like Whose Line, Delta Green.
It's exactly like Whose Line, literally in that we're going to play some improv games.
A very tall man named Colin Mockery.
Ryan Stiles.
Oh, right.
You're making a Colin Mockery of us by not knowing Ryan Stiles' name right now, Tom.
I feel like Colin is tall for some people.
He is tall for some people.
Well, for some people.
That's true.
He's tall for me, but not for Ryan Stiles.
That's great.
Wow.
Zach, what do we do today?
Thanks, Joe.
I appreciate you asking that.
Well, I'm going to just go ahead.
Wait, wait, Zach.
What are we doing today?
Oh, yeah.
That was good.
I'm excited.
Thank you, legendary podcaster Beth May.
She hasn't left the Zoom call yet.
I sent you guys a message that said that your ship's crew has been invited to interview
for a mysterious job.
Our ship's crew?
Your ship's crew.
Because?
Because you four are?
Are?
Pirates.
Seamen.
Salesfolk?
You're on the high waters on the seas.
Your salesman.
Salesman, yeah.
Is that the name of the boat?
The Death of a Salesman?
The Death of a Salesman.
I love it.
Salesman.
That's way funnier than what you pitched in this part.
Oh, my God.
Sales.
Like, sale.
Oh, my God.
Sale.
First, you must sail to an unnamed island northeast of the Antaeus Maoris in the North
Atlantic Ocean.
You will then compete with five other seafaring crews in a bizarre interview of sorts for
the chance to win a job that claims to pay enough gold to comfortably live off for the
rest of your lives.
Hi, my name is Jorgen Stick.
Thank you for coming on the boat today.
Welcome to my crib.
We are here on the what's currently known as the Silent Doom, but oh, no, it actually
just changed.
At the last meeting, it's called the Death of a Salesman.
We all voted.
We have a democracy here aboard the Death of a Salesman and welcome to Caribs, the Caribbean
version of Caribs, and welcome to PTBP, Caribs.
This is the Death of a Salesman.
We're going to show you around who would be on the main deck right off the bat.
Wavy Adler.
It's Waverly Adler.
He goes by Wavy.
Is the camera crew now pointed at me?
The camera crew is directly pointed at you and Jorgen is just kind of like showing you
off like Vanna White.
He has a spyglass ad and he's looking out to the horizon and he notices that he's now
the center of some attention.
Oh, hey.
Oh, hey, didn't notice you there.
Didn't see you there.
Oh, hey there, Jorgen.
Can I help you with something?
Oh, yes.
No, I was just showing people around the ship.
Oh, we got a bit of a change here.
Yeah, I was just showing people around the Death of a Salesman and I was hoping that
you could just tell them what you do around here.
Oh, here.
Sure, of course.
And he kind of straightens out his jacket that's kind of tattered.
It was nice at one time, but it's old now and rumpled and licks his hand and puts it
through his hair real quick.
Well, here is the main deck.
That's the steering wheel over there and I kind of stand here and look out the edge there
and make sure we don't hit anything.
And then people come up to me and they ask me questions about things and I try and set
them on the right direction.
It's usually the direction the wind blows.
That's the secret.
I on a sailing ship it often is creeping right from behind a mass that's like right behind
you comes.
Oh, and me Christian name is Edward Spitz, but if you're on me ship and you know what's
good for you, you call me Mr. Spitz.
Mr. Spitz.
That's Mr. Spitz there.
Hello, wifey.
Jurgen's showing somebody around the boat.
Jurgen's got a camera crew.
Mr. Spitz, I was just hoping that, oh, I'm leaning right into it.
Oh, Mr. Spitz.
I was hoping that you could show the dear people around.
Oh, yes.
I've always been Irish ever since the beginning.
Oh, from the top of the bottom to the bottom of the top, I've been Irish and I'm hoping
that you'll tell people what you do on the ship.
I thought he was vaguely Scandinavian, but what I do on the ship, I do everything on
his ship.
I'll make sure this gross tub has an Irish civility.
You see, I sort of the food.
There we go.
We got to the final answer there.
Oh, but I don't do it like no typical pirate scowl, you know, I bring some class to it.
No, he does it up real nice, doesn't he?
Plus I can read, which is more than I can say for any of you.
The tines on our forks, sometimes there's three of them.
Yeah, often there is three tines instead of two.
And Geneva had that before Edward Spitz was on board.
Never.
That's right.
Things really started looking up around here when you joined us.
Mr. Spitz brought you three tines.
And then we, uh, we hear, uh, the wood slapping wood and a stumble emotion as Beth knows what
she, what she must do now.
Hey, what's going on up here?
Dr. Shark, uh, just showing everyone around the ship and, and, and what it's me, Dr. Shark.
Hello, Dr. Shark.
Hey there, doc.
Hi, doctor.
Anybody, uh, sick or anything?
I mean, just the typical worms and malaria, but as she asked, or as he asked the, a door
flies open and alabaster, Chernabog projectile vomits, and you see this pale skinned, like
long greasy, dark hair, open sores all over his face.
Um, his shirt is white and it's just blood and pus.
Just soaked.
And the camera freezes on you and then whip pans back around to Beth May, our guest.
And uh, and we get a good description of what her character looks like.
Well, he says, I'm sick as soon as she says, he says that,
Oh, Dr. Shark looks like Tony Soprano.
Um, and um, but like in like more twenties garb, I know that we're supposed to be in
like the 1800s or whatever.
I said a year earlier.
I don't remember what it was.
You said like in a mobster suit or whatever, and I pictured you in a huge oversized zoot
suit.
Yes, that, but like physically Tony Soprano inside the suit, but, uh, Dr. Shark only has
peg legs.
No, no, no biological legs there.
What sound does that make on the deck?
It makes a real like sexy sound, which you wouldn't think, right?
But it makes like, that makes me horny.
Just one clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk clunk.
It's a real jazzy clunk.
I know what the four of us are doing after this recording.
Yeah, jerking it to the clunk clunk.
No, you don't know how this podcast is run.
He's going to make us stay in this room and make wood noises until we tap on wood in the
perfect way.
Until I finally get poley erect based on your wood.
Yeah.
He's like, that's not quite my speed.
Um, and that's how Zach gets wood racking.
I was clunking, I don't know.
And then, uh, Dr. Shark is accompanied always, uh, his permanent, his permanent companion,
a parrot on his shoulder, Mrs. Knife and Mrs. Knife just squawks.
Mrs. Knife.
Oh damn, that was good.
I'm going to use that exact audio for all birds in season two.
There you go.
This will be a bird-centric season.
There's going to be so many birds.
We actually haven't started recording season two, but I just put a bunch of birds into
it in my head.
So what is it?
What is Dr. Shark's face?
Like what do we learn from his face?
What does his face betray exactly when, when, uh, when Al, when Al busts through the door
with a, with a heave and a, in a wet, wet mouth.
Oh, well, I think he's seen this all before.
I think he says something like, Al, I said, if it is anybody's sick, that is anybody,
you know, Al, like, you know, Al sadly, sadly looks up understanding having heard this
many times before.
I mean, I could pop up the hood and give it a look.
You know what I mean?
Al has heard this before and vehemently shakes his head no.
In the age of sale that meant like opening up your rib cage and peeking inside.
We get a real good face shot of Jurgen's stick here.
He's got brown.
Does he do a gym take?
Uh, yo total gym.
Oh my gosh.
As, as the, uh, as the whole classic interaction between Dr. Shark and alabaster Al, uh, is
going down like it does every Tuesday.
You're going to stick Jim's the fuck out of the camera with his brown chin length hair
parted in the middle, short goatee, early thirties with his early thirties brought to
us by patron modern cannabis from grand junction, Colorado.
Thank you.
Modern cannabis for Jurgen stick.
He's whimsically joyous when he shouldn't be.
So he, uh, he does a quick little jig in the, in the yak that, uh, the alabaster Alice
sicked up onto deck.
I think that, uh, that, that about does it for the shift, doesn't it?
Uh, did we meet everyone and you see an entire like massive crew of pirates?
Yeah.
We probably met everyone.
Right.
He met everybody who matters.
That's certain.
What was that?
Patron's name?
Modern cannabis.
Uh, my mom lives in Western Colorado, so next time I'm out in junction, if you want to smoke
me up, that would be rad.
There's one last person that we need to meet.
Oh yeah.
That makes sense.
And that is the emperor Tamarind monkey that is currently eating alabaster's puke, which
is the only reason Mr. Spitz is not like screaming at you because he knows it's going to get
cleaned up.
Yeah.
I know your monkey will eat your mess.
And yeah, up to this point, alabaster was only just given like sad nods and he wants
more sad nods at you while he watches his monkey clean his mess up.
The name of the monkey?
If we don't know yet, because I don't know yet.
And uh, does anyone have an extra writing utensil?
Oh yeah.
That's what I needed right there.
I needed to write down your character names.
It's super handy for a GM.
That's a little pro tip.
A pen?
A pen is a great tool for anyone in your life.
And really anyone.
Yeah.
Wait.
Thomas, what's your name?
Edward Spitz or Mr. Spitz?
Mr. Spitz.
I love that.
Thank you, Beth May.
Yeah, that's good.
Joe, what's your character name?
Wavy Adler.
Duh.
I'm so sorry that I had to ask after you spent the time to create that.
Wait, Luke, what was your name?
My name is Alabaster.
You can call me Al Chernabog and my monkey that will get named later.
I love the promise of a premise.
Like fucking that monkey is going to get named later.
Alabaster has told him multiple times, when you prove yourself, you get a name.
Yeah, that monkey has to kill.
And then it takes the name of the first man it kills.
You guys head out past the islands that make up the Antis Maerus.
You can just say Greater Antilles.
What is it?
Greater Antilles.
Mm-hmm.
Philly.
All right, my bad.
You can just say Labia Majora.
If you sail past the Labia Majora and into the Labia Minora, which basically all I was
getting to during this is, we're going to fast forward into a dark night.
Most nights are pretty dark, Zach.
There is no moonlight on this night.
You can't see the hand in front of your face.
Well, can't do surgery tonight.
Can't see the hand in front of my face, so.
Oh, darker shock is our commission tonight.
Will you please, please, I need my leg taken off right now or I'll lose my everything.
Could you stop bleeding on my dicks?
I can't, I don't know where.
I can't see the blood.
Darker shock can operate in the morning.
Yeah, sorry, matey.
I'm going to wait for the morning.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll bring up some candles.
Oh, that'd be great.
Oh, okay.
All right, yeah.
Oh, official law.
And as some light-
Modern wonders.
As some light gets in there, you see Jurgen's stick is just up against the wall of this
small cabin and he's just bleeding profusely from his kneecap.
I just tripped down the stairs.
There's a bone sticking up out of his knee as the candle finally makes its way up above
and he looks right into the eyes of Dr. Shark and he's like, I just need, I just need.
Well, let me, let me console my nurse here.
What do you think we should do, Mrs. Knife?
Cut it off.
I think we got to cut it off, so.
Mrs. Knife never lies.
And Dr. Shark takes a big, what do they use?
Like, saws?
No, saws are pretty slow.
Well, they're like big surgical saws.
We just watched Master and Commander to get in the mood for this.
Yeah, and you have a little cork to chew on.
I'll give you a little cork to chew on.
They're literally called bone saws.
And then yes, I get out the bone saw and should I go for it?
Hi.
Can you roll a surgery?
Yeah, I'll roll first aid.
Yeah, whatever the roll is.
Are you not familiar with Call of Cthulhu?
I'm not.
I'm not, I'm not really.
I played it once.
Oh, nice.
Did you have fun?
I had a ton of fun the ones I played it.
Oh, shit.
I have not because I never subscribed to your Patreon.
That's fine. You don't have to.
I didn't.
You can just subscribe for a month and download it all.
No, I don't have a lot of money, Zach.
Subscriptions start with as low as $5.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Us too, I've heard it all.
I was going to say, you're a shit salesman.
Like, you don't have to.
When people are like, sorry, I don't subscribe to the Patreon,
I'm like, well, I'm not going to talk to you until you do.
Oh, yeah.
Luke goes for the total ice out.
Okay, so do you roll like D20s in this or what?
Oh, D100s, 2D10s.
Oh, that's such a good question.
Yeah, so are you using a mechanical dice roller?
I'm on Google.
Just roll dice.
Yeah, I just said mechanical dice roller.
I don't know what that is, but it sounds cool.
I want one of those, man.
That's a status symbol for role playing podcasters
is they get a really nice clacky mechanical dice roller.
Okay, so I'm rolling a D100.
A D100 is what we're looking for.
What's your skill in first aid?
My skill in first aid is 90.
Oh.
Then you're probably going to roll under it,
which is what we're looking for.
Now, wait, also Call of Cthulhu, if you just have a...
We're not playing Call of Cthulhu.
We're doing our standard role play game.
Oh, it's just madness.
We're out of left field here.
We're just rolling under to succeed.
If your dice match, it's a crit.
That is a success.
Crunch as a bone just snaps
and literally one of the
nerves is like hanging out
on the end and it's just
wiggling back and forth and
Jurgen is like, I don't think I can take it anymore.
I earlier forgot I had this accent
when I was bad. My leg cut off
and now it's just...
And then he's just gone.
His eyes roll back into the back of his head
and you look down at a bloody stump
that you've created and you know
exactly what to do next, which is...
Yeah, I say
good work, Mrs.
I mean, good work, Mrs. Knife
let's tie a tourniquet on you.
And then I tie a tourniquet on the leg.
And then I'm like, you're gonna
be fitted for a wooden leg.
He's gonna be just like me.
As he just lays back, tongue hanging out
eyes rolled in the back of his head
you can sense
just sort of a pride
of Dr. Shark and of the ship in general
from everyone in the room
including Jurgen Stick who's passed out
which is fun for everyone.
It's just like a really positive atmosphere right now.
I love that. Because somebody's leg got chopped off.
But also Dr. Shark has like
crazy mobster clothes
in the 1700s.
I used my tie to tie
the tourniquet. It was really nice.
Yeah, I really hate the one.
Everyone on this ship thinks Dr. Shark
is the coolest person in the world.
And desperately wants two peg legs.
How many peg legs have you added to the crew
like voluntarily?
I'll see. Let's check the chart.
Right next to the map
looks like 72 peg legs.
Weird because we only got
like 14 crew members.
He did me hand
as well.
And I hold up my very shitty
metal prosthetic hand.
And some people get addicted
and they just saw their peg legs off.
Shorter and shorter.
We got the shortest crew around.
Oh my god, then you could fit in all the little
you wouldn't have to have a nice boat
because you could fit in all the small cabins
if your peg legs were shorter.
True, we got the smallest cabins too.
We're going to have to think about that one
visually, but also
really, you're not thinking of the possibility
of just intimidating enemy crews
by having everybody river dance.
Just pounding pegs
on the fucking
speaking of enemy crews
speaking of pounding pegs
you guys
everyone wakes up
the next morning to
the sound of
someone having a lovely time
pleasurable experience
on deck
doing a peg jig?
total morning after peg jig
just doing pegging
just hanging on the deck
which is what we call our little dances.
Alright, let's leave.
As you guys awake in the morning
to this lovely exclamation of joy
you realize that it is
probably
Wavy Adler who has
noticed that in the distance
is a beautiful
beautiful island
Land ho!
With smoke rising out from the middle of it
there are four other ships
that are parked
what do ships do? They park
dock
or dock
off the coast a bit
they all have backup cameras
what did we do before these things?
Dude, I don't know
I live in a residential ass neighborhood
and I'm like how did I not run over
children repeatedly
before a backup camera
you didn't know, you didn't see them
I just maimed and moved on
so there are four other ships
their flags flying high in the air
as well as their little friend boats
hanging out on the shore
tenders
their chicken tendies are hanging out on the shore
there's four of those
little man boats
what are they called? tendies?
so the tendies are already
hanging out
so you guys are the fifth to arrive
what else we got?
that's pretty much all you can see right now
unless you want to give me the old spot
Hayden or
I'd like to give you a spot, yeah
yeah
it's a 41
it's 41
so my talent is that I can roll a bonus dice
can I just do that in case I get a
yeah, in case you match your dice and get a crit
I got a 19 on a 25
that sounds like such a fake talent, I believe you
but my talent is
I can roll a bonus dice
it's a really great talent
it says I get to keep doing it as long as I want
let me know when you crit and then we'll move on
basically if I'm not happy
I just get to decide
I also succeeded on the spot, Hayden
yeah, I got a 20
I succeed
with every single person succeeding
I'm going to give you a full run down
so what we've got here is
we've got four other ships
I'll describe their flags to give you an idea
of who these pirates are
one of the flags has a
cannon that is wearing
a powdered wig
one of the ships has
the exact military flag
from Great Britain
the ol' chestnut, what do they call it?
the Union Jack
that guy
he's got a
bottle over the middle of it
they've embroidered a big bottle of rum
over the middle of the Union Jack
the next one is
a skeleton
with horns
and then a beard
that is not on the face
so much, it's just around the neck
area of the
skeleton
argh, there be neckbeard
it's the dread pirate neckbeard
of course you've heard of him
and then the last one
is two music notes
not sure when those were invented
quite a while
but
those two music notes are
like swinging
off of one ship
the notes are flinging themselves
away from the ship that is on the flag
as well, on the shore
you see a massive
statue, you're not sure yet
until you get there what the statue is
of, but as islands
ought to have, there's a
large humanoid statue
right on the shore
as well as some other just like
piles of seemingly ash
that's pretty much all you can see from here
and we're gonna get you guys on one of those
tendies and head into the shore
I would assume
Jurgen is getting over having
a quarter of the legs
that he had before
knee down on one side, I believe he is
about a quarter down
yeah I guess, yeah
court low
Dr. Shark as they make their way
onto the deck
I'm a doctor, sorry I was gonna say
I'm a doctor not a fraction
doctor
I don't care which number
is above another or
what have you, but I'm alive today
and that's likely I made it through the night
because of you, oh yeah no problem
just don't mention this to anybody
laughter
he quickly unrolls his pant leg
to cover the peg
who would take
charge in this situation of
getting the crew ready to
go ashore, I can get you there
yeah I mean you're good at like navigation
and stuff so you would probably be
commanding the tender
I rolled
a 3 for my navigation skill
which means we get there so
slick and smooth
no issues whatsoever
in the boat on the way there
Alvester looks at Dr. Shark
and he's like
I found another one
and he pulls his shirt up and there's just like
another sore on his body but there's also
like hundreds of sores
oh wow that's quite the sore
hey Mrs. Knife check out this sore
what a looker
laughter
and Al feels like
happy, he feels like
yeah it is a good one and then he just puts his
shirt back down and like stares off
into the distance, yeah it's an impressive sore
laughter
oh now I'm doing mob
about halfway there Al
wants to swim because the salt water
really helps his
stings real bad in the sores
I knew a guy that we used to
drag behind the boat to get him to talk
so I mean as long as you don't say anything
we could drag you behind the boat
see how your sores like it or whatever
laughter
Al takes the doctor's advice
to heart and he uses
what is it, rope use
skill to tie himself
behind the boat, very well done, I don't think
you need to roll but I appreciate you going for it
he succeeded, yeah nice
I love Pope Cthulhu, yeah he succeeded
carry on
he ties himself behind the boat
he's having a decent
time back there, like an inner
he's inventing wakeboarding
laughter
he is the wakeboard
he is the wakeboard, what's Mr. Smiths doing
on the way in, Mr. Smiths is
Spitz, Spitz, Smiths
Jimmy Smiths is
Mr. Spitz is
eyeing the island with incredible
suspicion, but he also has a moment
to praise the navigation of
Wavy Adler
is I always thought being on a
sheer glass when you had
a window with Mr. Adler
it's just a matter of making sure that your
oars are in sync with the natural
motion of the waves, he's not
listening, he like
one eye is so
incredibly squinted at the island and
the other eye is so big
at you?
both dead on at the island
but he is just assessing
Mrs. Smiths don't trust no Spitz
change your name
Mrs. Spitz
Mrs. Smiths don't trust nobody
not even in Ireland
as you come upon the island
also I've got a monkey on my chest, I forgot about my monkey
also I have a monkey on my chest
also we're all playing I have a monkey on my chest
wait, wait, let's talk about it
let's not
what's eating you son?
this monkey is giving you sores
10 feet behind is
the boat
you're in the salt water
with your open sores and your screams
are haunting us all
but my monkey is there to give me comfort
Jesus
which is my monkeys name
now, Jesus the monkey
give me comfort?
give me comfort
that's blaspheming son
that's a cult leader name, hello my name is
Jesus give me comfort
yeah, love that
when you guys see this statue as you approach the island
you notice that the statue actually
has a lot of alligator facial
features that are alligator-ish
it's got a alligator face
it's a human body with an alligator head
it's an anthropomorphized gator
man
I'm not the only owl here
does it have a gator tail?
oh you're not sure, the gator tail might be
buried, however the long
snoot of the gator seems to make
a bit of a platform that you could
walk out on and as you
oh it's massive, and as you get there
you see that there's actually a ladder
up the back that
is kind of like scales, but it's a ladder
that you can climb up about
13, 5 meters, I don't know
15 feet up to the
13, 5 meters? 13.5
I'm a doctor, not an expert on the metric system
she already said
now I'm doing her
you guys hit the
hit the beach, and as you
just slow-mo
scene of us hitting the beach
oh my god, cowabunga
splashylvania towels
flowing in the wind
oh yeah, the
PTPB shop is now up, you can buy
a splashylvania towel from season 1
splashylvania, you'll want to
soak your buds
you'll want to soak your buds, it's pretending
pod dot shop, please buy a
bath towel from us for $40
are those real?
oh my god, I'm going to buy one
do it beth mae
you'll want to soak your buds
wait, soaker splash
soak, you'll want to soak your buds
I want to soak your buds
it's a vampire themed
abandoned water park from season 1
I start climbing down
the ladder
are all these other pirate crews that we've now joined, are they all being
cordial to each other, or is there a fighting breaking out already
as these tendies hit the beach
you see that the other four
wait, the tendies hit the beach
the other four tendies
are empty
mad empty, and there's
no one on this beach that you
can see currently
but as you all are there
you notice that there seems to be
like a ditch or a channel
dug into the sand
along the coastline
parallel to the water for as far
as you can see, and it's got a red
liquid in it
let me see if I can tell if this is blood
not that I would do anything
I don't see a person here to fix
or whatever
should I roll to see if it's blood
I mean that seems a bit absurd
you get down, you stick your whole head in it
no, so it's definitely blood
you can smell the
iron as you approach the
long channel, it's about six inches
wide, but it is
blood, I can smell the iron in it
it's about six inches wide
it's wet, but not water
it's ironic
isn't it?
she liked him
yeah, as everybody's announcing it
Spitz is taking just a huge
fingerful and tasting it
a full
thirty seconds after it's been announced
it's a swig bit coagulated
it's blood
it's kind of a filmy layer on top
when you dig your finger in
you would have a film on your finger
as you lift up
it's coagulated
what movie?
that was a little joke about the film part
sorry
moving on
Mrs. Knife is such an asset
Jesus Christ, go look for
the other pirates
I want to send my monkey out to scout
oh, yeah
awesome
alright, send Jesus
I was about to be like, I'll put you in charge
how does your
monkey work, dude?
animal handling, I guess
a pass
what does your monkey sound like?
ok, sick, I'll see what I can do
alright, so
oh, better than I did
you sound just like Jesus Christ
sand
sand is like flying up behind
the monkey's paws and feet
as it clambers about
toward the tree line that is
on the opposite side from the water
on this beach it has hands, by the way
it's a monkey and then it stops really quick
on its hands, because it's a monkey
and it turns around
it turns around by putting its head
in between its legs and looking back at you
oh, it's a funny monkey
oh, it's a hilarious monkey
which you know to mean
there's somebody watching
boys, what do you say?
there's somebody watching us
holy shit
let's check it out
oh, so we watch them back
Wavy flings out his
spyglass in a really
efficient flourish
pulls it up to his eye and he wants to spot
hidden right where the monkey was indicating
awesome, yeah, go ahead and roll with
your
it's a 16
you want to roll again?
or a 56
alright, so with the
success there, you notice that
there is a tall, bald
overweight man who is not
paying attention to you
but he is just kind of like standing and
surveying the beach, he seems
to think that he is being sneaky
but he is not?
we got a guy over there
he looks like he's trying to hide from us
he ain't hiding too well
hey you, you look like you're
being sneaky, but you're not
being very sneaky
ya bastard
I start running at him
we've been playing the forest
yeah, yeah, yeah, okay
so as you run, you'd have to jump
over this little channel of blood, yeah?
I step right in it
step right in it
oh, that's not what you want to do in a Delta Green game
no, but I have open sores all over
my body, so, you know
oh god
it just gets right in there
so yeah, it like helps
it's blood
if you could expect these consequences in 12 to 32 hours
maybe like 6 now
also it's old times, but before germs
leg
right into the blood, running towards
the bald guy
he doesn't even notice that you're running at him
I yell, I see that he isn't noticing me
and I yell at him because I don't want to like
tackle him, but I'm, that's what I'm
about to do unless he tells me not to
his eyes get really big and he just
kind of stares at you with these big
eyes
is he a pirate?
no, he doesn't seem to be dressed like a pirate
he's just kind of a guy dressed like a dude
he's just wearing normal clothes
for like a person of this time
period
I give it a second thought and I stop
inches away from him
oh, hey
hey
I'm Mitch
Al, did you step in my channel?
I just look down at my leg
like duh
can we go check and make sure it's okay?
what's okay?
you heard something?
no, it's just my trench
and he just starts walking kind of
back towards the beach to check out
this moat and he's like, yeah, these are
my moats, so they can't be
broken
hey doc, in your professional opinion
is there any reason a man might have a blood trough?
in my many years
I've seen like a few blood troughs
but never any that people
willingly and a lively captive
you know what I mean?
not for no good reason, Al
no, we've got good reasons, but that's not
you're not here for reasons, you're here to
do the ship race that you guys
are in
if you want to come with me this way, let's get going
yeah, let's do it
I'm kind of like messing with the sand
to fix where Alabaster Al
had stepped on this blood trough
and he's just kind of making it the exact same width
as everything else
I'm Mitch, hey
Mitch, is this the blood of the other crews
who compete in this competition?
no, they're waiting
we're all waiting for you guys and one other crew
we gotta get going
it's obviously some sort of blood curse
and I dip my knife into the blood
so that I have the blood curse knife
that's fine, you can have the blood
you can have a blood curse knife, that's okay
I don't think that'll help
at least make somebody sick if I stab them
yeah, that's gross
well anyway
so yeah, these are all my canals
just kind of like
water courses, whatever
just going through
shout out to Nate Abbott from St. Louis
for Mitch Diggory
by the way, Diggory's my last name
I'm Mitch Diggory, it's nice to meet you guys
I love being useful
so I'd just really like to help
direct you to the way to go
okay, see you never
is his character description that he's helpful?
he loves being useful, I mean I love being useful
that's great
Zach's like, I wrote this scenario and I had a lot
of canals of blood to dig
so
it kind of worked out perfect
and a huge backlog of NPC names
that we need to get rid of
are you going to name everybody in these pirate crews?
no, it's just I'm Mitch
so let's keep going
and so he starts walking away from his
ditch and his gutter and his trench
I say we follow him
like this is the way, the money, right?
yeah, yeah, yeah, you guys wanted to
win the opportunity
to make a bunch of money so you never
have to pirate again or whatever
yeah, the pirate games
oh, is that where you guys have been calling him?
that's where we've been calling him
yeah, that's where I've been calling him, I've been trying to get
cash on, I think Wavy
is with me but I don't know if most of the crew
wants to see it, I like the Olympics
the Olympics
has a significant supporter
a lot of people
are just calling it the Crucible
yeah, I never read it
I've been calling
it the big thing, like we
getting ready for the big thing
I
always got to appreciate your funny way of
talking, Dottoshock, you sound like
you're from another time entirely
you sound like you're from another country
entirely
pretty wild stuff
Dr. Shark has had to go to
multiple HR meetings about
the other international people on board
yeah
obviously a mobster from the 20s
would have to go to a shitload of
fucking HR meetings
weird, I'm the only one who came back
from them
oh fuck
as you guys head off
Beth, I need you to choose between those flags
that we saw earlier
do you remember any of the
I want the neckbeard boy
yeah, well of course
perfect
so as you guys are heading
further into the jungle
of this island you're going through
there's a path that's already kind of been created
that Mitch is sort of leading you
down and as you guys are going
you really can't see too far ahead of you
because the thick is
he's kind of moving you through
this sort of channel
of a pathway as the jungle
kind of creeps around your head
almost and creates a cave
that you're kind of walking
through almost
and then all of a sudden you hear
a
oh no
fucking shit
no, this is somebody
else's fault
oh no
and
this is somebody
else's fault
from Mitch or a voice ahead on the trail
no, it's a voice ahead and off to the side
and you guys hit a clearing
and you see ahead of you
there is a slight fork in the road
and this other pirate crew has clearly
gone the wrong way
and the captain
he's wearing the hat and everything
and boy does this guy have a beard
but it is not on his jawline at all
or above his lip
it is just pure jaw down
and it connects into his
hamburger meat which is reaching
up
oh I hate that term
his hamburger meat?
we've covered this before
it's chest hair
apparently in one of the fast and furious movies
ludicrous calls his chest hair hamburger meat
and Zach threw that out casually one night
and everybody says
yeah that's wild lore to just be a part of a conversation
I respect it
though, so there
and so like I said his hamburger meat is just climbing up
to meet
the surly, surly
hairs that have made their way down
from the chin toward the nape
the nape and neck
the nape and nape
the lips, the teeth
and he is
drowning in some
sort of quicksand
and he is
I'm gonna go ahead and roll real quick
he is
he is up to his thighs
already and he is
waggling so hard
he is not being calm
he is just like
oh no, no everyone
hey, hey, Waverly
fuck, that's me, hey
do you remember me?
oh my god Neckbeard what are you doing here?
it's a great guy, I'm Neckbeard
and look at my crew
and the crew is all like standing around
and pointing at him
and talking amongst themselves
how far from like the edge is he?
oh he's right in the middle yeah
you'd have to get something long
like how long? to kind of reach out
maybe like five, six feet long
to be able to pull him out
that's longer than a monkey
I know one way to handle this
Mrs. Knife
cut the legs
no, no, no, no, no, no
there's got to be another way
trust him Captain Neckbeard
he's a doctor
I'm already up to my thighs
what are you gonna take me out the hip?
yeah, we might as well
Captain Neckbeard up and see a lot of years
and I never met a doctor
as shrewd as Dr. Shark
if he says your legs gotta go
they gotta go
boy let's find some wood planks
to sit down so we can get over there
to sew his legs up
you're like Australian now
that's what I'm gonna stick with
happy birthday
my joy, joy, joy
oh my god
say yoyce
noice, noice, no
no I won't do it
he, as you guys are
literally having this conversation
he has sunk
he's sunk hip to nip at this point
damn
I'm sorry Nepo
you're so hip to nip
there's no hope for you
and his arms are just like
flailing about
and he's like
seriously
no one
throw me a rope
fuck
I can't cut the torso
so I'm out of ideas
okay you just save the head doctor
mmm
maybe, maybe
what about the neck
he needs his neck
well
I mean it's not his best feature
does he need it though
I mean we should ask the doctor
does he need his neck
for his bed
most people think you need your neck to live
umm
there
there yeah
I mean
most people but
there's a chance of a miracle
ain't that right Nepo
well always good to give it a shot I guess
why don't you just pray
hips to nips was a four
he rolled a one this time
so now he's nips to pits
damn
wait
hips to nips, nips to pits
what's
he went from his hips to his nips
now he's gone from his nips to his
pits
he's about to sink
I get you
a one is a nip to pits
you're about to run out of rhyming biology
so you're getting really dire
you are fucked as a GM Zach
well next is his dimps
that's my secret
oh
the dimps yes
the dimps and then the temps
and then the temps and then your kaput
okay then he's fine
yeah he's fine
he's got plenty of time
yeah
then he's limps
can I like look on his crew to see if any of them happen to be wearing a rope as a belt
yeah go ahead and roll
on what?
rope use
fuck still no
I failed
none of them are wearing belts
they're all using both hands to hold their pants up
which is why they're not helping
no he failed his rope use roll so he can't identify the belts
they're all clearly ropes
as he starts to go under
yeah
because it's what's happening
it was good seeing you again captain
hey I know how to I know how to handle this situation
mrs knife off with his head
all right gotta chop the head
yeah I mean the neck you need sometimes but uh not tonight
not tonight
you gotta trust him captain he's a certified doctor
certified somewhere
always helps me
blood is just like pouring out of my face
so I'm gonna try to crawl across the quicksand essentially
to see if I can like chop off his head and get back before I start to sink
yeah that seems really good
so Beth I have here in order to crawl across this all you have to do is stay calm right
so you just have to pass a marbles check
so I want you to roll your marbles and see if you can hold on to your marbles
okay and what what am I rolling for marbles 100?
and you're gonna roll against your marble score which is equal to your power
okay where is my because I'm not sure I passed
P.O.W. at the top of the sheet
power power power
under sizzler
it's also under sanity
okay I rolled yeah I rolled an 88 and I have an 80
oh no
watch your marbles
it was 80
okay well
that'd be a critical failure
oh no
you're not calm
we'll say that
you lost your marbles
as Dr. Shark begins to crawl out
your left hand hits this quicksand and immediately you are shocked
by how quickly your hand disappears into this quicksand
and honestly your gut reaction is to hold still but there's nothing inside Dr. Shark that can hold still right now
as you lose your marbles
I think he's just like oh my god oh my god stop no what oh my god ew
ew
and ew is the last word that comes out as your second hand goes in
and then the weight of your just moving forward pushes your face directly
as you're like ew oh my god ew
it's just ew
as your mouth fills up with this quicksand and you start going head first in
and now we just see
let me roll a d4
that's a four
yeah so you are head shoulders
it looks like she's doing a handstand in there
he's showing off
Dr. Shark is fully handstanded and your bottom half is sticking up out
so we've got no biological limbs
yeah we've just got two sticks in the air
do you have like really cool mobster shoes on?
probably yeah
okay uh Mr. Spitz steals those
no
Mrs. Knife is like every man for himself and like completely disappears
oh no
I can see a shoe still on your shoulder
I thought that part would be more on me about my shoes but
Jesus Christ go go check his pockets
I send my monkey and a pill for the rest
oh you're gonna drown your monkey
yeah now the monkey jumps out onto the legs
onto the peg leg like a zoo
oh I forgot it's a peg leg
like a zoo enclosure fake like limb on a tree
it jumps out and drabs onto this
they were peg legs
so you had awesome like gangster shoes
onto your peg leg
and then the monkey reaches in
what do you got in those pockets Dr. Shark?
oh I think there's like
like a bunch of like rings from people he's definitely killed
and like a cool like
in surgery
a cool like $300
no I think this is like
from straight the streets of New York
like mobster shit
$300 in like 1933 bills
he's got like a quarter from 1975 for some reason
like a note that's like
please give this to my wife and it's just like
lol like I love you so much
like
lol but lots of love
it's old people text
like there's like a cell phone there
like
the monkey brings back a cell phone a note
a quarter and then some like
American dollar bills and I like
throw everything away besides
the note and I'm like
he was a good doctor I'll give this
to his wife whose name is
is
uh
mrs. knife
mrs. wife
her full name is
knife wife
mr. spitz is gonna go after the
the cell phone
as he throws it away
it goes towards you and we have a cell phone
I think we hit the end of that episode
at mrs. wife mrs. knife
honestly
zach how are the listeners gonna know
about my cell phone
it is gonna be so weird when that
like I don't we don't talk about
it ever again
seriously beth
thank you so much for coming on
thank you for doing this thank you so much for making a huge
mistake
tell your friend travis
thank you so much I will
I will I'll tell him tell him hey for us
tell him
tell him to listen to our podcast
if he ever does something
cool then we'll have him on
yeah for sure
he's a cool dude
so should I stop recording
yeah
maybe just say how much fun
you had and stuff
there's gonna be a little blip in the record
and then you're gonna hear like oh my god
I had so much fun but I'm gonna say it like
more convincingly than that because I actually had
fun say it how you're gonna say it
yeah let's hear it
oh my god I had so much fun
this acting thing is not working well for me
oh my god that's too bad
I had so much fun
but I did have so much fun
beth where can people find your book
oh yeah I've got a book called the immortal
soul salvage yard that's a real like
wordy dumb title I know but it's a
cool poetry book I think and so
if you can check it out wherever you find books
if you go to like amazon you can
find it I know boo amazon or whatever
but barnes and noble
might not have it in stores but you can order online
etc and then I'm on a podcast
called dungeons and daddies
and you can find that wherever you consume
podcasts wherever you're listening to this podcast
you can also get dungeons and daddies
isn't that so cool and then you can find me
on instagram and twitter at
hey beth may that's hey like you're saying hi
beth like my first name and may like the month
or my last name
but yeah whatever cool
alright you can go to the show notes
for all that stuff have you ever done that
before yeah
that is concise
what a wild
experience thank you so much for listening
we were so happy to have beth may on
if you couldn't tell
if you enjoyed listening to that
please check out the rest of our
show we are 9 episodes into
season 2 so you can start there with
episode 1 or there's
115 episodes of season
1 waiting for you
alternatively we've done some short
4 or 5 episode long runs
that are also on our main feed
you can check those out as well
we really appreciate it and for those of you
who have been with us since the beginning
hell yeah dude
so
oh we are frozen aren't we that's nice
i like that it's a decent
image of us i look like i'm
no you're smiling
that's yeah that's what i said
oh right
i b s every shit is a blessing
i mean we could
exit out of
are we frozen
yeah you're frozen for us
for me there's nobody else here
you and the tortie
hang out in the zoom room and we'll be right back
ok cool
that was just me by myself
talking to myself
i am the host now
pretty cool
is she the one you want
are they the ones
you want
am i the one you want
is he the one
you want
is she the one you want
are they the ones
you want
am i the one you want
charts areexistence
is she the one you want
are they the ones you want
are they they're portraits
but is she the one you want
I think it's time that I pull your card
and figure out who you really are
my name is
if she is the one you want
is he the one you want is she the one you want
are they the ones you want am I the one you want