Introductions and greetings, my little furballs.
It's your best friend and worst enemy, Wolf the Dog,
here to gas you up, then make targeted insults that make you wonder if we were ever friends in the first place.
Nah, I'm just kidding.
Or am I?
I am the DJ of the radio station known as 694.2 PTBP.
I only demand one thing from you, my loyal, royal listeners.
Your unending love and admiration at all times, regardless of convenience.
Speaking of, this howlin' with Wolf is from Spencer Furnace in Akron, Ohio.
Wow, I hope the trip from Akron was worth it.
Spencer tagged at Pretending Pod on the internet, and for that I am eternally grateful.
Not eternally, just feelin' that gratitude ticklin' my intestinals for a finite period of time.
Spencer Furnace, right?
Well, hey there, Sir Wolf. Fancy seein' you round these parts.
I'd love to give a shout-out with all of my love to Tom and Steph, Joe and Rachel,
for givin' me a place to stay and a positive perspective to get through some of the hardest times.
And the boys at PTBP for givin' me an auditory hug
when I needed the sound of people who care for each other and my ear holes.
I'll leave y'all with a joke.
What do you call a hundred million year old pig?
Jurassic pork, baby, get you some.
Thank y'all for all you do.
Damn, I do love a good joke, Spencer from Ohio.
I'd love to hear one sometime.
See, two of us can do jokes, Spencer from Ohio.
But thanks for writin' in and sayin' those nice things about the show.
If you wanna write up somethin' for your fur-zaddy wolf to howl, tag us on the internet.
Yeah, yeah, we're still on the internet.
I know, I heard they're makin' everyone still on the internet.
Go to a classic Catholic confessional booth
and rattle off the sins to a lifelike blow-up doll
that kinda looks like Cameron from Ferris Bueller's Day Off.
But not enough that it was actually modeled after him.
What was I sayin'?
The links are in the show notes.
Oh shit, another word for what's next is succession.
And I just realized that's the same guy.
Whoa, speaking of, it is time for the news.
Last time here at 694.2 PTBP,
the Cannes crew finished up the tense exchange with Ruth,
who is deathly thin, smokin' meth, doin' Adderall,
and looks every bit the part.
Julie has fed her another pill
with a thick GPS tracking device attached,
which is just awful.
And then, on the way to the city jail,
the city action news team learned a wild amount
about Julius's father,
takin' us now to the concrete steps of the city jail,
where Beck is filmin' Cal,
takin' concrete steps to get to the top.
It's Alter Girl with My Life is Great
and It's All My Fault.
And it's all my fault
Cause my life is great
And it's all mine
And it's all my fault
We went around the neighborhood when I was in, like, fourth grade.
My brother was in, like, eighth grade with a video camera
and asked people to, like, for interviews for a school project,
and then we would just ask them random questions.
But the first question that we asked this one guy
was his thoughts on capital punishment.
And he talked to us about his views on capital punishment
for, like, 15 minutes, probably,
and we recorded the whole thing and then left,
and we're just like, I guess that was a prank.
Yeah, you thought you were fuckin' esoteric,
Longmont Potion Castle?
Find the humor in this, bitch.
We conducted interviews.
No, the whole time you were tellin' that story,
I couldn't stop thinking of burp.
Dude, at work the other day, I was, like, doing something with my boss,
and he's like, hold on, I'm getting a phone call.
And he, like, answers it. He's like, hello? What?
Uh, yes. Okay, bye.
And I was like, what was that?
And he's like, it was, like, a very young child asking me
if my refrigerator was running.
And I was like, did you know the number?
And he's like, I did not know the number.
He's like, I heard the mom in the background,
loud whispering, what to ask me.
Oh, wow.
Well, that's so weird.
It was, like, 1 p.m. on, like, a Tuesday.
I love the idea that the mom wanted to prank somebody,
but didn't have the balls to do it herself.
Isn't Maddie, like, nannying a kid or something?
Or is she just looking after a house?
Looking after a house.
Okay. Plants.
She got the house to call?
If it was, then yeah, the house called.
It was a haunted mansion.
My God.
Okay, this is not much spoilers.
This is not spoilers for The Sopranos.
But, Luke, you know at the very end
when Tony and the other guy are really feuding
and they try to go to his house to talk to him
and he's just, like, yelling at them from.
Yes.
Okay, so there's a joke on the subreddit
that he's just become a house.
And it's really fucking funny.
If you've seen The Sopranos, make sure to reach out and.
Are we recording?
Yeah.
That's good.
Let's get 30 seconds of silence.
Those bugs are loud as shit.
Yeah, we should actually, like,
maybe take a mic outside and get some of that.
Ooh, yeah.
Open the window up and get some background cicadas.
Get let some bugs in here.
They went in so bad.
Are those, like, a Midwestern thing
or are those everywhere?
They're everywhere.
I think they're Southern.
I don't know if they have them Northern.
I feel like there's some part of our country
that doesn't have them in there.
Are you trying to say this is the South?
But I think a lot of the East Coast has them.
You know, they go in cycles.
But there's pretty much, like, always a cycle running.
Have you guys always called them cicadas?
Yeah. Yeah.
Some people call them June bugs.
June bugs are different.
Those are different things.
Those are totally different things.
June bugs are, we got June bugs, buddy.
I thought people called the chirping cicadas
June bugs sometimes.
I've never heard that.
I haven't either.
But there is another name for cicadas.
Maybe I'm thinking of the wrong word.
This is a cicada.
Sleeping beauties.
Yeah, no, I know what a cicada is.
But a June bug is the brown one.
The green and brown thing.
The brown beetles that just fly dumbly
into you. Just straight into you.
Yeah.
Starting around late May.
Really picking up in June.
A cicada and a locust are different things, right?
Locust is what I was thinking of.
But yeah, I think they are slightly different.
Well, locusts are like grasshopper kind of things.
Yeah, June bug is like, that's what I think of
when I think of a June bug.
No, that's like a scarab.
Why is it so green?
They turn green.
They get like shiny.
They're like that and then they're green too.
You used to tie a little string around their leg
and let them fly around like a kite.
Katie did.
It does say that people do call cicadas locusts also.
Anyway, they're loud at night.
They're loud at night.
Tell you what.
I went outside, I said, ooh, my ears are hurting.
Oh, I swear to God.
Oh my God, these bugs are gonna be the death of me.
The death of you?
The death of me.
Oh, okay.
They're so damn loud.
Katie did's are different.
Yeah, Katie did's are like grasshoppers.
Yeah.
Guys, bugs, you know.
Bush crickets.
Do they have bugs everywhere?
Do you guys, send in what bug you think of
when you think of where you live?
I would say cicadas.
I am sick of this.
We have plenty of role-playing to get into
and I refuse to not play this story for any longer.
Hell yeah, let's do it.
Okay.
Sorry to break it to you, Zach,
but we're on podcast strike.
Oh, no.
Actually, we don't write any of it,
so you should be on strike.
The writers, the directors, they folded.
The actors, we're the actors.
We're actors.
Well, I didn't write anything for this,
so we'll see what happens.
Yeah, but we're not gonna play it.
Give us something.
What do you want?
Like, get us new La Croixs.
Rejected!
Oh, no, I can do that.
We got them, boys.
They folded so fast.
Did you guys hear that the warden threw a party
in the county jail?
Warden threw a party in the county jail.
And the prison's band was there and they began to wail.
Let's rock, guys.
Let's jailhouse rock.
Yeah, let's jailhouse rock.
Let's dive in.
You guys are at the jail.
We see Cal Colorado on these big concrete steps,
hands out as if they're in cuffs,
and he is giving a hell of an intro to Beck Wilder
who is filming.
Standing behind, we have Julius Summers.
Some people call it a prison industrial complex.
Some people call it justice.
We're going behind bars tonight to find out the truth.
Stevie walks up and is like,
wow, you really nailed it, and hands you a towel.
It is midday, probably afternoon at this point here,
on Thursday, July 7th, 2022.
Brought to you by Insert Sparkling Water.
Belvie.
Not unless they pay us.
Oh, wow.
That's my favorite part of that.
They said it was painful at the end.
It wasn't, it felt good.
It felt good, it hurt real good.
What is the date?
I was waiting to open this until you stopped talking
and I didn't pay attention.
It's Thursday, July 7th.
It's mid-afternoon, which is when the sun is beating down
at its hottest stand.
The four of you are outside of the city jail.
Is it a jail or a prison?
It is a jail, it is the city jail.
It is where folks are kept for short stints
or just before their trial if they're not out on bond.
That reminds me, did we figure out definitively
if she is just awaiting trial or has she been sentenced?
That is correct, she is awaiting trial.
Well, let's go in.
What do we wanna ask her?
I figured we would just make it up as we went along.
I say we get a feel for her immediately,
see if she's lost it or if she's with us.
We wanna know more specifically about
like why her roommate tried to get inside her
because we think that might be connected.
And I think, you know, reviewing the footage,
maybe ask about the beer itself.
It seemed that she was the one making it
and that is what set her friend off.
Yeah.
Do we need a quick overview for the listeners?
I mean the viewers, the Kaylee situation.
Well, she was drinking a beer, talking to her friend
and then her friend attacked her and then she killed her.
Specifically saying things like, I gotta get inside you,
I'm gonna rip you apart, I want in.
Yeah, diving for her stomach.
And then she called City Action News
to get to the bottom of it.
She trusted you, Cal.
And here we are, we're here to help.
Let's go.
Okay, yeah, cause Dr. Murray said something about
people trying to get inside or even like
getting inside other people at the zeitgeist.
Right, it's all connected.
Okay, wow.
Potentially.
Haven't you been watching the news?
You walk into the city jail and it is a large
en, en, en, en, enchants, foyer?
There's a large foyer.
Wow, that's a great foyer in this jail.
Big columns, big concrete columns.
I like that you tried to French up entrance.
Cause we were just listening to that episode
where we talked about the city's cage inheritance.
Oh, and then you walk into the entrance.
Now what?
And yeah, it's like the,
I think it might've been a bank in the matrix
where there's a big shootout in,
big columns lining either side.
And then at the far end, away from you,
you see that there is a man in uniform.
Ooh, la la.
Zach, what do you think jail is?
What, so far?
So far it's pretty cool.
I know that the architecture should be sad and oppressive,
which is what I'm going for with the concrete
and the big blocks and-
We passed by the arcade, but it says closed.
So saddest thing I've ever seen.
Beck, get a shot of that.
Zoom in on the out of order sign on all the machines.
At the end of this foyer, there is a wall
and part of the wall is this thick glass
and behind is this man in uniform, ooh, la la.
And he just looks up at you, his face is like red.
We're here to see Kaylee Silver.
Beck just holds up his lanyard that has the press.
Yeah. Lanyard on it.
Oh yeah, you guys recalled earlier, yeah.
Oh yeah, I remember you.
Yeah, you see it's Officer Peeler.
Name's Stu, and you guys are coming in for a story or?
Could you just go get him, yeah.
Oh, I have to wait until it's rung in.
I figured we could just chat.
Zach is making a truly horrible face
to voice this character.
It's good, feels fine.
Yeah, we're just here to do a story.
We're doing some investigating.
Cool, I love the news.
You guys are, you guys do the truth,
telling the people what we've been up to.
It's like makes them know how real it really is, you know?
Do you have any bad stories about this place?
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
Like what?
I ordered a sandwich from lunch today,
and it didn't have pickles on it.
Oh.
And who makes the sandwiches?
Jimmy John's.
Well, you know, freaky fast.
Sometimes pickles get lost in the mix.
Yeah, we gotta see things from other people.
Oh, they're ready.
As we file past,
Cal like discreetly places a tube of like hemorrhoid cream
on his counter and gives him the finger guns and winks.
And he's like, this should help.
I thought it was gonna be pickles.
Just in case my pocket pickles.
You can't just give your pocket pickles to any fucking-
Yeah, I would never give this man my pocket pickles.
Random stew on the street.
He buzzes you in through the door.
The first one's ready for you.
And as you head in,
you see that there is a metal detector.
Does anyone have anything
that they need to take out of their pockets?
Beck probably does,
as far as just having a lot of shit in his pockets,
but he's not gonna.
He just is carrying his equipment through there.
It's gonna buzz.
Everybody knows it.
God.
Yeah, I guess Cal takes off a watch
and he puts it like in Beck's like,
do you have a vest with like a bunch of pockets?
Yeah, I put it in one of those pockets
and maybe my smartphone.
And I'm like, actually you can just keep holding
onto this Beck.
Yeah, for sure.
Officer Peeler comes out the back kind of side door
to this room and he's like,
you're gonna have to give me the old wand
down on all this, okay?
And then takes a wand and starts beeping.
As he's doing this,
Julius just walks through the metal detector
and tries to like act nonchalant.
Does it crazy go off?
It goes off.
Yeah, roll stuff I guess.
We already established
that we're just sending Beck through.
And making him deal with it.
You could have given him your guns.
I got a seven, it's a pass.
Oh, I was thinking D and D rolls.
I've been listening to too many other podcasts.
Julius makes a seven.
You idiot.
Julius just kind of makes this high pitched screeching sound
as he does it.
Amazing.
Oh yeah, he always just makes that sound.
Sorry, when I get excited, I make that sound
and I'm excited, we're about to do a good interview.
So what did we sneak through here?
I have my guns on me.
Yeah, I thought those might've just gotten through.
And Julius went ahead and did a little shovel action
just down the side of his pants.
And it's like sticking up into his armpit.
Shovel action meaning you shove the shovel down your pants?
You have the shovel like on your hip
going up your side into your armpit?
Down to like my ankle, under my pants
and going up in and the handle is like
kind of up in his armpit.
You should do it the other way around.
Yeah, I think if you have the shovel under your armpit
against your body.
You turn around on the other side of the medical detector
and you're just like shuffling with something.
He's fixing it.
Taking your pants half off.
So he's got both his guns and Dr. Brock Hargrave's shovel.
Okay, well, you did pass that check.
So you slide on through and...
Beck doesn't have anything that's actually
like guns or anything,
but he does probably have a pocket knife
and he's got pliers and scissors
and just equipment that you would have
to set up a shot somewhere.
Beck has six Leathermans on him at any given moment.
Okay, well, Officer Peeler didn't do a very good job
checking you.
So he's just beeping the wand around.
It keeps beeping.
He's like, equipment, equipment, equipment.
Yeah, he's gonna beep, like you said.
Mr. Colorado, come on through.
Would you like to wand a celebrity?
Come on in here.
Okay.
And when you walk through, does it go off?
No.
Okay, so he goes up with a wand
and then as he's about to, he's like,
there's no need, I guess.
Beck, can I have my watch back?
Yeah, of course.
Thank you.
It was a spy watch, die, Officer Peeler.
So it was this room?
Yeah, if you go in there and you'll just wait
and then you'll see the line, they'll take you to it.
And as he opens the door for you,
you see a line of tape on the ground
that kind of leads you.
I thought there was a bunch of people here to see.
I was like, fuck.
Kaylee's quite popular.
Julius was following the line of tape?
Follow the line of tape.
You go through a room, out the other side, down a hallway.
Beck's getting footage of this walk.
Interesting, yeah.
It's just the boring inside of the city jail.
Nothing juicy, nothing too interesting.
All just the same sort of oppressive, bland design
and architecture.
You see a painting on a wall in a hallway
and even though it is this oasis
in a desert of horrible vibes,
something about the painting is still just manufactured.
Run of the mill.
It makes it worse almost.
Hotel art.
Yeah, exactly.
That's a nice painting.
Now Cal has taste.
For a jail.
The line eventually leads you to a room.
One wall is made up of little cubicle type spaces
with glass.
So there's six different spots that you can sit at
where an inmate would come from the other side,
sit at a chair, grab the phone that is right next to it,
pick it up and talk to you on the other side.
On this side, there is an old school speakerphone
sitting just in the middle of each table
and so no phone on your side because there's more of you
and it's a role playing game that makes it easier.
And as you walk into this room,
Kaylee Silver is being walked down a long hallway
on the other side and she looks rough.
Her sandy blonde hair is darker than it was
the last time you saw her a few weeks ago.
Space buns are actually still up,
still rocking the same dew
but it's messy buns on the other side,
flyaways and just like stray hairs.
They let her have hair ties in prison.
No, it's actually tied in itself.
It's like a self-tied knot.
I think I asked this the first time, are space buns Leia?
Yes, similar, yeah.
It's just a little buns on top of your head.
Now that they're like wrapped into themselves,
it's more like she just has two like dark dirty blonde knots
tied on top of her head that are flopping about.
Oh, have you had the dirty blonde knots at Big Slice?
They are garlicky.
And there is a distance in her eyes
as she walks up and sits down.
Everybody roll alertness.
Pass.
Fail.
Luke, Julius notices that Kaylee's nostrils are flaring.
Kaylee, do you remember us?
Her eyes get really big and she picks up the phone.
We're here to help.
I just want to let you know, we're here to help.
Mr. Colorado, Mr. Colorado, Mr. Colorado is here.
Oh, okay, that's who it is.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Okay, okay, everything's gonna be fine
because Mr. Colorado's here.
Everything's gonna be fine, Kaylee,
because Mr. Colorado's here and everybody's here
and everything's gonna be fine
because I can smell it again.
Oh, I can smell it again.
And she starts rubbing her face
and she looks at you, just really, really massive eyes.
Kaylee, Kaylee.
Mr. Colorado.
That's right, you're here live with Mr. Colorado.
Mr. Colorado is here, you're gonna help me,
you're gonna help me, you're gonna help me.
What do you smell?
It's only gotten worse.
Kaylee, Kaylee, I want the smell.
And she slams her face kind of up against the glass
and then rubs it along the side
until she makes it to the edge.
And even though there's cock along the edge,
she's just like trying to get her nostrils
as close to that corner as possible
and just ripping inhales through her nasal cavity.
And she's like, it smells, it smells like it.
It smells like the view.
Smells like when she,
it just smells like when she tried to get into me.
Excuse us.
It smells like when she was in me.
Excuse us for just a moment.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
It smells like when she was in me.
Ah, ah.
We're gonna step away for just a moment, Ms. Silver.
We'll be right back with you.
You can hear just repeating herself over and over.
Can we film this?
I already have been.
You're looking at Beck.
Beck's just holding the camera.
I've got a microphone that's like set up
in front of that little speaker
and the tripod's already out.
He wasn't asking like, should we?
He's asking.
Did Stevie come in with us?
Yeah.
Okay, who has the back?
Stevie slowly opens the bag and like immediately-
What the, Stevie.
Kaylee's feet hop up onto the counter,
like where the other side is.
And then her CO comes over and just like grabs her
and you just hear them kind of arguing
over the phone a little bit.
Stevie, why don't you, fuck.
Stevie, give us a moment.
And we step in for a little bit further.
Yeah.
We can't send Stevie out of here with the bag.
The last time we let them out of our sight,
they took off with their brother.
That's right.
I love Stevie.
They're the best damn intern Cairns had in years,
but they've still got to prove themselves.
I don't trust Stevie yet.
Not where their brother is concerned.
But this bag, we can't have this bag in the same room
as Kaylee and get anything out of her.
That's pretty clear.
I don't know, we haven't even tried.
We just tried.
Nobody asked her anything.
Nobody's even spoken to her yet.
Yes, I tried to speak to her.
She went insane.
What are you-
What are you talking about?
Pearl grip.
I didn't even give her a chance.
That's how everybody is when you start a conversation.
I think we should ask her if she knows what this is.
Stevie opened it from over here
and she went, Eepy, over there.
Stevie had it in their pocket.
Hey, Kaylee, what are you smelling?
She's screaming and being constrained.
Yeah, she's still like going ham.
Julius asks anyway.
He asks it again.
Hey, let her go.
What are you smelling here?
They can't hear you.
They just let her go.
Like the phone is how you communicate with them
and the phone is currently like hanging from the cord.
Julius knocks on the glass.
Kaylee like has a hand of against the glass
where you're knocking and is all smiles
and so she grabs the phone and holds it up.
What are you smelling there?
You brought it, you brought it, can I have it?
What did we bring?
What is it you want?
Have you seen it before?
It smells like when she was inside me.
Julius goes to grab the Ziploc bag.
Whoa, okay.
And pulls it out.
As you grab it, Kaylee is like once again
just losing their mind.
But they keep it under control
and sit down and start to breathe really strongly.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
Julius is just looking at Beck and Cal.
Somebody asked her, was this an ingredient she used?
That smells like forever.
It smells like it.
Did you use this in the beer that you brewed?
It tastes, yeah, yeah.
Where did you find it?
Where'd you get it?
Yeah, where'd you get it, Kaylee?
The what?
The ingredient.
This.
Oh, it was America's American Nail Dry Yeast.
America's American Nail Dry Yeast.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, is that what you have?
Is that what you have?
Did you make beer?
Did you make some beer?
Can you bring it?
And they turned to their CEO.
Can I drink beer?
Can I have it?
If they give me some, can I have it?
Oh.
You guys, she wasn't like this when we last talked to her.
Do you think she could have been re-exposed or something?
Or maybe she's like, fiending for it.
Oh, right.
She's been having like a steady supply and it got cut off.
Or you just have to even have it once
and then this is you now.
Kaylee, which one of those things we just said?
Haven't had it.
Haven't had it, want it.
How many times did you have it?
Last time I had it, she got in me and I got her out
and then I had to kill her.
I had to kill her.
She got in you?
She got in me.
Yeah, she got in me, she got in me, she got in me.
I've been thinking about it.
I've been thinking about it so much.
I don't think that I thought about it when it was happening
but she was in me, she was in me.
What do you mean by in you?
It was crazy, she was like, have we in me?
It was crazy, I have to pull her out completely.
She was gonna be in me and then I had to pull her out
and then she was out and then I had to kill her
because she was gonna go back in.
She was gonna go back in, she was trying to get back in.
She wasn't her, it wasn't her.
I saw it in her eyes, it wasn't her.
Yeah, we saw that video and it was self-defense, you're okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
But you're saying that maybe there was a little more?
Can I have that, can I have that?
Can I have it, can I have it?
Do you want to get inside?
Do you want to get inside me?
Oh, this is not that kind of show.
Not what I meant, not what I meant.
Just, you know.
Was that the first batch that you'd brewed
with that America's American Ale dry yeast?
Yeah, yeah, didn't even get to try it.
What made you decide to go with that brand?
New brand, new brand.
New brand from where?
New brand, just got online.
Where online?
Julius Googles immediately, America's American whatever,
what is it, America's American all dry yeast.
America's American Ale dry yeast.
America's American Ale dry yeasts.
Where did you get it, Kaylee?
Where online?
I don't remember.
Julius Googles it.
If you must.
When you Google it, guess who sells it.
Godel.
Play-Doh.
So Godel?
Yeah, the Godel company.
I didn't guess very good, I'm sorry.
Oh my, look, guys, look at this.
Fucking Godel.
Holy shit, it is connected.
Oh yeah.
Stevie, do you know anything about it?
Stevie, they're putting forever in the yeast.
What?
We need to find out how many people ordered this yeast.
Maybe it was an accident.
Maybe it's like at the factory,
whatever this stuff is got mixed in with the yeast.
Joe, can you roll a grip for me?
Fail.
Number one grip.
How many letters are in Americas?
Oh my God.
Damn it.
Eight.
How many letters are in American?
How many in Ale?
Three.
Dry?
And six.
Yeasts.
Eight, eight, three, three, six?
Oh, that's kind of weird.
I mean, maybe not even.
I'm sorry, it's yeast's plural?
It is.
Well, I don't think,
I think the plural of yeast is yeast.
Yeast die.
That's even weirder.
We've got-
It's an apostrophe S.
Okay.
Cal-roll-crip.
In this shot for the audience,
this conversation's going along
and Beck is counting on his fingers
and then looking up at the sky
and he goes back to his fingers
and then he just starts staring dead ahead.
It's the fucking numbers, guys.
They're here again.
Time for another visit from the numbers.
Oh, God damn it.
Beck's got the numbers in him.
Beck, Beck, calm down.
America's eight.
American, eight.
Ale, three.
Dry, three.
And yeast is six.
That's what I'm telling you.
Why would it be yeast?
It should be yeast.
Five.
They must've made it so it would be six.
Oh my God.
That's just lazy, Julius.
Julius is Googling-
Come up with a different word.
America's American ale dry yeasts Reddit
and looking on the brewing, home brewing subreddit
to see if anybody's mentioned it.
Beck is, during his diatribe,
gonna look at Kaylee, grab the phone
and say, eight, three, six, eight, three, six.
You're just picking up the speakerphone
and like yelling into it.
Computer, eight, three, six, eight, three, six.
Oh yeah, Kaylee.
You lived in apartment, eight, three, six.
Why are you saying my apartment number?
What led you to choose that particular apartment?
I don't know.
It was just a sign to me?
I guess-
Assigned to you.
Assigned to you, whatever do you mean?
I guess it was just like the landlord put me there.
Oh, well that makes sense.
When's your birthday?
August 36th.
Whoa!
Beck starts to slam his head in the glass from this side.
What's your birthday?
I mean, I don't know what else to ask her.
I think we need to track this down.
Who is your landlord?
Yeah, who owns your building?
Is it the Godel Corp?
Julius, use your devil box to look that up.
He Googles Godel Corp apartments.
City County Assessors.
Did you mean the Godel Company?
I look up the Godel Company, what do they own?
Land.
Have you Googled anything before?
That's just as quick as he can type.
He's just keywords, keywords.
Role of computer science or accounting?
Fail.
OK.
Surprisingly, that doesn't come up
with any helpful information.
No, I don't know.
Try the City Assessor's Office.
Here it is.
The Godels have bought just like wild amounts of land
just under the name the Godel Company.
And you can imagine that they must own even more.
Shells within shells.
It's turtle mares all the way down.
Whoa.
And the building Kaylee Silver lived in
is owned by the Godel Company.
Son of a bitch.
I'm talking not to the speaker now.
And in fact, trying to maybe get away
from the speaker a little bit
and just talk to the guys and Stevie.
You guys think maybe the Godel Corporation.
Company?
The Godel Company was conducting
like a specific experiment on her
and maybe this American yeast or whatever
was delivered only to her.
Yeah, what if they implanted an ad on her social media?
I wouldn't put that above the Godel Corp.
Company, yeah, I wouldn't either.
We all hate the Godel Corp.
Yeah, we all hate the Godel Company.
Godel Co.
What happens if I try to,
if I try to go order.
Paration.
If I try to order some of the yeast,
does it, is it sold out or does it let me get it?
Yeah, you can order some.
Where'd you order it to?
Your home or the jail?
The can offices.
Okay, speedy delivery.
Yeast for you, sir.
Yeasts.
Guys, I went ahead and got some.
I'm not sure that we like want to test it, but.
That's worth a shot.
I mean, we, yeah.
We know that now that she was assigned this apartment
by the Godel Corp.
It's Godel Corp branded yeast.
Yeah, Godel Company for sure.
And we know that this horrific event took place
after using it.
We haven't really heard about that happening elsewhere.
Right?
Stevie, does Godel make the products like in the gorge?
Yeah, they do now.
Fuck.
I think we got to go back.
Well, eventually for like a climactic conclusion,
but not before we get an army of rat boys from your dad.
I mean, is there anything else we want to ask her?
836.
What?
No, no, no.
Kaylee, were you a home brewer before this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Pretty, pretty avid, huh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Had you bought from the Godel Corp?
No.
No, what led you to buy from them?
There's an ad.
An ad on?
Instagram.
On Instagram.
Oh, those can be persuasive.
You know, Kaylee, I recently went digitally clean.
Bragged.
Well, yes, it is a brag because I'm living
a happier, healthier lifestyle
and everybody should emulate this.
But, but no, before that, I.
Are you gonna help me?
Yes, Kaylee.
You know, I bet they don't give you a phone in here.
That's half the battle already,
but we are gonna get to the bottom of this
and we're gonna make sure what happened to you
doesn't happen to anybody else again.
Okay, but are you gonna help me?
I'm gonna die in here.
The evidence that you have, I think,
once you go to trial will exonerate you.
Yeah, when is your trial date?
I pushed it back, said a roll went wrong or something,
but it's in two weeks.
Can you make it in here for two weeks?
We're gonna see if you could, is there any way, hey,
is there any way that you can send some of that in
even if it's just a little bit like the residue on a letter
and maybe just like rub it on the letter
and then send the letter in just so I can spell it again?
No, Kaylee, we're not allowed to make the news.
We can only investigate.
We can't really interfere.
I can't materially support the suspect of a murder
even though I believe her to be innocent, do you understand?
Otherwise it would question my impartiality.
But in two weeks you'll get exonerated,
you'll get out of here
and you're gonna have all of it that you want.
No one's gonna believe them when I tell them
Kaylee Silver's innocent
if I've also been sending Kaylee Silver gift packages.
She slams her hand against her thigh.
Ah, shucks.
Oh, shucks, okay.
And you can tell that with everything in her body
she wanted to release, she wanted to scream,
she wanted to slam her head repeatedly
into that glass right in your face.
She wanted to lose control but she held on,
she held it together and she smiles.
Thank you, please help me.
We'll do what we can, Kaylee.
Stay safe in here,
you don't have much longer to have to put up with it.
Do you know Burl Summers?
Julius kind of waves, Julius like waves over
at the correctional officer.
The CEO comes over, grabs the phone.
You done?
Yeah, I believe we're done with Kaylee
and I think we had a private room to meet with Burl.
That's right, follow the green line.
Green line?
So you follow the green tape heading down the corridor,
similar corridors, this one's a much closer trek.
Julius is walking very stiffly,
like one side of his body at a time
because he's got the shovel stuck up his pants and shirt.
Julius, have you thought about like what you're gonna,
you know, say?
Well, I brought this and he like points at the imprint
of a shovel in his clothes.
Yeah, I was wondering why.
Yeah, well.
You didn't want to kill your dad.
No, he's a smart guy and I think
if I give him a tool, he'll figure out what to do.
Oh, he could dig out.
You're not gonna beat him to death with no.
No, I'm trying to get him out of here.
Gotcha.
Anyway, I'm gonna say hi,
tell him what I've been up to since I saw him last
and then tell him I might not ever see you again.
I give him the shovel and say, you can get out of here
but you gotta tell us about the rat man first.
That's right, thank you.
Do you mind if I film?
100% go for it.
He loves cameras.
Before I even met him, I knew he loved camera and shit.
I actually wanted to talk to you about that.
Do you think?
I don't know.
It just seems like he has an eye for photojournalism.
I mean, if we can find a way to get him out of here,
I guarantee it.
He'd be the second best camera man Ken's ever seen.
Close one.
But I mean, we gotta get him out of here first.
I don't even know if we can.
And here is the room that you're now in,
this private room.
There is a...
Shrimp cocktail.
One of those city things.
It says out of order.
Cow's nibbling on it.
Wait, what?
It says out of order on the shrimp cocktail?
Right, it's like the arcade.
It's a joke, it's a joke.
It's like they have nice things but they can't use them.
Cow's eating it.
Also, it's broken.
Yeah, it's rotten.
It's not.
It says out of order but this is really good.
Roll a constitution.
A 60 and a 60.
Wow.
Cow like stops for a second.
It's good.
The camera Fast and Furious style,
like through Cow's body as if it's the inside
of a car engine.
We see different pistons firing
and the nitrous is about to take off
and explode into a blue and orange flame of ignition.
And then we see that the stomach acids come in
and put out the flames of this intense reaction
that was about to happen inside of Cow's body.
And there's like a little beach with umbrellas
and the shrimp are like partying on it.
But two of them are swimming
without any sort of flotation device,
which in the lifeguard's opinion is totally out of order.
They're shrimp, they're from the water.
The lifeguard would live in his stomach
and so therefore it would want the shrimp
to drown in his stomach.
None of this matters.
They got drowned by the stomach acid and dissolved.
Cow yells to the voices in his head.
What?
No, I said that.
You shouldn't eat those.
Probably not.
I think it's giving me weird ideas.
The door opens and a tall stringy man walks in
with stringy hair and he has handcuffs on
and I mean immediately the CEO is like.
No touching. No touching, yeah.
He's like, do this like hugs for a little bit
and then backs off.
Hey, let me just hook him up real quick to the table
and you see that he's gonna lock him in his handcuffs
to a spot on the table and Burl Summers sits down.
He's got stringy hair and you see three long singular
strands of hair coming down from his chin.
Oh, look, it's even better than the last time I saw ya.
It's way longer and it's only been like a month.
Thank you, Julius.
Are you doing okay in here?
Doing all right.
I didn't expect to see you.
Well, I didn't expect to see you either really
but since I've seen ya, I got reassigned
and I'm on the news now or I work with the news
and we're investigating some pretty mild shit for you
but it's pretty wild to me.
Reassigned?
Yeah, I'm with Diggory now.
Agent Diggory?
This is like my first thing.
They didn't give me a break at all.
Have you followed up with anybody else?
I think I'm the only one that got out.
Is Diggory keeping the path?
For now.
And both of you make eyes a little narrowed
at each other like Luke and I just did.
But, I mean, if I'm honest, I'm kind of with these guys now.
Beck waves from behind the camera.
Cal Colorado sticks a microphone in his face
and he's like, Cal Colorado, City Action News.
How do you like jail?
It's not the best or worst place I've ever been.
Remember the fog?
Yeah, this is way better.
Your son has an emotional goodbye to say to you.
I mean, I guess we better make it quick.
Officer, and he just like holds up his press pass.
Could you give us a minute?
Rolled bureaucracy or law?
That's a 57 on a 60.
Which one do you have 60 in?
Bureaucracy.
Nice.
For being in the firm for you so, you know.
Why would I do that?
Cal, tell him.
The news?
And Beck is holding up his press pass as well.
Yeah, so is Cal.
The CEO just kind of has this look
of befuddlement on his face.
So does Cal.
But with, you know, three confident Stevie holds up
their pass behind you, four confident adults,
telling them how things work.
He's like, I need to read the fucking rules again.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, and Stevie's his lawyer.
Nice.
That'll do it.
And he nods his head, dips out of the room.
Cal, that was great.
I just wanted you to say the news.
But that last thing was even better.
Give him the shovel quick.
I don't think this will work long.
Here, I got a shovel in case you want to like dig yourself
out or something.
I don't know.
And then here's a gun.
You can have that too.
And then, so basically we found.
Keep one of the guns for us.
Oh yeah, I got two.
I'm keeping one, sorry.
We found out Godel company is really bad.
Like our level bad.
Like really bad, dude.
Like maybe shit we haven't ever seen before bad.
Except maybe shit you've seen before maybe.
Yeah, but like this is crazier in a different way
instead of like, you got to kill it.
This is a, you know, big thing.
It's true, sir.
They're bad.
Okay, well, if it goes all the way to the top.
All the way.
Well, you got to get me out of here.
Can you do anything about these handcuffs?
Julius like looks over where the officer went.
And if he's not looking, he just takes a shovel
and slams it onto the chains.
Julius, when you grab this shovel and slam it
just a single time on the chain of this restraint,
sparks fly off either side.
And suddenly Burl Sommers is loosed.
He grabs the gun on the table and immediately.
Beck holds up his hands.
Cal catches the camera.
He drops the clip out the bottom of it,
flicks one of the bullets up in the air off it,
grabs it, slams in the bottom of the clip
and then slams the clip back in the bottom of the gun
and Beck I got that.
Julius looks.
That was so cool.
Julius looks at the restraint.
He thought this was going to be multiple batches
to even possibly work.
And he looks down at the concrete
and looks at Cal and Beck and looks at his dad
and just shoves the shovel down into the ground.
When you shovel the shovel,
when you shove the shovel into the ground,
it moves through the sealed concrete
like the most fertile land
and you just shovel out part of the flooring.
Holy shit.
Everybody roll grip.
55, critical failure.
96, which I think is real bad.
50, but a fail.
So did you both crit fail?
I crit fail you.
Is a 96 a crit fail?
Oh yeah, holy shit.
I mean, this isn't the wildest thing
after having seen what you've seen,
heard what you've heard.
It's also a shovel digging.
It is a shovel digging,
but it is a shovel digging at a wild.
Through concrete like sand.
Yeah.
So Beck is going to lose one grip.
Julius and Cal, you're both going to lose two grip.
Julius pulls the shovel up and kind of like fake lunges
at Beck and laughs and then starts digging again.
Julius, my dude, that wasn't cool.
It was a joke.
All right, you got me.
Julius, everyone is laughing after a joke.
Julius looks at his dad,
like, what did he think of that?
Your dad is not in the room.
The door is open and you see a slumped body
of the CEO in the doorway.
What is, what the hell is wrong with us?
Are you fucking, I mean, yeah, come on.
Okay, Julius offers a gun to Beck
or offers him the shovel.
Oh, I'll take the shovel, dude.
Julius has the gun and is going to run after his dad.
Whoa.
Okay, Cal's going to motion for Beck to stay back a second.
All right, Luke, leave the room.
Oh my God, what the fuck.
Beck is holding the shovel like American Gothic
and the camera's under, cradling under an arm.
What the fuck, dude?
Are we accessories to this?
All right, that's all on them, right?
We didn't, did we abet this?
No, and it's, no, I mean.
We're just documenting the news.
We just filmed what happened.
We didn't happen it.
We're bringing a human experience, a jailbreak,
to, oh God, he gave him the gun.
He gave him the gun back, then he killed that guy.
Oh Jesus, oh Jesus, oh Jesus.
And Beck wants to throw the shovel to the ground.
Does it do anything when he hits the ground?
It burrows.
Keeps burrowing, zooms out the other side of the earth.
It doesn't keep burrowing, but it does just like,
if you throw it into the ground, it's like.
It sticks like a knife in the table.
Exactly, like both of those things.
Oh, what happened to the shovel?
I mean, this is a whole fucking new thing.
We didn't even have time to address it.
The shovel's a fucking magic shovel.
He always had this fucking shovel, you know.
Like, I've seen the shovel.
It didn't used to do this.
Oh shit, I don't fucking.
Wait, is that true?
I ad-libbed that, but does that need to not be true?
No, it's fine.
I mean, even if it did do that,
maybe he didn't show you that it did that.
I'm imagining him like banging his shovel
on shit at dinner parties, like New Year's Eve.
Oh, well, I mean, yeah, he could turn it on and off.
Okay, I'm gonna get in front of the camera
and I'm gonna state that we don't condone these actions,
but we're here to document this unique.
We're silent observers and we cannot interfere.
Exactly.
I'd pull up the camera and get it on you
and the shovel is laying on the ground
in the background of the shot.
This is Cal, Colorado.
Explosive development here at the city jail.
Our, a can, oh, how do I say this?
Stevie, you're the lawyer.
Stevie rolls their eyes bigger than eyes have been rolled.
How do I phrase this thing?
But you can't see because the hair is covering it.
We've just witnessed something extraordinary here.
Something, something possibly,
oh God, I can't call it extraordinary.
It could be like extraordinarily a thing that happened.
Yeah, like a miracle.
No, that's, that's what we don't want to apply.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't want to give it a good connotation exactly.
He's, cause that, Stevie, could you go check on that guard?
Stevie's just making these noises as they go over.
Slowly check on the guard.
First they, they did a check.
They were not sure whether the body was breathing
and then they did successfully do first aid on it.
So if, if, if they're alive, they're stable.
Oh, thank God.
Okay, so he didn't kill anybody.
Yeah.
We would have heard the gunshot.
Maybe, well yeah, they didn't get shot.
He hasn't killed anybody yet.
Okay, this is Cal, Colorado.
Full disclosure, a CAN associate who will at this time
remain anonymous has, has gone rogue
in the middle of an assignment
and broken their father out of jail
or is actively attempting to flee prison jail
with their father.
We don't condone these actions,
but we will document them for you, the people of the city.
Let's go back.
Camera goes down and Beck wants to go back
and carefully pick up the shovel.
I think, I don't think we should leave this behind.
No, we, that's, we need the shovel, yeah.
I'll take it.
Sure.
Okay.
That's kind of your thing, you carry things.
Yeah.
And with everything else, Stevie pack mules the shovel
under an arm, you know, with plenty of bag, a toe.
Careful with the end of that thing, man.
I don't really understand, like.
And as you say that, there's a glint on the end
of the shovel that you've seen a few times at this point.
Stevie, be careful with that end.
Well, yeah, obviously.
And they turn it like sticks into a wall.
No, it's not that, I mean, you threw it, you know,
with a little bit of force in the ground earlier.
That's why it stuck.
But you've like carried it around.
You've set it down on stuff.
You do think back to all the times.
Beck, you juggled it.
You almost.
I balanced it on the end of my nose.
With the back of the stuff.
No.
Is this all gonna be part of the story?
That's the great thing about journalism, Stevie.
Editing.
Yeah.
Well, editing and we don't know what the story is yet.
It's still happening.
Choosing what the story is after the fact.
I mean, sorta, yeah.
Like this could be a hero moment
if it all shakes out the way we want it to.
Sure.
Do you wanna do another take?
Like maybe Julius is the hero?
If that's like maybe a possibility.
I don't expect that would be a possibility.
Didn't he say a second ago that like the Godels were bad
and then he looked at his dad and he said,
like just as bad as the stuff we used to do.
Did he say that?
No, no, I thought he meant like.
I took that into meaning like the stuff
that they investigated.
Yes, exactly.
Meeting the criteria for their organization addressing it.
Remember their X-Files.
Yeah, that's right.
That's a much better read.
I like that.
I'll go with that.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Yeah, let's go.
I guess we just follow the trail of bodies.
Well, we've only found, we just have a body so far.
No, yeah, for sure.
There's just one body.
I'm just worried there's gonna be more.
And he's stable.
He's stable.
No, for sure.
And we could even call an ambulance for him
once we get out of here.
Well, we can, we should call an ambulance.
Stevie, call an ambulance for him right now.
I wanna say that like alarms start going off,
but I don't know that's true.
Right, maybe they've killed everyone in the prison
by the time they're killed.
Or maybe they just patiently waited around the corner.
What?
They're just sitting there.
They're taking him so long.
They're listening to us.
They're like giggling to each other about it.
Okay, you want us to get Luke?
Yeah.
All right.
But we are, we are leaving.
We are following where they were going.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, cool.
You guys leave the room.
Now leave the room.
This is LARPing.
Tonight there's gonna be a jailbreak.
I didn't know that there was gonna be a jailbreak.
So.
So Luke, this is fucking awesome and wild.
Julius runs out of the room.
You run out of the room.
You run past this body and you see.
Is the body shot or?
Not shot.
You didn't hear it.
Incapacitated.
Currently incapacitated on the ground.
Julius thinks about how cool that is
and tries to really think about the training
his dad gave him.
And you see that dad,
Pearl Summers, stringy man,
stringy hair blowing behind him
as he is dipping down this hallway.
Makes it almost to a door
and then you see him crouch down at the last second.
The door opens and he flings his stringy body
up into the air,
wraps one of his legs around the security officer's neck
and then spins this officer down to the ground.
The officer is not moving
and Pearl looks back down the hallway and sees you
and turns and runs through the open door.
Julius does like a little jump kick like kick ass
and then runs to try to catch up with his dad.
Just vaults the dead body.
Roll athletics.
Your dad succeeds.
I succeed 20 on a 70.
You're both hoofing it, hoofing it.
Is this the way out?
Do you know how to get out of here?
Yeah, I've been planning this.
Let's go.
Fuck yes.
Wait, pause.
He holds you back against a corner
and you see officers walk just around the opposite corner
and then away from you down the hallway
and then they turn right and go out a door.
They were five feet away from you.
You see that happening in your brain
as you hear these officers approaching
but you're gonna have to pass a stealth roll
in order to make it a reality.
34 on a 40.
Woo!
You still got it.
That was incredible.
Which way do we go?
Where's the shovel?
I gave it to Beck.
And he looks behind him like,
I thought they were gonna be right behind me.
Hey, how would your dad react in this moment?
I'm trying to build your dad's sort of-
To us escaping?
To you not bringing the shovel mid-escape.
If he was planning on using it, he's probably not stoked.
You see the pain in his eyes and he goes, that's okay.
Yeah, no, that's okay.
Did we need it?
I figured you were-
No, it'll be fine.
It'll be fine.
We can go back and get it.
Nope.
Probably fine.
I mean, whatever you think is best,
we've just got to get you out of here.
Okay.
Alive.
I mean, I planned this whole thing without it, so go.
And then he dips around the corner.
Julius falls right after him.
You make it to another hallway
where there's an intersection of hallways.
An intersection of hallways.
People could be coming from either side.
Do you know how to get out of here?
Yeah.
And he points to the left.
Is the left even close to semi the direction
that Julius thinks he came in from?
Roll intelligence.
Crit pass.
Yeah.
That's definitely the way you can-
Okay, if you trust him, hundo P.
He goes, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's this way,
but we have to wait here.
He starts counting.
One, two, three, four-
Julius holds up his watch in front of his dad.
Nice.
Seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16-
Julius is wondering if he's going to count to 836.
When it gets to 400, you continue that thought.
When it gets to 800, you're like, oh shit.
Is this really happening?
829, 830, 831, 832, 833, 834, 835, 836.
And he grabs you.
What does it mean?
And starts dipping down the hallway and runs.
Roll grip.
Crit fail.
What does it mean?
Shut the fuck up.
And immediately alarms go off.
Fuck.
You see doors in the corridor on either side of you
with windows that are interior
and all their blinds were drawn.
And when you scream blinds on either side of you,
just open.
I'm going to cut back to them.
Okay.
Smells like weed in here.
The alarms start going off.
We were right.
Okay. Yeah.
Probably bodies then.
Okay. Fuck.
We got to get out of here.
We can't be here.
We didn't even fucking ask him about the rat men.
Fuck.
Let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
I guess we'll follow their trail
unless we see an obvious way out.
This is from the camera's point of view,
like the horror movie running.
Oh wait, shouldn't we just-
Oh, do you want to go back the other way?
Yeah, why don't we just go out the front door?
Yeah, we could do that.
I mean, yeah.
We'd learn less, but it's a lot safer.
It's also the way that there might be people to stop us,
whereas they might've cleared the way ahead of them.
That's also true.
They might not just believe that we're not with them.
We could also be-
Because we are with them.
But we could also be like not with them
and be like, help, help.
Something crazy's happening down the hall.
Do you think they're going to believe that
from Cal, Colorado?
Yeah, maybe, maybe.
Can you sell it?
You're right, dammit.
I could sell it.
That's right, Cal.
You could sell anything.
Okay, what do we think?
That's right, you could sell anything.
Julius, or?
What?
Oh, that was a lazy shoe horn.
This is a panic moment, Zach.
That's right, shit, what?
I was not selling you anything
when I told you to believe in yourself, Stevie.
That's nice.
Now, which way do we go, dammit?
When you walk out of this room,
you see the green tape on the ground
that leads past the body that is slumped over
just outside of this room.
Do either one of you have a very high first aid?
No, just the 10 baseline.
Okay, not a clue.
And then when you look down the end of this corridor,
you see that there is another body slumped by that door,
and it is face down and its head is to one side.
Oh, it doesn't hit to one side like broken neck
or just like laying on it?
It could be laying on its stomach
with its head to one side,
could be broken neck with its head like that.
Not sure from here.
Pretty far down there, maybe 20 yards.
But you do know you need to walk
at least like halfway down this hallway
and then go left before you get all the way down
to that next door to go back the way you came at least.
I mean, you know, it's not a bad idea
to link up with like the two guys
who know how to deal with crazy shit.
We gotta go most of the way towards where they're going.
Yeah, let's get to the juncture and-
Let's get to the juncture and then we'll-
Junction and figure it out there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, guys, come on.
To the junction.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Signs are still going off
and you see there are alarms on the walls
every 10 feet or so with lights that are just blinking
and in the distance you do hear
the kind of movement of officers
and as you make it down to the end of this corridor
you see the body on the ground.
If you don't want anyone to roll first aid
as you walk by, go for it.
Wait, Stevie, you were pretty good at this.
Yeah.
Why don't you take a look at them?
They're dead.
Oh, I rolled a 10 on a 10.
Oh, shit.
What do you think, Beck?
Hey, they're dead.
It's not good, my dude.
It's really not good.
That's two deads then.
Yeah, at least one dead for sure,
but yeah, probably two maybe.
I mean, maybe a criminal did it, a different one.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
Have we heard any gunshots?
No.
With that first aid roll,
how did this guy die?
Did he get knocked in the head or?
His neck was snapped.
Gotcha.
Yeah, you were right about the neck snap thing.
That's an awful way to go.
Is it?
I mean, it might be quick.
I don't really know.
Maybe we should take his clothes?
That's the end of the episode.
You can't just give your pocket pickles to any-
Yeah, I would never give this man my pocket pickles.
Random stew on the street.
I'm saving those for my daughter.
Hi ho, silver away.
Everyone loves daddy's pocket pickles.
Oh, okay.
Everyone feel good?
That one made me feel real good.
Not since childhood.
And it's all my fault.