Good morning, y'all.
How are y'all doing out there?
It is December 4th here in contention,
and it's been a jam-packed week here,
so I think it's good to remind y'all
what time it is every now and then.
Speaking of y'all, y'all done wrote me something
to read on the air again against my will.
Here is today's Howlin' with Wolf.
Up.
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Ah.
Ow.
Are you provides?
Ha ha.
Tess said that all you wolf pups out there
would know what that means.
To some of our Canine listeners, y'all already
know the drill to all other species,
I apologize for that small outburst.
Thanks Tess, for making me lose my shit on air.
Now for some mole shit, it's the news.
Officer Bishop learned that the chief's car
had been at the mill on the other side of the city
since the night of December 1st.
The county coroner reports that during the investigation
of an active crime scene, Officer John Lee
Pettymore of contention slipped and shoved
a possible murder weapon into the eye
socket of the deceased Maggie Cook,
fumbling and digging around atrociously
as the charred bones themselves began
to crumble to no longer be a part of the situation.
Also, anyone out there having some fucked up dreams?
Shit, I know I have.
Last night, I was eating cereal in my basement,
but it wasn't like my basement, but it was.
When I looked down, my spoon was made of wet tuna
and the Count Chocula had turned into forgotten memories.
Then I saw my dog, Wolf, and he had my face on his face.
What the fuck is up with that shit?
Well, you know what they say.
Now I'm gonna need y'all to wave your hands in the air
like you just don't care, because in contention,
nihilism reigns supreme and the points don't matter.
It's kudzu with no backbone.
Ah!
Hey guys, howdy.
Ah.
Oh, this is my new character voice.
John's phone rings.
Real quick, roll a constitution check for me.
Pass.
Fail.
Okay, so John, you will get one hit point back
and the other two of you will get a D4.
I was gonna say two D6 would be great.
I rolled a three, I get three back.
Good work, Clark.
That brings me almost to perfect health.
One back, I still am 21 out of 25.
I've got 25 out of 26 hit points.
Well, you guys have insane.
What are you at?
I'm 18 of 20, but 20's my max.
My willpower is at two.
Which means I need a little help from my friend.
Your willpower is at two.
You guys put a lot into con.
I went middle of the road, baby, 50.
John, your phone rings as you're getting ready.
It's Keith Vigna.
I don't answer.
Okay.
I send John a text.
Hey dude, can you bring a little bit of stimulants for me?
I'm having a real off day today.
I text him, I have no idea what the fuck
you're talking about and I put the Shrug Guy emoji in there.
I put two snowflakes and a winky face emoji.
I send back all caps,
I don't know what you're talking about, angry face.
I send back, bring me something
where I will explicitly text it to you.
I don't reply.
God dammit.
Okay, I drive to John's house then.
Oh, oh god.
Damn, I'm already on the way to work.
I mean, you can resolve it if you want.
What's the timeline?
Does he come to my house or?
Keith, do you leave early enough to like?
Yeah, I do.
I get up and I put my clothes on
and I drive out there and I'm pissed.
I just woke up mad.
Okay, I'm gonna have you roll luck at a negative 20
to see if John is still there.
He's not.
I'm gonna break into his house though.
It.
I'm desperate.
So instead of getting some five hour energy.
That's not gonna.
You're gonna break into your coworker's house
and steal cocaine.
Yeah, because that's my only option right now.
He told me that that's.
I did not say that cocaine was your only option.
Yeah, but you said coffee wouldn't work, so I assumed.
Just jump all the way to cocaine.
It's literally like the most readily available option
we have here.
I thought this was gonna be a quick one and done.
That's why you're all in the room right now.
Okay, I get to his house and he's not there, I guess.
Yep.
Okay.
Definitely break in if you wanna like
really upset John later.
Yeah, I mean, I'm already upset.
So yeah, I'm fighting mad.
So I.
Because John, do you wanna describe your house?
It's the first time we've seen it.
Yeah, so it's a nice.
Poopy trap till I get it home alone.
I slip on some marbles and fall down the stairs.
It's a nice little property north of town.
You come down like a quarter mile
of secluded gravel driveway
and you come into this little clearing
and there's a nice fucking, you know, older
but single story smallish home.
There are some, like there's a random truck
and a trailer around, you know.
And it really looks just peaceful and beautiful
and there's like rabbits and deers jumping around and shit
and you're about to, you know, disturb that harmony, so.
So I pull up and I have lock picking
so I'm gonna try to do that first.
Is that cool?
At his front door?
Yes.
Okay.
With a minus 20, that's a pass.
26 on a 30, which I have 50, so.
Sounds good.
And then like struggling, just like get out of your car,
get up there and start work.
Just sweating.
Yeah, just work your way into the house.
I go inside and I look around for wherever it would be.
Okay, roll a search for me.
It's a crit fail.
Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh.
John, what does he find?
He knocks over all my Smokey and the Bandit DVDs.
Ooh, doggy.
And almost tips over like the Dukes of Hazzard DVDs
right next to him.
Oh wait, hold up, Smokey and the Bandit is not a TV show,
it's a movie.
You had a bunch of copies of it.
Special edition.
Yeah, so every director's cut, yeah.
International releases.
And anything remotely related to the Smokeyverse.
Okay, well, I'm not leaving until I get what I need,
so I'll just go from room to room,
searching violently through everything till I find it.
Okay, is that how a crit fail search role works?
Yeah.
You violently turn over the house of John Lee Pettymore,
unable to find the cocaine that you know
is on the premises somewhere.
Wow, so this is what you want,
just our characters to get in an actual fight.
I mean, I'd be, I'm already pretty useless as a cop,
I literally could not do our job today without this.
So I don't find anything? Nope.
I text him one more time, I'm like,
dude, tell me where it is.
Tell you where what is, why, what are you talking about,
I've got, I brought some stuff for you,
it's at the station.
Oh, cool, thanks, see you there.
I try to put the DVDs back a little bit,
but then I just go, I give up and go to my car,
drive back to the station.
Okay.
I didn't want to do any of that.
You didn't?
No, but I had to.
I don't know if you know what those words mean.
All right, well, the three of you arrive
at the police station, rearing to go
on the morning of December 4th, you arrive at 9 a.m.
I sit at my desk and just put my head down.
Okay, you know that the FBI will be here in an hour
to meet with you, and as you are milling about the office,
as the day is beginning, you hear a news story
come over Drew's speakers at his desk,
and you hear the news story say,
10 people have died in a brutal fire at the city hospital.
46 more are in critical condition.
The fire started early this morning,
and the building has just now been cleared
after hours of fighting back the fire
and sweeping the premises for survivors after the evacuation.
We do not have any word yet on how the fire started,
but we will deliver updates
as they roll in here to the studio.
Hold your loved ones close today
as we send thoughts and prayers
to those who lost friends and family.
Stick around for our next segment,
experts say we're all showering too much.
With your morning update, I'm Yolanda Squat Pump.
And immediately following, Drew turns it down
to let you guys know that two children
were reported missing late last night
from a home in the suburbs.
Their names are Aiden and Alice Little.
Repeat those names, Drew.
Aiden and Alice Little.
Okay, we'll get right on that.
Okay, good, their parents are very worried.
I can only imagine.
Wait, where was that fire at?
I missed the first part.
The hospital.
Oh yeah.
The city hospital.
All right, what do you guys wanna do around the office?
I don't know.
I bet we have a lot of paperwork to do.
I bet you do.
Is there anything that you want to-
Good thing the chief's not here.
Is there anything you wanna take care of?
Oh, the chief's dead.
We should-
Yeah.
I didn't even, it's a new face.
Good thing the chief's not here.
Ugh, rip.
Hey, John.
Good thing the chief's not here.
John.
Yeah, Vigna.
Dude, can I, did you bring me any medicine?
Yeah, hey, you're smart enough to know
not to be texting about that shit on the open lines.
I just-
All right, I have some for you,
and I dangle a little baggy,
but I'm gonna need you to clean out
the cat man's cage first,
because he left a number of human-sized dudes in the corner,
and I'm not touching that.
Okay.
I'll get right on it.
Do you want a little bump first to help on these?
Okay.
I take a bump.
Roll a D6 for me.
Three.
All right, it is 9 a.m. currently,
and you are gonna-
So for the next 45 minutes, he'll have three.
For three hours, is that right?
For three hours, you will not be at a negative 20%.
Hell yeah.
Have the makers of this game ever done cocaine?
Yeah.
Yeah, you just roll a D6.
That's how it works.
Dictates the hype.
I happily go clean the shit out of the cell.
You missed a spot.
Is that true?
Dr. Jacobs says as you clean the cell
that she shares with her-
Hey, what charges are we holding her on again?
How long can we keep her here?
We looked it up at the time.
I think 24 hours, maybe 48.
It's because we wanted to investigate her.
Yeah, exactly.
And you know what, everything's in disarray.
Our chief is dead.
Oh, you know-
And-
We got the FBI coming.
Is that what you're getting at
when they shouldn't have a Catboy in there?
No, if anything, I think that helps us.
That anything that can confuse and distract the FBI.
I'm just thinking further on down the road
when she brings a civil rights lawsuit against us.
Sure.
We'll call some imprisonment or whatever.
I think we're still within our rights for today.
Oh, that's what we'll tell the FBI.
Cool.
Before you ask, we're well within our rights today.
I cleaned the spot that I messed up
and I said, I would even eat off this floor,
but I'm not hungry.
Thanks for the input, Keith.
And then I come back up to John,
I'm like, can I please have that?
Yeah, I give him the baggie.
I stick it in my pocket and then I'm ready
to talk to these feds.
Fellas, we should maybe talk about our story here.
Do we want to tell them everything?
Tell them nothing?
No, I was thinking they're getting here in what, an hour?
I'll just roll out, I'll go get some,
you guys want me to pick you up some breakfast or something?
Have you guys eaten yet?
Oh yeah.
I go grab some food for us,
get back like right as they're getting here
and then act like, hey, I got our breakfast.
Also, anybody recognize this?
I don't know where it came from.
I found it in the trunk of my car.
That's the plan.
I like it.
And then I'll somehow remember that it's from John's house.
So when they were talking to me last night,
they seem to know a lot about a lot of stuff.
So if they start asking us about stuff,
are we gonna lie to them or?
I'm playing dumb.
I don't think we should let them know more than,
we're already giving them the one thing they wanted.
But what if they can help us?
Well, let's see how they, let's see how they,
let's read them.
Exactly.
Is that a skill?
Humant.
I got 80 humant, so.
And now I'm not at a negative 20.
So hell yeah.
Keith Vigna is fully aware of how much people despise him.
Yeah.
Also, John.
Later tonight, we'll have to have a personal talk.
What about?
In which I profusely apologize for what I did this morning.
Don't, we'll talk about it after the FBI.
I don't wanna worry you.
You don't have to apologize that much for those texts, man.
Okay, yeah.
Well, that makes me feel better.
I just wanted to.
Yeah, it's.
Yeah.
Okay, well.
Just try to maintain, you know,
discipline when texting about drugs.
Like, absolutely heard from now on.
Yeah.
What do you guys want for breakfast?
I want a supersonic breakfast burrito.
Okay.
Don't we, what's the local,
did we make a breakfast place?
Beans on Beans.
Yeah, let's go to Beans on Beans.
Because it's Bean Street, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm gonna head over to Beans on Beans.
Let me get that Big Bean special.
The Big Bean special?
You want the Big Bean Sonic burrito
that they import from the City Sonic?
I mean, Sonic's right around the corner.
If you could just stop at Sonic.
I'll swing by there.
That'd be great.
That'll kill me some time.
So you want the Big Bean breakfast?
Yeah.
Do you want, what kinda,
you want black or pinto?
Black eyed.
Black eyed?
Yeah.
Okay, extra bacon?
Extra bacon.
I know you.
One piece soggy and one piece crispy.
Okay, I can do that.
Just tell them it's Clark's.
Order them now.
Oh, the Beans, Bishop's Beans breakfast.
That's it.
Gotcha.
Bishop's Beans breakfast.
They told me they were gonna add it
to the menu at some point.
I think it might be.
I haven't been there in a minute, so I'll check it out.
Okay, cool.
Clark, frankly, I find it disgusting,
and I'm not in a habit to comment on a man's breakfast,
but I find it disgusting that you let them
dangle one strip of bacon in the bean water
and leave the other strip.
Have you tried it?
No.
It's so good, buddy.
Haven't tried it.
All right, fuck it.
Screw it, make it two.
Two, okay, well.
I'll try it.
I'll be back in about,
let me know when they get here,
and then I'll be back then.
Just, they're getting here in an hour.
When you see their car pull in.
Heard, okay.
Keith, how do you feel about the street name Beans,
Beans on Beans?
I really try not to think about it too much.
You don't associate the two?
I do, but it makes me kinda sick of my stomach
the more I think about it,
so I don't wanna think about it.
Fair enough.
Why?
Keith's actual last name is Beans.
I forgot all about that, Beans.
I changed my name to avoid embarrassment
when I came back to town.
No offense to anyone named Vigna,
but kinda picked a dumb name.
I mean, Beans is a dumb name, but.
I think we're gonna.
Has that come out in character?
Well, I think you did mention something about.
Did you tell it to us, or just the?
I can't remember.
Yeah, it might have been out of character.
It was his dog.
His dog's name is Beans.
His dog's name is Bean.
Yeah.
That's weird if you're trying to escape it.
Yep.
I like to think that the dog has been around.
Before I was Keith Vigna.
Okay, so I go to my namesake street and breakfast joint.
It's technically your ancestor's namesake.
Okay, and the two of you are hanging around the office
waiting for the FBI.
Yeah, I actually, I need to talk to Drew for a minute.
Okay.
Hey, Drew, can I talk to you for a minute?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, so what time did Clark come by the station last night?
It was like 1 a.m.
That is about when we were meeting
with the people next door, right?
Yes.
Well, see, that's pretty strange, Drew,
because I was with Clark at 1 a.m.
Did you notice anything, besides the limp,
did you notice anything funny about him?
I mean, he looks kind of messed up,
like he'd been through some shit.
His uniform and everything seemed right.
Well, he wasn't wearing his uniform.
He had just come in earlier to change
into civilian clothes.
I guess he changed again into some other civilian clothes,
but yeah, no, he looked kind of messed up,
but he was wearing normal clothes.
And he warned you not to go to the Chief's house,
and this was before or after you were contacted
by the reporter?
This was before.
Jesus.
Okay, all right.
So from now on?
Yeah.
If you see one of us without any of the other of us,
that makes any sense?
Sure.
If I see any of you individually.
Yeah.
Just keep an eye out, because maybe it's not us.
What, what do you mean?
I don't rightly know,
but you know how we got that cat man in there?
Yeah.
Because he got Freaky Fried Ed with his cat?
Yeah, you guys keep saying that, but what do you mean?
What?
I mean, I get it that he wants to be a cat,
and he thinks he's a cat and stuff, but like-
Oh, shit, have we not put you in on this loop?
Maybe this is a bigger conversation.
Honestly, I'd like, yeah.
Once Clark gets out of the bathroom,
I think he should know about this too,
but I just wanted to go over it real quick.
Oh, yeah, well, while we're here,
you guys moved all the cocaine?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit, did we not tell?
Also, the FBI is gonna be here in about 20 minutes.
What?
Yeah, so we had to get the coke out of here.
Okay, yeah, good thinking.
It's all on my property.
Oh, that's amazing.
That's even better than it being here.
Yeah, oh, yeah, it's buried in a secure vault.
Perfect.
Okay.
Hey, that cake is safe, buddy.
Oh, yeah, it autocorrect messed up this morning.
Oh, I thought you were just being discreet, unlike Vigna.
What?
Oh, Vigna was texting me for some coke
because he knew it was at my house.
He's very tired and an idiot.
He is certainly that.
But hey, you know what, from now on,
why don't you call it cake or just anything besides coke
if we're texting?
I really like that.
We'll call it cake.
You know, I don't know how well that's gonna stand up
in a court of law, you know,
if they were viewing those texts.
Like, I think that's kind of one-to-one,
so we might wanna circle back and think of some.
But for right now...
If we're talking about kilograms of cake.
Yeah, that's gonna tip him off.
Man, this is a lot.
Honestly, I am in this.
I'm like, let's make some money,
but goddamn, this is a lot on top of all this
goo monster nonsense and the chief dyin'
and all the other things we haven't followed up on.
I'm gonna miss her.
Yeah.
Yeah, me too, buddy.
Clark comes back from the bathroom
and Drew and John Lee Pettymore are at Drew's desk talking.
Hey, Clark, could you come here a minute?
Yeah, what's up?
Hey, so I got a text from Drew this morning.
It seems while you and I were at the donut shop,
another you was at the station talking to Drew here.
What do you mean another me?
You heard that right.
Another you.
Like, somebody who said they were me?
No, so I saw you...
You came to the station last night at 1 a.m.
and you told me not to go to the chief's house.
And you were limpin'.
I'm really sorry that I went.
Now, I wish I would've listened to you,
but was that not you?
I mean, you must've been confused.
It was somebody that, it looked like me, maybe.
He said he was you.
Well, Drew, I was up at the donut the whole last night.
That was one o'clock, wasn't it, wasn't it, John?
Oh, yeah. We were there.
I was with, that's why I brought you in.
That's why I'm telling him, Drew,
because I was with the man.
So you must be mistaken.
It wasn't me.
Drew rolls a sanity test.
All right.
Nah, I don't...
Should we roll it?
Yeah, what's Drew's sanity?
He crit fails.
He's dead. Drew explodes.
Drew has a 100 power.
No.
I can see it.
It's like Kenneth from 30 Rock.
Yeah, exactly.
He rolls an i8.
Wow.
So he's sane as hell.
My boy's sane as hell.
Don't be telling him
that he's not seeing what he sees.
Clark.
Yeah, for the sake of the argument,
what else do I say?
You just came in, you were limping,
you were acting really weird, and you...
Acting weird how?
Was I mumbling?
Was I falling over?
You were kinda talking to yourself as you came in,
and you were wearing different clothes
than you were when you left with your CVs on,
and you were wearing normal clothes,
but you came in, you were limping,
you looked really haggard,
and you'd been through some stuff,
and you exasperatedly told me
not to go to the chief's house,
and I asked you why,
and then you were mumbling something,
and you walked away, and you just left.
And I was busy here, so I didn't worry about it.
I figured I wouldn't go to the chief's house.
I didn't understand why you didn't want me to go there,
but later when Mr. Dorsey came by,
when Harold stopped by and he wanted to go there,
he wasn't gonna take no for an answer,
and so I...
I went with him, I wanted to let him,
I didn't wanna just give him the chief's keys,
but he wasn't gonna leave,
and I was just trying to be nice.
Drew, you did good.
You did good there, don't worry about that.
Did you, I walked out the door,
but did you see if I got in a car and left, or?
I just stayed inside.
How about we check the tapes?
Can I see myself walking in, maybe?
That's a great idea. That's a great idea.
Forgot we had the...
Okay, so you guys go over to the security tapes,
and as you are watching them,
you see a figure limping,
wearing a hoodie and jeans,
limping their way into the police station
just from around the corner on foot,
then not even a minute later,
the same figure leaves around the same corner on foot.
We've probably got cameras inside the station, right?
Real world, probably, a police station would.
They would have cameras inside, yeah, sure.
Yeah, you got cameras inside.
Let's check that tape next.
Okay, so then you would see Clark Bishop
walk in to limp into the police station,
wearing the same clothes you saw the figure wearing outside,
say something to Drew,
Drew doesn't get up from his desk,
and then Clark leaves.
If you could both roll me a sanity check.
Fail.
I crit pass with an 11.
Okay, that is not you.
No way.
Not a chance that that's you.
Fail.
Would a crit pass?
I don't know.
Shouldn't he be like, that's me and I know it.
That's me and I know it.
That's an interesting perspective.
From my point of view,
the reason that I said there's no way that's used
normally when we do sanity loss,
the losing of a sanity.
Is from seeing the unnatural.
Yeah, so.
If I saw this and didn't lose sanity,
it probably didn't seem unnatural to me.
Exactly, yeah, if you lose no sanity,
you would deny its existence as being unnatural,
whereas you are wholly convinced
that that is Clark Bishop and you lose a D4 of sanity.
What do you think about, I mean.
That's in line with how we've been playing.
There was that guy who called me
and told me that the body was older on the inside
than it was on the outside,
and I crit passed a sanity check on that,
and so I just chalked it up to bad test results.
Yeah, that doesn't make sense.
It just seems like it's a little,
you wanna maintain your sanity for game reasons, right?
And then.
You wanna push the plot forward.
And understand more by passing rules,
but I actually like the discord between the two,
where not losing the sanity is good mechanically,
but not understanding the truth
is also technically good for your character,
even though we all know that learning more
about the unnatural causes the game to move forward.
Does that make sense?
But learning more about the unnatural
causes you to lose sanity, yeah.
One.
All right, so you only lose one?
You could also say, I know it's not me
in a more literal sense that I'm like so,
there's some tell that I'm so sure
that that's an imposter or something like that.
What do you think that would be?
I don't mumble, but I do mumble a lot.
You don't have a limp?
Yeah, right.
You don't own a hoodie?
Obviously it's not me, because I ain't limping.
Well, I think you're arguing past each other.
I'm not suggesting it is you, Clark,
but that's someone with your face.
Can I tell from the tape maybe what gave me my limp?
Are the pants ripped or any blood,
anything on them or anything?
Nope.
Maybe this is asking too much,
but given that this has been three or four days
of game time and this has been four months of game play,
have we in the past week encountered anybody limping
or heard about anybody?
Just Keith.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
John and Clark slowly look at each other,
realization passing between their eyes.
It's fucking Keith.
It's Keith.
He's a shapeshifter.
I'm a face taker.
Drew is looking at you.
Guys, I'm really scared.
I tell Drew, I put a hand on his shoulder
and I say, Drew, all I can tell you is that that wasn't me,
but maybe from here on out,
if you are talking to one of us, you might text us also.
I told him the same thing.
Yeah, that way we can be sure.
That way we'll know where you are?
Yeah, if it's not me, I'll text you back.
I'm not at the station, for example,
and then you should grab that person in front of you
and hold them.
Okay.
Unless somehow the imposter gets a hold
of one of our cell phones and knows about this arrangement
and then orchestrates a double switch.
That's unlikely.
Yeah, what if they get your cell phone?
No, it's the best plan we have,
but I'm just saying, be aware for anybody who comes up
asking to look at your phone or anything.
We can make a covert.
What if we handcuffed our phones to our hands?
No, that's stupid.
Drew, every time I see you,
I'm gonna say bubblegum tree.
Okay, yeah, I love that.
And I'm gonna say lollipop bush.
Okay, and I'm gonna say bubblegum bush.
Well, see, you should have your own thing.
You just kind of took our things.
Yeah, but I took the two that made it alliteration.
I like it.
Okay, hey, yeah, you do you, buddy.
What was it again?
Bubblegum bush.
I'm not gonna remember that.
And yours is lollipop bush and his is bubble tree.
Bubblegum tree?
We got it, we nailed it.
We definitely have this.
What if we all just say bubblegum tree?
Oh, that would make more sense.
Okay.
We all have the same word.
That sounds good.
Flash, thunder.
That's from D-Day.
Bubblegum tree.
Okay, so it's you.
Yeah, bubblegum tree.
Yeah, you got it.
Nailed it, buddy.
Bubblegum tree.
Hey, Drew.
All right, cool, hey.
Okay, well.
Hey, do you mind texting the entirety
of that conversation to Clark?
Could you do that for us, buddy?
I mean, Keith, I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
I'll let him know.
It's probably about time for us
to get him back here, right?
It's 11, 15, or what time is it?
It's like?
9, 15.
Did you mean Keith?
Yes.
Okay.
I thought you were saying Drew texts Clark
because we don't know if this Clark is the Clark.
I was also confused by that.
Oh, fuck, what if we just gave the password
to the fake Clark?
You're just gonna have to think that, I guess.
My eyes narrow and I just.
Hey, Drew, is there, can you think at any time
that maybe one of us came in here
and said something to you
and then never talked about it ever again?
Could this have happened before?
I mean, Clark, that happens literally all the time.
You guys talk about a lot of stuff
that you never follow up on again.
Fuck off, Drew.
There's only so many hours in a day, Drew.
God damn it.
Drew, I didn't ask your professional opinion
on our prowess in the copping world.
Did you get at the fucking,
God damn it, yeah, what are you, Detective Drew now?
You think you could do our job?
I hand Drew my gun and my badge
and I'm like, be me, motherfucker.
Walk a mile in these boots.
He gets a very serious look on his face
and he reaches out slowly for your gun.
I slapped his hand away.
God damn it, Drew.
Oh, okay, it was a joke.
I text both guys in a group message,
hey, it's cheaper to get this with an egg.
How do you want your egg cooked?
I text back, scrambled.
I didn't see the, I don't respond to the group text.
Okay.
I met beans on beans.
I ordered all three of the same thing with scrambled eggs
and I'm on my way back.
Oh, Joe is asking, did Clark recognize the clothing
that the other Clark was wearing?
Is it stuff that I knew that I owned?
It is not stuff that you own.
Okay, cool.
And that is one of the reasons
you found it hard to believe that that was you.
So I pull up to the police station
and I wait to see the FBI.
There is a large black SUV that pulls up next to you.
The windows are completely blacked out
and Agent Kennedy and Agent McKinley
make their way out of the shotgun and backseat of the SUV.
So they got a driver.
Or it's a self-driving Tesla FBI van.
Okay, I wait for them to go inside
and then I wait like 30 seconds
and I go around to the back of my trunk,
get that bag out and bring in my three bags of beans
and the black Nike bag.
Okay, sounds good.
Three, two.
Okay, so.
You didn't say one.
Son of a bitch.
So Clark and Drew and John are all standing around
Drew's desk right at the entrance of the police department
when Agent Kennedy and Agent McKinley walk in.
Clark, you are the only one out of the three of you
who has seen these two before.
So I'll describe them again.
Agent Kennedy is a short, young woman
and Agent McKinley is a tall, old, gruff man.
She has a bit of a spark in her step, glint in her eye
and he has very slow steps
and very dead eyes.
And they walk into the police department.
Agent Kennedy says,
well, hello there, Agent Kennedy FBI.
Good to see you both.
Hi, how are you?
And immediately upon looking at you guys,
Agent McKinley scans you and freaks out.
This is the tall, old, gruff man.
And his eyes get enormous
and he looks at Agent Kennedy
and he goes,
and then he sprints out.
He turns and he dips.
He runs straight out of the police department.
So Keith Vigna, you will actually see
as you're walking in with this stuff,
Agent McKinley running out,
going and gets back into the SUV
and slams the door shut.
When you say he scans us,
or would it take that he's some kind of robot?
No, I don't think so.
I just use that word.
So he's for sure a siren.
He's a robot.
He's a robot, 100%.
Cool, cool, robot.
It's an octo, octo, octo, octo?
Ocular.
Ocular pat down.
I'm gonna get the word out sooner when it helps.
That was incredible.
Some kind of obstacle pat up.
Optic, but octo, octo, octo.
Optical.
So Agent Kennedy immediately starts apologizing
and she's like, oh yeah, no, oof,
I am so sorry about that.
I mean, he is just off his,
our last mission went very poorly
and he's just all over the place these days.
So did you?
Never mind him.
Where the hell are you from, lady?
Oh, I'm from Minnesota.
Minnesota, Ireland?
No, just Minnesota.
It's in the United States of America.
So you're from the Netherlands.
Is that what I'm getting?
No, it's in the US.
I am from up north.
This is how we sound up there.
I guess you haven't been.
I guess not.
So I walk in and I'm like, what's that dude's deal?
Oh, he's just had a real rough go of it the past few days.
Hey guys, I got your breakfast.
Oh, thank you.
I toss each of them the bag of breakfast.
Ms. Kennedy, this here's a, this is a officer.
Agent Kennedy.
Agent Kennedy, sorry about that.
This here's Keith Vigna.
He's an officer here with us.
Agent like Mr. Anderson.
I watched that movie the other day.
Keith, Keith, no, it's a, this is a,
This is a real live FBI agent.
It's a real agent.
Oh, you're real, you're real.
Yeah, she's not from The Matrix.
She's from.
Oh, oh yeah, you told me that she's gonna,
I forgot to get you breakfast.
Do you want some of mine?
No, I am good on the breakfast.
You don't like black eyed peas and bacon?
One soggy, one crispy.
That sounds.
Some scrambled eggs.
That just sounds deeply unappealing on all levels.
That's what I'm saying, lady.
Have you tried it though?
No one's.
No?
No one's tried it, Clark.
It's good.
Hey guys, also, I can't remember if one,
like if you guys, if this belonged to either of you guys,
I found it in the trunk of my car.
I was cleaning all the shit out of my trunk and.
Here, let me take a look at that there, Keith.
Well heck, this is a, this is a black Nike bag.
Isn't that what you were looking for?
I comically slap like hands on both cheeks
and I'm like, oh my God, what a coincidence.
What do you mean?
She is elated.
She is like clapping her hands together very quickly
and jumping up and down and.
We fooled her guys, we fooled her.
And she's like, oh my goodness,
I've been looking just all over for this.
Oh my, you have no idea.
I got bad news for you, Agent Kennedy.
It's empty.
Perfect.
And she will reach her arm out to grab it.
Hold on, hold on, just for the listeners.
Luke was nodding his head very intensely up and down
and Thomas was vehemently shaking his head no.
I hesitantly, go ahead and hand it to her.
Hold on, I put my hand out.
Hey now, what did you, what's this bag worth to you?
I go ahead and start pulling it back.
She stops clapping, stops jumping up and down
and gets a very serious look in her eye.
I don't think you'll want to be doing that.
That's all I need.
We just want a little information is all
we're really aiming for here.
A little quid pro quo between quid pro quo
between fellow officers of the law.
Okay, if you're looking for information,
how about this?
Let me use that bag and then I will give you information.
What are you going to do with that bag?
I just need to put something in it.
All right, this might sound like a strange question,
but it gets to the heart of what we're after here.
Do you want to put something strange in it?
Oh, sorry.
I'm pretty hungry.
I'm just going to go ahead and,
go ahead and start eating on this.
I sit down at my desk and start eating my beans
while I watch this unfold.
I suppose yes, officer petty more.
It would be something quite strange.
What sort of strange.
She reaches into her back pocket and pulls out
a small lock box that is two inches by two inches
and it has a combination lock on it.
And she starts messing with the numbers.
Now I'm not going to open this until I can drop
what's in here directly into that bag.
All right, can you open it up for me officer Bishop?
Sure, I go and I reach out and I hold it open underneath.
She clicks the numbers into position
and then holds this lock box right above the bag.
And then she opens it and there inside is
a small metal sphere about an inch in diameter
and she immediately just tilts it
and it drops right into the black Nike bag.
And she closes up her packet and puts it in her back pocket
and breathes the deepest sigh of relief
you've seen someone breathe in some time.
With the bag still being held open by me,
I pull up to where I can see into it.
Do I see the ball at the bottom of the bag?
No.
That's a heck of a trick lady.
Thank you.
Now I appreciate you finding that for us
but I'm going to have to take it
and we're going to leave you to it here.
Real quick, that little ball, what was that?
That was why Agent McKinley is so unintelligible these days.
That little ball caused us so much trouble.
Huh, I'm good to finally be rid of it.
What kind of trouble did it cause you?
Officer Bishop, we can't really get into that.
You see, we have you a bit over the barrel here
with all the goings on and I happen to hear
that your chief's home blew up last night.
Now, we're not sure what kind of a situation
that that puts you in here but I'm not sure
of a situation that that puts you in here
but with all the strange happenings here in contention,
I would think that you have far more important things
to be worrying about.
I think actually, you're right
and we're in agreement there but where we might not see
eye to eye is that I'm not so sure
this ain't both of our problems.
Eye with a mouth full of beans, I've.
What, what was that, Keith?
Get over here, I gotta ask you something.
Oh, all right, I'll hook over.
Should I tell her about that silver ball that we found?
I was just gonna see if we could keep the bag
in case we need it.
Yeah, okay, I was gonna say something
but I thought you guys might get mad if I did
so I'm not going to.
That was a good instinct.
I was more than the bag.
I was gonna see if we could keep this FBI agent
in case we need it, you know what I mean?
Get her to help us out.
She seems to know about strange shit.
What are y'all talking about over there?
You're the next part of my plan.
Holler, just keep your voice down.
You're not needed yet.
Just shut up in there.
Stop your husband from pissing so much if you wanna.
It's her cat.
That's, it's like we said, it's confusing
as to what that is.
That's her husband's body, pissing like a cat
all over our goddamn prison walls.
But if it was her husband, it wouldn't be him pissing.
He wouldn't piss in there.
The cat is what pissed in the cell.
I got you, I understand.
I know what you meant.
I was just making sure we remembered what happened.
Yeah, yeah.
It's thorny.
Signing blame in this scenario.
Hey, anyway, Agent, are you staying in contention
for a while?
We could show you around the night life.
What she just told us is that she's not.
So we gotta work through it.
Oh, see, I was too busy thinking about
balls and beans. You got a mouth?
You got a mouth full of beans.
Just balls and beans.
It's all it ever is with you, Keith.
Why don't we, we should call you beans.
No, we shouldn't.
Keith beans is what we should call you.
No, don't call me that.
He does love him so much.
Don't call me that.
You love beans so much, we're gonna call you
Keith beans. Let's talk about something else.
Okay, beans.
Hey, Agent, FBI person.
My Lord.
Yeah, hey, you.
Yeah, come over, take a look at our cell real quick.
She begins walking over where you are.
So I was imagining Keith's desk is way back
in the bullpen.
You guys definitely stuck him in the back
of the department.
And so he is the closest one back to the cells.
So she begins walking across the station
and makes it to where you guys are
and peeks her head in and looks at the cells.
Hey, you see that man pissing in the corner like a cat?
She looks over and she sees the body of Doug Jacobs
on all fours, but with one paw just like up on the wall
of the cell and he is pissing kind of back behind him
and then he starts to kick up his feet onto the like nothing
to cover the urine that is on the cell floor.
Hey, hey, Dr. Jacobs.
Yes?
Could you tell our guest here exactly what happened
to your husband?
My husband believes he is a cat.
What the fuck, lady?
All right, no, your husband was turned into a cat by radio.
Ma'am, these men keep telling me these crazy stories
and they've locked me up in here with no proof
that I belong.
They did not read me my Miranda rights properly
when I was arrested.
Yeah, you got no proof of that and we did, by the way.
I'm almost positive we always do that.
We do that every time.
So just don't stop your hearsay.
Are you a federal agent of the law?
And Agent Kennedy is just kind of staring
at this whole situation.
She looks at you guys.
All right, she's being uncooperative.
Obviously anybody would be pissed off
about being stuck in a jail cell with their cat husband
for however long we've kept her in there.
But hey, that is a cat man and a radio did it to him.
A weird radio and there's a weird gun
and there's a weird camera
and there's all this oil all over the place
and this shit is frankly scaring the hell out of me
and I don't know what's going on and I need you to help.
I'm standing next to John and hearing him say it all,
like that is kind of a relief for me
and I'm kind of like nodding earnestly.
And that is a fucking cat man and what do we do?
Agent Kennedy looks at you all
with a deep knowing sadness in her eyes
and she says,
Well, I guess that means that
you guys are in.
I'll be right back.
And she walks out the door of the police station
and walking back in is Agent Kennedy
along with a young bald fit man with sunken intense eyes
wearing a black t-shirt and jeans
and you would all recognize him as Billy Harrison,
the man that was tied up in the back
of Charles Donovan's car.
Oh shit, Keith, it's that guy who made a fool of you.
I don't think I rush him,
but I am like hand toward the gun.
That's a wanted fugitive.
Yeah, same.
Hey, hey, you stop right there.
So as he walks in, he is carrying Keith's uniform
pressed and folded in a pile in one of his hands
with Keith's service revolver sitting on top of it.
I look down at my uniform that I have on
and there's black beans just spilled,
or black eyed peas just spilled all over it
and I'm like, okay, I could use that.
I get up and I stink eye him and I walk up
and I grab my clothes out of his hand
and I am red faced with embarrassment and anger
and I walk back to my desk.
As you walk away from him, he says to you,
I sure hope that you're feeling better.
Yeah, I mean, no thanks to you.
I did everything.
What the hell was that?
I did everything that you asked me to do, Officer Vigna.
Keith, what the hell did you ask him to do?
I just didn't ask him to attack me.
That's what he did.
John and Clark's heads are turning back and forth
between each person.
Yeah.
This man looks incredulous
and he looks over at Agent Kennedy.
He's like, I don't know what you're talking about,
Officer Vigna, if you wanna keep what happened
between you and I private, that's one thing,
but don't go spreading rumors about me.
Keith, Keith, what happened in that hospital?
I told you what happened already.
He told us.
Hey, he may look as dumb as he is,
but he's our friend, kinda, so.
Well, your friend made me at gunpoint
change into his clothes
and then handcuff him to a hospital bed
and then prance around the room
yelling about some Keith beans
and he wanted me to smack him in the face repeatedly,
but very lightly.
It was deeply uncomfortable for me and I.
Stop, just stop right there.
I don't know what the hell you're talking about or how.
No, no, that all scans.
If it's some Dom sub thing that you're into, that's fine,
but I didn't like being dragged into it personally.
Yeah, Keith, you gotta keep that.
I don't know who the hell you think you are, but.
Hey, buddy, that is,
you gotta keep that person alive personally,
you know, not on the job.
I just. Let you free.
Hey, you know.
I just go sit down and eat the rest of my beans,
fuming, angry.
That's why we call them beans.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
Hey, okay, so who the hell are you people?
What's going on here?
Yeah, what'd you mean by we're in?
I knew it.
You're a goddamn X-man.
Agent Kennedy looks at Billy Harrison and says,
they've seen a lot of shit,
so I say we just let him keep the bag,
give him the number and bail.
You wanna get home, right?
And he's like, I need to get home.
Does she noticeably lose that accent?
Oh yeah, it's gone.
Okay.
I pull my gun out and point it at Billy Harrison and say,
if you leave right now without telling us what's happened,
I will kill you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Keith, Keith, Keith, that conversation we had about guns.
I don't care right now.
He is, I don't know who this guy is, but I don't like him.
Hey, hey, Keith.
All right, keep your gun on him,
but also come over here for a second.
I stand exactly where I am, I'm fighting Matt,
I'm furious, looking right at him.
I'm gonna come over there.
I'm gonna whisper here, okay?
Okay.
All right, hey, guess what?
Like I won't tell Clark, but it is what he's saying, Drew.
No.
Are you sure?
I swear to God.
Are you sure, buddy?
That's why I wanna shoot him.
I wanna shoot him right now.
Okay, well think about if maybe you haven't done
anything today that somebody wouldn't get
shooting Matt at you for,
and if anybody needs to die, you know what I mean?
While you guys are having this conversation,
he speaks up and he says,
and I would like my gun and my ID back, please.
We do, I think we have those, right?
Yeah, go ahead and go.
Pick it out and evidence.
Go get it out of the evidence bags, yeah.
Don't give him his gun back again.
So when you, Clark, when you walk back into the room,
Keith has his gun trained on Billy Harrison,
and John is whispering sweet nothings into Keith's ear,
and Billy is just standing there looking at you
as is Agent Kennedy.
I'm gonna kinda edge my way if I can in front of that gun.
I do the, I put my hand way over and aim it over him.
I'm doing exaggerated fake yawn, and put my hand up.
You can't, don't leave here without,
I don't know who you are,
how you know what you know about me or us,
but just tell us something before you go.
I take, I'm taking the badge and I have his gun, right?
You have, yeah, his ID and his gun.
I'm gonna just.
Well, wait, Clark, before you give him that gun,
let's have a little pow wow.
No, I still, I go walk up to him,
and I have the clip out of the gun,
and I hand him the ID and just the clip,
and I'm holding onto the gun, and I'm saying,
I'm not gonna let him shoot you,
but the sentiment does ring true.
We wanna know what's going on around here.
Okay, well, what is going on around here?
She kicks in and she's like, you're fucked.
Each and every one of you are completely fucked.
Guys, the world does not work in the way
that we all grew up knowing it to be,
and you are now charged with understanding that.
That understanding of the world will cause your life
to crumble before your eyes,
but the thing that keeps us going is that daily,
we are saving the human race
from getting wiped out of existence.
We're going to give you the same information newcomers get,
which is a phone number, and he reaches in his pocket,
and he pulls out a card, and it's got a phone number on it,
and she says, now you give them a call
if things get completely out of hand,
or they will call in 48 hours if you don't.
I hate to do it like this, but this is your problem now.
I'm gonna leave this bag here with you.
Anything you put in it disappears.
This bag, we do not know what it does
or what it is capable of outside of that,
but we do know that it seems to make things
that we need to not be on this world anymore.
It makes them gone.
Very few have heard of it, even fewer believe it,
but we've all seen today, all of us for the first time,
that Agent Victor's Nike bag is legit.
I'm going to leave it with you all,
and you can drop it at a secure location
when the job is done, and he says,
and I'd like my gun back, please.
I turn and look back at Keith.
The whole time she was talking,
I was just slowly lowering my gun and jaw dropping.
I'm kind of slowly realizing what's been going on
the past few days and putting it together,
and gun is holstered, and I'm kind of just staring off.
I turn back and go ahead and hand him his gun.
Good luck, and they walk out.
Guys, we're fucking X-Files now.
["How Am I the Only One Trying to Pull Over"]
How am I the only one trying to pull over?
How can you have enough drowning out
of the noise?
There's no one more home.
No one more home.
Fly, fly, to the stream.