What's up? What's up? What's up? What's up? It's Zach. I'm Zach and I'm popping in here real quick
with a very fun announcement. But first a quick story. You know when me and Joe and Justin,
Luke and Thomas decided to make this show we had a silly little conversation about our pipe dreams
for PTBP and my deepest sincerest hope was that someone out there would draw a character or scene
that came from our brains. And well now there are more of you listening than I ever thought
would happen and the illustrations and the sketches that y'all have posted have not only
blown us away but they've helped us see these stories we've told through your perspectives which
is absolutely one of the coolest parts of this whole wild wonder of a situation that we're all
in together. So with all that being said we're gonna do a fan art contest drawing here in season
two. It's a contest because we're gonna pick a contest winner and it's a drawing because every
entry has an equal shot to win the drawing and it's a drawing because of the the the drawing and
I'm sorry for that what I just did so to make it up for you we'll do two drawings and each of the
two winners from the drawing drawings will receive any one item from the Pretending to be People
merch store. You want a shirt, a hat, a fanny pack, even a beach towel? Take your pick if you win and
you can win maybe if you give it a go. Speaking of winning the contest winner will receive any
three items from the Pretending to be People merch store. You want a shirt, a hat,
and a beach towel? You want three fanny packs? Do whatever you want! Okay also for this year contest
slash drawing we're gonna go ahead and say let's keep it to stuff created by your brain and your
hands without the use of AIs. Pretty wild times that we're specifying that right? Yeah but uh
you know also go buck wild on the medium itself if you want I don't know. Draw and illustrate
of course we fucking love that shit but feel free to write some fanfic or do a sculpture
or choreograph and produce and film a flash mob or whatever your heart desires we're super stoked to
see whatever you come up with and when you're ready to enter the contest slash drawing head
on over to reddit.com slash pretending to be people and find the pin thread at the top. All
right last thing for additional entries in the giveaway you can post your entry on Instagram,
Twitter, and Facebook and you tag at pretending pod and do the hashtag PTBP contest two so tag us
and hashtag PTBP contest two and we're not going to put a limit on the number of works you can
submit so go off if you feel like it. All right that's it for me fan art contest slash giveaway
no AI any medium on the subreddit additional entries for social posts and seriously thank you
all so much for listening to our show we love making it for y'all and I love passing it on
to wolf the dog howdy do to you and you it's me wolf the dog the dj of this space and time the
numbers 694.2 PTBP well now those are the very nice numbers of our radio station and the letters
okay too I guess and your sweet sweet ears why they are here for us to seep into audio wise as
per usual we got us a brand new howling with wolf god damn y'all must really really like what we're
doing here this here howling with wolf is from Lydia in New York who tweeted about the show and
tagged at pretending pod the nicest thing any Lydia from New York has done for old wolfy
and you can too Lydia from New York writes greetings I'm just writing to ask for some
quick advice I think I'm being brainwashed every day I wake up and I can't help but tune in to
694.2 PTBP and throughout the day I can't stop listening to pretending to be people
between classes and all of my free time I spend listening to the contention PD even though they
act pretty stupid and are horrible officers it's entertaining to hear them scramble around like
lost pups trying to find a solution am I being brainwashed by PTBP well greetings to you too
Lydia from New York I would never advocate for something that is trying to wash those little
nasty brain beans y'all have I however legally am not allowed to say that we are not doing some
mind manipulation of some sort listen I just know that sometimes when my voice reaches certain
frequencies and vibrations it can produce certain effects certain behaviors
now if you want to write up something for your wolf to how tag at pretending pod on instagram tag at
pretending pod on twitter tag pretended to be people on facebook or write up a five star review
on the podcast app of your choice and make sure I hears about zits and if you want to support the
show financially in exchange for a bunch of bonus episodes I know a guy who can help you get the
goods over at patreon.com pretending pod we've also got some real fun merch like a splashylvania
beach towel to show your friends that you really are truly invested in that weird show you keep
telling them about maybe if they see your financial dedication they'll finally check it out
and you'll have someone to talk to about Julius killing his uncle like what the what was that
freaking mess but if your friends are afraid to jump into these murky waters join other messy
freaks like yourself in the discord and subreddit the links to all these delightful destinations and
more well my nasty friends the links are in the show notes turning now from informing to selling
it is time for the news last time Dr Murray sewed up Julius's shoulder and then whipped out a device
similar to the futuristic tech the can crew saw in Godel's gorge to finish up the job Beck got
another top up while it was around Stevie shared some reddit articles showing unnaturally smooth
holes popping up or down rather all over the world unable to piece together the puzzle they decided
to wait for the reddit nerds to figure out where God will strike next and after hearing about Dr
Murray's wild night at the zeitgeist the gang is planning on checking out the scene before calling
in the night it's been a long day and a long night and it could get longer at any moment
taking us now to the 30th episode here in season two of pretending to be people
it's altar girl with my life is great and it's all my fault
because my life is great
30 seconds of silence please the Luke Ginniman story
it sounded like I said 30 seconds of silence please and then you said
he said gop but I was thinking if I see a cop I kill him the Luke Ginnigan story
the Luke Gigigan over and over Luke loves quagmire we call him the Giggity man I do like 30 seconds
of silence please that's yeah that's what you're gonna call your memoir about raising your kids
someday I hope it sells well I did too Thomas thinks you're gonna have loud kids probably
no I just think you're gonna write hack comedy about them
it's unfortunately it's take my wife please
back in my day that's how all the jokes start every single one you used to be able to
yep you fill the last part in call someone on a pay phone
yeah that's a good one true yeah it's hard to do now c-o-l-l-e-c-t dial down the middle
bob she had a baby it's a boy bob she had a baby it's a boy um didn't alph do collect calls
I'm alph and calling collect is out of this world and I think he eats cats or something I believe
so it was uh Paul Reiser too I remember the Paul Reiser
1-800-C-O-L-E-C-T I'm mad about calling collect yup is that really what it was I maybe
I was young enough that I knew him from that show so maybe I'm just filling in those blanks
I don't know who Paul Reiser is he's the guy from mad about you I don't know what mad about you is
and a bunch of other stuff he's actually Paul Reiser's in it Helen Hunt was mad about you
weren't you I don't think you can say that
I'm Cal Colorado and I'm standing outside the zeitgeist once the city's pride enjoyed our
sparkling spire now a decrepit needle of shame poking our skyline in the eye and popping our
civic pride last night we're told something very strange happened here the gops won't look into it
so we will follow me and we're out dude good one cal thanks back and uh cal gets kind of a
distant look in his eyes and uh take my breath away starts playing as the camera pans up from
the parking lot to the restaurant level of the zeitgeist and text over the screen says august
everyone's on coke except for cal color
but he doesn't notice because he only has eyes for um
Virginia uh his fiance whose last name I haven't made up wolf Virginia wolf
wait Virginia wolf the dog whoa dude because that's from our podcast it is from our podcast
what about Virginia wolf the dog the bounty hunter
he's he's sitting across Virginia wolf the dog the bounty hunter Biden oh
oh so you're sitting there with Virginia wolf the dog the bounty hunter Biden
and cal's sitting across from the love of his life Virginia McIntyre
she's wearing a uh a tan like power suit and her hair is fucking huge and so are our peoples
because she's on coke too cal is sweating fucking bullets because he's coming down from coke
because he's about to ask her to marry him and he's about to say Virginia
do you remember our first date here uh when something catches his eye in the parking lot
and we flash back down to the present day and uh cal kind of like shakes himself out of it and
he says uh yeah thanks back uh let's kind of do this one you know loose and live almost like we're
investigative war reporters you know what I mean yeah like on cops yeah like we're like we're cops
I don't know if I have the stamina as like one of those guys but yeah I'll keep up have one of
those energy drinks give me one of those energy drinks too whoa cal are you sure he kind of like
sniffs and his eyes get a hazy far away look and he's like yeah something about this place just
it's late I need a I need a pet me up a little kick sure here you go the sound of the can opening
uh like Pavlov reaction in Julius and he just reaches his hand out for an energy drink I pass
him one chugs it throws it over his shoulder and takes a look cal takes like two careful sips out
of his and then passes the rest to you julius julius is double fisting energy drink single
fist and you just threw the other one over your shoulder yeah stevie already picked it up and
tossed it in the recycling okay he's sipping on this one and you all see um or we see
Beck Wilder cal colorado julius summers stevie gottel approaching the zeitgeist up from where
they did the spot in the parking lot with the zeitgeist up in the background cal colorado
strong in the foreground it's a hazy night late late heavy humid summer night the air is thick
with the humidity and the presence of what happened here as you walk up
Beck directs his camera at some holes that have been dug in the ground
recently as of last night seemingly looks like it's been covered Beck Beck are you getting this
it's it's holes yes they're they're they're not they're not all that smooth what's that in there
disturbed get the camera on that zooms in julius julius pick that up yeah julius hops and grabs
there's a bigfoot stuffy julius what you've got it's uh like a carnival toy it's a goddamn bigfoot
you see another one strewn on the ground nearby there's a small one julius like you do like
x-files type stuff is is this a clue are these real i'd say it's probably a clue have you seen
a bigfoot julius julius shrugs holy shit you seen a bigfoot julius have you seen a fucking bigfoot
uh don't no but i heard about him
okay okay never mind never mind that look it looks like the door has been forced open recently
can i get a second roll actually sorry real quick i i'm gonna ignore what i just said and so are you
sorry you were saying the door was a jar the door is a jar so we better find a lid for it
oh good one cal thanks thanks still got it even late at night as each of you is starting to feel
the wear and tear of exhaustion and uh we got that energy drink baby multiple days the energy
drink is keeping you going and it is the only thing currently keeping you from rolling at a
disadvantage it may make it more difficult to sleep tonight uh julius do you have any more of
that that one i passed over to you he hands it back three sips is enough for cal colorado's
delicate ecosystem
do you remember that show parks and recreation with the life of man chris trigger
seldom ever related to a character more on tv
i like that show it was just nice julius pulls his gun out and is gonna like
swat style enter this building uh this is the first time that beck and cal have seen you
in this mode and stevie too is kind of in a worrisome confused excitement as uh they look
over at you yeah cal's cows kind of freaked and he's like uh don't don't don't worry viewers at
home uh julius is our segment producer as you know he's he's relying on some training he had
before he came to uh to can and and we're really you know sorry to say strange things are happening
we've got to put the action and city action news we're gonna follow him inside the zeitgeist
julius clears the first room and starts up the stairs
as cal falls behind him he kind of like glances over at this uh like abandoned um reception desk
and the colors go like pink and electric blue and uh and you see a very a much younger cal
colorado like arguing with this this host he's like no i i specifically said i specifically
said 6 30 for friday evening cal colorado you must have it you bet yeah so i am not sure we
currently have that no but i made this weeks ago it's it's dreadfully important you said your name
was colorado yes colorado colorado cal colorado i'm sorry i don't usually yell but oh i'm i'm
going to ask the woman i love very dearly to marry me tonight what is that worth to you sir
everything i'm willing to spend my life with her he kind of holds at his hand expectingly oh
oh oh okay cal pulls out his wallet and gives you like 150 bucks in 1987 dollars
just make sure it's a good table she'll be here any minute and cal kind of like chuckles to
himself in the present walks back up the stairs he's going up the stairs bic uh has a big flood
light on top of the camera at this point and you are showing the raggedy ass like paint chipped
walls of the stairway as you make your way up to the very top uh yeah each floor even has like a
number on it and some of the numbers are like peeling off julius on the way up points out
julius summers uh like scratched into the wall um but he knows that he did that a few days ago
but kind of pointing it out like look hey i've been here before
you were here a few days ago he doesn't say that out loud
julius this looks like it was scratched into these walls just a few days ago super fresh
julius like motions like because he's uh doing combat business
yeah cal quiet he's doing combat business you're you're right you're right
and uh julius proceeds to clear the front of the staircase
is it is it all all clear it's all clear it's all clear julius this looks pretty fresh just a few
days old why were you here recently it's from a long time ago what do you think beck it's dated
it's three days ago yeah uh just one of those crazy coincidence i wrote the first date i could
think of way back when that's wild that i'm here very close to that date not exactly on that date
though uh julius i don't think we believe you i mean i guess you guys are in this now i might
as well not lie yeah i was here this is where me and x meet up to uh talk business did you
know about what happened here no i i was here three days ago this happened last night still
it's a troubling connection i must say it is weird that like this is your secret place but
like a lot of not very secret stuff you think everywhere i go just has dead bodies
a lot of the places i've been with you it wasn't me i cut i don't mutilate the bodies it's not
about that oh jesus it's not about that what's it about i didn't do it i i believe you but did
you have any hand in setting it up i don't know anything about it i'm genuinely want to know i'm
trying to find out same thing you guys are do you remember if you picked this as your meeting place
or did x pick this as your meeting place we always meet at the tallest point wherever we are
impractical hey for everybody else it's impractical too so there's not a lot of people
there aren't any uh eight-story buildings in this neighborhood in the city those are on the other
side of the river that's right where we are is real heavy i get it you're your general locale
right your immediate it's tall it's the tallest thing around sure and it looks cool it's got
zeitgeist is the name you know it worked out well i guess also if you're like if you're not as close
as you thought you were maybe and you're at the top of the zeitgeist and x is at the top of the
next nearest building in her vicinity you could probably like shout it out or at least wave to
each other i hadn't thought about that but yeah if it ever doesn't work out that way you know you
could you could keep that in mind yeah or you guys could just talk at home well no that because who
knows you know you guys only talk in like your attic the high or on the roof no we don't i mean
we don't really interact too much i i don't really know her that well i just met her on this
assignment did you say online i mean i met her online when i was introduced by our boss but
who's your boss x you know for now who introduced you it doesn't matter and he looks super sad and
he kind of just walks away and is gonna look around back did you get a sadness i saw that
did you did you was it framed well oh yeah okay we'll have to ask him about that you guys are
whispering to each other in this dilapidated room that cal still sees through his eyes here and there
here and there and it's former glory but now is as we've seen before you know windows are busted
out and the bar is just like overrun with like moss and age has clearly taken its toll even more
intensely now that nature has made its way into this abandoned structure i need you guys to roll
sig into pass a 77 on a 60 well hold on i have a zero but you still roll for crits right yeah
i got a 69 holy fucking and i passed always a success yeah we've got a big crit we've got
a crit fail and then we've got a pass yeah cal's eyes are darting across this room and he hasn't
he hasn't been here like since it shut down and his memory of it is so vivid this day was so
important to him he can easily see like all these these things he remembers and they're you know
broken and turned over and you walk over to the like beautiful window booth that you sat in the
best seat in the house and as you approach it when you look down you're standing next to julia
summers and the two of you are looking down directly into the spot where there are holes
covering the ground that have been excavated and refilled and each of you is familiar with braille
for one reason or another and you quickly surmise the code punched into the ground
number sign h c f which you know means
i have literally no idea you don't because you just passed you you put it together you're like
number hcf huh and cal with the 69 you know that braille num numerical values the numbers
eight three six three six beck's over on the opposite side of the room filming a dripping pipe
i'm getting some good footage over here guys beck uh beck come over here a moment
no hang on i want to get some more of this hang on no you've got to see these holes you got to
see this pipe it is dripping becketh come film this all right okay if i could feel that with
my thumb i would know what it said no no uh julius i i did a three-part series where i
lived as a blind homeless man on the streets of the city i remember that yeah i learned braille
it says hcf i gave you money at some point when you did that i didn't know it was you well i'm
glad you were one of the ones who gave me money instead of beating me up and taking that makes
really hard to see if he which money did but uh look julius it's it's the letters hcf but there's
a pound sign a number sign in front of it eight three six it says eight three six how'd you do
that so fast i i can read braille i know but i just have to feel it but how'd you convert it
out numerically so quickly what you don't know everything about me clearly i guess not you you
contain great depths maria summers cow and the other two real grip cow and the rest uh pass but
why uh i do not pass a crit fail begets a crit success it's an 11. hey nice i didn't pass uh
okay uh julius you're gonna lose one as this number has shown up once more in your lives
and you are having a harder and harder time keeping a grip on reality when there's clearly
some sort of numerical value that is like following you beck this only strengthens your
resolve once again i think you should feel good gain one grip and cal you recognize it
how is this number continuing to show up it's pretty straightforward it's a gottel
corp conspiracy the number is significant to them in some way perhaps it's stevie yeah
the number is eight three six mean anything to you uh
no what was your grandfather's birthday august 36th
that's that's it
why is that weird was that a real answer
no i was doing it i was doing a joke did you yeah that's a pretty good joke stevie thanks
julius is gonna google 836 do it and then 836 conspiracy and then google do it again
do you know what the first thing that comes up is
is it the transcripts oh my god is that what's happening
that is not the first thing that comes up when i google it
for me it's thompson rudder's practical law it says 5a836 conspiracy to murder
well that's my third one so uh julius does that and it puts his phone back in his pocket
uh it was a leap year is that anything what was no i don't think so 836 like i meant maybe like
august 1936 oh yeah no i i don't even know my grandpa's birthday like do you know your
grandpa's birthday yes july 4th 1905
wow okay i mean i i just don't i guess i i know
i know my dad's birthday what's your dad's birthday august 36th
august 36th julius text x 836 mean anything it's a good text good text game
let me let me get a search role while you guys are up here since you're since you're up here
oh yeah looking down around the beautiful sights below yeah so cal spots whatever it is with these
with a 21 on a 60. fuck yeah what do we got i did not pass a 58 on a 40 once again back
just distracted by the drip a mouse just went by i am chasing it in a crazy outfit
oh the drip i get it and uh how did joyus 13 on 70 the two of you see a a glint in the moonlight
hidden under some brush a little bit into kind of the thick of the tree line
past where people would hang out there uh you know they're like picnic tables and stuff about
of course those are gross and old too but a little bit further in where one might get
ticks i'm not stalling you see something shiny julius do you see do you see that shining out
there yeah i thought it was just like tricking me but i've seen it like five or six times it kind of
comes in between the trees it looks like there's ticks out there i wish we had jeremy with us
do you have his number right oh yeah cal sites texting jeremy get him out here tell him to bring
off meet at zeitgeist immediately or asap with off it uh as you go to text it says jeremy the
intern which i assume is what it is in your phone uh is notification it just says the enter
notifications are currently turned off notify anyway hey if i call him you can click notify
anyway oh i click notify anyway cal what do you bet i could get this uh this stuffed bigfoot
into one of those holes uh 50 dollars julius positions the bigfoot on his on his foot
and like kind of eyes it and gives it a little kick trying to get it right into the hole this
is peak role playing role athletics or if you have like a carnival skill no that's a 90.
well that isn't gonna do it you did a lot of practice rolling before do you think that
helped i hurt damn can i push the push the rule uh in order to push the rule you would have to
risk like falling out the window oh don't for the that's a pass
fucking idiot
this would have been like so much of the story depends on your roommate i would have killed you
right now i wouldn't even for doing that shit i would have killed you right now i've been happy
with it uh 86 is what you would roll fortunately i pass uh and so he flicks it off his foot and
it's not aimed correctly nope and so at the very end he re he like leans out the window and flicks
it and it goes into the hole do you uh you think that means something uh well that's one of the
damnedest things i've ever seen beck were you filming that uh please please please tell me
beck is in another corner and it's a bunch of tables and he's kind of poking at him with his
foot and they all slide i got a really good one over here there's a table sliding like there was
something behind him or something kind of spooky like it's a good shot guys beck you gotta be
careful to not make the news you know what i mean oh yeah no i just thought we'd like spice it up a
little like nothing's really doing anything so far cal is looking at you like in astonishment
and pride he's like you've really learned a thing or two in your time here i mean i learned it all
from you guys so you sounded like a producer he gets a little bit sad but he he's like no no no
that's that's cal let's go see the shiny thing julius you know if i'm the head boss if x makes
me that i can fire myself and hire you or we could be cohead bosses i'm really reigniting my passion
for news here doing this kind of stuff and well wouldn't you rather be with us than whoever the
fuck they are oh yeah i don't know the how that really works uh never tried to like leave but
that's i mean that's good news that's we can talk about it after we figure out whatever
is going on here okay hold up i i might be am i not following this way you could have
because tife i and she kind of looks at julius and grimace isn't um well you'll be the like
lead producer so like wouldn't julius's role still just be what i am or we could bump you
up one and you essentially do the same thing but stevie also does that too whoa would you
like to be a segment producer stevie by being confused that's amazing is that what you were
asking for yes that is what i was asking for wow and beck you're good where you are yeah okay let's
go cow's just like giving you a thumbs up and nodding when he says that he's like all right
all right well we've got a hey we've got ourselves a news organization people let's go do the news
okay and he starts clearing the stairwell do the news yeah and as as everybody walks down cow
lingers at the top and he sees he sees himself down on one knee the air has like a fine mist
like a white haze in it um from all the coke and you and you see yeah and and cow you you do
believe has not done any cocaine but it's in its system and with the courage he's never known he's
down on one knee right in front of uh virginia macintyre that's right virginia macintyre would
you make me the happiest newsman in the world would you be my wife and she bursts into tears
and gives him a big hug and she says yes cal yes i never thought you'd ask you were so hesitant
virginia when i think about the rest of our life nothing makes me want to hesitate i want to start
it right fucking now and he like picks her up and walks her out of the restaurant and the whole
place is fucking cheering and you see cal like looking back and smiling on that uh and he uh
he sniffs asks he shouts julius do you have
any more of that energy drink uh and heads on down the stairs
oh man i don't want to be too weird but like that was cool man thanks
good shit do you have luck uh i should have used it if you already have it because you got it
again again again i actually have two scratches written down so i don't know if that's happened
before i should probably spend my luck if you fail a roll guys luck can help if it's appropriate
just a quick reminder from your local luck council zach thank you you're welcome he shouts to the
restaurant i've got some news everybody we're getting married and take my breath away
swells like fucking crazy
yo she took my breath away and he covers
he leaves enough money on the table to cover the bill and then they go downstairs
julius kicks open the door at the bottom of the zeitgeist
back back did you get that that one i got hell yeah and as you do so the four of you walk
confidently as a team across the grounds of the zeitgeist here on this misty dark heavy summer
night eight three six punched into the ground to the left of you and in your direct path in
your future now lies whatever it was that caught your eye and as you continue approaching the edge
of the woods you see the glint of the tip of a very pristine and sharp shovel
the scariest gardening tool because it's a horror podcast yeah oh my god it's a shovel
no no anything but that anything but a shovel is it like just stuck in the ground or it's just
laying on the ground and it looks like it's been covered purposely by some randomly assorted
shrubbery and foliage i could use a disguise roll to see that
the earth is disguised around the shovel yeah it very much is you can just uh very clear uh i mean
you can roll for that if you want but you can very clearly tell that yes it was disguised it was uh
hidden it was it was purposefully yeah and therefore the most obvious and clever way to
unhide or disguise it to remove the stuff on top of it the shovel now uh with the foliage removed
uh you can just see it is an extremely clean pristine clean and sharp shovel look as i
undisguised the shovel a shovel like that looks really valuable maybe someone carved their name
into it it's a thought and he chucks it at julius take a look grabs the shovel and really
thoroughly inspects that shovel well let's see uh what would you like to roll to see if there's
a name on this shovel how about alertness i'll give you a search pass 40 on the 70. okay
absolutely as you search around uh this shovel you see that uh it's actually got a um like a cover
like a tip on the end of it for nice gripping on that side but as you peel it back a little bit
you see etched into the wood the name dr brock hargrave do you guys uh you know who brock
hargrave is dr park park hargar son of a bitch dr brock hargrave i've interviewed him a dozen times
what kind of doctor is he surgeon he's uh no uh of i don't really like doctors archaeology or
or anthropology oh like uh one of those doctors yeah but he's like a real you know he's not like
one of those boring dinosaur nerds he's like a real indiana jones type i've watched all his
youtubes he he makes for some good news we should try to get him on the is he from here
yeah i believe he's from the city originally but um he's been globetrotting for the last
wait 30 years if he was he's an archaeologist he's digging around here what is there dinosaurs
dinosaur bones no again like i said he's not that kind of archaeologist but indiana okay yeah
but he's digging for something but this is a good lead this is a really good we could
follow up on this julius is onto something there that that indiana jones should totally do
dinos a dino movie so if he's not digging for dinosaurs what else a treasure a rock could it
just be a rock he likes weird rocks hmm well anyway i'll text him maybe i can set up an
interview tomorrow and count count like uh thanks out hey doc been a while meet at the foundry for
lunch tomorrow oh cool
facts like worlds collide but they're my own this is getting a little uh weird
i mean we haven't done this before because like all of our side stuff has always been
very side stuff and this is like your girlfriend
taylor that's your ex-girlfriend whoa whoa rip scott ockerman oh he died so old
oh fuck i'm the best all right the live show is when jason keeps joking about him being like 64
and he's like it's it's too close that it hurts
well you guys are still out here so i guess uh roll another shirt
roll another what search sorry i got a little slurry with it and it's a piece
i passed also 12 on a 40 cal fails 61 on a 60 i flipped on the night vision nice
and julius pulls out his readers but they don't help
uh and julius has trained himself to see in the dark aka looking over beck's shoulder in the
viewfinder all right the two of you notice wait what's that
a little ziploc bag it looks like a little ziploc bag it's been like for ham sandwiches trampled
underfoot and has made its way into the ground becoming one with kind of the the grass and the
and the flowers and the weeds that surround it but it doesn't look like it's been here for a
long time just that it got stepped on a few times and is it's now stuck and obscured from
most people's sight hey steve you were always you're picking up my trash there's trash see
what it is whoa yeah julius man they're always picking up my energy drinks i figured they just
like trash they're looking out for the environment but that's no way to talk about your junior
segment producer yeah oh hey this is not the kind of workplace we're trying to foster here
yeah this could be a learning moment for you yeah i don't know how you do things in the x
files julius julius kind of that's not gonna fly and picks up the piece of trash
uh well when you go and pick up the piece of trash i need you to roll uh grip
uh not pass fail
i guess uh if you guys thomas and joe could leave the room for una memento
that would be good dude i had blood drawn and there's a big old bruise oh snap why'd you have
blood drawn i just had a doctor's appointment oh physical thing i don't do that i should do that
i paid 15 bucks with my insurance i finally have insurance and i'm afraid to use it because i
am scared of how it works they don't tell you how you gotta just go figure it out
seems like a nightmare and i'm scared about it and i uh busy i'm too busy plus nothing
probably nothing's wrong with you oh i can keep telling myself that if i don't go
what happens when i when julius picks this ziploc bag up dude the smell is overwhelming
you pick up just the slightest hint of some sort of saline
salty oceany and then all of a sudden it's overwhelming and it's all you can
smell and you're just back in that moment seeing that entity that thing that
wet energy
oh boy come back yeah lose one grip
why why would you do cold water i just flipped it on man i was trying to get it done
i only wash my hands with warm water i wasn't paying enough attention to until then to realize
what you're talking about and i thought you meant like heated water in the toilet bowl hell yeah
dude we have the height of luxury just in case our splash our splash back is warm if you drop
a deuce in there that's real heavy and it splashes up splashes right into your asshole not gonna be
unpleasantly cool it's gonna be soothingly warm whoa i did have a little bit of water that's wild
yeah and he's back back again joey's back tell a friend hey luke joe's back
you took my friend
yes joe hey joe you're back nice yeah julius summers lets out a rip roaring scream in the
night in the thick heavy fog surrounding everyone with this blood curdling scream something tingles
in the back of your necks you have a weird feeling like you're um in a graveyard at night
it's probably all the mist and holes beck whips the camera around to julius that bag's got
something bags got gone and it's got something to do with god hey back i smelled god back
we're on a mission from god the blues brothers yeah yeah we were just listening to it yeah
julius what what did you see in there it's the same smell i smelled in grover's gorge
it's just it's what god smells like and i as soon as i touched it i just that's all i could
even feel what does god smell like like salt water like just it's like just fucking
nasty seawater and it just takes over you can't think about anything except the smell
beck zooms in on the bag are you holding it still or is it on the ground
up to you he let go of it as soon as he could beck zooms in on it on the ground does he see
anything there's a little dark waxy substance as you zoom in closer it's it's like on it's
on the outside of the bag and you see that the ziploc is like turned inside out i think it got
turned inside out took it eaten does it look like somebody took a bite out of it
julius if you're saying that smells like god whatever the fuck that means i don't think we
should touch it the last guy that we saw come in contact with the god thing is now ripping
holes throughout the world i mean that's the clue we should probably bag it up somehow safe
stevie pulls a uh another ziploc bag stevie god is in your brother and i smelled god maybe if you
touch it you'll talk to him or you got a better relationship than i do uh stevie i'm gonna advise
you against that but he's your brother so no their eyes are huge and they're just looking at
you and you say advice against that they're just like yes like not like absolutely nodding like
you're right no no he's your brother and i don't want to get between family but sure sure yeah
all right so i guess you don't want to find your brother
can i roll persuade
they take the bag that's inside out and put it inside a clean ziploc they kind of take a
quick smell and their face just like goes somewhere else for a second and then they close it
yeah you all right you still with us they're looking at julius do you smell it yeah
whoa julius like eyeballs the bag again well now i want to see what god smells like give it here
beck hold on don't be so rash you've got to film me fill it at first
and it's all my fault
suddenly cal's little hearing aid is it's discreet you've not noticed it before
he's a vain man but it starts ringing like crazy and he he hones in on the source of this this
signal or are you trying to get us to decipher a code that is deciphering a code for sure
the same thing happens to his eye implant
you