The hardest part of waking up is deciding what to wear, but today I woke up missing
me, and it's been downhill from there.
One, two, three!
What's up, everybody?
I'm Zach.
It's me.
I'm here.
Hey.
What's up, everybody?
It's Zach.
I'm here with...
Who?
Let's do it one more time.
You can have the energy to the first one.
It was good.
Yeah, everybody!
No, I'm back.
Well, hello there.
I'm Zach, and this is an announcement that I'm pretty excited about.
I tossed.
I wasn't giving you an intentional, you did bad face until that last one, which was creepy.
Hey, everybody.
Watch our video.
Daddy's here.
Hey, Daddy.
Daddy.
It's me, Daddy, and I'm here to tell you...
I'm not that one.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
We made a promo video.
Yeah.
We're really excited about it, and we wanted to let you know and encourage you to watch
and share it.
As you're listening, you can go watch.
You can find it on our YouTube.
YouTube.
But we'll also have it posted places.
Links to the YouTube.
Twitter.
Social media.
Instagram.
Fuck all those people, and fuck Matt Huffman, I think is his name.
Which one's that?
I think he's the Reddit guy.
Fuck Greg Huffman.
The Reddit guy.
Fucking whatever.
Anyway, we have a Reddit, and we're going to be sharing it around on there, and if you
feel like, I don't know, commenting about if you like the show or telling people about
it on there.
Maybe send in people a YouTube link.
Yep.
Which you can find on the Reddit and all the other social medias.
We think you're going to like it.
We hope you're going to like it.
We really like it.
We want to thank our friends who did it.
It was made by some really good friends of ours who are really talented and very kind
people at Mood Ring Films.
Mood Ring Films.
So lovely.
Paul and Nicky.
Paul and Nicky did an excellent job.
It's so good.
Isaac and Michael and...
Isaac and Michael and Jonathan, and each brought so much to the couple shoot days that we had.
We knocked it out of the park.
Absolutely.
Each individual one nailed their job, and were an absolute pleasure to be around, and
we had a great time on set.
We got to have a fun time and not do any of the work.
Yeah!
It was so easy for us.
And yeah, this video looks amazing and makes our podcast look way better than it is.
Yeah!
Which is very nice of them.
But don't tell people that.
No.
Yeah, tell people it's good, right?
Yeah.
Be like, I honestly expected more out of this video, but you should watch it anyway.
We're just so thankful that you have allowed us to get to this position by listening and
following along with our silly stories that we're having such a fucking good time creating
and sharing, so yeah.
Thanks.
So go share it with your friends!
Go like it everywhere.
Go upvote it.
Go comment.
Go share it.
Send the links.
Watch it on repeat on YouTube on all your devices.
Leave it just playing in the background.
Oh, that would be good, actually.
We will consider it a failure if it doesn't hit five million views in the first hour.
In the first hour.
Right.
To get to work.
So yeah, if you want us to keep loving you, you can either donate to the Patreon or share
this fucking video around, so like, one's free.
It's not like that, but please share.
Thanks for listening.
Yeah, thanks for listening.
You're gonna like the way it looks.
We guarantee it.
Boom.
And it's all my fault, cause my life is great.
And it's all mine, cause my life is great.
Fuck that up, man.
I think he's the Reddit guy.
You know, but the Reddit is a good point.
We have a Reddit profile that we'll share it, we'll share it, we'll share it.
Let's do it from the top, man.
Yeah.
Fuck Steve Huffman.
Everybody just yell, fuck Steve Huffman, and I'll get it.
Is that even his name?
I'm pretty sure it's right.
Don't look it up.
It'd be so good if it wasn't.
Steve Huffman is a Nobel Peace Prize winning philanthropist.
It's Craig.
It's Craig?
Fuck Craig Huffman.
Craig!
Thank you, Craig.
Three, two, one...
And it's all my fault!
Today I woke up missing me.
I forgot her yesterday, where I left my made-up enemies, and this song was not a thing.
And the truth is, this is 100% real, cause my life is wonderful, and I blame it on me.