what is good my dearest listeners it is the good boy voice inside your head wolf the dog
and i am embedded into your ear holes here from the 694.2 pt bp contentions most truthful and
accurate radio broadcast we are all here together in the past where the supposed dinner tastes like
the future's wettest scraps you know what that means friendos the slop here is stankier angrier
and rootin tootin yankier than even the nastiest shit back in the future so do not fear for your
old buddy wolf the dog i am happy here and i am also happy to announce the community project is
in full swing over on reddit.com pretending to be people help us create a delta green scenario
piece by piece we are currently working on the setting so write up a creepy and fun location
and check out the other entries by clicking the link to the subreddit in the show notes
click the other show notes while you are at it or i will make you disappear
hahaha fuck mark zuckerberg fuck jeff bezos fuck donald trump all hail silas coal and now
sponsored by the contention mining company contentions only hope at becoming anything
more than unincorporated land it's time for the news please stay inside your homes do not go
outside do not trust preacher sheriff dr bobby custard do not trust judge ephraim courtland
do not trust jack pearlman oh do not trust professor horace green and obviously do not
trust ever pace that is all all hail silas coal and now a tune to take your mind off my words
while internalizing my message it's the creek rocks with can't you hear them wolves a howling
they'll get my darling
can't you hear the wolves howling all around my poor little darling all around my poor little
darling i'm afraid they'll get my darling can't you hear them wolves howling all around my poor
little darling all around my poor little darling i'm afraid they'll get my darling
in 1856 the us camel corps was an experiment by the united states army
they suggested using camels as pack animals in the southwest
which the army declined why on earth would they decline that
there's no way to present what just happened
um
and your and your video was frozen and then yeah and then like everything you did after
you said that was like but we we were all silent so it was like we were waiting for you to finish
your long drawn out word well because it was yeah i thought he was at first i was like what's
happening with luke holy shit good times easy credit ripoffs um good times yeah too bad it
didn't record that did you know at one point they were gonna introduce hippos into like the
louisiana area uh to farm for their meat when it's awesome recently is hippo tasty i don't know
it was this was back like i don't know 1800s probably they didn't do it which is good because
they would have just decimated the ecosystem yeah also they're like the most dangerous
aminal yeah besides man they would get along with greer because have you seen those videos
hippopotamus is smashing watermelons yeah but would that be within greer's rules because
she got to smash them with is she smashing them with her legs or is she like yeah yeah uh hippo
couldn't i don't think it's thighs could ever move yeah could touch like that let me literally read
the can hippos smash watermelons with their legs google search give me a second to just read the
hippo wikipedia to you guys i think you'll see uh the description of this woman is fantastic it says
very tall very buff and can do that thing with her thighs where you destroy a watermelon owns a gym
nice good job is that yours or from somebody that's how you write a character that is all
i need what was that patreon uh-huh yeah shout out to em from michigan wow was that a home star
runner reference a little bit oh man home star runner patreon vote this episode let's all role
play home star characters in a delta green mission whoa shoddy shoddy the cheat can i be this 55 guy
sure was that e-bombs world that was yeah that was shifty fat or albino black sheep did you not watch
home star runner things zach ever i worded that sentence real good just uh justin it was really
big when you and me and joe were in middle school so it might that was the perfect time yeah and i
was being born you weren't allowed to be on the internet well your ball was being implanted into
an orphan spine that's how i like them so according to this uh article the uh there was a
did it do it again
uh luke are you on your hot spot yeah i'm on my hot spot balls can you hear me or see me
yeah your video is very jumpy yeah i can go to my regular internet and it's on its own yeah try
switching it and we'll see if it gets better yeah although it is fucking hilarious every time it's
happened so i'm reading this article and it says uh i mean
sometimes i just edit that out
thomas were you on the call when i was talking about the product for the commercial shoot i
did today no i'm not going to say the name of it but it's a wearable hand sanitizer and lotion
dispenser that goes around your wrist cool and it looks like a giant cock ring awesome all of
those things are cool the pot it's like pods full of one is full of lotion and the other one is full
of hand sanitizer and they're on either side of your wrist it's a two inch long pod so your wrist
is now a solid what seven eight inches wide uh-huh but at any time you can just be like
so you could be walking through the park and somebody offers you a hot dog and you say oh
yeah i could do that because i've got my hand sanitizer right here let me lotion up for this
dog real quick it squirts out like one of those like uh gel deodorant sticks that you just kind
of like squeeze out through holes on the top of it that's exactly what it looks like as it squeezes
out so walk me through okay you you've you've pushed the pouch and it's squirted do you take
your other hand and rub is that how it works so the hand that you are squeezing with it just kind
of like stays on the product and then you rub off the lotion it was honestly one of the most batshit
things i've ever seen i was like this is a joke right you gotta build up your imdb
credits though yeah instead of getting paid i just just like can i have 10 of them
i should have asked for one instead of getting paid that would have been that would have been
fun i could put cool stuff in it mayonnaise and mustard oh my god then you could get a sandwich
going anytime anywhere i like where your head's at that's exactly what you'd use it for
that's great mine would be sriracha and uh freddy's fry salt into it gooped up in there
what's their it's their it's their fry and steak burger seasoning oh it's real good a season a
seasoning salt does that have delicious seasonings in it yes i'll throw some cheese whiz in mine
have a little cheese ranch
i would just turn mine both of them into a chia pet
seriously though uh home tip you can buy their fucking uh their burger and fry seasoning at the
at the restaurants you can probably order it online but if you're making burgers at home
just toss in some fucking uh freddy's seasoning with your meat and like you're gonna blast
everybody's burgers away nice season you're meeting then you're gonna blast is all
what comp is this a competition or are is all grilling a competition yes yes no see but that's
just because tom is lost already so yeah uh not according to my girlfriend and mom
whoa who both live in canada
wow thomas is really cool over the summer but then he comes back and it's like
he's blasting on our burgers don't blast on my burg bro so the four of you the five of you what
is the name uh all all old western groups have a have a cool name right the magnificent seven
others i'm sure those are usually applied afterwards i think the fucking four
fast and the four yes well that's it there are five of us here does he
yeah custom i mean not that i do associate with this group yet but hypothetically if there was
one would would you count really i feel like i'm the leader honestly he's been with us the whole
time that's interesting that's i mean clearly uh clearly the judge is the alpha i think we were all
looking at every pace to take control of this group at any point now if if bobby's part of
the group we could be the fab five i don't understand the reference it just made it up
the fab five it is professor you're gonna have to learn to be more oh i missed the joke fuck
i'll hear it when i edit i just i just we're the fab we're the fab five where's the fab five
that's that's not a joke
and with that we're back into the reality is the 1880 some things with a burp from judge ephraim
courtland the five of you are surveying from a distance the land bobby's from missouri
nice i served him once yeah oh he's cool yeah preacher sheriff bobby custard not you
uh you see that the gay man from the future new the typically bustling new mine is a ghost town
normally men and women who work for coals contention mining company would be hustling
about up and down stairs from platform to platform hauling loads of equipment with
the conveyor continuously running a loud humming and the thick stench of sweat in the air today
however it's quiet except for those same low barking growls that you heard earlier and there
is a swarm i'm talking 12. is that a swarm is that enough for swarm 12 vultures
is a lot of vultures observe everyone a small swarm of vultures
you see him around here quite a bit lots of death and whatnot is it inherently weird to us that the
mine isn't operating today or is it it is is it a known thing always in operation maybe they're
installing fans in the mine that'd be awful nice of him i ain't known silas coal to be particularly
worried about being nice to folks that's true he did steal my copper wire i don't know he he
he does a lot for well even the courthouse you know got electricity before i guess it might have
gotten stolen but we don't exactly know by whom except for miss kitty lizzie said it was his wife
the little girl she said it was mary cole yeah you were right there didn't you hear i was right
there huh let's go get her we can find out about the smashed watermelons or whatever but i need to
get my wire i think we should probably stay the course to find the grave robbing miss kitty at
this point that's that's kind of top priority we don't want any more graves dug up yeah i think
your wire comes a second here afram judge why don't why don't we tie everything up uh later on
in the day with your wire yeah well i figured if we were heading down there i'd bring it up but
should we follow these horse tracks or the tracks do lead back down through the gate of the mine
uh into the property that the coals own i'd like to go down there and touch this goo
and you see that at the gate at his daily post is the mining company's security guard becker
piston you know becker was a co-worker of silas coal down in the mine but when silas bought the
mine he pulled becker up out of the ground sat him at that gate and he's been there ever since
becker piston lives on the grounds far on the other side of the mine from the coal residence
so basically one far end becker piston lives and you got the mine in the middle and then far on the
other side you've got the residents of the coals and over the top of the entrance of the mine
silas has built a three-story building with his office are we writing up to him
oh that's up to you guys how do you would we know if becker is uh typically a violent person
or anything or like unreasonable or do we just not would we not have known him in our day-to-day
goings-ons going awnings is going awnings the word uh he is one of the chillest people
that has ever existed not a lot bad happens around the mine silas runs a really tight ship
and everyone gets paid on time he takes care of his employees and he takes care of the town at
large and you know becker to be a glazed over chill are the tracks that we're following are
they leading into the mine they are leading onto the property you wouldn't be able to
quite trace where they are once they where are the vultures circling they're circling over the
coal residents hey judge and uh custard we should try and get onto this here property
don't you think i think old uh old becker would uh i think he'll be cool with it
yeah he ought to be uh we got a warrant wink wink let's go
took a quick suckle of a teat
so we go to the property
i am
judge preacher doctor
never gets old hello mr piston are you holding
uh roll psychology no no that
oh i rolled a five he looks directly at you in your eyes with super glazed over eyes
no but you know that the answer yes of course uh we're referring to um opium which is entirely
legal uh yeah of course we are i mean i don't know approves of it by and large at this point
i don't think they got any on you it's me asking you know yeah i don't think you can lie to a judge
even outside of court ain't that right custard we want to do your opium have i ever bought opium
from becker yes come on man becker we know you're you're all the opium you're the opium connection
in this town everyone knows and his eyes are closed let him sleep we'll search his cabin
uh hey uh you sure you sure to be on that last one remember i know it's hard to count and you're
in the state you're in but uh come on man like a big man needs a lot of opium it takes a bit
roll intimidate
48 on a 60
okay hey do it look at me and i like lean down from my horse and get like an inch from his face
and like spit a little chew down at his feet hand it over
and becker piston's eyes very large just slowly hand trembling
reaches into his vest pocket and pulls out a small little bottle uh can you not take it all
because this is i get out a uh pre-rolled cigarette and like drip the opium all over it
and then hand him and hand him the bottle back
professor green snatches it in mid pass and takes a dropper of it
every time there's drugs in the role-playing game everybody wants to do if you if you if
you'll remember it's my idea to do your drugs first you get the credit then i just wanted us
to hit all errors after i do that i light the cigarette up and take a few drags and then kind
of like hand it reach over to horace you know i don't agree with you about much but i do agree
with you about um well you know uh roughing up this old opium fiend for his stash as he's smoking
the cigarette i like take a few pulls from my flask and it's like dribbling down my chin i'm
like i declined the flask but i pass it on to the group along with the cigarette
oh interesting uh preacher sheriff bobby custard passes the cigarette oh were you not gonna give
hora sees him go for that and he's like he he remembers that all right you're in the fab five
so he starts to yank it away and then reluctantly he's like all right well he just passes the
cigarette immediately back to ever at pace and takes a drag off the flask uh ever it's gonna
take the cigarette and and look at it kind of funny huh okay i gave the stuff up a while here
here you go jack uh which wait i i'm a medical doctor more or less it will uh it will calm your
nerves i don't i don't have any nerves preacher sheriff doctor kind of ticks his head to the side
oh oh as much as you oh as much as you custard i make all my important decisions on this stuff
i don't have any nerves yeah
jack pearlman's gonna take just the the tiniest drag off the drag yeah bill clinton drag off the
the cigarette since he's been losing a little sanity he figures something to help calm his
nerves a little bit but not a lot because he's not his vices is alky hall and then he takes he
takes a big old pull off the flask though but he wipes it first because he thinks it's nasty
because it is it is it's nasty every pace go ahead and roll listen for me
i pass a 25 on a 40 okay uh everybody else take your headphones off nothing happens
you listen and listen and there's nothing
except for dumbasses doing drugs making their characters a little bit less effective
every pace you're listening well you're just you're just sitting there but well during this
whole conversation about passing the drugs and doing the drugs and everything you hear from the
home of the coals some sort of spat two voices being raised back and forth and then with that
successful listen check you hear you can just make it out it's just traveling on the wind
just enough to reach your ears are you here silas cole say yeah i said it's it's fine
i know how to handle it i know how to handle her she's out just trust me i know how to handle her
or it i know how to handle it i know how to handle her okay she's out just trust me
just trust me okay that's all
hey hey everybody quiet down quiet down let the coals they're they're fighting about something
over there's something going on over at the coal house i don't know how the listen check works if
i do if i point that out can they all hear it then can he share his with us oh we can
we just make checks or uh no however at this exact moment the door of the coal residence
opens and you see silas cole roughed up hair huge pants wearing a belt and suspenders
carrying a rug over his shoulder and he lugs it into the back of his wagon
one of his wagons here on the coal property and he begins unhinging his horses and preparing them
for a trip and i'm gonna roll to see and uh he goes about his business slowly and steady-handedly
oh shit fellas i think there might be i think there might be somebody in that rug i heard him
say i heard him say that he he had handled it and and he knew how to handle her and that she was out
and i didn't know what that meant but what if he meant that she was knocked out what if she's in
that rug i believe that that theory is plausible mr pace judge sheriff should we yeah should we
i say confront ourselves should we confront him now or i say any excuse to string that
boy but judge he is the reason that this town is what it is if we get rid of silas cole
contention is nothing you're gonna get him let him get away with murder well we get at least i mean
we could talk to him before we're done hanging by a rope well i wasn't gonna hang him before
we find out who would kill i didn't say he killed anybody i think she might just be knocked out
it's he says she's out custard i think we should ride which way hey becker anybody else come
through here recently uh no just the normal stuff no work today so why is that mary and
silas had stuff they needed to take care of sounds fishy well i didn't have fish last night but the
night before i did oh you said sounds not smells i was worried that maybe shut up i was letting
off a stink that you shut up let's go custard i think we should ride towards silas and stop him
before he does something he might regret hey on now hang on now there's a chance that silas is
the good guy here what if he found miss kitty she was in a tizzy she he knocked her out and he's
bringing her back into town as we speak maybe we should go ask about that in a rug i mean if
he's doing something that's okay we get to talk to him and feel him out see if he's nervous you
know are we like uh hidden behind a rock or something no uh roll stealth actually all of
us asking that question no just thomas i just just wanted to make a joke about coughing and saying
keith really loud and seeing if he looks
74 on professor horse green super stealthy nope he has the baseline 20
uh then there is not a big rock here and you could have made that rock appear brother
that's how i like to roleplay oh god ever is tottering out toward their wagon let's go let
me make a roll here real quick actually um now i'll roll it when you yell keith because you don't
do it in actuality because you wouldn't know to do that that'd be a wild thing it was it's about
something else sorry thomas yelled keith really loud and then silas cole immediately looked up
thomas busted his head into the truman show like through the dome above
like danny devito coming out of that couch
oh mr cole oh don't go through okay mr cole mr cole we did you find her and silas cole looks up
and sees three horses five men talking to his security and ever at pace and the preacher
sheriff dr bobby custard on the other side on the inside of his gate preacher on the horse and
ever just tottering in and silas hears did you find her and freezes in his tracks
uh what do you mean her and you guys are like a hundred yards away from each other
miss kitty you were at the meeting we're all looking for her we think she might have ran
into your mind over there uh no no good luck are you sure who's in the rug i'm a judge i i've seen
people lie before we should probably go questioning more thanks for coming by i appreciate you guys
asking let's uh like trot our horses yeah kind of faster towards them yeah jack kicks gets jeremiah
are you selling that rug
uh yep how much i'm in the market for one can i take a look yes lay it out he'd like to inspect
it for stains shit he like literally kicks the dirt at the ground beneath him like a frustrated
villain in a cartoon yeah come on down and check out my rug all right i'll be there in a minute
and little step by little step shaky he goes toward the wagon are you are you walking there
just plow past we trample him on the way
he tumbles under all the horses ever at pace dies
hey silas do you think do you think a body would fit in that rug
preacher sheriff dr bobby custard is good at only one thing and it's riding horses and he uh he
grabs he grabs ever at pace's arm and like lifts you up and throws you on the back as he's riding
hey that was a nice trick i didn't break your arm did i i sure hope not
come on yeah let me i grabbed my dice i was like well fuck
no you're good so you guys ride up and silas kohl is messing with the reins and and the horse
like bdsm stuff saddle uh other ropes i don't know what it's all called you got it tack
you can call it all tack see that's that good shit that i was looking for
and he's just kind of messing with that as you guys approach you guys uh all roll animal handling
for me pass oh wait yeah pass oh 33 on an on an 80 oh pass i fail i didn't ask to be on this horse
though so don't you fuck me with this no this is just a knowledge this is a knowledge check
don't you fuck me i didn't ask to be born zach
i decided you were born
judge jack did you pass as well the two of you know silas kohl is un he is disconnecting one
of his horses from this wagon currently as you guys are approaching oh that's fucking dope
what what you doing there you're not gonna use the wagon anymore block him right right in front
of him just uh getting ready to sell this rug to one of you fine gentlemen i want to ride am
i doing the character voice good luke we'll just dub me in there i want to ride my horse like
super quick to get like right up next to him like how far away are we at this point actually with
that crit on animal handling you can get right up next to him before he is finished doing what
he was doing i just pull up next to him and what you doing nothing a busy day today yeah why was
the mines shut down like i said busy day today that doesn't tell me much well maybe uh if you
stayed in your fucking courthouse instead of coming down here where money's actually made
for the town well maybe if you didn't rip the fucking copper wire out of my courthouse i could
be working i did no such thing i heard otherwise what'd you hear i heard maybe your wife had
something to do with it my wife i got witnesses
my life silas kohl would immediately say my wife
we're not in junior high here what is what is what is that accent and what is junior high
you're both speaking like fools if you could tell me why you're here judge open that rug up
okay let's get everybody's dexterity real quick oh no wait do we need a roll or just
tell you oh actually yeah fuck yeah let's roll dexterity so we're rolling against dexterity
blackjack rules and we'll go in order well then not so cool i got a 10 what do you mean blackjack
rules highest goes first classic without going over but not over price is right rules yeah normal
the the game mechanics rules that we always yeah nope i failed 81 on 45. 97 on a 40
oh my god i fail a 31 on a 30 i was so close so bad judge ephraim courtland you are up first
after i tell him to open the rug up what does he do he reaches for his gun i reach for my gun and
aim it at him whoa whoa whoa now i was i was only readjusting my holster can i spit chew on his face
yes please spit chew in keith's face of course you can his name is silas cole thomas right
you can roll intimidate okay to see if you hit or not 52 on a 60. oh fuck describe it baby
i aim the gun at him and he's like whoa i'm just adjusting my thing and i go sure and just right
onto his face a big like i haven't drank water only whiskey recently so it's just a thick
whiskey chewing tobacco blob just sticks to his forehead uh yeah go ahead and roll a d6
and we'll see if it's a one two or three he'll be disabled for one round if it's a four five
six he's disabled for two rounds five two rounds uh fucking thick ass glob just covers both his eyes
fill him with lead boys and can i just stumble can i jump off my horse backwards
and no fuck you no great turn you did stay on your horse i'm telling a story
he stumbles backwards and his hand comes off of his holster and he just falls through his knees
and begins collecting dirt from the ground and trying to get the the juices out of his
eyes and he's just like oh it burns preacher sheriff dr bobby custard hops off of his horse
and grabs a pair of shackles from his side bag and begins approaching silas cole and it is everett
pace's turn he's gonna he's gonna hold out his hands to bobby custard help me down help me down
the reason that preacher sheriff dr bobby custard couldn't get all the way to putting the
shackles onto silas cole is because he turned around halfway and helps everett pace off of
bucky i put you up there it would be a shame if i didn't help you down it just go quicker is all
i want to if i can move around to toward the back of the wagon toward the carpet
yeah uh you can get to the back of the carpet and when you get there
you see in the bottom of this rug that has been rolled up a pair of shoes and the tread
of these shoes is something you've never seen before first off they're like kind of white-ish
tread and that's just not a thing and there's a logo on the bottom of them which you've never seen
before a little thing that says est 1949 roll intelligence i pass a six on a 60 then that
means you get to roll sanity oh shit oh yeah i'm good at that i pass 14 on an 80 what do you
tell yourself she got weird shoes nailed it
jack promen you're up uh i'm gonna be making my way towards uh the down
i thought you were frozen i was trying to do it was perfect
no i'm going towards silas cole with gun held on like the the holding onto the pistol no actually
you know what fuck it i have the rifle out at this point but i'm not aiming it at him i'm just
holding it while walking towards him menacingly yeah yeah uh because i want to help subdue him
basically not hurt him sure horse green you're a blast sorry professor horse green thank you
horse horse gets off the horse and um draws his pistol on silas cole and like unsteadily walks up
to support everybody else but it's not he's he's not trying to get into it he barely looks like
he's held a pistol before judge uh i get down off my horse and i want to aid the sheriff in
blocking him up or shackling him or whatever he was doing okay silas cole is continuing to try to
try to get this dirt on his eyes but he is still second round of this horrible can i add something
to what how i help yeah i just want to push him down okay so preacher sheriff dr bobby custard
and judge f from courtland walk up behind silas cole and the judge six foot ten puts one of his
big ass boots on the back of silas cole and just silas hits the ground and immediately preacher
sheriff dr bobby custard is on top throw shackles on his wrists behind his back grabs the back of
his shirt and lifts him back up so he is on his knees and he is shackled pace it's evert's turn
fellas we got a body our suspicions confirmed there's a body rolled up in this carpet back here
and somebody somebody come help me pull it out is it kitty i don't know i just see i just see the
feet right now i don't even know they could be alive still we we gotta get them out of here are
those strange shoes on the feet yeah she got weird shoes on pearlman you're up jack uh wanders over to
evert pace to give a hand and check them shoes out horse are you doing the same has silas cole
been disarmed he's shackled but they haven't disarmed him from his holster yet i want to walk
up and take silas's gun done is it a crazy noisy cricket no he'd be fitting in yeah like doing mad
science experiments all over town just blending in
actually it looks come to think of it it's this old revolver uh it's like got wood on the sides
and this like big ass cylinder
oh
oh no nothing else strange about it just a big cylinder on this motherfucker fucking dope
ah henry points it at himself and wants to end it all who does oris
do
no it's not the end we're not there yet oh if that happened
fuck you let me take chorus to the future uh let me go p real quick also there's no
weird tubes or lights or anything on it but i'm gonna go pee also same i'm not gonna good
joe just stay there you fuck now i can be mean to you no one's here to hear what i'm saying
done already did the peas though i don't piss seven times in my pants all
it's recording the whole time we're recording piss my britches just now
thomas that thought that green light was lit baby he thought there were tubes on that gun
and he was ready to leave but it also would make any sense to uh for his character to shoot himself
henry henry would never do something like that
so
the guy who i prevented from drinking his own throw up one night because he
because he's because he threw up into his water glass after drinking games and he was about to
drink and i was like no i'd like grab his cup from him it's like you're gonna die you said that
at a funeral do what what are you eating there bud hot dog
i can't wait to try to cut that into something
damn a hot dog every episode just starts with hot dog
it's like our absolute get it cut to the drums of no backbone
do you guys want me to make you one yeah please boil some dogs over and leave them on your
doorstep for me wait boil you don't like boiled dogs no you gotta put it in the microwave
oh boilings no that is all you have to do microwave with water fucking put it in
put it in the bun you don't even need water just put it in the bun and microwave it for
30 seconds and it tastes exactly like a fucking boiled dog that's true i don't like my buns
microwaved you hey man if you want to feed yourself in exactly 30 seconds that's actually
a good i never do it cannot be beat do you like a good cold hot dog no you don't know
it's different it's different when i will eat a cold hot dog i used to like cold hot
dogs and then i had one recently and it was not the thing that i remember like my taste buds had
changed or something i was not into it leaves on your teeth yeah exactly uh positive i'd say no
hot dogs are bad the type of dogs they used to use when extinct so for you the cold ones don't
taste as good now that's true i like bread pug meat yeah if i'm eating a dick sandwich it's going
to be a brat for sure controversial opinion but hot dogs are way better i like both for different
reasons but i think i like hot dogs more my dad has been making his own brats lately and they're
fucking great my daddy's brats are better than yours oh no he's back he's arrived i love my dad's
sausage so what i what i like to do that god if you boil them and you slice them dogs in half
lengthwise i think like where and then you fry them in a pan hot dog style yeah that can be good
they get a good crust on the bottom and you can throw them on a sandwich instead of eating them
on a bun because they come out to like being more of a rectangular square so you got log sandwich
yeah it's flat on the bottom and then like round on the top if that makes sense oh no i love it
the shape you cut it completely in half or do you leave a little bit so it's all one piece no i don't
do that oh you mean like yeah so they splay open right but it's still connected yeah but it's still
open like so yeah if this is your hot dog like a hoagie and then you splay it open no like
justin's mom when you split my mom in half and fryer or like that fucking dude in bone tomahawk
holy shit have you guys seen that movie bone tomahawk bone tomahawk these guys should both
watch it it's fucking brutal i watched it to like get myself set up for running this old west story
which clearly like i learned a ton about the old west and the ceiling fans horse in horse garters
or whatever what about bone tomahawk yeah he's on he's on my uh celebrity pass list
the hidden character bone tony yeah it was a dlc code on halloween if you collect 12
tapes the 13th one is of thomas and bone tomahawk when thomas is on one of his passes
thomas is waggling his eyebrows who knows if any of this will be in the actual let's hope not
all right i pray to god every day yeah we're in the we're like in the middle of a oh yeah what
were we doing we were in combat and it is now technically at an end because silas cole is done
got and so judge and preacher sheriff doctor are both behind the shackled silas cole and ever at
pace is around back of this wagon looking at this rug and the feet that are inside of it with shoes
that he does not recognize but they're just weird and pearlman and green are walking around back
and the three of them are discussing what to do oh i think jack was helping me pull out the rug
when we left off and now that green uh has disarmed cole he's gonna go help them too ever
at pace jack pearlman and professor horace green you begin moving this rug out from the back of
this wagon the sun is high in the sky and the rug casts a shadow directly beneath it as sweat drips
from each of your brows and this humid summer thick air are you gonna thunk the other side
onto the ground or are you going to like slowly place it onto the ground i figured we'd set it
down and then give it a fun yank so it all unravels horse green says that to the group
i think we should lay it gently on the ground and then give the end a fun uh a fun yank so it
unravels quickly and whatever's inside comes whoop just zipping out but i mean it's it's
it's a person they they could they could be knocked out they could they could get hurt if
we're not careful here whoever is inside sorry yeah i think we should be careful i think we
should over ever come on we can we can do this alone there's a little bit of urgency in evert's
process here i mean he thinks there's a chance that there's a knocked out unconscious person
in here maybe not just a dead body so he's gonna he's gonna try and get her to the ground and
start maybe unrolling it maybe get around to the other side so he can make sure the head is there
and that not not bashed or anything and he wants to unravel the carpet and jack helps as ever at
pace and jack pearlman are doing this kind of slowly unrolling professor horse green kind of
reaches into the middle as it's unrolling and just i got outvoted oh okay i was just gonna
help out your cause i suppose so you guys unroll it slowly but surely and ever is moving his hands
kind of into the rug and you do you feel ahead of hair on the opposite side then i want to i want to
i want to try and stabilize that head neck area as it's unrolling trying to make sure we don't
cause undue harm to that body in there uh yeah go ahead and roll first aid hey i'm glad you asked
because i got a high one i pass uh 54 on a 70 this body that comes rolling slowly gently out of this
rug is wearing clothes that you've never seen before and colors of cloth so bright you'd think
that this teenage girl might be some sort of royalty and her hair is patchy and thin on top
the scalp kind of peeling away holes have formed in the middle of it and all of her skin is the
same way at her cheekbones the skin is so thin that there's a slight cut underneath each eye
fresh cut and so blood is pouring down like tears from eyes that are right below tear ducts
but her eyes are closed until they aren't
oh no until db mitchell lets out a massive deep unnatural
get the brickhouse lady here i think that's german
so
i'm afraid
all around my poor little darling i'm afraid they'll get my darling
can't you hear them wolves howling all around my poor little darling all around
my poor little darling i'm afraid they'll get my darling
so
hot dog