Well, where the shit am I now?
And when the hell are I?
Let me check my map I got from that interdimensional gas station.
Southwest Arkansas.
There ain't possibly a place named like that.
I guess I better put on a good show no matter where or when I am.
Fuck.
I'm coming at you live from wherever I said earlier.
From 694.2 PTBP.
The only radio station that broadcasts from Arkansas.
Probably.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Nathan.
AKA at APOC underscore Golem on Twitter.
From Aberdeen, South Dakota.
Who tweeted about the show and tagged at Pretending Pod.
Which is a praiseworthy thing to do with your fingers.
Nathan writes.
Dearest Edward.
I will see you soon.
I tried to stay strong.
I promised.
And I failed.
I thought I could trap it inside me but now I'm the one trapped.
It is in me now.
It forces me to move against my will.
I scream inside my own head while it makes me do things.
Bad things, Ed.
I'm so sorry.
It comes for you now.
I feel my feet wrench and spasm in a mockery of walking.
As it forces my body to lurch in your direction.
It is patient.
Dearest Edward.
I'm so sorry.
I will see you soon.
Well, you heard the guy, Edward.
He's coming to see you soon.
Sounds like it's gonna be a fun time for you and your BFF.
If you wanna write up something
for your arken-saucy wolf to howl,
tag at PretendingPod on Twitter
or write a five-star review on Apple Podcasts
or I guess also two more things.
Tag at PretendingPod on Instagram, fuck Mark Zuckerberg
or tag pretending to be people on Facebook,
fuck Mark Zuckerberg.
We love it when people are excited
to tell their friends about our show here
but seriously, fuck Mark Zuckerberg.
Maybe Wolfie can give that pasty half alien
the physical delights the human part of him craves.
He ain't never ever met a wolf like me.
And if that excellent pun gave you the blues,
let's see who won in this week's The News.
And that winner from Twitter's mostly bitter litter
is the Twitter outfitter at tdunder-beck
aka Cosplay underscore by underscore Tyler.
He guessed the special guest
who will join Allie, Lindsay, and Taylor
for all five parts of Operation Bigfoot Underground
Search and Hunt.
That's right, Operation Bigfoot Underground Search and Hunt
will be played by the crew who you knew
when they brought you their story in the Contingent Woods
alongside Eleanor DiLorenzo, the delightful creator
and GM of the Lost Mountain saga,
a dedicated role player on the Glass Cannon Network's
Androids and Aliens, the foul-mouthed Twitch streamer
who once laughed so hard she could barely breathe
after reading the name Mike Oxmaul.
Well, better not dwell on that name.
My mouth might get jealous of all that nasty trash
going in the wrong hole.
Let's fill them ears with something that clears the gears.
It's Molly Healy with Circles.
["Circles"]
I'm glad you were honest with us.
Yes.
We're cutting this out.
That's requesting my first cut.
Oh no, the Thomas Roll.
Oh no, it's staying in.
Fuck, Allie, you said it.
Oh no, it was just about to get cut.
Welcome to Pretending to Be People.
I am here with a whole table of special guests here.
We're going to go around the table here.
We're going to start with,
she's played Gerald Fingersen.
She played Sharon Shadow Berryman.
She does the sound of phone calls.
Ring, ring, ring, ring.
It's my wife, Borat Voice.
Taylor.
Hello, I'm his wife.
Did that work the opposite way?
I don't think so.
Anyway, hi.
We have Liz Lonklin, the Doc Martin wearing punk,
the designer of the infamous PTBP fanny pack
that I fucking promise will exist one day.
It's Lindsay.
Hello, I'm Lindsay.
Nailed it.
Just top notch, boom town.
She played Krista Krinklehoff.
It's still hard to say.
She played a bro bot named Brett.
She's my new coworker.
Thanks for getting me the job.
It's Ali.
Hello, I am Ali.
I regret getting him the job.
I'm loud and in the, well, I used to be in the office,
but now no one's in the office.
Woo.
And finally, she's an actor.
She's a standup comedian.
She's a Twitch streamer.
She's a player on Glass Cannon Network,
Starfinder podcast, Androids and Aliens.
She's the creator and GM of her own show,
The Lost Mountain Saga,
which is getting a season two coming soon.
It's Eleanor DiLorenzo, Lindsay.
Woo.
Thanks for the applause, guys.
Thanks.
Oh, there it is.
It was a little delay.
I request that the rest of us also get a echo out.
I'm so sorry.
Honestly, it's doing Eleanor DiLorenzo, it's very good.
No, but also Taylor Reeve, she's the worst of the game.
So today we're playing Delta Green.
I know that that is new to Eleanor here.
Eleanor, are you excited?
I am incredibly excited.
I've been wanting to play this game
ever since I heard about it the first time,
which was in, I don't know, doesn't matter,
but I have been wanting to play it
for a really, really long time.
And I'm so excited that you guys invited me to play
because it seems like you guys know what you're doing
or maybe that's just...
Oh, that's funny.
One of us at this table does.
It's good.
It's good to have your confidence.
It's me.
So a quick rundown of Delta Green.
It's a role-playing game.
Okay, moving on.
So...
That's all you need to know.
Delta Green is a role-playing game about...
Oh, no.
How are you so good on all those other podcasts?
Listen, I've been drunk for the past five years.
I don't even know.
I'm doing dry January.
So this is the first time I'm playing Delta Green
without a beer in my hand in a long time.
Wow.
Congratulations.
It's also till 10 in the morning.
Yup, still would have done it.
Not a doubt in my mind.
It's Saturday.
Saturday's for the boys.
So Delta Green is a role-playing game
about losing your mind or dying
in the process of trying to stop
the inevitable end of the world.
Oh, really?
I thought it was a romantic comedy.
Someone told me it was like a period piece
set in the 19th century Britain.
Yup, based on menstruation.
19th century Arkansas.
We are playing...
This game will be set in Mississippi and Arkansas tonight.
We're gonna kick it off in Mississippi
and then drive on up to Arkansas,
which Eleanor, you had to do some research
on...
What do you mean Mississippi?
I thought it was...
Oh God, I thought it was...
Wait, Mississippi the river or Mississippi the...
It's a city, right?
We're just gonna meet...
The characters are gonna meet in Shreveport,
which is in Mississippi,
but then you're gonna drive into Arkansas.
You don't need to know anything about Mississippi
other than what should she know about Mississippi?
How to spell it.
M-I-S-S-I-S-S-I-P-P-I.
I've been swimming in the Mississippi.
Wait, you swam in the Mississippi?
Maybe, or I took a piss in it.
Actually, that's a Swedish saying.
Take a piss in the Mississippi.
Actually, that's what my mom says all the time.
Like when something is irrelevant,
it's like fart in space,
but we also say it's a piss in Mississippi.
Oh, that's really good.
Yeah, P-I-S-S-I-S-S-I-P-P-I.
Piss is hippie.
Has anyone ever thought of that?
Are we the first?
Oh my God.
Google it.
Google it before you tweet it.
Okay, so just gonna give you a rundown.
So normally Delta Green is a game
with a lot of really fantastic scenarios
that are written for it
and published by Arc Dream Publishing,
which is a publishing company that publishes games
and scenarios for Delta Green.
However, instead of running
one of their extremely well-written and edited scenarios,
I'm gonna run you through something I wrote
that's just in a Google doc here.
Hell yeah.
All right, well.
I don't think Zach's killing children in this.
Based on his face.
Gonna run a different scenario.
Don't worry about it.
Kill as many children you want and puppies.
Monster.
That's what I was waiting to hear.
All right, so let's meet these characters, shall we?
Let's dive in here.
Let's go in alphabetical order of first name
of real life human.
Allie.
Hello.
Who is your character?
What's she look like?
What's her deal?
What's she been up to?
Give us the rundown.
I would love to.
Thank you.
I'm gonna pull up my summary of my character.
You guys all, I asked this group
to answer some questions that I'd sent
and then to write a little bit of backstory
about how they ran into the unnatural.
And all four of you did an absolutely stellar job.
Should we do season two together as a group
instead of the normal?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Bye.
Okay, my name is.
Joke.
Oh no, not again.
Do you remember that?
I remember that it's a joke.
I just don't remember why.
You started it.
This happens to me all the time.
I'm just making so many jokes all the time.
All right, here we go.
My name is Rusty Hooch.
I am a scientist.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I didn't choose my name.
My parents did.
They chose your last name?
Yeah, totally.
So you're Dr. Hooch?
I'm Dr. Hooch.
Rad.
Yeah.
The Hooch.
They call me Rusty.
What kind of science do you do?
Mostly like potions and stuff.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Well, I did just win a Nobel Prize
for curing mad cow disease.
Congratulations.
Did you do it with potions?
I did it with potions.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm hoping to cure tinnitus next.
Okay, yes.
And also the emotion sadness
because I think it's unnecessary.
Unnecessary emotion sadness.
Unnecessary negative emotion,
which I will be curing with potions.
I love this so much.
How old is she?
47.
47 going on 53.
Going on 53.
A Nobel Prize winner at 47
we're amongst a genius.
In the presence of greatness.
I'm also very hot.
Yeah.
Okay.
I love you so much.
Just let that be known.
What's your charisma score?
Nine.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
That's like the lowest charisma
you can have to start.
Good.
Because you said that
your character leans into like.
Yeah, I'm kind of mean.
People see me as kind of
an obsessive relentless bitch,
but I would never have been able
to cure mad cow disease
if I wasn't a relentless bitch.
What's your haircut?
Short, blonde.
Bangs.
I don't know where I got that.
Also, I'm hot.
Don't forget.
And what are you typically wearing?
Normally black trench coat.
Probably some pearl earrings.
Whatever your hot people wear
is what I'm normally wearing.
My God.
I'm sensing a lot of Robin
Robin Wright from House of Cards.
Like that sort of vibe.
Yes.
Yeah.
But hotter.
Oh wow.
But hotter and Nobel Prize winner.
I love it.
Exactly.
Humble.
And humble.
All right.
Give me a rundown.
What was your experience like
the first time you saw something unnatural?
Let me tell you about it.
So I was flying my DA40 home.
I have a DA40.
A small plane.
Of course.
The DA40.
Yeah, I know.
I looked it up.
Yeah, so I own one
and I know a lot about it
and I know how to fly it.
So I was flying it home
to my secret cabin in the woods
that none of my children or ex-wives know about
because I like my privacy.
Smart.
So one night I was flying my Diamond DA40 home
and I saw a gigantic explosion come from the woods
but I didn't hear it.
It was completely silent.
It was blue and wet looking.
Ew.
Thank you for that.
Silent and wet and blue.
Silent and wet.
So I landed my plane nearby,
ran down the road to where I thought I was close to it,
hiding because I was afraid of who might be back there.
And then five minutes later I saw six black escalates
drive past on the road.
I was hiding in a bush.
Also my plane was covered by a...
No need to get too deep into the weeds.
My plane was hidden.
Into the weeds that are covering your plane.
And they couldn't see it.
Anyway, then I ran to the side of the explosion
and there was nothing.
I couldn't see anything.
Nothing was different.
Not a leaf turned.
Not a branch broken.
Not a stone unturned.
Not a stone turned.
Ever since then, whenever I'm flying my Diamond DA40 home,
that I know how to fly.
Brag.
A brag about a fictional character.
So I've just been seeing a lot of these silent explosions
but I can't seem to get close enough to see what's going on.
How many X's do you have?
Hard to say.
Science is easy.
Counting is hard.
Three, at least three.
Well, some marriages were like, you know,
Vegas marriages.
Do those count?
Like that's kind of a half marriage.
Legally, they do, yeah.
So your most recent one is...
Oh, Jillian.
Yes, Jillian.
Jillian didn't sign a prenup before we got married.
That's my bad.
Smart lady.
You would think I would have learned my lesson.
So she's receiving quite a bit of alimony from me right now,
unfortunately.
But I'm rich, so it's fine.
Rich and hot, rich and hot, humble and fucking smart.
Genius.
Ally, when you play a role playing game,
you're supposed to create a character
that is different than yourself
to try to embody someone else.
Yeah, because I actually am a pilot in real life.
Really?
And I have a diamond DA40.
I thought you were gonna say pile of garbage.
I don't know why.
I'm a pile of garbage.
Yes, Eleanor, I am a pilot.
No, stop lying to Eleanor.
I'm so disappointed now.
I was like, oh, I could hire her as my pilot
when I become rich, famous, noble, priceless.
Okay, no, I'll learn.
I'll learn.
Yes, please.
Tell me about Belvedere.
Oh, so Jillian and I share custody of a...
Dog.
Hold on, no, I have to actually look up at the dog.
Saint Bernard.
My ex-wife Jillian and I share custody of a Saint Bernard.
His name is Belvedere.
I love him very much.
I have him on the weekends.
We take a lot of hikes, but Jillian has him
during the week.
It's Monday night.
You're getting ready to go drop off Belvedere at Jillian's.
This is the last moment that you get to spend
with your beloved Saint Bernard
before he goes and spends the week with Jillian
and her money that you pay her.
My money.
All of a sudden you hear cars, more than one,
they're pulling up outside.
You look out the window, you see the string
of those black SUVs, and they are lining your driveway,
but only one guy is walking up to the door and he knocks.
He keeps knocking.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Yes!
I mean, you couldn't help yourself.
I just helped yourself.
He couldn't help yourself.
Maybe I could.
Sound person.
Are you a fully artist?
I don't know what that means.
We have to get through all of these.
This whole episode is just Allie's introduction.
Allie, banging now on your door.
I don't answer.
Banging.
Louder and louder.
Is Belvedere upset?
Okay, I answered the door very reluctantly,
and I don't have one of those locks on the top of the door,
the chain locks, and I don't undo that.
Dr. Rusty Hooch?
Yes, can I see some identification, please?
What are you doing at my house?
Yeah, no problem.
He holds up his hand as if he's holding a badge
of some sort.
There's literally nothing in his hand.
And he says, you don't really need to know who I am.
We've been following you, and we understand
that you've been noticing some situations
that have been happening out in the woods.
I think due to some of your expertise,
we're gonna need your help.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't go in the woods.
I live in the city.
Dr. Hooch.
And he calls out your plane's number,
like your ID number.
Look around you.
What am I supposed to be seeing right now?
Well, I suppose it's your choice.
Do you see all those SPVs down there?
Yes.
You can come with us.
Maybe you'll learn something.
All right, well, I have to take Belvedere
to Jillian's house, my ex-wife,
because she has them during the week.
So I'll come with you, but I gotta take my dog first.
Any chance that I can get you to leave your dog here
until we're done?
It won't take too long.
It's a legal issue.
I'll really get in a lot of trouble from Jillian
if I don't have him there by 10 p.m. on Monday night.
We're gonna have you back by 10.
Oh, all right, all right.
As long as we can get Belvedere to Jillian, fine.
I'll go with you.
Okay, so you guys head out.
You get into an SUV.
It's actually empty, this one, except for a driver,
and this unidentified man gets into the car with you,
and he begins asking you about how many times
you've seen these silent blue explosions.
You guys pull up to a small camp in the woods
that's being run out of the back of a big truck.
So there's just this one covered truck
with a bunch of lab equipment inside of it,
computers going, scientists running around
talking to each other.
There's a bunch of military-looking guys
who are not wearing camo or any sort of military gear.
One of them approaches you with a, it's like a jar.
It's not a mason jar.
It's far more scientific.
It seems to be sealed on both sides.
It looks like a high-tech version of the bank teller thing
that you put in the tube, right?
And it is filled with this like bioluminescent blue liquid.
We're hoping that you can reverse engineer this.
I'm gonna need to know some more information
before I do anything for y'all.
Do you know who I am?
I just won a Nobel Prize for inventing mad cow disease.
I'm gonna need some context.
It's not gonna hooch.
We know exactly who you are.
Let's show her some context.
And a couple of the military guys go over to one of the SUVs
and pull out a guy who is bound.
He's wearing just like the raddest old clothes
you've ever seen.
Looks like he hasn't showered in months.
Filthy, filthy dude.
He's just kinda like dazed.
Looks like he's been drugged.
They kinda pull him out into the middle
of this clearing in the woods.
All right, come with me, come with me.
He walks you over to this guy
who's just kinda like put down on his knees,
hands tied behind his back, feet are bound.
And he opens up this container and it, oh, sorry, Taylor,
do you wanna do the opening of the container?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Psst.
Got it in one.
Nailed it.
He puts a finger in this like bioluminescent goop
and it kind of sticks to him like paint.
And then he draws a symbol on this bound man's forehead
and it kind of looks like waves that have teeth,
this weird symbol.
And then he closes the container.
Taylor?
Psst.
Pfft.
God.
It's art.
And he starts counting down.
39, 37.
And he says, we're gonna wanna get away.
42, 38, 35.
And you guys are walking and you see that other people
are walking extremely quickly.
And he is not, he's chilling.
He kinda turns back.
Are you ready to see the craziest thing you've ever seen?
I highly doubt this is gonna be the craziest thing
I've ever seen.
I've seen my dog take a giant shit in my Diamond DA40.
In it.
A bioluminescent explosion begins to pour out
of the bound dude's face and fill the ground around you.
And it begins to create a massive dome
that is engulfing this guy
and then slowly expands and takes over.
And as it's taking over, the guy looks at you next to you
and he's like, it would be all right.
This blue hits your face.
Your hair blows back and suddenly you see inside
and you are standing in seemingly the middle of the ocean.
You see all of this wildlife around you.
Fish, schools of fish swimming together.
Sharks, part of a whale at the dome
on the far side away from you.
And there's coral everywhere and it's dark
and it's blue and it's glowing.
And then suddenly it just collapses in on itself.
The only change is that this bound dude is gone.
What the fuck?
Shit.
Well, so first I checked my pocket mirror
to check my hair since it got messed up.
So I fixed my hair first.
As you're staring at yourself,
you see that your lips and your eyes,
your nostrils, your eyebrows,
everything on your face is fucking trembling.
You've never seen yourself look this shook.
I'm going to sue the shit out of you motherfuckers.
What did you just do to me?
You get a phone call from Jillian.
I walk up into the woods to take this call.
And that is Dr. Rusty Hooch.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
Radical, radical, radical.
It's now a good time to say that I'm afraid of sharks.
In real life or the character?
In real life.
Oh, for real?
In the character, yeah.
Okay, Ellie.
Oh my God.
You're up.
Give me a rundown.
Dr. Olivia Miller.
I based this off of the Swedish crime dramas
because every protagonist in Swedish crime dramas
is the exact same dude.
But in this case, I just made it a female.
Early fifties, incredibly tired woman.
Like everything about her is so freaking over it.
Like mentally tired, physically tired.
She has two daughters.
One of them won't speak to her
because she's a 15 year old little bitch.
And the other one is off to college,
but it's like teen daughters.
We all know, we all know what they're like.
She was recently left by her husband for a younger model.
And she's just so freaking tired.
You know, she's a workaholic.
She's a surgeon.
She's a very brilliant surgeon.
She's been doing that for a long time
and people call her for the tough cases.
But since everything else in her life sort of fell apart,
she's been really burying herself in work.
Takes on extra hours.
She's on call almost all the time.
And she's gained a couple of extra pounds
because she's not taking care of herself.
She picked up smoking because it was the only thing
that sort of calmed her nerves.
Even though she knows it's wrong, she's a doctor.
Lots of fast food, very little exercise.
And the idea I had in my head for her was Bill Murray
because of this constant through the signs, sad face,
but like a female version.
It's amazing.
I'm picturing Kate Winslet in mayor of East town.
I don't know if you saw that.
Yeah, that's very exactly that type of like,
because that's basically every crime drama
of like this resigned brilliant detective
just being so freaking like tired of everything.
But then like, well, I've seen worse or have I, you know.
Are there any happy detectives?
I don't think so.
I don't think you can be happy and be a detective,
but we shall see maybe in this game.
Maybe she'll find joy.
Yes, I think in this game, we'll find joy.
Yeah, psych.
That's true.
God, that show is great.
Eleanor, you've created like the opposite character from Ally.
The two doctors, Dr. Rusty Hooch and Dr. Olivia Miller,
both in name and juxtaposition could not be further
from each other.
Fun thing though, my charisma is 13, so I'm charming,
which I didn't realize.
But she's also started sleeping with her neighbor
because that's like the one, also another takeaway.
And so her neighbor kind of wants something more to happen,
but she's just like, no, no,
this is a very transactional thing going on.
But it's one of her bonds because they sort of drink whiskey
and play chess together or something boring.
I was about to say that sounds fun.
Yeah, I wrote for her tagline,
she's technically a lovely woman in need of a hug
and hopefully other things.
What was it, the occult or the unnatural or whatever?
The unnatural.
Yeah, when you asked that question,
I was just like, wait, what?
Because I thought for some reason thought this was like,
I've been trying to not read up on Delta Green
because I love going into something spoiler free.
And then I'm like, so there is an element of unnatural
because people have told me it's terrifying,
but I wasn't sure if it was like murder mystery terrifying
or if it's like, you know, unnatural, but now I know.
And so-
Little column A, little column B.
I envisioned her to say she's a very good surgeon.
She was called in for this weird case,
an autopsy of a corpse and what she found out
as she was doing it,
she had to extract this thing out of the body,
this black gooey blob of fat, basically.
And as she was picking it up really carefully,
it started like moving in a way
that suggested it's still alive.
And then she had to move it into a separate jar
and some people in black suits just took it away.
No more questions needed, so to speak.
Awesome, so awesome.
Dr. Olivia Miller, it's a school night.
And strangely, your 15-year-old
has requested a movie night with her mom.
This is very out of the ordinary.
How do you react?
What movie do you suggest?
Oh, I've heard that the latest
Downton Abbey movie just came out.
Would you like to watch that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, let's do that.
Or we can watch a Star War.
Okay, no, the Downton Abbey sounds nice, actually.
Just something calming would be good.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, honey?
Is everything all right?
It's fine.
It's just, can we talk for a second?
Of course.
Let me just...
Your front door starts rattling
and someone is just boom, boom, boom, boom.
Jesus, honey, please, just sit down.
I'll get you a...
Dr. Miller, Dr. Miller!
Fucking Christ, what is it?
And she walks over to the door.
If you peek your head through the window
or see through the peephole,
you see that the team of those men
who took away the jar with that fatty tissue
that seemed to be alive in it last time,
they are here at your home
and they have in custody a woman
who is shaking violently and screaming,
please, just fucking kill me!
Just fucking kill me!
All right, she quickly opens the door because-
They barge in.
They just boom, barge in, take over.
The men slam this woman on your kitchen table
and this woman is just like, please, please, kill me!
Doctor, doctor, we need you to...
Sorry, she's not dead yet, but we have to remove it.
You have to remove it.
Do you have any equipment here?
Of course.
And immediately she goes into professional mode
and takes out her medical equipment
and starts ordering everyone around like,
you, get me a towel, you there, start heating up,
like start disinfecting my tools and that she-
Yeah, somebody's got the stove going,
you got towels coming in, we got everything you need.
They've knocked off your bar cart.
They've like shoved everything off the top of the bar cart
and put it next to the table to put all the supplies on it.
And she looks at her daughter though, like, Laura, please,
I need you to-
What is happening?
Honey, you need to go to your room right now.
We need to go to your room and you stay there
and I'll find you soon.
Okay, and you're right back to business
and you're looking over the situation.
You see on this woman's neck,
there's just this kind of like,
pulsating sack of fat and fluid.
Meow.
She tries to do like an incision or like tries to-
Try and roll surgery for me.
Ooh, my first roll.
You said, okay.
Oh, I don't know, that's probably a fail.
It's 83 and I think I did put, oh no.
Yeah, that's a fail.
I only have 15 surgery, fuck.
As you cut it open, this fatty tissue begins to pour out
like you've seen it kind of jiggle in your hand earlier.
It's moving on its own.
It busts out.
You've accidentally cut it.
Your hand has slipped.
You didn't just cut through the skin.
You actually cut into the tissue itself.
The thing begins to unfold and twist itself inside out
as it turns to dust and this dust flies up into the nose
of one of these black-suited agents
and immediately one of the other agents goes,
oh, fucking Jason, pulls his gun and fires it
into the back of this guy's head.
As he hits the ground in your kitchen,
he fires three more times shattering the tile
underneath this guy's head.
You just had the kitchen redone.
You look over and at the end of the hallway,
you see your 15-year-old daughter is just staring in shock
from behind her door.
That's Dr. Olivia Miller.
Jesus Christ.
Hey, Ellie, Eleanor, welcome to Delta Green.
Yeah, oh my God.
Oh my God.
Well, cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
Next up, it's Lindsay.
Alphabetically.
Lindsay.
Hello.
Tell me about, what is this character's name?
Doreen Maureen, if you will.
Really just Doreen and then anything
that rhymes with Doreen.
Oh, anything.
If you go on for too long,
are we gonna call you Doreen Boring?
Yes, yes.
Boom, if you know a lot about the setting,
we'll call you Doreen Loring.
Oh my God.
When you go swimming, we call you Doreen Chlorine.
Genius name.
Doreen's pretty simple.
She's, just imagine like simple, super down to earth.
She's a fed agent, she's 45
and she doesn't really have a whole lot of friends.
She has a very, very small group of friends
and then it's just like no family anywhere close.
It's just me and my whippet, which is my-
Your drug of choice.
Gotcha, boom.
Y'all ever done nitrous?
It's both that and it is a type of dog.
It's a, imagine a teeny tiny gray hound.
A little scared, a little shaky, really thin.
That's my dog.
She's pretty lonely, but likes it that way.
So she's pretty run down.
She's got like box dyed hair.
It's grown out quite a bit since last time she's dying.
So she's got some dark gray roots coming in.
She's got some sunken eyes
and she just wears like super baggy clothes and-
Baggy clothes that I believe you wrote.
Baggy clothes like she's ready
to shoplift a bag of marshmallows.
That's how I'm referring to all baggy clothes from now on.
Like she's ready to shoplift a bag of marshmallows.
She's ready.
Yeah, so she's more fun on the page than in person.
Her favorite-
She's more fun on the page than in person.
A perfect character for a role-playing game.
Yeah, she's always just like got pockets full
of like the wrapping of hard candy.
I got a pocket full of hard candy, oh my God.
I'm so tired.
When you leaned into the mic, Allie,
I expected you to join me.
No, I'm exhausted.
So disappointed.
God damn it.
And then, yeah, it's either that
or just some loose Mentos in there all the time.
She just got trash in her car.
I got a pocket full of loose Mentos.
I'm not even gonna look at you.
I tried to join, but then I just, I just couldn't.
I'm sorry.
She spends a lot of her extra time just like scrolling
on Pinterest on her iPad and like petting her with it.
Jesus Christ.
Honestly, that's all you needed to say
to get a full idea of who this woman is.
I know this woman.
She just scrolls Pinterest on her iPad.
I know who this is based off of someone I know.
Your mom?
Is it your mom?
It's based off of my mom.
I was gonna say, it sounds like I was doing a burn,
but I think it's probably, she's just literally my mom.
Is it your fucking mom?
He's just your fucking mom.
She religiously listens to this podcast, you know.
I think she would be appalled.
She would.
She absolutely would.
Mom, if you're listening to this,
only portions of this are based off of your mom.
Not for moms.
Except for Eleanor.
She can listen.
That mom can listen.
Eleanor, you're allowed to listen.
Otherwise, not for moms.
I think we have a lot of mom listeners, actually.
I'm so sorry I discriminated against the mom community.
I didn't mean it.
Can you, I mean, if you're at home all day
caring for your child, what better to listen to than-
Horror comedy.
Oh, for sure.
On behalf of all moms, I am incredibly offended,
but also a little aroused.
I think that's a green light.
All right, I think we know who this woman is
just based off that comment alone,
so let's dive into her experience with the unnatural.
All right, her experience,
it's caused a lot of trauma for Doreen.
I was called in on a murder case.
I had been working on this case for a while,
and I, oh, and do I need to read it in my case?
Hey, I don't know if you're gonna do a fresh person, maybe.
One night.
There we go.
I get this call one night,
and it's from an unknown number.
So I answer the phone,
and somebody's telling me to meet them
at a location I'm unaware of.
I didn't know this place existed.
I decide it's a good idea
since this case has been going for a while
and I'm really tired of it, ready to end this case.
So I show up at this house.
I open the front door
because the door's just kind of leaning open a little bit.
When I walk in,
everything is just covered in black rubber,
the walls, the ceilings.
You can see that there are things in this house,
but they're all just covered in this black rubber.
Sorry, I got...
Sorry.
You spooked yourself?
I scared myself.
Oh, my God.
No, I scared.
Are you really scared of rubber?
It was Ramona.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I could smell the rubber.
I can smell it.
It reminded me of the time I forgot to use a rubber.
Why do all my jokes keep going back to condoms?
Condoms and condoms.
I gave penis on the brain.
Penis on the brain.
Penis, penis on the brain.
No one wanted to keep going on that.
I danced.
All right.
Everything inside of this house
is just lined in this rubber,
and it's thick, and it's weird, and it's soft,
and it's making me really uneasy.
So a dick.
As I'm walking through this house,
I start to hear a little bit of laughter,
and it's really creepy, really uneasy.
It's somewhere in the house.
I don't know where it is,
but it's somewhere in this house.
I gotta find who's laughing at me.
The laughter gets stronger.
So I pull out my gun,
and I start walking around gun first,
and I'm looking for where this noise is coming from,
and all of a sudden I see something not covered
in this black rubber, and it's this big old mirror,
and it looks really old, antique,
and it's all rusty on the edges.
And as I'm looking into this mirror,
I see these two little kids,
and they're staring right back at me,
and they're just covered in blood
like someone's just been beaten up.
I'm sorry.
Like someone's just been beaten up.
You immediately recoiled.
Covered in blood.
Just covered from head to toe.
I turn to see what they're doing.
They're standing behind me a little bit.
I turn, and they're not there.
So I turn back, I look at the mirror,
and they start melting.
They're melting into this metallic,
silver, metal-looking lava.
Now they're really in the room with me,
but they're just two puddles of lava,
and they start coming right at me, rolling towards me.
And as I get closer, I start losing my bearings,
and so I start running out of the building,
only to find when I get outside
that there are a bunch of agents in black cars and suits
pointing their gun at me.
I didn't know what to do.
I got called here by someone who I don't know,
so I just start running away in a zigzag pattern,
and I'd never seen them since.
That was the end of my story, though, so.
Dope story.
Terrifying.
Thanks.
The next time we see Doreen Marine,
that'd be hard,
she is on the stand in a courtroom.
It's a bright, sunny day, the sun rays are coming in
through the windows, across one side,
onto half of the people watching.
The lawyer in a smart suit is asking questions
about what happened in that house.
You can see one of those people in the black suits
that were outside, the woman who was up front.
She's sitting in the back row, and she's just staring.
The lawyer continues.
So, how long were you inside the house?
Oh, I don't know.
It couldn't have been longer than maybe 10 minutes.
And did you?
She laughs and rolls her eyes at the jury.
See anything like what the defendant described?
Objection!
Sustained.
Did you see the spooky, melty children in the mirror row?
Objection!
Sustained.
What did you see that night?
I saw them melty, spooky children in the reflection.
There's only one mirror.
I saw them children.
They were coming at me.
The lawyer is just rolling her eyes, looking at the jury.
You literally see some of the jury members
are putting their hands over their mouths
to stifle laughter, and the judge is rubbing his temples.
Cut to the bathroom.
Doreen Marine is splashing water on her face.
Spsh, pow, spsh, spsh, pow.
Ha ha ha ha!
I think I'm getting better at this.
When suddenly,
you start to hear laughter from behind you.
Roll sanity for me real quick.
Ooh.
This is a really good teaching moment.
What'd you roll, Lindsay?
88.
Can you say that a little bit louder for me?
So, in Delta Green, when the dice match,
like 88 or 44 or 22 or 11.
What about 55?
That's another one.
When the dice match, it is critical.
So if it's under your score, that's a critical success.
But when it's over your score in Delta Green,
it's called a fumble or a critical failure.
Critical failure on a sanity check is not good,
especially in an introduction
where we haven't really started playing the game yet almost.
So I'm gonna describe this scene from the perspective
of the federal agent who is sitting in the back row
who just walked into this bathroom
to see Doreen Marine kick in the door of the stall
that was behind her with just nothing in her eyes.
She's just gone, blinded by anger and fear.
She is just slamming two kids' heads into the toilet.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, shit, oh, shit, fuck, fuck.
And you see a vape fall out of one of their hands,
which is why they were in this stall together
in the first place, just vaping,
just getting away from the parents for a little bit,
vaping in the bathroom.
This woman pulls you off of these two teens.
What are you doing, what are you doing, what are you doing?
Look at me, Doreen, Doreen, Doreen.
No one believes you, Doreen, Doreen, I believe you.
We have to get out of here, get out of here, get out of here.
And in this fragile state, Doreen's ready to go
with just about anyone who believes her right now.
And two of you get into a car
and you drive to this warehouse.
I don't wanna freak you out,
but what I'm about to show you,
just know that we're doing a good thing.
And she opens up the door of the warehouse
and you just see it is filled with mirrors
and the smell of rubber is in the air.
That's Doreen Maureen.
Good damn.
God, oh my God, oh my God.
So cool, so fucking cool.
You guys all wrote, rad introductions for your characters.
It makes me so happy.
Now we're on to, I think it says here your name is?
The Chuckster.
My born name is Charles,
but most people call me Chuck.
And if you're a close friend,
you call me the Chuckster.
Should I get into it?
Oh yeah, please.
All right, I am about 34 years old.
I just moved out of my parents' house
about six months ago.
Yeah, thank you.
I'm basically a gamer.
I game and I sleep and I eat mac and cheese
in rotation is what I do.
And so I don't have any physical friends per se,
but I'm really tight with my online community of gamers,
of fellow gamers.
So we don't really know a whole lot about each other
other than our gaming tags and what each other eat
and drink, et cetera.
I am also a partier, solo partier.
I'm crushing them beers.
I'm a solo partier.
Crushing them beers day and night as I play my games.
Is that a partier?
In Missouri it is.
Yeah, I mean, I'm talking to my friends.
They're also crushing beers.
I think so.
What else do you want to know about me?
What do you look like?
I am ginger, my ginger.
Oh, a stud.
Yes, of course I am.
I would say I'm like fat strong.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it's the best way to describe how I look.
About five, six average height and yeah, like fat strong.
So I am very strong, but I got a layer of pudge over it
and I don't like work out or anything.
I guess I have strong thumbs.
Tasty.
From my gaming.
Tasty indeed.
So you are, you were ex-military?
Oh yeah, I'm ex-military.
I don't share this with many people
other than a couple of my tight online community friends,
but I was not dishonorably charged,
but I was like the level below.
Cause I was solo partying a little too hard one night
and maybe did some unsavory activities
involving piss and my Sergeant's bed.
My Sergeant's bed.
Yeah, that is not allowed.
It's not.
Unless the Sergeant's into that sort of thing.
I tell people, I tell people
that I was on a pretty righteous mission,
you know, fighting them baddies
and saving hundreds of children.
I rolled my ankle pretty bad.
So I got the purple heart and the red heart
and a green heart.
And now I'm a veteran of, you know,
the good old USA, getting them checks.
Stolen valor, the character.
I love it.
Great.
All right, so your parents,
you just moved out of their house.
They adore you.
They think that I was honorably discharged
for an injury on the battleground,
but I actually, I actually never,
I actually never saw battle.
Didn't make it there.
I was in my, what's it called?
What you start with when you're practicing for war?
It's the practicing.
The practice battleground.
The practice ground.
I was in the practice round.
What is that called?
You know, you know.
Tweet, tweet at pretending to be people.
Not our tag.
P-T-P-P-P-P-T-T.
Pretending pod to tell her,
are you talking about basic training?
Yeah, that's right.
All right, didn't even make it out of basic.
Sounds good.
Didn't make it out of basic.
Wow.
Yeah, and then I kind of laid low
because I was ashamed and I didn't want my parents to know.
And yeah, then I came back and yeah, stolen valor for sure.
But I was, I mean, I tried to be in the military.
So it's not, it's not that stole.
It's like partial stolen valor.
Question, how hard is it to get into the American military?
Is it hard or is it like-
You just have to have a heartbeat.
So it's Chucky a little pathetic
for not being able to make it out of basic?
Yes.
Oh no, Chucky.
I mean, to be fair, we're speaking about things
we know shit, jack shit about, like-
That's fair.
I don't know much about the military.
I don't think Zach does.
The military industrial complex is ruining the world.
Oh God.
They don't appreciate the chucks of the,
you know, of the nation.
All right, how did you,
how did you come to learn about the unnatural?
Yes. Okay.
So I was gaming with my bros, my brosips one night
and I, no, I can't, I'm not allowed to say that.
Oh, sorry.
No, I'm just shaking my head for fun.
Because brosips is a really stupid word.
That's why.
I was gaming with my brosips and we chat on the side,
you know, and then I've got my whole headset
where I'm like screaming into my mic,
but then I get this separate little chat window pop up
and it's like inverse colors, black with white type
and I've never seen it before.
And it's one of my buddies, one of my good buddies.
His screen name is dingdonghashtag451,
who I know to be Brett.
I mean, we're pretty tight.
Like we've been gaming for like two years together
and he sends me this message
and this random like private chat that says,
hey bro, I want to show you something,
but can you be discreet?
And I'm like, of course I can broseph, what's up?
So he sends me this video and I watch it
and it's from the perspective of a guy
and then there's two military type guys in front of him
and they're walking into a forest.
It's nighttime, it's dark.
And we hear this deep groaning sound, like.
Excuse me.
Oh, sorry.
At least let me do my own sound effects.
I don't know who you think you are, sir.
The crooner.
Okay, so it's more like.
Ooh.
Yeah, that's the scariest thing I've ever heard.
Something like that.
And it gets so loud at a point
that I have to turn the volume down as I'm watching it.
They get closer and closer to this clearing that I can see.
And inside the clearing, there is this bottomless pit
with a glowing orange light coming out of it.
And the groaning is so loud at this point
that you can see the men holding their ears.
It's clearly unbearable.
And I've turned my volume down almost to
almost a complete mute.
And then all of a sudden I see this huge black tongue
surface itself out of the bottomless pit,
split into two and wrap itself around the two men
that were holding their ears.
And at this point they've like gone down to their knees
cause it's so difficult to be around.
So tongue split in two, wraps around each of them,
throws them up in the air, catches them,
wraps around again, and then the tongue
goes down into the hole.
At this point, the man holding the camera,
he's like dropped it and he's running away.
But you can still kind of see half that the ground
starts to just mold itself over
and the trees grow back up again.
And it's as if it wasn't there at all.
Oh my God.
Jesus.
So I see this video and I got to keep cool for my boys,
you know, always keeping cool for my boys.
So to Brett, I'm like, dude, so tight,
like whatever this is, I'm in.
But I'm like completely tense.
And I don't know much about this personally,
but I believe that maybe my ball sack
has like gone into my body.
Is that a thing that happens?
Yeah, that's definitely a thing that would happen.
Maybe not the sack itself going into your body,
but the testicles would definitely coil up.
Yeah, which would shrink the sack.
Okay, so shrunken sack for me.
It's the shrunken sack for me.
Also, I didn't say what my screen name is.
We got the episode title.
I didn't say what my screen name is,
but it's a Ballbuster 420, hell yeah.
And it's the complete screen name.
Okay, eventually you get a message from Brett again,
ding dong, hashtag 451, which by the way,
Taylor was like, did you guys notice?
The D in ding and the G in dong for capital
for a very, yeah, very subtle reference to Delta Green.
Wow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You brought, most of you probably,
yeah, wouldn't have gotten that, but.
Ellie, are you okay?
I'm like, what?
You guys are brilliant masterminds.
I did not see that, thank you.
Brett's gonna come pick you up
and you're gonna head out.
He's gonna take you to meet some of his friends, yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're joining up.
All right, so he takes you to,
okay, so it's like the most recent holy tongue site, right?
So we're calling that thing the holy tongue.
Get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it.
Holy tongue.
It doesn't have holes in it, it's split into,
oh, it goes in the hole, I get it.
Nice, all right, you get it.
So we've tracked it down to this corn field, right?
Okay, so we're gonna head on out
and as you guys get there, there's this corn field,
there's a couple tents set up, dudes on laptops,
a couple military bros hanging out.
All right, so we're going in with a third guy,
come on over here, come on over here.
And this dude walks up and he's like, yo,
Bill, we're nice to, oh shit, not Bill,
Bill, not Bill, gamertags?
Yeah, sorry, it's a rumple foreskin, what up?
How's it going?
And he puts out a fist for you to bump.
I go for the fist, but then I do the octopus,
is that what it is?
Jesus fucking Christ.
Squid, is it a squid?
So I squid him.
Oh!
You inked me, bro.
And then I grab his arm and then I go in for a bro hug.
Oh yeah, you guys slap the shit out of each other's backs.
Dude, I knew you'd be tight.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, tight as hell, bro.
All right, sick.
So plan is, what we're gonna do,
this thing is probably gonna come up,
hey nerd, when's this thing popping up?
And this dude on the computer is like,
huge sigh, pushes up his glasses and is like,
14 minutes.
So we're gonna wear these
and he puts on these noise-canceling headphones
that are super high-tech over your ears
and then he keeps talking,
but you just see his mouth moving.
And then he's like, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And then he takes off your headphones.
And he's like, all right,
so we're gonna wait for this thing, right?
And then-
So whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
we're gonna meet the tongue?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, it's gonna be sick.
I just wanna make it like maybe not the best idea.
Whoa, bro, are you not down?
No, no, no, no, I'm super down.
Don't worry about my downness.
I've never been so down, down in the ground,
underneath the body.
Yeah, exactly, that's where we're going.
We're gonna go down into it, all right?
So first we're gonna stun it.
Cool, cool, cool.
Right, so those nerds over there,
and he points back at this like whole tent
where they've got this crazy, like metal, shiny,
EMP looking thing.
What's an EMP?
Electromagnetic pulse.
So that would like send a shockwave
that would knock out electronics.
Yo, but this one is gonna knock out this fucking tongue.
Apparently they already tried it like 10 times
or twice or whatever.
And so like, we're definitely gonna be able to stun it.
It'll be chill for like 15 minutes.
All right, all right.
So we are going to, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I mean, splunk, I guess is the word.
It's not a cave, but you know, it's a hole, baby.
Ha ha, they fist bump.
You've got cameras,
you've got these strange like energy reading devices.
He's like, yeah, I don't know what they are,
but apparently it's gonna give them
like the information they need.
Obviously we're gonna have a bunch of guns and knives
just in case shit goes down.
I brought my knuckle busters.
I brought my throwing stars.
I'm ready to get down.
You have throwing stars?
Hell yeah, I got throwing stars.
Can I see your throwing stars?
I mean, when the time presents itself.
Oh, play close to the chest, play close to the chest.
I dig that, all right, cool.
So let's fucking go.
Cut to the Chuckster, if I may.
I think we're tight enough now, yeah.
You're stabbing your knife into solid ground
for the first time in what feels like an eternity
as you finish scrambling as fast as you can
out of the roused holy tongue.
This thing is alive now.
It's back and you crawl toward the team
on the ground away from it.
This team that's firing now at the whole situation
from behind cover, just a bunch of military dudes
firing over your head as you're crawling to safety
and you hear Brett ding-dong, hashtag 451.
He's screaming.
You look back, you see one of these tongues, boom,
grabs him by the ankle and it starts slowly
dragging him back in.
What do you do?
Well, first of all, as it's happening,
I'm yelling, not tight.
Tight.
Ding-dong, I'll save you.
I'll come back for you.
And then I just continue to scramble away.
All right, hell yeah.
No sign of Rumple foreskin.
Rumple foreskin is gone.
There is no Rumple foreskin to be seen.
I'm just trying to say that a few more times
before we never hear it again.
Okay, so.
Wait, where's Rumple foreskin?
Nowhere to be seen.
Damn.
Ding-dong is being pulled back slowly into this thing
and the ground begins to kind of reform itself
and right at the last second, right before,
you think that ding-dong's entire body
is gonna be yoinked down into the hole,
but it doesn't quite all make it.
And as the ground finishes forming,
the head of Brett is just sitting on the ground
and you think maybe he himself is just stuck there
until slowly the head falls over on its side
and blood just starts squirting out from the bottom of it.
Jeez.
That is Charles Chuck, the Chuckster.
Thank you, thank you for playing.
Fucking, oh my God.
Sorry, I'm reacting and sitting here.
How do you feel?
I'm super intrigued by all these stories.
They're really cool, but also they start off
like penis joke, Brett, foreskin, military complex
and then like, you're dead, you're gone.
And there doesn't seem to be a way to protect yourself
which makes it even more terrifying.
It just lands on you.
I think I'm gonna go back for that tongue.
Go for it.
Yeah.
Breathe it in.
Clasp your fist, or fall apart.
Water leaks through your fingers.
You're standing in a swirling flood.
And only darkness lingers.
Falling fast into a deep abyss.
Till it sets you out again.
Find your feet on your broken bones.
You're out for the edge again.
Yeah.