Welcome. Please enter my future listeners.
It's your new obsession, Wolf the Dog, and I'm crawling deeper and deeper into your ear holes from 694.2 PTBP,
the newest, best, and only radio station in a very real town called Contention.
Tune in to our hit show, Pretended to be People,
to hear three bumbling police officers.
Keith Vigna,
I'm not a bad cop, I'm just a bad cop.
John Lee Pettymore IV,
I fire my pistol into the air.
and Clark Bishop,
Can we call the president?
as they struggle against their own incompetence in a futile attempt to save their small town from an ineffable threat.
The limp bodies, after sliding into a pool of their own blood, are picked up and slammed into the ground repeatedly and at an absurd rate by some unseen force.
And then, as if they were never there at all, both bodies are gone.
All while navigating some unique citizens.
A cold chill runs down Clark's spine.
It's a fucking cat man!
Surreal horror.
It was somebody who knew I watched Wheel of Fortune every night.
And gruesome crime scenes.
The skin on her back was branded with the phrase,
This is a fool.
And the cause of death was blunt trauma.
Hell yeah, dude.
Keep in mind, Pretending to be People is available wherever you listen to podcasts.
So come on down to Contention.
Join your new grown-ass man-pet-friend-narrator DJ Wolf the Dog in this greasy dumpster filled with deliciously wet nibbles.
And enjoy Pretending to be People.
Thanks for watching!