Shit.
God damn it, quit poking and prodding me.
I can't see shit.
Who put this fucking blindfold on me?
Hey, I'm talking to you, whoever, or whatever you are.
Cut that shit out now.
I got a damn show to run here.
Don't you know I'm broadcasting live from 694.2 PTBP,
the only radio station currently being run by an in-prison DJ
Wolf the Dog?
Now, we got a new Howlin' with Wolf, y'all.
And this week's comes from Nathan,
who claims he is either deep in the heart of Texas
or deep in the hell that is Texas.
He writes, shout out to Eric N for being the most badass
bone-digging buddy one could ask for in this dirty business.
And to my wife, Erin, who is so good at wrangling all those
werepuppies and kitties, I'm so glad you're diving
into a world of unseen horrors.
Love you, insert creepy cackling laugh.
Oh, shit.
To those hardworking cultural resource archaeologists
out in the field, keep on digging those holes
and hopefully those sinister abandoned cabins we find
on survey aren't the layer of any backwoods Eldritch cults.
Stay safe and sane, says here a creepy cackling laugh
again but better this time.
Oh, God damn it.
Well, Nathan, thanks for forcing me to cackle not once
but two times on a day where I don't especially feel
like cackling.
I forgive you this time but next time.
Oh, buddy, you better hope it's a cackle day or else.
If you wanna write up something for this
and caged wolf to how, click on the show notes
and tag us on the internet at pretending pod.
One of those links down there is to patreon.com
slash pretending pod.
For the whole month of November, we here at PTBP
are taking any new and upgraded monies,
doubling it and using that scratch to buy blankets
and sleeping bags for cold folks in Springfield, Missouri.
And y'all have been super duper kind.
So far, you've raised $375.
So wolf gonna double that and we can spend $750
on supplies for those who need them.
And congrats, I said I'd give away a couple
of PTBP logo t-shirts to a couple fine patrons on Patreon.
So yay and good job to Jasmine Johnson
and Chainsaw Unicorn.
Please reach out by any means necessary
so we can send you a damn shirt.
Woo hoo hoo, it's time for the news.
The news is wild, y'all.
There's a pregnant girl in this motel room
that we all thought was meant for storage.
Hmm, hmm, Scott Adams, hmm, indeed.
Now I'm gonna give you all what we all need.
It's Brat Pit with Ms. Mary.
Mary, yeah.
I gotta work in the morning
and this shit's so important
so I can't get high.
No, I can't get high.
I thought this stuff helped anxiety.
There must be something inside of me.
Does anybody know why?
I can't get high.
I think we both thought you wanted to open it.
No, I was saying like this, I don't really like it
but it's really not that bad.
It's not.
But also every time I drink it, I go through,
I don't like it, it's fine.
I don't like it.
And of course, we're talking about
the new Limoncello Naturally Essence
Sparkling Water from La Croix.
We'll like it if La Croix does podcast ads.
That is true, until then, fuck La Croix
and fuck every brand that doesn't.
Yeah, we will keep talking shit about you
until you pay us off.
It's like a vanilla lemon thing.
There's too much vanilla in it, though.
No, it's kinda gross.
We're here with David Winters!
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
Wam, wam, wam, wam, wam.
Winter is coming, now is the winters of your discontent.
What's up, man?
Yeah, hi.
Have you been having fun with us?
Have you enjoyed this?
You got some hot energy coming in.
Yes, yes, I have.
These are like those one-word answers
when your parents call and you are in the middle
of something and you pick it up.
Is this like when you're at like a con
and people ask you questions, you're just like,
hey, I loved the show so much, how is it?
Yes.
So are you a lawyer in real life?
No.
Who's your favorite PTV people?
Yes.
It makes for good radio.
It does, yeah.
Who's your favorite?
Really short.
Glass cannon.
To the point.
No.
Okay, so if you had to pick only one Colin Hanks movie
and then replace him with every.
Can you name a third Colin Hanks movie?
I can name Orange County and I don't know any more than that.
That's the end of my list, too.
Oh, right, I said Dexter, that's not even a movie.
All right, let's dive into this shit, shall we?
We just learned a lot of information, so much information.
Well, you learned some of the information.
We got cut off so rudely by the end of an episode
right at the about halfway point of an info dump.
I'm willing to keep dumping
if you're willing to keep receiving the dump.
Oh, please dump on us.
Dump all over us.
Please dump on us.
We got a glass table right here, we'll pull out.
Well, that made it weird.
Steam and hot info.
Yeah, you made it into like scat or something,
that was weird.
Yeah, we just want knowledge shat all over our chests.
Right.
I love these big steamy dumps that David is taking.
You just cracked open his notebook
and got a dump of several different happenings
that he has seemed to have researched in the area.
Things like livestock mutilations, livestock alterations,
some missing time, some helicopters being sighted,
including some muzzle flashes,
lights being sighted in the hills, some crop circles,
some notes about J.A. being Jane Allen.
Pregnant three weeks equals six months.
Exactly, and the aldermen who never go home.
That was in the notebook, his wide ruled school notebook.
Freak.
You, again, should be questioning his sanity.
And you still see his Macintosh power book
in front of you plugged into the phone outlet
as you had learned earlier when you tried to dial them.
Is there anything you'd like to do?
Can I ask a kind of retroactive question?
When I was looking at Jane Allen,
when Tan was looking at Jane Allen,
did she seem older than she should be?
Nope, she's still a high school senior,
looks like a high school senior,
actually looks very similar to some of those photos
that you saw of her family in her house
when you were there, right?
When her mom was dressed to kill.
At least one of you,
yeah, at least one of you was looking through
all the family photos and she looks as you would expect.
So back to the computer.
Sure.
Jodine goes over and turns it on and we saw he had AOL.
He does, however, in typical 1990s computer fashion,
it does still ask for a password as you open it.
Does anyone have an often underused skill?
SIGINT, signals intelligence.
I don't.
Exactly.
I have a 50 in pilot.
Can I pilot this computer too?
Can we negotiate with you here?
Luke, we need to seriously have a conversation
about the fact that I took special training in parachute.
Yeah, I knew both of those
and I didn't want to connect them yet,
but I know what's going to happen.
You don't need SIGINT.
SIGINT is one option,
but fortunately there's a second one
which is computer science.
Oh, good.
I've got computer science at a 50.
50, with a 50, given how much time and effort
you've invested in knowing computer science.
You know, in the early 1990s,
people don't use the most secure passwords.
Not realizing that information security is important.
Guess me a password.
Love, one, two, three.
Okay, that doesn't work.
Watch the sky's exclamation point.
Purple.
Watch the sky's exclamation point actually worked.
That's all it was.
Well, I didn't try that one, so.
Shit, I'm not there.
Cindy.
I'm sorry, Joe.
Oh, Cindy's not there?
Oh, oh, okay.
I'm sorry, Joe.
Sorry, it's not, so did purple work?
Yeah, Joe, guess like 15 more.
I try watch the sky's one.
No?
I try watch the sky's two.
Oh, no.
I accidentally.
Maybe I should just have you roll.
I accidentally hit caps lock.
I go back to the one,
because I thought I might have mis-hit that one.
I countermeasured triggers,
and the computer catches on fire
due to 10 failed password attempts.
No, I'm just kidding.
I'll give it to you.
I wasn't going to actually make you guess every password
until you got to football one, two, three
was the correct answer.
Hey, I was on the backtrack.
Go team, you were, you were.
It cracks open.
You find a document on the desktop,
and I am going to display it in front of you now.
If you check out your television, it's long.
This is a long multiple paragraph document
written in kind of first person stream of consciousness.
It looks like it's,
they're looking for evidence of extra sensory perception.
I am wondering about the possibility
that the brain translates information
in terms of the extra sensory.
He literally told us not to read this.
And that's why it achieves.
Can we shut up for like two minutes and just read it,
and then we can talk about what it says?
Is it just like a stream of thought?
Yeah, it gets just insane.
Omni parent consciousness, open network.
Yeah.
It starts out kind of coherent,
but it gets a little rambly.
Oh, we get into some Jesus stuff.
I thought so too, but that's not what it is.
Yeah, it's French, just sweetie.
Yeah, French Jesus.
So it's a long,
and the reason why I said not to read it all out loud
is it would make no sense.
And people would have to rewind several times and be like,
what the hell are these guys talking about?
But suffice to say, this is something presumably
that was written by Scott Adams on his computer
stream of consciousness,
talking about extra sensory perception and existence
and seeing things and consciousness
and all sorts of nonsense related to thought
and the sensory experience.
He should have stuck to Dilbert.
He's branching out, okay?
You have to try new things.
Yeah, the file title was S-Z-E comma T.
Of course it was, of course it was.
But now you have that, that's thing number two
from this steamy dump.
Thing number three, you see a file on the desktop.
It's simply titled message.
It's a wave file.
And I am going to need an alertness roll from everyone.
Fail, 73 on a 70.
I also fail, a 75 on a 50.
Succeed, 39 on a 50.
I got a 36 on a 50, nice.
All right.
So Zach and Luke, keep your headphones on.
The other two of you, please take your headphones off
and then we will swap.
Dude, Zach, we can literally say anything about these guys
in the beginning.
Fucking idiots.
I love them both a whole lot.
Me too.
You fire up the message
and this is the clip you get.
Dealing with, it's been a long time
and we have many things to do
and you are not sure what you are doing.
Stop, stop, stop.
That's all you get out of it.
Okay.
So someone's telling this guy to stop what he's doing
because he doesn't know what he's dealing with.
Is that right, Luke?
Did I do it?
I wrote down, not sure what you're dealing with.
Stop now.
Wow.
One in the same.
Pop, swap, swap, swap, swap.
Zach didn't teach you the bird.
When he wants to call us back in,
we do this on our screens.
Oh, really?
We did it when we were remote
because we couldn't.
People can fly away at home.
You could see on the screen if we needed them back.
Fair enough.
Well, I've got you two now
and now it's time for you to fire up
this metallic squawky voice.
Dealing with, it's been a long time
and we have many things to do
and you are not sure what you are doing.
Stop now.
Tone Brown, is that like the Brown note?
He did say duty.
He just said duty.
Can I do the bird thing into the camera?
Is that how it works?
Yeah, do that.
Let's see if it works.
No one's looking, that's the problem.
We often combat that, yep.
Oh, it worked, it worked.
Saw the bird.
So we, Joe and I like sat there
like rubbing our ears vigorously
for like a minute and a half.
Saw that, yeah.
So we couldn't hear anything
and you two chuckle fuckers are just like sharing memes
and laughing and faking.
Yeah, I wasn't paying attention to you at all.
Luke has some really funny pictures on his phone.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, that seems ominous.
Yeah, what did you think about the,
do you think he's working on the Brown note,
the tone that makes people shit their pants?
The Brown, what?
I had not, what?
The Brown note.
He said a Brown tone.
No, I didn't hear any, what?
That's not what I heard at all.
What do you mean?
We all heard it.
Play it again.
Here's the deal.
I'm not sure what you're dealing with, but stop now.
Yeah.
That's what we heard.
Yeah, we heard a man's voice, right?
It was kind of garbled.
We missed some words.
Right.
But it mostly just said,
you don't know what you're dealing with.
Stop now, stop now, stop now.
What did you hear?
Over and over and over.
Well, we heard some garbled words too, but we,
well, I think you took it down pretty well, huh?
You didn't hear a name.
They said Billy Webb.
No, we heard, we didn't hear no name.
They said a name?
Billy Webb?
Yeah, they talked about duty and they talked about.
A Brown tone.
They said to talk now.
Who's Billy Webb?
Was he on the list of the,
in the notes we got of all the different events?
I just remember Beau Laramie.
Nope.
Doesn't look like it.
Billy Webb.
Like a web of Billys.
I don't remember if computers had this kind of stuff
back then, but is there anything that we can click on
that shows us when the file was made, like created?
Yeah, the file is only about three days old.
As far as this audio file goes,
the ranty dream of consciousness file,
that's only about two days old.
That seems to be a little bit more fresh.
And then obviously the notebook is handwritten.
So you'd have no idea exactly when stuff was written.
However, there are various dates
over the last month and a half.
It's tough to say which of those dates were reported to him
or maybe which of those bits of information
he collected himself.
There's nowhere a way to delineate between the two.
Sure.
What did you hear about Billy Webb?
That's it.
Just they said a name.
They said Billy Webb and then they kind of broke up.
And then there was a...
Did Billy Webb used to play center field
for the Ohio state?
University?
USO backwards?
Tan goes to the office and asks Riker for a phone book.
Nice.
And Riker will produce a phone book.
I go to W looking for Billiam Webb.
You can go to W and there are no webs in this town.
What a tangled web we don't weave.
Jeez.
Let's see what he did there.
So is this like one...
Okay.
Why did we play an audio file and we heard one thing
and you heard another?
Well, you misheard obviously.
Yeah, I think you guys are just wrong.
Well, if we don't know what Billy Webb is
and there's no Billy Webb here,
doesn't it probably lend itself to the belief
that we heard the correct thing?
I mean, we all heard the same thing.
You just misheard.
It's not like there are no Billy Webs ever.
It says Laurel just over and over.
Tan who is not a part of this conversation
cause he's in the office asks Riker,
do you know Billy Webb?
Is that, do you know?
No.
Okay, that's it.
Bye.
On the computer, is that literally all we find?
Is there anything else that we should look
in this computer for?
That's really all that's relevant.
You can go through all the other notebooks and notes.
He has notebooks for various other towns all over the place.
He's based out of Tennessee.
So most of these towns are all related
to sightings in the area.
However, the Grover's Ville notebook is chock full of stuff.
It's just page after pages.
These are kind of the more recent pages,
but you go back and there are just progressively
more outrageous things that he has records of.
Little gray people walking through Main Street
and sighting of eight flying saucers.
And it goes back years actually of this Grover's Ville stuff.
It's only more recently when you're seeing specific things
about choppers or weird things about pregnant girls.
What is the oldest mention of like an alien occurrence
or sighting in Grover's Ville?
It's probably two or three years,
but it's similar to his other notebooks.
Most other places go back two or three years.
You can reason that's probably
when he kind of got in the UFO game.
Gotcha, okay.
He stopped writing comics and then got into the UFO game.
Good for him.
Tan goes back to the room and signals Cindy
to like come outside.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So he doesn't know anything about Webb.
I got an idea though.
Well, that's because Webb wasn't a thing.
What's your idea?
Yeah, I got an idea.
Okay, you know, everybody in the town's weird.
Yeah, for sure.
Probably an alien.
Sure.
They're covering something up.
Yeah, yeah.
What if we parade Jane down Main Street,
make a big scene,
and then we see who comes out to deal with it.
Then we got our main suspect.
That seems horrible to do to this poor girl.
Hearing that through the open door at Joe is like,
yeah, I think everyone would come out
to stop you from doing that, alien or not.
Plus the aliens, their whole deal
is that they're acting like people.
Yeah, but it's gonna piss them off.
They're gonna be really,
they're gonna be blase about it
like they've been blase about everything.
What we need to do is go to who has the most money
in this town and take them out
because they are provoking, they are threatening,
they are going around dealing in stuff
that they don't want other people poking their heads in.
And what do we know, Joe,
about people who don't want people poking their heads in,
who threaten other people?
It's always about...
Money.
It's always about money.
Joe is like looking at you intently
and he kind of like holds up a cardigan and hands it to you.
She puts on a second cardigan and calms down.
I only got one more, fellers.
As she's calming down,
you hear out in the parking lot a car arrive.
We all turn and look.
Now, before we do that though,
I need to just talk to Joe.
Joe the character or Joe the human?
Sorry, Joe, that was such a bad choice, Thomas.
I think it's a good name.
It is a good name.
I don't fault you for that.
I think, look, do me a favor.
Next time you have a victim like myself
in this similar situation,
only use your four names scrambled between them.
There you go.
Send us Troy Lavallee and we will do that to him.
Luke Zach.
Go, Thomas.
I want to talk to Joe the human being.
Real life, Joe.
Everyone else, wait for the bird signal.
It's just me and you, David.
It is just me and you.
And really, you know, I just wanted to take a break.
I'm good with you, yeah.
And really just, yeah,
just relax without those chuckleheads.
That's really kind of the main thing.
What you getting for dinner tonight?
Bad thing about saying that is at some point,
someone's going to be editing this
and I just called them a chucklehead, so, you know.
I hope it's you editing this episode and not anyone else.
However, I have news for you.
And I have news for your character.
I guess not you,
but that news is you feel a little bit different today.
You have no real change in appetite,
but for whatever reason, you're incredibly thirsty.
You just feel like you're always dehydrated.
You always need to be drinking something,
thinking about where you're getting your next drink.
Not necessarily an alcoholic beverage,
just water, coffee, anything,
but you can't quite quench that thirst.
Additionally, speaking of the dumps
we were discussing earlier,
you can still urinate,
but there's no more number two for you in your future.
Is it a constipation thing
or I just don't feel the need to?
You don't feel the need to.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I don't want to make it sound like
you have suddenly just become constipated and you need,
yeah, you need to go to a drug store and get,
no, it's not quite like that.
You have absolutely no urge to.
Okay, cool.
And that's pretty much it.
That's all you know.
Just the standard, last night was thirsty Thursday.
Today's Friday.
You know, it happens.
Some Fridays you just need to drink a lot of fluid
and you can never defecate ever again.
That's it.
You know.
All right, I'll do the bird thing.
It's working, it's working.
We got him.
A car has rolled up into the parking lot.
It is an early nineties Lincoln town car, in fact.
And it rolls up, sees you all
and a sharply dressed individual, a G man, if you will,
hops out of the car with a large duffle bag
and comes up towards the office, towards Riker's office,
kind of asks where you guys are.
Riker's in that office, points kind of down your way
towards the Scott Adams, Jane Allen room.
And he gets there and knocks on the ajar door.
Wait, hello?
He stands like in the middle of all of us,
quiet and then knocks on the door?
I thought you were inside.
You and I are outside.
Yeah, we're outside.
They're inside.
Cindy and Jane are outside.
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I thought everyone was inside.
So we're like waving at him as he comes towards us.
He just walks past you and ignores you.
No, just kidding.
He stops you.
Sorry.
Zach's head whipped to us.
He's like, that's fair.
What's that mean?
Okay, that's wild.
It's a clue.
He can't see you anymore.
You're now invisible.
We're the aliens.
Am I real?
Sorry, I didn't realize you were standing there.
Hello?
And he whips out a badge.
Agent Jordan Cook.
You are the agents, right?
Agent Cindy Wodabaga, DEA.
I'm Agent Tan Loothide, ATF.
Excellent, excellent.
Well, I have a delivery from your handler, if you will.
Thank you.
Yes.
Gives you an envelope and gives you a duffel bag.
Oh, sorry.
I almost forgot something.
He looks around back and forth,
makes sure Riker's not listening or anyone else.
Bubble gum tree.
Nice.
And then he turns around and just walks away.
How heavy is the duffel bag that I'm carrying?
Relatively heavy.
It's about 20 pounds.
And then you have one of those envelopes,
kind of an inner office mail sort of envelope.
One of those big yellow ones with like the string.
Manila envelope.
Vanilla envelope.
It smells like fresh vanilla.
It smells like a Yankee candle, kind of.
These new Limoncello La Croix envelopes
are not that good in my opinion.
I look at them and it's okay.
And then I look at it a little more and I'm like,
I don't like that.
I just don't know about it.
But I go ahead and open it up anyway.
I also unzip the duffel bag a little bit.
We like walk into the room as we do this.
Sure.
So in the envelope is a single piece of paper
with some stuff typed out on it.
And then in the bag is a bunch of liquid.
Six gallons of liquid with two spray bottles.
Almost the same kind of spray bottles
you would use to clean with.
What does the liquid look like?
The liquid is basically colorless.
It just looks to be slightly foamy and bubbly, transparent.
Does anyone else have a high pharmacy?
I have a 50.
I don't know why I'm looking.
I don't have any.
How about you just look at the piece of paper?
Yeah.
In the envelope.
Yeah, maybe we do that.
Let's do some rolls first.
Yeah, let's do some rolls first.
She starts smelling them.
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We read the paper.
Are you sure?
I mean, you can just mess around with the liquids
if you want.
We can also go that route.
Let's talk to the liquid for a while.
Slap these bags real quick.
Let's just start spraying each other with them.
You can.
Spray fight.
It's gonna be acid to break down a fucking body, dude.
No, as Tan is like reaching into the duffel bag
and about to touch one of the containers.
Yeah, no, go ahead and stop doing that, please.
If your stomach doesn't already hurt
from being aware of what we're about to do,
then I have the unfortunate pleasure to let you know that,
well, you can go ahead and read Harlan.
Your eyes look pretty big.
Go ahead and read that note there.
Okay, I read the note.
Yeah, I'll read the note to you
because there is no note for you to read.
How is it gonna talk to David?
Yeah, let me tell you what it says.
And it's a memo from Derringer, typed out on a typewriter.
He didn't even want this thing to hit the computer network
or be saved anywhere.
The tissue test came back on the muscle tissue
in Billy Ray's body.
And they're not really sure exactly what it is.
It's some sort of matter, extraterrestrial substance
that basically replaced his muscles.
And they're not sure exactly how it works,
but they've developed a detecting compound
that they've rushed together for you.
That's what's in the duffel bag.
You can spray it on things.
And when you spray it and it detects this matter,
things will turn purple.
Oh my God.
We're just gonna spray every folk in this town.
Yeah, Tan sprays his own arm.
Oh yeah, let's spray each other
and make sure we're all clean.
I spray everybody.
Okay.
Cindy, you did your nightly routine, right?
I did indeed.
Last night?
Yep.
Your entire face turns purple.
Harlan, you splashed water under your armpits
and threw on a fresh polo.
Your upper arms turn purple.
Anyone else that had a glass of water, I believe, up front,
your mouth, your lips,
the inside of your mouth turns purple.
Oh shit.
It's all over your hands
if you wash your hands after going to the bathroom.
Joe, I know that you stopped washing your hands
on purple hands years ago.
No, I said he used the bathroom.
I said he has a drink.
I don't know if surely he drank some water,
but we could also just have him back away in terror
from all of you.
It looks like they miscalculated.
It's just picking up sweat.
These are sweat glands, obviously.
Yeah, my face is really sweaty and purple.
Alien sweat glands, you son of a bitch.
I need two sanity rolls right now.
The first sanity roll is the fact that this stuff exists.
I had a fail and a crit fail.
The first one's a fail.
Okay, yeah, let's do the first one first.
On a fail on the first one, you're gonna take one.
I failed as well. Otherwise it's zero.
That's the unnatural though, so no check boxes for that.
The second though, realizing it's in your body
and the fact that to some extent,
you have ingested something in this town,
washed your hands in this town,
it's basically in the water supply.
You know that much so far.
Okay, that's gonna be one on a success, four on a failure.
And what about a crit fail?
I believe that is gonna be eight, no?
You can do whatever you want, dude.
I like that.
Think about, Tan, how you were sick
at the slightest sight of anything so far, right?
First, what was the, I forget the first time you puked.
Was it in?
It was at the office, the first video.
Was it the office, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was at the office the first video
and it got progressively worse
when you caught the smell of that dead body.
And now on your very first mission,
you recognize that it's not going particularly great for you.
So with taking eight sanity damage.
Right, I will say obvious.
Did you take one first?
Or did you pass that one?
I did, I took one.
So you took nine total?
I took nine total.
Jeez Louise.
I am at 37 and my breaking point is 43.
Yeah.
So I'm quite a bit past that.
Okay, so technically- And I'm feeling good.
Yeah, feeling good, nothing happens.
Technically losing that five in a clip,
you're gonna go temporarily insane.
You can potentially suppress that
by projecting that onto one of your bonds
if you so choose or not.
You can just go temporarily insane.
It's totally up to you.
Tan really likes his bonds, so he just takes it himself.
Okay, all right, I'm gonna roll a die.
Your temporary insanity is going to manifest
in you fleeing.
Realizing this, you're just going to run away
from the hotel without saying much
while everyone else is there
also feeling pretty bad about things.
You just start to run away.
You will kind of come to after booking it,
losing your breath and kind of turn around
and be able to walk back.
Tan, he chokes down some vomit and then just runs away
and he runs right towards the mega deuce.
You run towards the mega deuce, okay?
Harlan hit a breaking point in that sanity loss also.
So did Joe Dean.
Well, I guess we all need to reset our breaking points.
I didn't hit a breaking point,
but I did lose five sanity.
Okay. Oh, shit.
Cindy is gonna submit, curl up,
just disconnect from everyone,
maybe go back into her room.
Oh, yeah.
Flashback to some of the crazy shit
she's seen in the field.
She goes to start a bath for herself
and as she goes to touch the knob
to turn the hot water on,
she like freaks out, hits the wall behind her.
And as she hits the wall behind her
in this small motel bathroom,
she sent into a flashback of her throwing her husband
up against the wall of a small motel bathroom.
And then she shakes her head
and goes and lays down in the bed.
Everyone else is going to have some anxiety going forward
when it comes to mealtime.
The thought of putting anything in your body at this point
is going to be somewhat anxiety provoking,
at least in the immediate term
before you seek any professional help.
As Tan runs towards the Megaduce,
that hits him and he gets scared again
and runs away from the Megaduce
because there's food there.
You've realized there's some substance out there
that got injected into Billy Ray,
presumably it's elsewhere in this town.
Clearly it's in the water supply
because it's on your hands, your face,
your mouth, your armpits.
Harlan's going to make eyes with Jodine.
It's in the water supply.
That makes sense now.
That's what we saw.
Right, shooting out of the tub.
I kind of fill in Tan and Cindy.
Real quick, I think that makes this the EPA's problem.
Also, Tan is just like wandering
around the parking lot right now.
Oh right, I forgot you were gone.
But it looked like mercury.
But it seemed conscious.
It seemed like it was moving of its own accord, right?
It seemed like some kind of unstoppable force to me.
I don't know.
I don't know if what I'd saw,
I'd call consciousness as we know it.
It dodged your glass.
It flattened itself out to break it, right?
Yeah, I guess that is pretty thoughty.
Or reactive at the very least.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I don't want to eat anything from the diner.
Should we get just a bunch of like little Debbie's and stuff
that comes in plastic from the gas station?
I want to hit the vending machine.
I'm parched.
The idea of not being able to drink the water here,
that scares me.
I need to top up.
Well, let's get you a Coke.
Everybody knows in 1992 that it's fat that makes you fat,
not sugar.
You can get some Olestra chips out of the vending machine.
You can do that though.
There is a vending machine right near the manager's office.
Soda, little Debbie's, little Dorito bags.
Harlan buys a Coke and he cracks the top on it
and he downs the Coke without it getting away from his lips.
And he tosses it in the trash can and buys two more.
A little thirsty there?
Yeah, I'm thirsty.
I don't want to drink the water here.
We can't drink the water here.
Yeah, I mean, that's a reasonable conclusion.
Would some of this mealtime anxiety be alleviated
when we do have like these prepackaged foods?
Yes, yes.
You feel safe enough that eating this,
it's more any food that someone else prepared for you.
Would be very suspicious to us.
Yeah, that is not a multinational corporation
trying to jack you full of low quality calories
through advertisement and other things.
Basically, you hate small business food providers.
That's kind of what I'm getting at.
No food trucks, no diners, you know.
All right, yeah, I love little things.
That tracks, dude.
So yeah, Joe Dean gets a couple sprites for himself.
He's like, yeah, maybe I will be thirsty, like Harland.
And then I guess they go back with the others.
Tan is in the parking lot.
He ran towards the Mega Deuce
and then ran away from the Mega Deuce.
And he's still got like one of the spray bottles in his hand
and he's just like spraying cars in the parking lot.
Well, hold Tan, Tan, Tan, Tan.
We don't want to go wasting that.
He stops spraying cars in the parking lot.
As you spray cars, there's not,
nothing's really turning purple.
Cindy Woodabaga walks out of her room,
moves her hands toward her cardigan
to kind of put her hands on her hips,
which reveals the baton and pepper spray she has
on either side on her belt.
And then she says, Merle.
So Cindy, we do need to talk to him,
but you know, you were talking earlier
about just taking him out.
I don't think we're quite at that place yet, are we?
We'll find out.
So Joe Dean has brought back some snacks
and he hands a candy bar to Cindy.
Here, have a Snickers.
You're not you when you're hungry.
Hey, that's a good, they should use that.
That's good.
No, that's nothing.
That won't ever be nothing.
She takes a couple of bites
and the camera whips back up to her face,
which has little granny glasses on it all of a sudden.
Took her down a couple notches, I think.
We just left Jane in that room, right?
You did.
Let's give her some food.
And this dude, the Delta Green, the FBI guy,
he took off once he gave us the duffel bag and the...
Yep.
He just bounced.
Woodabaga will go give some little debbies to young Jane.
Young Jane takes the little debbies
and just starts pounding them.
Much in the same way that Agent Nash just pounded that soda,
she does the same thing with the little debbies,
the Doritos, the Funyuns.
Whatever you put in front of her,
she just houses all of it.
She housed those Funyuns.
Housed them.
I've never heard that, but I like it.
Housing?
There's someone even in charge of it
at a government level.
You live in a house, Luke.
What do you...
You don't know that.
I was all for going to Merle,
but now that I've had the Snickers,
I'm up for whatever you guys are up for.
Well, we should just go to Merle,
but maybe not with murderous intent.
Man, it was just a baton and pepper spray.
During Cindy's rant,
you mentioned that Merle had been harassing people.
Did we get that from somebody?
That is the giant leap that Cindy Woodabaga has drawn
from someone was harassing Scott Adams,
and she just assumes that it's the person
who has the most money at risk and at stake.
So what did we hear on that recording?
It didn't matter.
Billy Webb and something garbled,
and then What Your Duty and something garbled,
and they said, talk now.
It sounded like a command, talk now.
They also said, I'm sorry, I'm talking like Clark.
I've been John for at least an episode and a half.
And that ending, it said Tone Brown.
It wasn't actually Brown Tone.
Do your voice though, I like your voice.
It was Tone Brown.
Tone Brown and Duty.
Do you see how that means nothing?
Well, what did you hear?
We literally heard someone saying,
not sure what you're dealing with, but stop now.
Stop now.
Yeah.
Not sure what you're dealing.
Stop now, stop now.
You're not sure what you're dealing with, stop now.
That makes a lot more sense, doesn't it?
So it does.
Putting our notes together,
one of the things I got was talk now.
So you're hearing stop now.
Yes, we probably just heard it right.
Don't you think?
Yeah, I mean, it's almost like we failed a role
and you passed it.
And I don't wanna, obviously role-playing wise,
it'd be great if we just-
No, I know it's hard for-
I can't believe in that.
But I was wondering if we could put anything together
from it and really glean the truth.
Yeah, sure.
If you wanna try-
But we do gotta keep this moving.
Adult men can never admit that they're wrong.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you, Cindy, you're right.
We heard it right.
I believe that's a mundane day.
So at least two of you heard it right.
Let's recap where you are now.
You've already gone and questioned
the mother of the missing girl,
who you have found and just happens to be very pregnant.
You've talked to the sheriff.
You've talked to one of the aldermen.
You've talked to the guy who runs the only bar
with a liquor license in town.
You've talked to a bunch of random kids at the reservoir.
You've talked to the manager of this hotel.
We've gotten a lot done.
You got a lot done.
You've talked to, this is only a 1200 person town
and you're starting to near the double digit percentage
of people interrogated.
We're good cops.
Yeah, we are.
Yeah, you should just line the rest up
and we just go down the line.
And we'll parade Jane Allen in front of them.
Shame.
Where do you wanna go?
It's an investigation.
Merle.
Yeah, I think that's our last big.
He's the papa.
You wanna go to Merle?
Billy is not that child's father.
Oh, you think Merle is?
No, I think it's aliens.
Yeah, I think it's aliens too.
That does bring up an interesting question.
What do we do with Jane?
We have to kill her.
That's literally not what I was thinking.
Well, that's why you guys are friendlies
and we're the agents.
Okay, I was thinking maybe.
She kinda puts her hands on Tanner's shoulder
and is like, we have to kill her.
No, we don't have to do that.
Okay.
What?
Then what is your solution?
I was thinking maybe we bring her back
to her parents' house.
And then how would you explain the pregnancy?
We let them explain it to us.
This is a real 12 Angry Men situation
and we got Harlan quick.
I'm still leaning towards parading her down Main Street
and seeing who gets pissed off about it.
Your two options are taking her back to her loving parents
or publicly humiliating her,
but never killing her and the aliens
spawn inside of her.
I don't wanna kill her,
but she's got an alien baby in her,
which basically makes her an alien.
So I don't know if she can feel human emotions.
So who cares if we parade her downtown?
I just think the optics are bad.
I don't think we can-
Yeah, use that same mindset.
But what we can say is that we're gonna do it
and then let everybody line up.
Here's the deal, the optics don't matter
because we're not supposed to even be here.
So nobody's gonna hear.
What, no, just because, no.
Agent Dean, would you like to pull rank?
All I'm saying is I suggested that you told me not to.
I have accepted that we're not gonna do that.
So what, I mean, what, we leave her in the hotel.
I say drop her with me and see.
That's what we're saying.
I say drop her with Nancy.
What if we use our car phone to call our handler
and see what he advises?
He said not to call him.
Oh, I thought he said,
do call me if you have any trouble.
Cause it wouldn't be handy-
He said they would only use a courier.
We should have talked to him.
We should have sent a message to him.
Wait!
He's like, so gone.
We hop in the Bronco and tear off after him.
No.
She was fine in there for the last day, right?
What if we threw in some snack foods
and figured this out later?
She is going to punch someone's head off.
No, I don't think she is.
She doesn't seem to have the muscle stuff going on.
She's just got the alien baby.
That thing is going to put itself in someone's head
if what you told me was true happened in that bathroom.
And then that thing is going to kill someone.
You know, I'm not going to disagree with you there.
That does seem, yeah.
We have to stamp it out at the root.
Oh, I don't like Delta Green.
I refuse to be a part of this.
I refuse to be part of this.
I'll talk to Merle all day long,
but I'm not killing,
even if it's an alien, I'm not killing the baby.
You don't have to.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm not going to.
Go home.
I'm going to go talk to Merle.
You, Tanner leaves the room
and just like sits down on the sidewalk outside the motel
and it's like fucked up.
Jodine follows him out and sits down next to him.
And he lights a cigarette and offers it to Tanner.
Tanner accepts and also pulls out his own pack of cigarettes
and lights one up.
What's your brand?
He smokes Palmalls.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, Palmall extra, extra red long
for seven teams.
Oh my God.
So Jodine takes a real deep sigh
and then a deep drag on the cigarette.
And he says,
I've had this moment too.
Well, in what sense?
Something real similar happened
on my first time as a friendly.
I'm not having a good time.
It's not a good time.
Nobody said it would be.
Do you want to kill that girl?
Do you want to kill that baby?
I don't want to kill that baby, but we have to.
Tanner, what's inside that girl's belly
is a danger to the entire world.
Our participation in this organization
is kind of precipitated on that understanding.
Tanner is literally just like frowning
and like dry crying.
And not only does she have to die at Tanner,
but if you don't get along with that picture,
Cindy's gonna kill you too.
What?
Cindy's gonna kill me?
She's nice though.
We have tattoos together.
Cindy's not nice.
I'm not gonna do it.
I won't stop you from doing it, but I'm not gonna do it.
That's all we're saying.
Oh, actually, yeah.
You know, you are the youngest rookie.
So you do have, sorry, I forgot the Delta green haze.
You actually do have to kill this alien baby.
There are rules in place, yeah.
So when you guys look up from this conversation,
you see, hopefully, as long as it's cool with you, David,
Cindy walking this girl, Jane Allen, huddled over.
She's got a couple cardigans on this girl,
maybe even the comforter off the motel bed
wrapped around her.
And she's gonna walk her out to the Bronco.
Wait, what about,
and it goes against my Christian faith to say this,
but what about an alien abortion?
I think that it would look really cool
in one of those hardcore metal fonts
where you can't really read what it says.
Yeah, it would be.
We were talking junkie graveyard.
It's junkie graveyard, alien abortion.
These are good things.
Good name.
No, but surely there's a crooked doctor around here,
a midwife who, I mean, look, these, I had a baby.
Does that mean you know how to?
We're in some dangerous territory right here.
This doesn't feel like it was already iffy
when we were killing somebody.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
I know, but you're really like, let's just kill her
instead of trying to save her life at all.
I think that's kind of a Delta Green thing,
isn't it, to cover up?
We gotta cover it, dude.
Okay, but then you can't call the episode alien abortion.
Tan is having like a serious-
I can.
I can call the episode whatever I want, Thomas.
Tan is having like a serious like mental breakdown.
When he sees Cindy Woodabaga walking Jane out,
he's like crying and he pulls the 44 off his hip
and like looks at Joe and like aims it at Jane
and is like looking for some sort of approval.
Yeah, Joe lowers your hand.
I don't trust you not to wing Woodabaga
and then she would kill you.
Yeah, Tan breaks down once again and just starts crying.
You just seem a little shaky in your gun hand right now.
Cindy will get behind the wheel of the car.
This whole time, Harlan has been kinda solemn into himself,
but he is definitely walking toward the Bronco
with no objection.
Kid, why don't you and I go talk to Merle?
We'll take the DEA, the DEA cruiser.
Yeah.
We go out to the middle of a field,
outside of town where there's no one in sight.
And her water breaks and you have to-
You have to deliver the squid, baby.
It's minute black, it's minute black.
I'm not gonna make you roll on that.
Can we just do the thing and they do a movie
sometimes where it's now a shot at the top of trees
and there's the birds fly off, a bunch of birds fly.
Sure, yes.
Just the crack in the distance.
And then it cuts abruptly to the two of you at town hall,
rolling up in that sick DEA cruiser,
the self-driving Knight Rider DEA cruiser.
You've not been using that functionality
for whatever reason.
You have arrived at city hall.
Thank you, CopNet.
Does this have that brand new CopNet feature in it?
Yeah, I think it does, but really the main,
the shining beauty of this particular model
is the garphone.
Hey, have you eaten anything?
Are you hungry?
I was gonna go to the mecaduce,
but it scared me to even think about doing that.
I hand him a couple of moon pies.
I eat both of them very quickly.
Great.
And then I look at myself in like the mirror
and see is there like still purple around my mouth?
You could have wiped it off if you wanted to
or you can just walk around with that.
There is still purple around my mouth and I wipe it off.
And I guess theoretically,
as your tears were streaming down earlier,
as you were crying,
I've got like contact purple like streaks down my face.
A purple rain, if you will, down your face.
30 seconds of silence for Prince.
Fingerprints.
I barely knew him.
I'm surprised.
I'm surprised you didn't do any of that with Ryker yet.
Tan wipes the purple off his face and just looks over at Joe
and well, should we?
No, I kind of just wanted you to calm down.
I don't think their business is gonna take too long.
Why don't you eat another moon pie
and we'll wait for them to roll back into town.
After eating two moon pies,
he takes a third one and just like eats the marshmallow
out of the middle and then contently sits there.
You're gonna wait until they finish their business
out of town and presumably meet you there?
As soon as he eats the marshmallow out of the middle,
they hear a very distant faint gunshot.
Okay, they catch up to you.
You wait long enough,
a Ford Bronco comes speeding into town.
Cindy has dirt all over her cardigans.
Yeah, Harland's not as disheveled.
He's obviously tried to clean himself up a little bit
before getting here.
You see some really like dirty shovels in the back.
Joe takes Cindy aside.
How did Harland do?
He did great.
You eliminated Jane and the Vector.
Vector one down, 1,199 to go.
All right, well, the kid calmed down.
He's doing all right,
but we're gonna have to keep an eye on him.
All right, well, let's get going on to Merle's.
When you go back to the car,
you find Tan just like cleaning,
like taking apart and cleaning his 44.
He's prepared himself.
Should we go to his house or to his office?
Well, they said the aldermen never leave work.
Oh, he's an aldermen, that's right.
And that's where you met us.
So I get out of the car
and I go ring the doorbell of City Hall.
Where we are greeted by, what was her name?
Jennifer Kahn.
Got it.
Yep, she's there at the front desk.
Just chilling.
I go pee real quick just in case, you know.
Hey, there's a bathroom right there.
Yes, just in case.
You are more than welcome to go to the bathroom.
And there's still a water.
Should I role play this out?
He walks into the bathroom.
Do you wash your hands?
He does not.
In for a penny, in for a pound.
In fairness, he didn't wash his hands
the first time you were in town hall
and then you shook hands with Bradley Allen
and it was wet and then you tried to lie.
It was horrible.
And he saw right through it.
Cindy loved that so much.
So everyone at this point is assuming
you didn't wash your hands.
So, you know, the aspect of the role play
is strictly if you want to make peace with the fact
that maybe you should start washing your hands
now that you have this stuff all over you.
He thinks about it, but then he just like
imagines purple flowing out of the sink
and he's like, no.
While you guys are waiting for him
to get back from the bathroom,
you look over and Harlan is gulping down
from the water fountain.
Harlan.
Harlan, Harlan, bud, bud, hey.
Oh, shit.
Oh, damn it.
Oh, and he starts wiping his mouth.
Sorry, I forgot.
Fuck.
Here, have another Coke.
Yeah.
Did you like Pavlov-ing him?
Gentlemen, the receptionist sees you.
Merle, Merle, we need Merle.
Let me, let me go get him.
Is there like a directory,
like a map directory thing on the wall anywhere?
All their offices are downstairs.
So you, if you remember,
you're going between the offices to see, you know,
which one had the evasive answers,
which one had the direct answers.
Those are all downstairs.
And there's actually one for each of the aldermen
that were mentioned kind of in that note.
So Merle has one, Bradley Allen.
So Jane's father had another,
that was the room you were in where he used his computer.
So that's one hallway downstairs.
Upstairs is like the conference room,
the big boardroom where all of like the aldermen
kind of bigger meetings happen.
And then kind of the other side of town hall
are the municipal things like the county court
and things like that.
Cindy pushes past Jennifer Kahn and says,
we know the way, sweetie, it's okay.
No, no, please don't.
No, no, no.
We actually like to talk to all the aldermen.
I know they're very busy.
It seems like they almost do nothing but work,
but we should have to take a moment of their time.
Do you guys wanna all flash our badges at the same time?
Yeah.
And we all flash our badges at the same time.
Flip, flip.
US Marshall.
I-T-A.
The E-A.
And what bureau are you with, remind us?
Oh, was that the, that was the county of Grover?
You're not in a bureau, that's right.
Okay, well, Cindy, lead the way.
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
I'm gonna have to ask you to not.
All right, thank you.
Just to freak her out a little bit,
he remembers the name of the color of lipstick
that he found in her purse.
And he's like, oh, yeah.
That's so fucking creepy.
Coral reef looks real good on you.
And she just gets really, really quiet.
And we turn and walk.
And your arm too, right?
We have arms.
You're also, you're-
Two of them.
In my hand, I have my Magnum 40.
Oh my God, so much worse now.
That you demon put away
while you're going to the bathroom.
He's just kind of like,
he's like scratching his temple with like the muzzle.
And he's like, wow, Coral looks real good on you.
Oh, I hate it.
A little drip of piss falls off the barrel of the gun.
Jesus Christ.
Because you pissed in the barrel?
I was holding the gun while I pissed
and it just got a little bit on there.
Oh, we've all been there.
Plaques, go embarrass yourself before this is over.
So you sufficiently freak her out.
She stops in her tracks silently.
Why don't you lead the way, Ms. Khan?
I thought we were gonna-
I said we knew where we were going.
Yeah, we're going to Merle's office.
Cindy.
Are we going to Merle's office?
I just feel like she's kind of on his end.
They're all upstairs.
The offices are all empty.
They all seem to be upstairs.
Just like last night, if you remember.
Bradley Allen came down from that room
and based on what she said here,
she's saying like they're upstairs.
Yeah, we go upstairs.
Okay.
You get to the conference room.
It's double doors, double wooden doors,
labeled Aldermen Conference Room.
Pretty straightforward.
Hello, Aldermans.
Should we knock?
No, the door's open, we walk in.
Okay.
You walk in and you see a couple.
And I knock anyway.
You knock as you walk in.
It's polite.
Yeah, and I ring the doorbell and ring, ring.
It is polite to call ahead, in particular,
when you're ambushing a bunch of Aldermen.
Especially in this instance,
because as you open the door,
you notice presumably what the conference table was
in the middle of the room has been hacked into pieces.
And those pieces have been put up,
basically boarding up the walls.
All the bookshelves are turned over.
The bookshelves are also used to block the windows.
There's very little light coming into this room.
And in the center of the room,
occupying almost half the floor is a big pile of goo.
And that big pile of goo has about eight bodies
extending out of it.
You see legs kind of coming out of the bottom,
some arms, a few heads.
They look like suited humans,
just stuck in this pile of goo.
And this is a metallic goo,
very similar to the stuff from the water supply.
And outside of that,
the only other thing you see in this room
is a very high-tech looking computer,
up against the wall, plugged in,
and also wired into the internet,
in a giant pile of metallic goo.
Uh, excuse me, Aldermen,
could we interrupt your meeting
to ask you a few questions?
I gotta work in the morning,
and this shit's so important,
so I can't get high.
Can't get high.
No, I can't get high.
I thought this stuff helped anxiety.
It must be something inside of me.
Does anybody know why?
I can't get high.