good morning afternoon and evening contention no matter what time of day it is you know wolf the
dog is on the prowl and i'm digging up all them secrets from 694.2 p t b p this story comes from
dawn on our newest segment hallen with wolf one day my boss comes in the drive room where he kept
all the old stuff i'm filing he's holding the fire axe the axe looks like it's covered in hershey
syrup but i figure out right quick it's blood i'm fast that way he says to me dawn i say yes sir
he had the axe right he says you want to know a secret something owns us he holds the door for me
like nice and so i go and when the door shuts i hear him just open up i mean just screaming and
smashing the shit out of everything he was a smart guy my boss not prone to violence not an unkind
word in years but he read everything every file that crossed that threshold knowledge is power
he'd say to me knowledge don that's the key and he was fucking goddamn right thanks don again i uh
i hate to say it but you people are into the weirdest shit to have your old pal wolf reading
that weird shit submit a five-star review on your podcast app screenshot that shit and send it to us
or tag us on social media at pretending pod on instagram and twitter pretending to be people on
facebook now keep in mind you can even just tag pretend pod on those instagram stories you know
your old buddy wolf loves seeing us get a little love in them stories now for a little news the
talented and beloved contention police officer keith vigna found himself saying's uniform
weapon and cruiser at the clinic he had to call his partners to pick him up meanwhile
officers bishop and pettymore detained dr marie jacobs and her blood-covered husband
doug jacobs in a cell at the contention police department after discussing these absurd recent
events the three officers went to charles donovan's room at hotel motel now uh wait a
minute do y'all feel that do y'all feel that beat this could only be one thing it's kudzu with no
backbone
so all three of you are going up to room 202 what do you want to do just open it up no knock it's a
me and what are the two of you guys doing oh i i had a backup gun right i i got a walkie-talkie
gun and everything back is that correct what gun did you grab because you lost your small powerful
gun i did wait i thought i just had my regular pistol gun my my that's a madman with a noisy
cricket well it's a small extremely powerful that's the one he stole i thought he just stole
like my i would assume that you always had that on you oh see i wasn't assuming that as well as
your police firearm i thought the yeah so you still look for it though like i feel like you'd
go for the surface revolver so he has both of my okay how about this not i don't i thought that
that gun was still in like lock up you can leave it in lock up and he just stole your police side
okay well so then i guess i have that gun on me because it was the only other pistol that i could
get so i have that yeah i didn't think we were fucking with our crazy shit yet more than welcome
well now i have to use it because you know i don't have another police gun if you didn't want to we
probably do but no i want to um okay i'm john and clark what are you guys doing uh i think vigna is
kind of a jinx so i'm standing back is there a window into this place from the outside are we
we keep calling them a hotel motel and are we for sure it's all outdoor yeah it's a motel it's
called hotel motel uh and so is there a window facing the lot yes and the blinds are closed i
stick the key in turn it and then try to quietly open the door i'm i'm to the side of the door
i'm at the door jam okay cool so you would see as you open it up the television is on and you hear
hey and happy days is playing on the television and there is a
woman on the bed and she is a gaunt woman with like crazy hair and enormous thick glasses that
make her already large eyes look even bigger and she's wearing jeans and a white shirt and a
leather jacket and when you hear fonzie on screen say hey she also goes hey and then looks up
immediately freaked out by you so is this like a greaser professor trelawney professor trelawney
is exactly what i was trying to think of yeah it's a greaser professor trelawney
sans tea leaves so she just is looking at me yep i say don't move officers coming through
i'm trying to be a cool guy cop like the fonz what does she do she's frozen
we need to ask you who are you we have questions for you
you ask her if there's anybody else in the room is there anyone else in the room
speak ah no just you it's just me who do you know here what how are you staying in this room
do you know someone who's staying here why are you here for you if you don't tell me what's up
do you know charles i put my hand on my gun
when you put your hand on your gun she puts her hand under the pillow to the right of her
i said i am a police officer not the tooth fairy get your hand out from under that pillow right now
damn that was a good line vigna thanks i've been proud as he's as he's doing this i'm coming in
behind him gun drawn gun drawn gun drawn uh but still behind keith okay so keith she immediately
just like wings her arm at you she's she's throwing an object at you uh what do you want
to do how do you want to respond to that action can i tell what she's throwing her is it too
quick of a motion uh go ahead and roll alertness for me
nice zero that's the bad one i got a hundred oh then you have no chance of dodging out of the way
so let's see if she passes her athletics role she does yay i'm so excited we thought you were cool
lady uh only rolled a one on damage however so keith you look away for like
half a second and all of a sudden there's a knife sticking in your um arm just like right
just like on your forearm like a how big of a knife it's a it's a small knife about six inches
long and sticking all the like all the way through my arm or what no it actually just
like under the skin yeah it didn't it didn't get in very deep it kind of went in at a weird angle
uh so it didn't mess with any tendons or anything hell yeah uh but you do take one damage okay i did
already i look down at it and i look up at her in the moments between or not between but as soon as
the knife is in his arm sure i've registered as such yeah what is she doing so she immediately
is reaching back under and throws another at clark bishop okay so how are you handling
that situation there's a knife being thrown at you currently i had the gun pulled i want to just fire
okay sounds good can i can i try to uh you can't grab the knife out of the air there's no one in
this town no this is fucking america like i'm gonna get lit the fuck up are you going for a
kill shot or purpose i mean i'm not but it might happen you can try to avoid a kill shot at an at
a penalty you can aim for a specific uh you know like a called shot is that the one yeah it's a
called shot so you would take a negative 20 on your firearms check to do less damage what is
that's what i want to do so my firearms is normally 80 so i'm rolling at a 60 right now correct
i pass crit pass crit pass ones just a single one yeah dude these are new these are different
dice too yep that we have been rolling high yeah they've been rolling shitty yeah oh my god okay
clark where do you want to shoot her in the throwing arm the arm that she was reaching back
under the pillow with that's perfect literally uh as she starts to fling an object you shoot her in
the hand and the knife just drops onto the bed next to her and she is going to uh roll over
off to the left side of the bed and john it is your turn what do you do you heard a uh gunshot
just now uh yeah i just like i slide in on my knees between keith and clark through the door
and i've just got my drunk gone drawn gone got my gun drawn
are you just gonna make us kill everybody like i've set up i've set up characters in specific
locations doing specific things why do they all attack cops this is america like we have to shoot
them you don't have to but you do i mean you can do it however you want however some of these
people are extremely aggressive and have things that they need to do i guess they don't think much
of the contention after i take my shot can i just say i winged her so that you know that i've at
least got her i mean like yeah i slide through the door and i'm like don't you move a fucking muscle
okay cool does she move a muscle she doesn't you can see the top of her head like she's on the far
side of the bed but you can see the top of her head peeking over hands in the air right fucking
now slowly raise your hands she slowly raises her hands in the air is there anything in them
yeah there's a lead pipe in one of her hands drop the pipe fonzie okay
she does not drop the pipe and keith it's your turn i pull the knife out of my hand or out of
my arm try to stab her in the arm with it to make her drop the pipe
so you've got a gun and she's got a pipe but i got a real powerful gun i don't not trying to
unleash this shit yet i'm doing it she i'm she's facing away from us right i would say based on
where you are in the room because i picture you kind of where the tv is and then she is to like
if you walked in the room the bed's on the left tv's right in front of you facing to the left
tv's right in front of you facing to the left and she's on the other side of the bed and you're
standing there so you can kind of see her at a side angle yeah i want to try to like slice at her
hand that's holding the pipe and then like pin her down on the ground okay go ahead and roll melee
i do not pass yeah she crit succeeds so as you swipe with a knife she immediately
like uses your momentum against you and holds the knife to your throat and she's got you hostage
and so it is clark's turn uh help me ma'am ma'am hey whoa hey don't do it uh hey don't do it i'll
fucking kill him uh we uh we're just here uh to ask you questions and you started slinging knives
at us i mean he pulled his gun oh i think he was thinking about pulling his gun because you
weren't talking i don't like him nobody really does uh unfortunately we're partial to him so
i need you to let him go and then can i roll a persuade on just that yeah absolutely i mean
it's gonna be very hard to get her to just let him go but okay sure roll persuade
oh what the fuck awesome i watched it happen with my eyes just rolled an ott one i rolled a one
again how many ones have you rolled i was about to say through this campaign i've done it a bunch
it's and i'm using different dice every time i promise have you done a bunch i have that's the
fourth at least the fourth yeah and two of them have been going back to back that's shots that's
that's the note right there wait what are you trying oh you're persuading i was just trying
to get her to let you go without doing anything else how about this i won't i'm sorry i won't
kill him and i'll let him go if you let me go tell the tell her that's okay tell her that's
okay come on do you know what happens when a one is rolled you're in no position to negotiate i
mean if you want to ari like i i just don't see literally any possible way that she's just going
to be like after hurting a police after like hurting a police officer that she's just going
to let him go and be like yeah have me well but then what does a one get you she's willing to
slice keith's throat currently so makes her stop i would why what but there's no way we're letting
her go sure that makes sense to her though i mean that's easy to do but then we're just fighting her
again but without keith being right there yeah i think this woman would have been dead from the
second she fucking threw a knife in your arm at this point she doesn't seem to have like a firearm
and we are at the entrance to the motel so we could just like let her go and then just i mean
what is she's not gonna escape ma'am uh we're amiable for that can we just ask you a question
or two before you go i will allow that as she motions the two of you into the corner opposite
from the door she's wanting to scoot towards the door with keith all right we got the key
to this place from a guy that we know to be charles do you know charles the tall guy yeah
yeah how do you know we work together
do you know who you're fucking with
no you should probably get more information because you are going to regret this
can you point me in a direction do the words marvin glass mean anything around these parts
now out of character you guys know marvin glass is the mob dude in the city he runs the city
of course i know marvin glass then you know
no no
coughs and cuts
then you know that you probably don't want to be on his bad side right now you're on the
contention pd's bad side you know what i'm fucking tired it's been a long ass day and your buddy
charles got his head blown off by me where the fuck is his radio the radio
sorry the radio that all sounds like you
she's having like a breakdown
you just want the radio oh no we actually want quite a bit more but god damn you are not being
very forthcoming we got guns on you we don't really even like vigna like well that's uh
she wants to be in the doorway with vigna and she wants you two to be over by the bathroom in this
motel room are you gonna do that i'm not i think i probably am all right so john what are you doing
she's got a knife to his throat yeah i don't know man john yeah john like john will scoot
but he's pissed that makes sense mostly mostly at vigna
first i'm like sweating bullets right now i've i am not confident that she's not gonna still
kill me i mean if all you want's the radio it's in the bathroom how does it work i don't know
you probably turn it on turn it to the station you want why did you want it i don't know charles
brought it back he said don't touch it it's in the bathroom i didn't know it was a big fucking deal
why did marvin send you here oh i mean marvin marvin sent us here to find out what happened
to his son who's his son well i mean germane glass him and i mean him and alfred came to collect some
money from john peters and then you know only alfred came back and he's a blubbering idiot
now so what do you mean now he won't shut up about some gun
i don't know what gun some uh he i i don't know that he sounded like a lunatic but marvin sent us
out here to find it find uh find germane this is hilarious to me because now it's you who has
no idea what the fuck you're dealing with if you had any idea how long our day has been the shit
we've been through the things we've seen marvin glass you think we give a shit
about the crime lord from the city contention is in some real shit right now you're in some
real shit too because you had to be banging around with that charles guy i don't know what your man
got into sounds like he stumbled into what we're into but this is a lot bigger than some crime
bosses so why don't you fucking let keith go and come with us and answer some questions and we
might be able to protect you from what that's what we're trying to figure out that radio turned a man
into a cat bullshit that gun turned your buddy and alfred into an idiot that makes sense right
ma'am uh the gun can do that so can a radio he's uh he's telling you the truth we've seen some shit
today and marvin is not even ranking on the list right now do you know billy harrison no charles
had him in the trunk of his car i don't know a billy hairs i literally okay you're you want to
know the deal i'm good at killing it's what i do and i get brought along to kill if it's necessary
i like you're stopping me from watching my happy days and i just want to watch my happy days
so i i don't want to get caught up in all this i just want to go back home and
where's charl where's charles do you did you arrest him i shot him in the fucking head with
a shotgun was he a good killer because he fucking died pretty well oh my god okay so here's what's
gonna happen i need everyone to roll dexterity i got a 14 on a 60 i got a 7 on a 65 i got a 73 on
a 60 i failed fail and then you guys both succeeded and what were your numbers 14
seven okay she rolled a 26 so she gets to go first and then 14 and then keith vigno wait
she gets to go first correct she she rolled higher higher under how we always played i know
like that i would have known to roll higher oh i'm so sorry i told you it makes it so that if
she has a higher pool she can still be you that makes sense yeah that does make sense okay sick
so uh she's gonna take the first action she's going to do the classic hostage move where she
just pushes the person that she has and then she's gonna she's running yeah so she dips and
it is keith next wait the dexterity rolls were like initiative i was thinking that it was our
chance of getting away from her normally whoever has the highest dexterity goes first but i thought
since it was such a tense moment that we'd add a little roll in there on our dexterity's to uh
make it a little bit more playful uh because she has a higher higher dexterity than you guys do
so what's her dex 80 oh that's very hot so she pushes keith and then turns around and jumps over
the railing keith what do you do i run outside look over the railing and how far away is she
she hit the ground and is gonna start running i'm gonna do called shot shooter in the like leg okay
uh go ahead and roll at a negative 20 shit fail all right so keith pops off a couple rounds
john it is your turn uh yeah i mean i'm running to the balcony i'm shooting at her too
62 on a 60 all right and she's going to continue running clark what are you doing i'm running out
and taking a shot as well so she is across she's like halfway across the parking lot at this point
and is heading to a maroon car in the parking lot roll firearms are you just i'm just shooting
at her just shooting trying to hit her all right uh crit pass 66 on an 80. i'm good at shooting
boys yeah you're very good at shooting i'm a shooter boy go ahead and roll 2d 10 for me
eight intense 18 is zero zero and eight yeah yeah 18 that's 18 so
you fire and like i'm thinking probably three shots hit her center mass and she is i mean blood
just splatters not only like onto the ground but also uh onto the car that she was like running
toward and she she passes her constitution check to stay conscious and she starts trying to get
into this car like we're right by the stairs right i mean yeah just imagine yeah i run down
the stairs and i go like try to go up to her can i do anything else or you can just get to her
yeah okay i get to her then yeah before he gets to her i'm gonna shoot her again okay
fail 82 on a 16 pop off a couple more rounds in the general direction clark what are you doing
i'm following keith okay she gets the door open um she's bleeding just like everywhere and
she's crawling up into the driver's side yeah that's all she can do this round keith what are
you doing i get to her and i start she doesn't have a weapon or anything with her does she i
mean i think she has your knife or her knife that she threw yeah yeah do i see it in her hand yeah
all right i want to try to if i like punch her in the face that's melee right if you're unarmed
you're it's unarmed if you had a weapon i mean she's got three bullets in the center of her
chest are we still in combat with her like what can she do with a knife fucking nothing try to
stab me well yeah i feel like you can very much just lift her the fuck up and if she tries i just
want to like if so is she sitting in the driver's seat she's crawling she's like well she's crawling
up into the driver's seat currently with the door open she's got like one hand on the door and just
one knife in her hand just like can i come up behind keith and just kick her hand with the
knife yeah i was gonna think yeah if you do that and then i was gonna do first aid on her to try
to keep her alive just to be able to get any more info out of her yeah i don't want to kill her yet
if we don't have to oh yeah my intent in kicking her hand knife free was for you to start cuffing
her but yeah we'll cuff her and then first aid yeah you guys can do that like no problem
cool cool so i have her cuffed and then i want to immediately start administering first aid to help
or not bleed out or at least have her stay alive longer than okay go ahead and roll first aid 47
on a 60 nice so you find um something to wrap you know or like put pressure on the wounds um all
three of them are thrown through so you got six holes to contend with so there's blood all over
your hands and it's going everywhere and uh can i be calling drew yeah sure hey uh drew drew we
need you to send an ambulance down here to the hotel motel right away okay john what are you
doing continue fire yeah i mean it's me and clark um i'll search the uh i'll start searching the
hotel like from the edge i'm like hey you guys got this down here yeah yeah we got it okay uh
i'm gonna search this hotel room for time sensitive information is she i guess i would help him with
the first aid now you're stable you've stabilized her so she's not gonna bleed out and die until the
ambulance gets there and then she'll die no you you stabilized her and john as you go through the
room in hotel motel you do find the radio it is a old timey radio with a red light shining on it and
lots of odd glass tubes kind of going all around it and such there is little else in the motel room
except for a tech nine under the bed 151 what's a tech nine again i just know they're apper
sorry is it like a pistol it's like a black pistol
oh gotcha can you do that again yeah that nice and uh a box set of happy days most hotel rooms don't
have dvd players so it's they brought one they brought one there's also a dvd player brand sanya
brought to you by sanya insert dvd sponsor here brought to you by the box set of happy days now
on blu-ray and tuesday happy days thursday friday what do you guys want to do wait for the amber
lamps it come yeah i'm gonna throw that radio in an evidence bag i want to examine it too
did you describe it already i was actually this whole time picturing a standing old timey radio
is it small so i would say it's one that would sit on a desk that is probably i figured an
old timey radio but like the little half yeah i was picturing it about two feet wide a foot tall
and uh it's got a light on it that's shining red oh that's what you call a foot you call five
inches yeah it's uh it's uh it's got a uh two two like lights on it and the red and the green
and the red one is is lit it's lit there's the lit fame backlit dudes are cool life is tight
when the ambulance comes i just want to tell the emts she's dangerous you keep her alive
but you keep her restrained i'm gonna go with her in the ambulance i pull keith back keith
we've been thinking about replacing you on patrol duty with uh with drew can you guys
manage my arm up real quick for me while you're here are you asking us or the emts the emts good
uh yeah sure of course uh this drew are you related to drew oh no hello down at the station
oh no this is
it's just that contention accent i'm just that young guy from earlier
oh you sound a lot cooler all of a sudden he started smoking
everyone around here kind of sounds like this
that uh our our lackey guy what's his name tim or something lauren no it was ray but now it's not
oh lauren is the officer who takes care of everything for you guys okay that doesn't
sound right lauren i let's get it does though let's get lauren to uh meet the this perp at
the hospital and keep an eye on her didn't it start with a d or it was travis right
travis or i have no idea what you're talking about it's always been lauren you're pretty sure
i do want to send lauren to keep an eye on this perp at the hospital perfect is that l-a-u or
l-o-r-e yeah is it lauren lauren lauren it's lauren lauren lauren is it a boy or girl l-a-u-r-e-n
she identifies as a woman dope is she hot
idiot i'm sorry guys i am just i've had an off day you know an off well an off career so far
for future reference if a woman slings a knife at you you're an officer of the law you can shoot
her yeah but yeah and if then she then is just like peacefully like you know she surrendered
she was still holding a pipe though i don't know why you would close that distance well
because i am trying to get the most information i can out of these people i you know at the end
of the day it would be great to take down the mob in the city be known for that you know and
mob is like an oozy blackness spreading across decent society right we got one of
those in contention right now that's an actual oozy blackness spreading across
decent life forms you know what i mean like so do you want me to go
kill her is that what you're telling me to do i'm kind of confused here i mean i want to be you
guys are better cops than i am and i want to be a better cop so if you need me to just go kill her
that's going to make me a better cop and didn't just tell me to do it we're not saying kill her
now we're saying you probably could have killed her then but she's totally within your or at least
winged her i mean but guess what i'm alive and she's alive and we can get information i don't
see the downside of this right here she's barely alive let's yeah but barely alive is still
technically alive we did seem to come out ahead on this one you are correct okay so the next
perp i'll just kill him no well got it if they intend harm upon you keith go ahead and kill him
i assume that every criminal wants to intend harm upon a police officer because that's
criminals favorite crime right nothing i'm gonna have to maybe read up on this i don't
a little a little confused here did you go to the academy yeah in the city i did yeah they taught
me they taught me more up there than they taught you what year did you graduate i oh that's never
mind that sorry too too personal too personal i forgot years don't exist we don't ask those
kind of questions i'm just trying to i'm just trying to figure out that's yeah hr would be on
my ass if i knew well i try not to kill anybody but i guess i'll make it more of a make more of
an effort to kill then no it's again it's not about merely killing like so make them make them
make them suffer maybe just be a little safer okay keith we're not telling you to make people
suffer we're not telling you to kill people make them suffer but but do if i have maybe don't let
them try to kill you or make you suffer right that's what we're golden rule i'll do some more
research on how to act like a proper police officer and we'll get back to you in the meantime
keith you ever played a video game do you like video game guy particularly john peters was is
that what you're talking about that's probably what i was thinking of but you know when you've
when you got your melee class and your ranged class it's generally not advised for the range
class to try to close the distance and engage the melee class you know in their wheelhouse that's
kind of what happened with that lady in the pipe and you and the knife keith nods his head and
acts like he knows what you're talking about all right fellas uh she was talking about a gun that
screwed up i think she said alford yeah made him made him an idiot well there was that girl back at
mildred mitchell's house who she had a gun she had a gun that she shot at me and then disafucking
peered and boy i tell you what i'd be talking about that for a while also hmm maybe we should
they said alford did come back though right alford did come yeah alford yeah maybe we should be
talking to him trying to find him but changed clark you still have that gun oh it didn't
disappear with her for some reason i thought you guys took it i would assume oh that's right yeah
i do remember that you know i know it was just the other day but it feels like weeks ago yeah
we've got the we've got a camera a radio and again the gun they all have weird tubes coming off of
them they've all got red and have we tried to turn the radio on or anything yet oh i would not we have
not to do that we're not going to because of the cat man situation true unless you want to you have
a dog right i don't want to be a dog well if you want to volunteer to turn that on while your dog
is in the room so it's the one that gets well what if it switches with any but anything but if
i could switch with you that would be pretty cool for me not for you so much but you know keith i
mean in spite of all that we said here you you know i'm a good cop you're not that but you do
have an attractive bod i would i would freak you friday with you let's talk about that later
going back through my sweet little cop notebook uh there's one more item from that uh shop that
is unaccounted for which one uh it was a helmet that was purchased by the first church of
contention we haven't been to the church yet have we how about we do that tomorrow yeah yeah we get
a good night's rest oh we do that oh dang there's that guy on the there's a guy remember that guy
that overpowered you and took your uniform and just vaguely your service firearm and let's go
hunt him down what can we what can we do because we don't know what he was driving we don't know
if he's on foot we just know what he was wearing he's kind of what he looks like he's got my radio
i was thinking we should set up a trap yeah that radio trap we can mention something and just show
up there and if it doesn't work then we can go to sleep and try it again tomorrow what do you think
could trap him maybe he got on the bad side of charles and he was also snooping around john
peters because he's looking into these artifacts as well so if we put it across the radio that we've
got the radio and john peters or any of those yeah or that we've got a lead on where the radio is and
we're headed there yeah right and then he shows up yeah but then we're there already so what do we
say we have a lead on the john peters and the radio because he's he seemed like he was trying
to find john not i mean perhaps we don't know that john peters is alive so if he's dead yeah but i
don't think that this guy knows whether john is dead or not i think he was looking for him and
couldn't find him we don't know what he was looking for at john peters house lots of people
been poking around there lots of crazy devices turning people into catmen turning up around
there if they think john peters is going to be there it'd be extra incentive well how about we
give the description of a man who resembles john peters okay yeah let's do that i like that john
peters is a short balding man with large eyes and a tiny nose so that's where do we want to set up
this sting operation should we set it up like down the street from the police station let's
make it convenient on ourselves at uh what it's on that street well there's the donut hole they
could say he's there yeah is that a 24-hour donut hole where is the donut hole that's just something
i made up that might be near the police station i was thinking if we for sure yeah oh cops like
donuts yeah that's right so yeah that makes sense uh i just mean like if we could set up a place
that we have like a van like a security man no i just meant like if there was buildings around
wherever we're going that we could get on the rooftop camouflage right next door yeah like get
up on the roof he's got some hunting blinds displayed in the parking lot yeah so i'm thinking
like the downtown area where the police station is he has like roof access that we could like put
one on the roof put somebody in a car or like in a in in like a personal vehicle why don't we just
set up a dummy yeah in john peter's clothes in the middle of the parking lot and it looks like
he's fiddling with the radio yeah and then we just fucking elmer futhish you know we wait for
the bunny to show up not a terrible idea i don't think oh i do but i don't think we should have
the radio out there what could go wrong um what do we just like have them go to the be like yeah
they're in the donut hole and then just one of us could be sitting in there with like a hood on or
something be like describe john peter's wearing a hoodie we have the hoodie on and then one of you
guys like across the way on the top of the building and one of you guys or one of us in a
car i like it so who wants to be the guy inside you have that sniper rifle do you want to be on
the roof sure and then between me he already knows so this really does seem like a situation this guy
already knows what i look like that's true being neutralizing instead of killing yeah i think you
should be inside but he's he's already assaulted a cop he has his clothes yeah let's play it out
though so he comes in let's say do i take him down from inside or do we wait till he gets outside i
don't know if anybody should be sniping yeah i think we all just need to get this guy two of us
like one of us be in the bathroom or something one guy be sitting there facing away from the window
with a hoodie on and then one guy outside and then we all kind of like rush him once he like gets to
where you are okay do you want to be in the bathroom or do you want to be in the bathroom
do you want to be outside or in the bathroom i kind of got to go to the bathroom okay john in
the bathroom i'll be waiting outside in a car and then once he goes inside i'll be closing closing
in closing that closing that exit and then i'll just be inside be invading probably just take him
down as soon as you see i probably have civvies at the station right oh yeah i'll swing by the
station and put on my regular boy clothes yeah i'll put my regular clothes on too that way he
doesn't like see a uniformed cop sitting in a car be in the bathroom so i'll just wear my clothes
as soon as i see him i'll radio you i guess or maybe just shout you'll hear me shouting for
him to freeze let's arrange some kind of signal you have your radio off and then i'll be outside
once he goes inside i'll radio you there you go we'll close in on him i like it okay and break
what's the plan uh i'm gonna be waiting i'm gonna swing by the station and put on my regular
civilian clothes and sit in the donut hole i put on civilian clothes as well i sit in my car
across the street from the donut hole and i radio in i've got a description a short balding man
big eyes and a kind of small nose matching the description of a wanted person we have reason
to believe that he might be dangerous and he's got he's got that that radio that we've been told
about that we've been looking for so if we could get uh if we could get somebody down to the donut
hole uh yeah it's gonna take me an hour probably to get down there yeah i'm i'm not anywhere close
right now uh what about you john i am in the bathroom somewhere else it's gonna be a minute
okay well uh if we can have maybe lauren or or drew get down there but uh it's gonna take all
three of us a while to get there it seems like so i'm in route either way okay sick so you guys
wait i've ordered a coffee and a single glazed donut and i'm maybe reading the paper from
yesterday because it's like one in the morning yeah yeah real quick if you guys could all lose
one willpower for me i am so excited guys i hope our plan works for absolutely nothing to happen
okay so after about 15 minutes a black suv rolls up and parks a block away from the donut hole
a very short young woman and a very tall old man get out and they are both wearing a black suit
white shirt black tie black sunglasses and an ill-fitting windbreaker that says fbi in big
letters across the back clark as you sip on your coffee you hear the door behind you swing open
the door chimes jingle and jangle and you hear footsteps out of the corner of your eye you see
a short young woman walk across the shop to the counter the other footsteps approach you from
behind
oh
street me down takes me back