Hello my loyal listeners, it's your radiotherapist wolf the dog and I'm here to dole out suspect
advice to people I barely know anything about and soothe your worries when it concerns the
goings on and contention and the world.
Or uh making them worse sometimes, hell I don't know what I'm doing here but y'all keep
listening.
As always we are broadcasting from 694.2 PTBP, the only place your worried minds can go to
be soothed when the galaxy is trying to swallow y'all up.
Anyway this week's howlin with wolf comes from at 1983bit who tweeted about the show
and tagged at pretending pod.
Spreading the news about this show is the only thing that will keep it on the air y'all.
Plus it makes my heart full of kissy kissy feelings.
They right.
Did the outstanding officers of contention notice the signs at the town's border that
said it was twinned with a small town in England called Uddersfield?
This is a message from Wolf's British cousin who has heard the news of the strange goings
on.
Uddersfield is safe y'all apart from the influx of top grade cocaine courtesy of the local
church which is floodin the cobbled streets of this west Yorkshire town.
Don't forget to send us a postcard from Contention Wolf.
We await your next update.
Tom from Uddersfield UK.
Now listen here Tom the dog.
I told you to never ride into the show.
I told you what I'd do to you if I ever caught a whiff of you scurrying about.
I'd throw your soul into a dimension from which you'd never return.
You'd drift on slowly grasping at everything but touching nothing while you fade from
existence over millennia.
But nice to know things are good in jolly old London Thomas from Uddersby.
Speaking of jolly times.
If you want to write up something for your wolf to howl tag at pretending pod on Instagram
or Twitter tag pretending to be people on Facebook or write a 5 star review and email
us at pretendingpod at gmail dot com.
Also don't sleep on the contest happening over on the subreddit r slash pretending to
be people.
You could win your very own hardback slipcase set of Delta Green the Role Playing Game.
So join up with the community there and get to stepping on that contest y'all.
Sometimes when I hear about the horrors of the world I feel like stepping into a different
reality.
It's the news.
Last time Francis Beans embedded a big ol' rusty fish hook into John Lee Pettymore's
shoulder before Clark Bishop could step in.
Clark gave her a boot to the gut and she fell into the massive aquarium hitting her head
on the catwalk on the way down and they left her to float face down in the murky water
for pretty much the entirety of the episode.
Meanwhile Keith Vigna escaped from the creature that swallowed him and George Piston.
He pulled it off by firing his small but powerful pistol into the wall of this beast planting
a frag grenade into the newly made enclave and using George Piston as a shield from the
blast.
Keith hit the surface laughing and gibbering some nonsense about something being inside
him.
They tried to let Kathy Piston off the hook from which she hanged but they fucked up and
dropped her to the bottom of the tank.
John Lee Pettymore jumped in, rolled luckily and paddled Kathy Piston back into the presuming
safety of the catwalk.
Keith performed CPR on both Francis and Kathy but wouldn't you know it only Kathy survived.
After releasing Doug Jacobs in the body of Agent Trent Chad from his arm shredding fish
hook our three protagonists and their two new companions stand together ready to take
on the evil of Marvin Glass and foil his plans to take over the hometown of contention.
But first I've set aside just enough time to prepare a brand new song.
It may take some time to get used to like Bitter Coffee and Step-Parents but it's what
the American masses want inside of them like Bitter Coffee and Step-Parents.
It's kudzu with no backbone.
Let's start the episode now.
Zach later.
Start it here.
Pop pop pop!
Oh god.
Now you can see.
Yeah.
It's visual.
There was a guy on Reddit today that asked if you treated- fuck.
I think it was-
I think his example was IMDB scores and Rotten Tomatoes but I just used Rotten Tomatoes but
it was if you treated directors scores as a batting average that if you took all their
scores and averaged them out and I got really curious so I did a bunch of them and it was
really interesting.
Nice.
Who had the best?
So obviously because it's averages like Kubrick was way up there because he only has like
six films and they're all a hundred basically.
The ones I thought were interesting Ingmar Bergman and Martin Scorsese both have like
80% averages and they've both got like 35 films each.
They've got a huge list.
I was gonna say Scorsese would probably be up there.
Their status is way up there.
The one I was surprised was low.
What was it?
I think it was Fincher maybe had a really low score.
I wonder who the worst is.
I did M. Night Shyamalan just to see and it was 49.
It was really low compared to the others.
He's had some bangers in some really really truly awful movies.
Still batting 490 so.
If he was a baseball player he'd be in the Hall of Fame.
So as a GM and as a goon as I traditionally call myself or dumb as some have been known
to say I have an interesting time with how we end a session or an episode in some of
these cases do I do a cliffhanger is fun often or do I give you guys something right
off the bat the next time that you're not prepared for you just always wait for somebody
to say something dumb or funny and then I start screaming shut up it's over stop playing
the fun game and then we have to stop talking to each other you won't take this seriously
so let's go ahead and kick it off let's see where we're at I think you guys were on the
catwalks walking up to we had getting down we had just got a trench head Trent Chad Doug
Jacobs Chad yeah we just got him down and did we do anything else where was that pretty
much this I'm pretty sure that's where we ended I think that's about where it ended
you did you did some sort of a cheerful gathering the group together speech we all high-fived
freeze-frame high-five Francis Dunn at this point right or is she very dead very dead
and that's what I thought very dead Francis is bacon so you guys are standing on this catwalk
with Doug Jacobs in the body of agent Trent Chad who's trying to recover from everything that's
happened to him and Kathy piston who you've been having some interesting conversations with will
you remind me how much time has passed since the last time we saw Doug Chad the last time you saw
him would have been in the cage but I mean in mortal time did we put has a day passed or two
I think about a day okay though you've all been unconscious remember in the last 24 hours when
we died no not really it seems like weeks ago so you guys are all standing there and the there's
the catwalk that leads away from the torture chamber or prison or whatever weird aquarium
topping that you are currently standing in and on the other side away from that is the elevator
door and I need you all to roll alertness for me as you begin walking toward the elevator door
I pass an 18 on a 70 pass 54 on a 60 the eight nice yeah three successes so you guys all see
as you're walking down this catwalk busting up out of the water just to the right of you
is the fish man you saw earlier wearing the brown jumpsuit who is walking the perimeter in here and
he flops up onto the catwalk kind of like a fish out of out of water and begins to shake off and
we are going to enter combat cool enter combat now I've done something kind of fun maybe perhaps
interesting for this specific combat that we're in right now we all got to get ourselves drenched in
the bathtub this is very cool whoa I assume this will be posted on the Instagram it will indeed so
what I've done is I used a whiteboard to make a map of the room that you're in you'll see the
grid has the green where the water is and the white is the catwalk that you're standing on
remember catwalk is kind of great you know so you can still see and very much smell the water coming
out from underneath you that black X's are on a couple of the water spots those are where bodies
are hanging and over there there's a circle with a little frowny face and two X's that's where the
body of Francis beans is and then down here we have the catwalk leading to the elevator door we
also have five little little magnets three of which are cat butts the butts of cats I thought
they were dinosaurs they look extremely similar to brontosauruses and then we have two little
markers down here one is a kitty pen magnet thing and the other one's just a little brick so the
little brick is gonna be agent Trent Chad's body with Doug Jacobs trapped inside and the little
kitty there is going to be Kathy piston what color cats do you guys want to be we've got an orange
cat a gray cat and a black cat I want to be the orange cat I'll be the gray cat I got the black
cat then all righty is that elevator door the one we came in to get into this room it is indeed okay
so are we positioned correctly right now sure okay then we leave you got this Kathy so the elevator
door so this brown suit fish man flops in between you guys and the elevator door and stands up and
shakes all this water off of him and looks up at you and we are now in combat Joe Clark Bishop
always acts first what do you do I want to pull so I handed Kathy a gun last episode yeah I want
to pull the other one from my waistband and throw it to Doug Chad all right and if I can I'd like to
still pull mine out of my boot can I do two of those I would say that you could like pull one
throw it and then pull another but maybe not shoot this turn that's what I'll do if that works for
you and who's got a better dexterity between John Lee Pettymore and Keith Vigna I have 60 50
all right so Keith Vigna you are up next so real quick Doug Chad might not be able to catch too
well with his stigmata dance I didn't want to influence your role-playing decision but I'll
roll for him let's see if he'll have a 40% chance to catch it that's not bad given where the cat
butts are I could just grapevine it down to him he rolled a 31 yeah so that's our Doug Chad he
grimaces and is like alright ready to go and then he loads he like cocks the pistol so you can tell
he means business and it is Keith Vigna's turn I pull out my tiny powerful gun aim it right at
that fish man and take a shot all righty go ahead and roll firearms for me 74 and a 70 oh so you
fire into the wall and it actually makes a divot in this so the wall right next to the elevator is
that same like onyx kind of like black obsidian and you fire into it and it actually like kind of
cracks and you can see in the reflection it like shatters into a bunch of different like mirror
reflections all coming back and it looks very cool awesome miss thanks John Lee Pettymore it's
your turn I want to sling my shotgun like down to my hip and pull my pistol out with my other hand
and give them a blast with each with each yeah dual wielding yes all right I'm gonna have you
roll firearms at negative 20% oh man hopefully this was a good call yes 25 on a modified 60 so
40 congratulations all right so you are almost point-blank range so you're gonna be in your
second damage increment on the shotgun so you're gonna roll 3d6 for damage on that on just the
shotgun yeah and then also it was a pistol you said the heavy pistol in yep so 1d 10 3d 6 plus
two hell yeah good shot oh no okay so eight plus so 10 10 total all right so that blast goes
directly into his gut and have you ever was aiming for his guilt has he ever gutted a fish
before yeah what's it look like on the inside fish guts yeah so it's that you blast through
and you can tell especially since it's his turn next you'll be able to tell that he's gonna be
able to continue to act but according to what one might call I think it's D&D is it Dungeons
and Dragons rules he is certainly bloodied immediately he's oh wow for talking ooh ooh for
talking talking talking for talking ooh ooh for talking talking talking yeah that's
talking talking talking you hear that all happen in quartet fashion as three other fish men show
up on the map and I will place them they're going to be on either side of you and in the
back of the room by Francis beans body they're flanking us there was another cat but available
and you saved it for a fish man there was what are those cats called it's got a black tail it's
like the one in meet the parents like Siamese sure and so with that these other you hear a
full quartet and surround sound of this chance oh by the way he has a smile while he's singing
more of a grimace than a smile I suppose more of a giant purple action figure for McDonald's and
he his teeth are like human teeth I don't know if I've ever explained that when he when he grimaces
these uh these mutated humans they still have it's like those fish clown fish they're not
fish I think I looked it up once and they've got real weird human looking teeth yeah and
this creatures in front of you also has those teeth with that his turn is finished and Doug
Jacobs Oh Kathy piston are both standing there with pistols in their hands well hey can we get
back to the magnet thing real quick Doug was a cat okay okay you're absolutely right I fucked up
really bad here so we're gonna take away the just swap them the brick the brick is now fish man
the brick is now a fish man and Doug Jacobs is rightfully a cat but it's called a sheep's head
fish oh I hate that yeah it's really gross like it what I'm imagining it's bad in my mind space
bad oh freaking out they are they're both gonna fire in two two different directions here Kathy
is gonna shoot the one who is flanking you from the back and side and Doug Jacobs is gonna fire
at the one right in front of him Doug Jacobs misses wildly and fires into one of the shattered
pieces of wall that Keith fired into earlier breaking it further into a prettier site oh and
Kathy piston fires true and does five damage to one of the fish men the one on the bottom the one
on the bottom nice good job Kathy Kathy piston fires straight and true she let loose a bullet
she slayed the fish man she shot gun real good fireball variable the other three fish men
continued in their their chanting and you hear a rumble and your feet begin to shake and you see
in the distance two massive claws grab on to the catwalk and begin ripping it down and the catwalk
fully breaks off into the water and where it once was you see this massive creature that looks
exactly like one of these fish men unclothed and four times larger and this one has a giant wound
in its side and it is bleeding out pus water and this black ichor what's the junk like oh it's
super tight that will be portrayed by this magnet for tank seven by Boulevard Brewing
smokestack series cool cool yeah making me thirsty and with that the giant monster fish
creatures in the game at the top of the order here it's gonna be Clark Bishop's turn and I
want to give you guys a few outlines for this combat basically in order to leave this room
from what you know right now you have to leave through the elevator in order for the elevator
to come you have to press the button you don't know how many rounds it's gonna take for the
elevator to come after you press the button so you have to survive until the elevator comes you
can each move you make an elevator come carefully you can each move two spaces which I'm gonna
dictate as grid spots so you can move from like one water to the you know move up different water
spaces in the grid or no sorry you can move one space and act or you can move two spaces with no
how many spaces away is the button for the elevator the button for the elevator is going
to be two spaces away from where you all are now okay like the elevator bridge represents two
squares basically sure yeah yeah yeah cool all right Clark Bishop top of the round what do you
want to do I'm going to fire at the fish man that is blocking our way to the elevator all right go
ahead and roll firearms for me yeah I pass a 24 on an 80 already rolled damage that's a four four
on one d10 do you say anything cool does he die oh yeah fuck so you you firing into him with your
pistol I got him hook line and sinker it's made all the cooler as the fish man stumbles back and
forth as being shot and looks at you and goes dogging and then falls off to the left side into
the water and you see blood start to dissipate all throughout the water he would have been a
really chill dude if he was like hook line and sinker barely knew her and then died that would
have been very chill you're a chill way to respond to somebody like action movie line yeah is Delta
green a game where if I've now used an action I can't move or can I go ahead and use the movement
I would have had game Joe is this okay it's a life it's a lifestyle in which you can move one
space after you fire yeah I'd like to go ahead and make my way middle of the gang weather making my
way the middle Clark Bishop is now in the middle on his way to the elevator one space away Keith
Vigna it's your turn hey do I have a clear shot on big boy you do he's pretty far away pretty
right now about 50 yards out I'll take one step or one square towards them and then take a shot
with my tiny powerful gun yeah do you do anything cool or do you just like walk slowly toward it or
do you tremble or are you scared at all this giant fucking beast that's in front of you I fought this
motherfucker already you fucking took this as I fire at him I say eat this noodle fish bitch
all right okay roll okay 93 wow you cannot roll a success to save your life sucks you just fire
this this gun I mean it the noise that it makes in this room every time you fire it is exhausting
to the ears as is your lack of good rolling strongly petty more stern can I make it to the
elevator this turn you absolutely can okay I want to do that and press the button now already pardon
me you press the button to the left of the elevator door and it lights up green a few more
times John Kathy piston is going to in full Keanu Reeves fashion just start walking slowly and
calmly to the fish man she already shot and continue firing into it succeeding once again
yeah awesome and compliant NPC oh but she she does fire true however she only wings them in
the shoulder and it does not seem to do any damage whatsoever which is interesting if you
had to put a numerical value on it I would say zero it seems like these fish men have some sort
of armor on their skin that is making them not take full damage from gunfire interesting like
an amphibious chainmail like an amphibious chainmail Doug Jacobs is going to join you on
the catwalk he's very scared he wants to get out of here he's tired his arms hurt and he's bleeding
all over the place he's very upset and for the last like couple hours he's just been doing
everything everyone says and he hated feeling that way and he's scared if it gets real bad we
just throw this bleeding bastard to the big fish like chum right I'm saying no of course not but
I'm nodding yes these fish men both jump in the water ooh sneaky habits is bloop bloop and then
they pop out on either side of Keith Vigna they got some movement on them the massive lumbering
creature is clawing its way right toward Keith Vigna who is now being completely surrounded by
these amphibious creatures oh that's close and it gets close enough in one turn to go ahead and
try to claw at Keith Vigna succeeding so so Luke if you die before we play the next game do you
want to just uber home instead of the claw does nine damage so claw basically one of the like
claw just reach it like goes directly into your shoulder and the back four claws all dig into
your back and it is going to with a successful claw attack it has a chance to grab and it fails
the group the grab so it digs its claws into you for nine damage and you start bleeding just
profusely and you actually feel a crunch where it entered you because it went all the way through
the layer of metal that is in that arm gosh well fuck I have two hit points left not to say we're
fucked oh you have two hit points left and so you took nine damage when you had 11 so I'm gonna go
ahead with two hit points you might fall unconscious why did I say that so oh because we're playing a
game fun when we when we play by the oh we shouldn't be shakes your consequences everything
she always work out so I need you to roll a constitution check to stay awake as blood just
gushes 93 with different dice yeah that is absolutely remarkable as Keith Emmett light
goes out and he falls on to the catwalk Luke I'm gonna need you to leave the room yeah I figured
oh shit we'll save you Keith I hope so I've actually got a pretty decent plan I think
the only one
try