wow this is crazy y'all damn hot damn hot and crispy
i just took over this radio station but y'all can hear me 26 years in the past that's some
fucking demographics that no other radio station can claim my past babies i am wolf the dog
and you are listening to me 26 years ago live on 694.2 ptbp these radio waves may be broadcasting
in the past but i am always living in the present when it comes to y'all showering me
with fan mail this week's howling with wolfers from fire lizard games who went above and
beyond by tagging at pretending pod with a nice little message on twitter instagram and
facebook thanks for the social media cross-pollination y'all they write fire lizard games a springfield
mo base company is running the second kickstarter for a short novel titled examination it's
written by an author that goes by the name perry hartree it's a dystopian sci-fi suspense
thriller with horror elements the setting for examination served as the inspiration
for the adventure module for fire lizard games tabletop rpg called base a card pg so
if you like to do a little reading and you like sci-fi suspense horror and backer tears
starting at two dollars head on over to fire lizard games.com or check out any of the social
media pages to find direct links to the kickstarter thank you fire lizard games.com a springfield
mo base company whenever i ask people to describe me they often tell me that i too
fill them with horror and suspense you want to promote your next kickstarter or shout
out your gaming group or send your wolfy a message of love and loyalty here on 694.2
talk about pretending to be people on the internet y'all at pretending pod on instagram
and twitter a five-star review on itunes also totally works if you want to support
the show financially instead of using your immense social clout throw us some bones over
at patreon.com pretending pod in fact last week we announced our new patreon tiers so
go check out the unveiled world of possibilities where you can submit an npc and location join
us for patreon exclusive live stream hangouts and even hop on roll 20 to play some delta
green with the pt bp crew all right y'all it's 26 years ago we've arrived a pro post
not too slow because we know the flow to come say hello to the cameo tempo it's dream girl
with pretty sexual
the tops of trees thick enough to obscure any view of what is below and covered in a
layer of kudzu seem to go on endlessly up and down over hills and valleys mountains
and gorges there is nothing but dense verdant forest a circular calm lake finds itself somewhere
in the midst of this lush wilderness and in the middle of that lake a small island with
less than a quarter mile from shore to shore a long wooden dock on the north side of the
island leads to a charming two-story boat house with six well-kept cedar canoes tied
up below the second story apartment if the island is the face of a clock that dock is
at high noon there are six cute cozy little cottages evenly dispersed along the shore
of the island at one o'clock three o'clock five o'clock seven o'clock nine o'clock and
eleven o'clock five of the six cottages are in pristine condition the eleven o'clock place
might be too but it looks doubtful since the entire building is covered in a massive blue
tarp surrounding each of these cottages is truly master craft landscaping stunningly
gorgeous flowers in every shade and shape fill varied gardens and planters that somehow
both overrun the terrain and complement it perfectly each cottage has a cobblestone walkway
lined on either side by these lovely flower beds and the walkways all make their way to
the center of the island where a large equally cute and cozy hexagonal building sits
break y'all there is a small welcome sign on the south side of this building right at six
o'clock welcome to calm comfy campgrounds and then we go into this main building this main
large hexagonal building and inside we find a room that is circular the wall never ceasing
and never creasing at any point even where the wall meets the ceiling and the floor the angles
are rounded off there are six chairs in a half circle facing a single chair in front of them
each chair has a bottle of water next to it and standing around this room or sitting in
these chairs are the four of you along with two others let's go ahead and go around and
describe these characters who wants to start I'll start my guy is in a really nice white
seersucker suit a nice head of hair on him he's a he's it's slick back and nicely quaffed he's
got big thick rim glasses on and he's handsome and he looks like he takes care of himself and
on his arm is his wife Angela who is a lively young woman with a thick mane of curly hair in
a floral sundress with strappy leather sandals that go up above her ankles and the two of them
are in a corner of the room standing and talking yeah well hey there Joe hey there's that are you
ready for this yeah okay so we see Roger Fairfield and Angela Fairfield a nice young married couple
right standing at six o'clock on this large island surround island surrounded by Lake calm and you
guys are walking up a cobblestone pathway up to a large hexagonal building ahead of you you see
everything the flowers just verdant gardens all around bushes and trees make up much of this place
and through some of them on either side you can see these small cute little cottages tucked away
in their own little areas but ahead of you is this large hexagonal building and you said we were
walking up from six o'clock yes so we started at the south side of yes and Angela looks at you
and she's kind of like bouncing back and forth between from cobblestone to cobblestone and she's
like Raj I just think this is gonna be such a solid experience for you Roger kind of stretches
out he's in a nice white seersucker suit that's his leisure wear yeah yeah of course and he does
a big stretch take in that sweet lake air and that that's that's real nice in it it's beautiful
I'm so glad that we could just get away and really focus on like finding our emotions and really
being able to communicate right Raj I don't know about all that but I'm happy to go along with
whatever you think is gonna help us I think it's gonna be great and she like twirls out and spins
and it's really taking in the Sun is beating right down on you guys and it is a gorgeous day
here at calm comfy campgrounds but as she's spinning her arms wide stretched taking in all
the vitamin D she can get Jesus I'm the worst you notice that on her arm on the inside of one of her
arms track marks that you have not noticed before and she stops spinning kind of like crumbles into
herself and looks at you she's kind of lurches toward you and throws her arms around your neck
and it's like this is gonna be a perfect weekend to start our marriage off on the right foot kind
of hesitantly but mindfully avoiding asking about those marks yes if you think it's gonna
help us I I'll do what I can turning around you see the sign for calm comfy campgrounds and you
walk up on to this large hexagonal building it's like made of wood almost like like a rustic
hunting house however it seems more modern than that it has certain amenities and you would know
calm comfy campground is a luxury so this is not just a cabin in the woods it's not it's different
than that it's on a island that's on a lake that's in the woods it's completely different gotcha a
cabin on the lake in the woods at the bottom of the ocean the main building this hexagonal
building is similarly bestroon with delightful flowers made of many shades and shapes and as
you guys walk in the inside is equally rustic and elegant and modern and there's a massive wooden
chandelier hanging over the foyer on the desk to your right is a bell with a sign that says please
boop for assistance and a vase with a single red rose there's a little area back there with a chair
but it's currently empty and then you notice on your left there's a table with a coffee pot and a
water cooler on either side of a bowl of fruit Roger's gonna walk over to that Bell and see that
sign huh don't mind if I do and it says boop as he rings says boop as your answer of course you
have to go ahead and roll alertness oh boy first roll or since you're listening for someone coming
roll search okay damn it I failed an 86 on a 60 oh damn I still fail there's just silence and you
don't hear anything but then now that taking up your oral connection in your brain is a slight
little you turn back around there she is Angela with a flask in her hand just like taking a quick
pull and she like puts it down and wipes her mouth she's like some coffee and water over here I mean
that's fine I assume they would have a bar but it's kind of early to be starting in it and Angela
I don't I don't know if we should be drinking before we start are we not on vacation oh you're
right I guess the work is something we can focus on at a sober time that's fine that's fine that's
makes sense and then she puts it back in her little clutch that she was carrying you guys
would have had luggage with you I was just about to ask have we been to our cottage yet no you have
not okay so are you carrying yeah suitcases yeah okay once we once we get checked in then maybe we
can break out the flask I just think that we should focus you know make sure our heads are
clear when they give us instructions and things like that she walks up to you slowly puts her
hand on your chest I just knew that once we got here you would be receptive and you'll make the
best go of this possible I love you look love you too Angie that goes without saying well that was
weird yeah we're gonna get real weird together Oh Joe maybe Oh babe
Thomas my character is off on his own it's the circular room there's no corners but it looks
like he's somehow managed to like squeeze himself into a corner kind of space you don't know how
he's done it but how is he done it he's he's created like he is just projecting this air of
like impenetrable personal space around him and he is he has a pager in one hand and he's looking
down at it and he's talking on a big old-fashioned cell phone in the other hand kind of quietly he's
wearing a nondescript CSU gray hoodie jeans and sneakers and a baseball cap and sunglasses
indoors and you are having a difficult time hearing the person at the other end of your
phone call as the service keeps cutting in and out what did you say and what I I'm having a
difficult time hearing you as the service keeps cutting in and out so good so good wow that was
realistic Thomas Zach you ready yeah Bradley Cooper is standing at six o'clock on the bottom
of this island the listeners can know right yes okay how about this be Bradley Cooper aka other
way around Bradley Cooper okay Martin Cooper are you not also known as so Martin Cupertino
I'll use your real name yeah I mean like if we're solo just call me Martin okay yeah and then
anytime I have to interact with somebody I'll lie okay sounds good I will too and I'll be really good
at it I'm sure I'll never slip up so Martin you're standing at six o'clock on this island and in
front of you is a long cobblestone pathway leading to a large hexagonal building this is the main
main Lodge for the calm comfy campground on either side of this cobblestone pathway or flower beds
just filled with these beautiful flowers of all different shape and shade and on either side of
you are just tons of bushes and trees and greenery it would be decently thick to have to walk through
but you can kind of see through on either side these beautiful little cozy cottages that are
lined out evenly across the island on the shore of this circular island standing there kind of
looking around you notice that kind of behind you off to the side a little bit there's a man
short stout man in his later years older guy he's got a thick white beard he's wearing a dark
navy beanie and a wool plaid shirt under olive corduroy overalls and he is just staring out at
the water Martin takes a deep breath and does it smell does it smell good it smells strange it's
it's it's not a smell that you've smelled before but with the Sun shining down from directly above
on you and this beautiful scenery it makes the smell seem nice is there at least also a smell
of nature around oh yeah absolutely okay he's he takes a deep breath and he's he inhales and he's
not dissatisfied and he notes the guy behind him he also he doesn't take the time to stop and smell
the flowers but he does make an interested note of them but he just walks straight on to the to
the main cabin absolutely and when you get up there there is a sign in front of the building
that says welcome to calm comfy campground and when you walk the main building that you're
walking into is similarly bestroon with all these delightful flowers of many shades and shapes and
when you walk in the inside is similarly rustic and elegant there's a massive wooden chandelier
hanging over the foyer and you see that there is a couple standing right in front of you a young
couple the woman in a sundress and the man in a white seersucker suit and they are holding each
other and an embrace I lower my baseball cap down I just yeah I kind of shrink into my hoodie make
sure my sunglasses aren't real well and I walk by them and I'm trying to find a check-in or something
looking for a check-in immediately to your right you notice that there's a desk with a bell and a
sign that says please boop for assistance also on top of the desk is a vase with a single red rose
in it Martin is pretty pleased because his expedience has brought him a moment where he
can stop and smell this rose he says to himself the shark who stops moving dies but if he gets to
where he's going he might get to smell some blood he boops the bell and and waits
Joe hey Roger here's the ding of the bell over at the desk pulling away from the embrace that
you're in with Angela you both turn and see a man of normal heights slight build he's wearing
a gray college hoodie he has a baseball cap on pulled down low big sunglasses jeans and sneakers
it should be noted that he does not look at you oh really you're just banging on the desk looking
at the desk I just pooped the bell once oh oh hey we got a we got another fellow camper well hello
there I'm uh I'm Roger this is my wife I'm Angela hey nice to meet you he puts his hands in his
pockets and nods nods hi hey hey hey there do you work here no I I booped that bill myself and
nobody showed up yeah we're waiting for the bell boy cuz it's a bell is there a room and like in
the back or anything behind the desk like a door a bell boy might appear behind there's a door
behind the desk where a bell boy might appear okay I go up to it and try to open it oh yeah
it's unlocked okay I head back wherever that is okay yeah you see that there is a young man in
cowboy boots blue jeans a plaid pearl snap button-down bolo tie and a white cowboy hat
and he's sitting on a recliner with his feet up watching a big-screen TV it's college football
and CSU is playing on the wall behind the TV there's a bunch of like banners and logos and
maybe a seat from the stadium like a signed football and a big jersey I look down at my
sweater my college sweater and I see that it says CSU and I walk over to him like hey it's
hi fellow fellow alumni Oh CSU hey how's it going go go team yeah I'm so sorry I didn't hear the
bell what can I do for you sir I would like to check in so I think what this young couple behind
me here oh yeah so sorry absolutely and he grabs the remote and he mutes the TV and he pops up I
grab him by the shoulder and I I slip him ten bucks mm-hmm which is like better than ten bucks
26 years ago it is obviously I need you to take care of me first oh yeah no absolutely you came
and found me so ah yeah you get you get the prize and then you guys walk back out and he gets to the
desk and he gets behind it and hops on into this big folder that he has I like before you can walk
up even though you got there first and rang the bell he positions himself right in front of the
hop and like leans on the desk I pull in Angela a little tighter to me you know what they say
about the greasy wheel fine I I don't need to check in this week and then she jumps on top of
you yes sir checking in Mart Mart Brett Bradley Cooper oh yes Bradley Cooper mr. just not a
famous name 26 years ago no it's absolutely not mr. Cooper and you will be in cottage five and
he grabs a key off the back wall and he hands it to you and it's got one of those big like rubber
key what are those called key chains yeah I know what you mean like one of the big key chain
paddles rubber things hanging off an old hotel key yeah and it's got a key on the other side
and he's like so if it's a clock you came from six o'clock and you'll be at five o'clock thank you
what was your name my name is Leon it's nice to meet you thank you Leon so if you will just what
was that it's a fairly common name if you want to leave your luggage here I will take it to your
cottage for you please make your way into the meeting room for orientation and he points to
a door that is on his right so straightforward if you would have walked it he you know I nod
and and walk into the orientation room fantastic get the fuck out of here all right and you two
must be the Fairfields I extend a hand a firm hand out oh he grabs it and shakes right away Roger
Roger Fairfield Roger nice to meet you Angie here and Angela Angela Fairfield nice to meet you both
you will be in cottage number nine so like I said if it's a clock you came from six you'll go to
nine and if you want to leave your bags here I'll take them over to the cottage for you please make
your way into the meeting room for orientation that's the the same room that that Brett Bradley
in front of us right that yes the same door as mr. Cooper I'll I'll just I'll follow his lead
gives you a nice smile and then comes around the desk to take your bags as you guys walk into the
meeting room hey do you that looks like a load there I could I could run those over to the cabin
and then come back please sir it is far more important for you to get to the meeting room
for orientation I understand if you think you got it I absolutely do thank you sir as you guys walk
in Angela's just like see you're just like you're already just so open I just want you to be like
that with yourself you want you want me to be more of me to you to do me more do yourself as
much as possible I will I'll make it if that's your first the nugget you've been able to crack
here already I you know that's something I watch Walter Grimes is standing there 16 years old
looking down at his shoes very still he's wearing a long-sleeve Metallica t-shirt nothing else
matters is printed on it he stands at six feet tall is about a hundred seventy pounds so thin
but buzzed hair but very thick black hair he's got a strong jawline chiseled almost think the
Schwarzenegger type I know line he has eyes that look like a husky Oh piercing Anderson
why but those eyes are staring down at the floor standing right behind Walter is Alan who is a
lean man in his early 60s with buddy Holly glasses and a charcoal suit so we must have matching
glasses yeah I didn't know my brother was here yeah father and he he keeps like tapping his
fingers against his hand and he is looking at everyone nervously big boy sip it up sip it like
a big boy Luke I enjoy this beer that is going to pass through my system okay so Walter Grimes you
are standing at if the island is a clock you're at six o'clock I'm gonna say this many many times
yes yeah there's a cobblestone walkway leading up to a large hexagonal building that is the main
building and you see a sign on it in the distance you can't quite make it out yet all around you are
trees and lush bushes and on either side of the cobblestone walkway there are flower beds filled
with flowers these gorgeous flowers of every shape and shade and Alan looks at you Walter
what are we here to do I'm here to see if I'm a real boy no not just that you know that you are
a real boy I am a real boy yes are a real boy I am a real boy you've already proven that to yourself
and are many many tests this is to prove it to other people thank you for doing this for me you
are my greatest accomplishment thank you I am so deeply proud of you I am proud of you too father
I love you thank you and you guys walk up this cobblestone path and you see a sign that says
welcome to calm comfy campground I love alliteration I do too and I that's just
something that came about through nurture Walter walks up to the sign and just kind of runs his
fingers in the grooves of the letters and looks at his father this feels nice thank you all right
let's go check in and he takes your both of your suitcases in his hands and he's walking up the
steps and he opens up the door into a very both like rustic and elegant foyer there's a large
wood for you for yet I wish that I could burp father one day one day we'll go up and as you
stand in this fire he looks around and he's like so we will teach you how to do it and there's a
large wooden chandelier right above you and to your right there's a desk are we talking lights
or candles lights everything in here is super rustic and like old-looking but modern also very
modern and looks like it was quite a penny pretty pretty pretty pretty penny was spent no a penny
pretty was yes yes and there's a desk with a little bell on it and next to the bell there's
a sign that says please boop for assistance and there's a vase with a red rose in it and
to your left there is a table with a coffee pot and a water cooler and in between there's a bowl
of fruit Walter looks at his dad and approaches the desk looking into his dad's eyes places his
hand over the bell and looks for some sort of acknowledgement Alan raises his eyebrows ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding and Alan smiles when you first ring the bell but
as you continue to ring the bell his smile starts to fade and he's like what Walter Walter yes that's
probably good ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
Walter yes father I think we're good on the bell if they didn't hear that then I don't think they're
close enough to hear it oh that's okay what should I do now I think we just wait and he
grabs a cup and starts pouring himself some coffee I stand at the desk I put my head down
like this and I like what audio medium I put my head down chin on chest standing there completely
still and ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
who's up next Charles Digby is also in his own kind of corner of the room so he can keep an
eye on everybody kind of observe the situation Charles Digby is like six feet tall little above
average average weight brown kind of like a little shaggy a little unkempt hair but still
kind of combed over just nice enough to not attract any attention to himself brown eyes
kind of scruffy facial hair he likes to keep it average as a like a button-up shirt kind of little
messy undid not tucked in jeans some nice leather shoes and yeah he's just kind of a what would you
call surveying the room kind of trying to get a feel for everybody there love it
hey Justin hi what's up man nothing how about you I am very very excited for our session tonight and
I'm also very very excited to have you on the show with an actual with an actual character
you gotta have an actual character otherwise it not less fun so I'll definitely remember your last
name Digby this time yeah can you remember the first name nope and so Charles Digby is standing
at six o'clock on this island if the island was a clock face you were at six o'clock and leading
in front of you is a cobblestone pathway up to a large hexagonal building that is both rustic and
modern it's made mostly wood but there's big glass windows all over it and on either side of the
cobblestone leading up to this building are these large flower beds filled with these gorgeous
flowers that take over most of this island however on either side of the fire beds you see a bunch of
trees and bushes and a very active earth bio things fauna yeah fauna and flora hell yeah there's
so much flora no flauna you can see there's no desert there's no custardy desert there's not
unfortunately maybe inside maybe inside so as you're walking up you see in the distance through
these trees there's these cottages laid out at one o'clock three o'clock five o'clock seven
o'clock nine o'clock and eleven o'clock on this island and through all this dense tree line and
stuff you can still see these cottages they're tucked away and you notice with your keen
investigative eyes so this is an automatic success because your alertness and your search I'm
guessing are super fucking high yes confirmation and so on top of cottage three which is immediately
to your right as you're walking up to this large building you see down this long cobblestone
pathway this cottage and on top of the roof of that cottage just far in the distance but with
your eagle eyes you see a young girl with pigtails on top and she's messing with some wiring hmm can
I get a little closer take a look at that yeah sure my investigative nature would be like I
gotta see what's going on yeah you'll have to get off the trail the path and go through some of the
trees unless you want to go into this building and then around the side yeah let's do that yeah
as you're walking through the brush you notice that she pulls out binoculars oh I'm familiar
with these items and they are pointed directly at you you're not so used to being on this side
of binoculars yeah I think I would uh awkwardly wave to like acknowledge like hi can I can see
you seeing me just like like a kind of an awkward like raise of the hand immediately she dips back
behind this like roof area and is out of sight okay I think I think I'd maybe still keep walking
towards that way or would this be weird what I would I know not to you wouldn't know anything
okay yeah I'll just I will investigate that's what that's what I do baby yeah as you're walking
closer and closer you see this little girl take off running from behind cottage three and she's
running along the shoreline of the lake toward cottage number one I will kind of like hurriedly
follow hey hey what are you doing like trying to get her attention see if she responds at all she
does not turn back and she continues to run toward the cottage and you see she goes around the back
of the cottage and disappears I'm gonna with a hurried a little pep in my step hurry towards
it just to be like what's what's going on here yeah so moving through all these trees and branches
and brambles you make your way into a small clearing where this cottage is and it's really
cute and there's a nice little front door and a window in front and windows on the sides and you
see some movement through one of the side windows and you think it's basically the rough outline of
a small person can I look through the windows without it being like creepy that is entirely
up to the people who watch you creep them yeah I'm gonna try and do a little like like how I would
do like some kind of like stealthy search maneuvers creep up to the window and be able to
like peek roll alert actually first roll stealth sorry I haven't rolled with a character and so
so very long yeah this is is this the first one and the one shot for the patreon oh yeah but yeah
this is the first like this character isn't just hastily Justin party time party time for Justin
with pretending people couldn't remember the name of the show I pass 65 on a 70 okay so looking
through this window you see that there is this young girl with pigtails and she is wearing
overalls with a little striped shirt underneath overalls and she is sitting at the kitchen counter
and eating a sandwich and then walking in from the other room is an average build man he looks
to be in his late 30s but his eyes have aged and his hair his grade like someone who is in the war
or went through some sort of traumatic experience he's wearing a white dress shirt gray slacks and
black shoes and he walks over pours a glass of milk and slides it over to the girl who then
drinks it okay I feel like a fucking creep I feel like a creep number one but I feel like I would
like try to dip out at this point because it looks like that's probably her dad or something yeah I
think at this point I'd be like oh I shouldn't be doing this like oh stealth it again nope it'll
count so you are enrolled a successful stealth we get up to that spot so you know exactly how
to get out of this spot yeah I will duck out to be like okay time to stop being a creep so now
the question you're at one o'clock do you want to enter the main building from that side of the
island or do you want to go all the way back around is there a reason we were going to the
there was just that was where you were and there was a sign on that side of the building that said
welcome to calm comfy campground and you see no such sign from this side okay yeah I'll go to the
main building okay so you walk back through all this brush and all these trees and bushes and I
need you to roll an alertness check for me crit success 22 on a 70 crit success yeah that's
fucking awesome so my first ever as you're walking your foot your toe cap hits a wire
and it lifts up off the ground as you step and immediately your eyes follow this wire to a tree
and then looking about 12 feet up the tree you see the small lens of a camera that's poking out
from a knot in this tree what the fuck can I investigate it yeah what do you want to do how
high up did you say it was 12 feet I'm gonna try and like clamber up it a little bit yeah
roll survival or athletics to climb up this tree because sometimes climbing a tree is for your
survival I'll do athletics because I ain't got no survival I'm from the city man what's your
athletics 50 all right roll it up hard fail okay so trying to get up this tree you realize that
there aren't any branches low enough and there's no like grips on this tree that are in the direct
area to begin a climb so you can't even get off the ground I think I'll just leave it alone for
now because I'm I would assume it's for some kind of security or something and I don't want to like
knock it out with a rock or anything so I would I'm just gonna be like okay that's weird maybe
I'll come back here later sounds good yeah so when you walk back around to the front of this
large building you see that sign and there are two double doors on a porch a couple steps up to
a porch and then the double doors going in I go ahead and enter upon entrance you see this
beautiful rustic and elegant lobby with a large wooden chandelier hanging above you to your right
there is a young boy and to your left there is an old man and I'll bring Luke into the building
which one do you think he is the young boy yeah God for the voices sake I hope it's a young boy
not as creepy old man voice is it anything like people puby so at that exact moment the recording
cut out and we ran out of space on that hard drive perfectly timed because Luke and Justin
went on with that voice for a while well I got just enough time to really get into it and now
I'm changing my voice Jesus so Charles Digby you walk into this foyer look up see everything that
you saw you see this kid on your right who is just incessantly ringing a bell that is on the
desk yeah this older man is like Walter and then they both turn back and look at you keep
in mind I'm a 16 year old I'm not I'm not a child but I am a I'm a child have you seen a
16 year old recently like nine years yeah if you're 16 and listening to this tell your parents so
that they can take your phone away tell your parents so that they can get on the patreon
yeah still your parents money there it is I can't listen to this until you give me $100
a month anyway the older man walks up to you and it's like hello there sir my name is Alan
I'm Charles Digby Charles Digby nice to meet you nice to meet you Alan and is this your that's my
boy hello nice to meet you and I'd like outreach the hand kind of awkwardly I don't know how to
treat teenagers I look at his hand I'm like thank you I put the hand back in the pocket
really awkwardly yeah we've been now we've been trying to summon I reach my hand out now as well
I reach my hand back out firmly try to grasp your head I like brush your hand a little bit and then
immediately withdraw it roll humid okay wait really yeah it's the two tens the one we usually
roll I'm a special guest on this show not anymore oh boy I quit oh I failed okay pretty badly too
can I sit by a different person eventually we're still waiting on the bell boy there
it's been some time but he's not there yes I Walter that's probably good on the bell yes
Alan walks over to the desk hello hello I'm gonna also walk up to the desk and kind of like looking
around see if anyone's about yeah roll search for me oh no that's bad I failed you here wait
that's a 96 that's fine no we decided that it's the opposite of 69 critical fail the worst crit
fail you can ask what's happening help no you're good so you are just staring at this Bell and you
are not paying attention to your mind is just racing for all sorts of different things you're
going back into some of your memories and not really paying attention then you snap out of it
and you realize that oh shit I was I was gonna try to check in but at that moment the back door
right behind the desk opens and a young man wearing cowboy boots blue jeans a plaid pearlsnap button
down bolo tie and a white cowboy hat comes out of that door behind the desk and you can hear a
college football game either on a TV or on the radio in the room he came out of he's like oh hey
there welcome to calm comfy campground let's see we've got Charles Digby I presume mm-hmm and you
guys must be the Grimes is that right yes okay absolutely so see Charles I've got number seven
for you and he hands you a key with a big rubber keychain on it this is calm comfy campground and
it's got a big number seven on it and then he looks at Walter and Alan and he's like and you
two are in cottage number three I take it and I rub my finger over the number six right five
five three three it's like a backwards five I take it and I rub my finger over the number
five three just fuck you said too many numbers number three I take it and I rub my finger over
the number three do you take it sir yes take the key I taken I'm rubbing over the number three and
then I stop and I give it to my father and I will take your things to each of your cottages if you
would all please make your way into the meeting room right there for orientation and he points at
the door just over to the side I immediately start heading that way as does Alan I do too
I'm following kind of behind a little bit though and then we go into this main building this main
large hexagonal building and inside we find a room that is circular the wall never ceasing and
never creasing at any point even where the wall meets the ceiling and the floor the angles are
rounded off there are six chairs and a half circle facing a single chair in front of them
each chair has a bottle of water next to it and standing around this room or sitting in these
chairs are the four of you along with two others and the door opens and a man of a man of average
build walks into the room he looks to be in his late 30s but his eyes have aged and his hair is
grayed like someone who is in the war or has gone through some sort of traumatic experience he's
wearing a white dress shirt he's someone shit in the war he look yeah just anyone just like anyone
about any war he might have fucked with the war there's a chance that he would have been in I saw
some shit in the war are you in the war I'm still fighting it bro he's wearing a white dress shirt
gray slacks and black shoes hello everyone my name is James and I am the executive director here at
you