Hello, my babies, and hello to my babies' babies.
Heck, even hello to those babies' babies.
Let's just get wild, y'all.
It's your local radio DJ
that you actually wanna listen to, Wolf the Dog.
This week, I have a message here from my producer.
It says, Zach and Taylor are on vacation.
He's real torn up about it,
but there just wasn't enough free time this week
to release an episode that is up to snuff.
For this, he feels shame, regret,
and just a tinge of arousal.
He wants each and every one of you
to know how special you are,
but quality time with the incomparable,
and formidable love of his life is paramount.
Thank you deeply for understanding.
You know, back in the day, old Wolfie Boy
used to have a little old Wolfie partner
that he would have missed the show for.
I still dream of her sometimes,
wondering what she's up to back in contention.
How many dumpsters has she dove in without me?
What if they're with some other new dog that ain't wolf?
So go on, Zach, whoever the hell that is.
Enjoy your life.
Eat all the trash you can, baby.
Next week is going to be a wild ride, y'all,
but for now, hold on tight
and keep your arms and legs inside the vehicle.
Playing us in and immediately out
is Kudzu with No Backbone.
["How Am I the Only One Trying to Pull Over?" by Kudzu playing in the background.]
How am I the only one trying to pull over?
How can you have enough drowning out all the noise?
There's nobody home, no one home, no one home.
Fight to fight, street me down, takes me back to where you're from.
When you don't stop a dying love, don't push on to only one.
There's nobody home, no one home, no one home, no one home.
["How Am I the Only One Trying to Pull Over?" by Kudzu playing in the background.]
Tell me it hurts.