What is boiling, my dumplings?
It's your chef de cuisine, Wolf the dog.
And I am pinching dough like a mad dog
so I can provide sustenance to all my glorious fans.
Hope y'all like that boiled dough with some mayonnaise inside.
And I am cooking it up live from 694.2 PTBP,
the only radio station to win a Michelin star by force.
This episode's Howlin' with Wolf is from at Sis Fordman
from Maryland, who tweeted about the show
and tagged that pretending pod,
the sixth best thing you can do with your fingers.
They write, the network has been compromised,
root access granted.
The reality we know or knew is DDoSed
and held by dark matter.
All bow, the new pseudo is here.
This exploit is sticking around.
Patch Tuesday, kernel panic.
Your disk is spinning fast and you can't dump the RAM.
Unplug yourself and pray.
Silas Cole is here to fuck up your day.
Sis admin, what the fuck did you just make me read?
If this is about computers again,
I'm going to be so fucking pissed off.
Remember, if you want to write up something
for your cream filled doughy wolf to how,
tag at pretending pod on the internet
or write a five star review on Apple podcasts, please.
If you're one of the blessed angels or demons
who make a post, forget the om,
I just want to say T Hanks, thanks.
I don't want to be cast away in a green mile of thick woods
solely-ing the forest with my gump.
I want to be big.
Now onto the next thing I do.
It's time for the news of the world.
Last time, Don D. Pettymore was confronted
with the fact that his nephew is a non-human being
that currently resides inside its own daddy,
Don's brother.
This was after John, as always, forgot
that not everyone already understands his current condition.
Jack explained, he was searching
for the door out of this place.
Keith promised Leo they'd come back for him
to take him away from this existence.
Don admitted he came to this plane through his Nike bag,
the same one he used as Agent Victor
to dispose of an unnatural rotary phone
that supposedly healed anyone of anything.
John gained a new understanding of his abilities
in this setting, and he dissipated an opening
into the wall of this junk room
where Keith claimed a rope bridge connected
and led to a second stilted bunker.
The group decided to call the number of the rotary phone,
and they heard a ring from across the oily,
colorful bridge inside this duplicate fort.
The entire party witnessed a dreadful sight
as Keith, Don, and Jack all walked out
onto the Bridge of Spies.
Boom, another Tom Hanks reference at the buzzer.
Now listen here.
No, closer, closer.
Get incredibly close so this one is extremely loud.
This track is in a league of its own.
It's Dragon in Three with What Kind of World Are You Livin' In?
["What Kind of World Are You Livin' In?" by Dragon in Three plays in the background.]
Bad girls on top of the water
Mary and Caroline, I'm on the borderline
Leaving my mind at your altar
Crossing the double line, doing it every time
Tell me what kind of world are you livin' in?
What kind of world are you livin' in?
Hello, everybody out there pretending to be listening.
We're pretending to be people,
and you are getting ready for another crazy episode.
My name is Zach, and I am your handler,
not your best friend, not your dad,
not your Dungeon Master, just giving you the handler,
handler, hand, handy, giving you, handle, hand,
I'm the hand, I'm here with my second, third, fourth,
and 17th best friends, and how are you guys doing?
Am I 17?
If you have to ask.
I'm doing okay, how are you doing, Zach?
Yeah, I'm doing pretty good.
I'm really sad.
Oh, no.
I was trying to cover it up
by really being over-hyped in the intro, but...
Bud, what's got you down?
My butt turned green.
Oh!
Your butt turned green?
You hate to hear it.
Yeah, the whole thing.
Is it mad?
It's jealous.
My ass is green with envy.
Who's it jealous of, or what is it jealous of?
Apples.
How many apples could you fit in there?
Inside or just within the cheeks?
Because I think just within the cheeks I could get two,
but I don't think any are going in my actual asshole.
Oh, standing up for sure, I mean.
Yeah, wow.
I don't think I could get any
unless I could use the stem,
and the stem was nice and long.
Like an apple tree branch filled with mini apples.
You could just drag them along like a dog.
Can I bite the apple into a shape
that might be more fitting?
As long as you put the whole thing in you,
you can slice it up.
Okay.
Do I get to eat it after-
Any part you slice off does have to go up there.
Yeah, the whole thing has to.
You guys know when you're eating an apple
and you bite down where the skin meets the flesh,
like the inside, and the skin just goes right up
in between your teeth?
That's awful.
No.
Yeah, try not to think about that
with your butt instead of your mouth, huh?
But your butt doesn't have teeth, though.
I'm doing this new thing where I say, huh?
I like that new thing you're doing, Zach.
Huh?
Your butt doesn't have teeth.
This is a good introduction to the podcast.
Again, right up on that microphone.
Thomas, I can't hear your sadness
if you don't get up on that.
I'm sad about the way you chose to start the podcast.
Do you have a better, do you have an idea?
Yeah, it could just be our normal bullshit,
but maybe you don't talk about shoving apples up your ass.
I don't know.
I didn't start that.
Yeah, it all happened so quick,
no one knows who started it.
Isn't talking about shoving apples up our assholes
exactly what our normal intros are like?
We've probably already done this one.
Okay, what do you want to talk about
putting up our buttholes?
Well, I don't know if you guys have heard
about the fuck barrel, but.
Save it for the den of sin, baby, save it.
Patreon people know what the fuck barrel is all about.
Yeah, they do.
Are they gonna have early access to buy it
before the general public?
They're gonna have a lot of access.
Oh, hell yeah.
Ah, the bridge, I jump off the bridge.
Back to safety.
Ah, the bridge.
Take it to the bridge.
Like the last episode ended on a bit of a cliffhanger.
And so first I need stealth roles.
Yes, slight pun intended, I suppose.
I need stealth roles from Clark Bishop
and John Lee Kevinmore because they were trying
to avoid being seen by a pair of children,
the Littles, Aiden and Alice,
who they had one interaction with previously.
Yeah, we got them sucked up into this world through a vacuum.
Am I close enough to hear him say this?
No, this is his own internal narration
as he has reminded himself.
Yes, he's reminded himself as he expertly avoids
identification by these children with a 39 on a 50.
Oh, well done.
Unfortunately, Clark is like peeking his head out
and like, what, what are we trying to avoid being seen by?
Cause he rolled a 65 on a 30.
Hey, look, it's those kids.
Hey, look over there and he's pointing.
Aiden and Alice Little are looking back up at Clark Bishop,
who's hanging out, hanging out Beatles style
of this doorway.
And they both give you the,
who's the meet the Fokker's dad?
Robert De Niro.
Yeah, yeah, that's what I know him from best.
He's giving you the best, like Robert De Niro,
pointing two fingers at their eyes,
these little twin children eyes,
and then pointing those same two fingers
right up at Clark Bishop.
John Lee Pettymore still has Clark's compact
and he's like watching that over his shoulder.
And that, well, that's exactly, he just gives a big woo.
How old are the kids?
Oh, they're children.
Okay, that's as specific as you got.
Yeah, I don't think I ever said maybe like
anywhere between 10 and 12, so 11.
Sigh.
Damn, that's getting into like capable rascal territory.
I was picturing way more, like these are,
these might be like pretty crafty little bastards.
And I was kind of picturing like much younger children
that we could just kind of, you know,
push off the bridge or something, but.
Ah, 11's normal.
I'm really glad, I'm really glad they didn't see me.
They are standing on a boat.
Did you say they're both little?
That's funny, because their last name is Little.
So the boat that is made of this inky darkness
that's super colorful has been written on
with the shimmering silver sea seemingly.
There are shiny numbers all over the whole of the boat
and it is the numbers that spell overseer.
And the figurehead of the vessel is a young man
with curly black hair who Don seemingly recognized.
You could see it in his eyes.
And I mean, this dude is being melted continuously
about from the waist down as he's halfway in the water
and his mouth has been steeled shut as well.
And he's just like.
He's just crying and screaming out in endless pain.
And Julie Maxwell was wearing a hospital gown.
Couldn't help but notice when I said
that she had a massive gash running down her forehead,
Thomas was cackling a little bit.
Before you said running down her forehead,
there was a pretty big pause when you just said
she has a massive gash and it made me laugh.
Running down her forehead in between her eyes.
Her nose is missing and she smiles with no teeth
or lips on one full side of her face.
You think doo-doo her face being smashed.
Hey, Zach, you just said doo-doo.
Doo-doo her face smash.
I don't have to pile on that particular theme,
but what's this about her doo-doo gash?
Jesus Christ.
She is missing like half of her face
and that side that is missing the teeth and lips has an eye.
There's an eyeball there.
That part isn't missing,
but across her face on the other orbital socket,
if you're at home, don't Google orbital socket
or orbital socket oozing.
But this one is oozing with this dark substance
is pouring out.
Okay, so her head snaps forward
and a metal sphere climbs out
like a massive spidery tendrilly metal thing
just like pulls itself up out of the body of Julie Maxwell
and continues to hold that body
at the end of one of its tendrils
as one of the other ones lashes out
and rips at the bridge that Keith Bishop.
Nope.
You gave it away.
You gave away the big secret
we've been keeping this whole time.
We were all brothers, carnival brothers.
I'm my own grandpa.
In this world, all it takes to get married
is to share a microwaved meal on the same recliner.
So you guys are technically married.
Okay, so this thing just like it plants
some of its legs down into the boat
and then one of them rips out at this rope bridge
that's made out of this same dark and colorful material
and Keith beans and Jack Russell
and who is the third person who is out on that bridge?
Oh, that's right.
It's Don D fucking Pettymore.
The three of you are out on this bridge.
What are you doing as the metal tendril rips down
in between the three of you
and this stilted room that Clark Bishop
and John Lee Kevin Moore are inside?
How far away are we?
Okay, so the bridge is 10 yards
and you're about five yards into it.
You're like exactly halfway.
Also, give me your dexterity.
Mine is 55.
Same.
I got a 60.
60 as well.
Okay, so we'll do the order is Keith, Clark, Don, John.
Don John.
Great movie.
Oh yeah, you love film?
Yeah, I guess you could say I'm a cinema enthusiast.
Don John is probably my favorite.
Just has a lot to say.
Not a lot of people get it.
Not a lot of people get it,
but it actually has a lot of really insightful things to say
kind of turns the whole gender thing on its head.
It's real subtle.
And Joseph Gordon-Levitt was the white man to do that.
Yeah, that was actually Joseph Gordon-Levitt
the whole time, which is crazy.
Oh wait, he was Don John?
Yes, the whole time.
Oh, cool.
See, like I said, you always find out new things
about that movie.
So if you consider yourself a film buff,
check out Don John.
All the stunts in the movie, he did for the most part.
That's crazy.
He actually cleaned an apartment as a man?
Yeah.
He did not have a stunt double.
Wow.
Keith, you are in the middle of this rope ridge.
Five yards to your left is the second large stilted room
that you have not been to.
There's a hatch that is just right there, five yards away.
And five yards on your right, on the other side,
you see this John made hole
and you see John kind of hiding.
His back is turned.
He's looking through a compact
as Clark is hanging his head out
and kind of waving at some children who are on this boat.
What do you do?
Above 50, I jumped to the hatch.
Below 50, I jumped back to the John made hole.
87, I jumped to the hatch.
Okay, make a dexterity.
10 on a 60.
Well done, well done.
Okay, fantastic.
So you are running, running, running
as this bridge is falling out beneath you
and you are going to be able to make a leap
without falling to your likely demise.
Good thing you passed that rule.
Oh yeah, good thing.
Clark, what are you doing?
So the bridge is collapsing
from the point that I'm standing, right?
Correct.
Like the bridge part that is nearest you is going to fall.
You're not sure whether or not it will go into the water
but if I said earlier that the bridge is 10 yards long
and from one of the stilted hatch doors of the room
down to the shining, shimmering, shiver sea,
I think I said that was maybe 10 yards, 15 yards,
but it definitely wasn't less than 10 yards.
And so if you're like holding onto the rope bridge
then you'll probably be safe from falling into the not ocean.
But I'm not on the bridge itself though, right?
I'm still in this.
Certainly not.
No, I was just trying to give you an idea
of like what it looks like as it's happening.
So I don't, yeah.
I mean, I don't think I have an action here.
I want to stay on this side of the place
because I'm thinking about the boat
that is still docked on our side.
He's not going to like run out there.
I guess, oh, we're in a room filled with junk, right?
Yes.
I'll see if anything catches my eye
that could be helpful in this situation.
Maybe like bed sheets or something.
I don't know.
100%.
I rolled a 50 on a search and that's not good.
I've got a 20 in search.
Okay, so as you're looking through, you find pillowcases.
It's like bedsheets, but worse.
It's worse than what you were looking for.
These'll work.
Don D. Pettymore, you're up.
Don D. Pettymore is going to like scramble
because the one we were going to
is where the telephone was ringing, correct?
That is correct.
And that is where Keith is like sprinting towards
very like agilely running across this bridge
that is currently falling.
Yeah, I will also like scramble that way.
Okay, roll dexterity or athletics.
Oh, my athletic, nope.
Dexterity it is.
Oh my God.
I got a 54 out of 55.
Oh, oh shit.
Okay, fantastic.
So you are going to be able to make the jump as well.
At the beginning of your next turn,
you're going to be able to make that jump.
John, you see Clark digging through
and finding pillowcases.
What are you doing?
How close is the boat to us?
And specifically the John Mayhole?
Picture it like a triangle.
You are 10 yards away from the hatch that is across
and then you are 10 yards away from the boat
that is an equilateral triangle.
I see that everybody else who's out there on the bridge
is currently running to the other bunker, correct?
Yeah, Jack Russell hasn't gone yet.
So he hasn't moved
because that's how games work in real life too.
But the other two are certainly running away from you.
John, just I want to just start like closing
the John Mayhole.
Rad, oh shit.
Okay, roll unnatural.
39 on a?
More than that.
One of these days you're going to fail that roll.
Oh, there I see it, 67.
Describe it.
He looks like he's frantically like trying to mop up a mess
with his hands.
He doesn't make like a good or like,
it doesn't look like a manmade solid wall
like it might have before.
You can actually see like his fingerprints and stuff
as he just like quickly goo-clayed it back into solid.
That's super cool, I can picture it.
And he leaves a tiny little peephole
so they can see what's going on.
Incredible, incredible.
Okay, so as you're looking through this tiny little peephole
you're probably the only one who sees Jack Russell.
I'm going to do the same roll that Luke did,
above 50 goes towards them,
under 50 tries to go back where he came from,
which is now closed.
I rolled a 94.
And so he's going to take off running
to follow Keith and Dawn, and he rolls a 10.
So Jack Russell is going to run along.
So the three of you, picture it like,
I'm picturing a Wes Anderson framing of this scene
because it's very flat, you know.
You've got this endless background behind you,
but then you have two identical stilted rooms
on either side of the frame,
10 yards above this silver sea
that just goes on endlessly into the background.
And then there's a bridge hanging in the middle.
Jack, Dawn, and Keith are sprinting to the right
as the bridge collapses from the left.
And as they run, the three of them kind of jump out.
And I'm picturing kind of a railing
going around the outside on this one maybe.
And so Keith is able to make the leap
and hopefully grab on.
So Keith, go ahead and roll as you see behind you,
this giant ball after it crashes down.
John, you can see this too
through your thimble sized hole.
Little smaller.
Oh, I got tiny thimbles, dude.
And so.
I just don't want your spider thing
poking one of its legs through it.
I'm trying to head off that eventuality.
You're not gonna tell me how big my hole was.
How many apples can fit through it.
And so you.
Can you chop them up?
We can talk about that.
I'm pretending to be people after dark.
These metal tendrils move into the shimmering sea.
They're planting themselves into this silvery ocean
and you hear a noise.
And you see these tendrils are all the same texture.
It's this shiny, shiny metal.
It's like the same texture,
but a solid of the ocean that is out there.
And you hear this like.
And you think that it is coming from the ball.
It is like reverberating this noise
through the world that you're in.
Does it sound like a person going re re re re re re re re
or is it actually like metallic sounds?
It is metallic sounding.
However, it does sound like the vocalizations of an entity.
Can you roll intelligence for me?
Can I roll on that?
Yeah.
Since I'm looking out the window.
I failed a 60 on a 55.
I passed a 54 on a 60 or 75.
John, as you're actually looking at this thing,
you're seeing it's like kind of stilted movements
of the ball as this noise is coming out of it seemingly.
Not only do you realize that even in ball form,
you would still be able to speak and vocalize
just like this thing is.
And it might sound like a little metallic,
but it would be your voice.
And this thing's voice sounds animalistic
and taking that idea one step further,
you think that this ball might've been inside an animal
for the past, who knows how long.
It's the raccoon.
And that's why it speaks like this.
Holy shit.
It's a feral ball.
Yeah, it's a rabid ball.
That's so dope.
Yeah, so John like looks back at Clark
who's frantically gathering pillowcases, I guess.
And he's like, quick update, door's closed.
We got a peephole.
That ball is some kind of feral ball.
So we probably don't need these pillowcases then.
I don't really know where I was going with that anyway.
And he drops it.
I mean, it can't hurt.
Oh, okay.
Gather some back up.
Find a Sharpie in here.
You could draw a little face on it.
And then that could be your mask from those kids.
You know, you give it like glasses and grumpy eyebrows
and a big beard, and then it won't look like Clark.
They're kids.
They wouldn't know.
Exactly.
They're stupid idiots.
Yeah, they're just a couple morons, you know?
So.
Keith, roll athletics or dexterity
in order to reach out and grab.
93.
Ooh.
On what though?
A 60.
Oh.
On a hundred.
Good thing I have a hundred decks.
You know how jacked Keith is.
You know, yeah, you know how Keith
was always darting off to the Olympics.
Every four years, he was really busy.
I know this isn't the rules,
but can I do a saving throw?
Fuck yeah.
Uh, no.
So you fall.
He could spend luck.
Oh.
I don't.
Ooh, well, how much luck do I have?
That would be a lot of luck, huh?
Is it?
It's not luck.
Luck doesn't start over with the new sheet, does it?
Ha!
Okay, you begin falling.
Do you want to describe it?
Yeah, I am running along the bridge
and then obviously start to lose footing.
And I like jump and I smack my arms
on where like the railing is.
This room is hot.
This area is pretty hot, right?
Cause of the melted ocean.
We've not talked about the temperature.
Well, how would you describe the temperature in this room?
It is exactly room temperature.
Oh, well I'm just sweaty cause I'm nervous
and my hands hit the bars.
I grab on just for a second,
like try to pull myself up and then slip off
and start falling.
So John looking through the peephole
relays that back to Clark.
He's like, Clark, you know how every time you go
to shake Vigna's hands, they're a little bit sweaty?
Right, yeah, of course.
Well, that just got the best of him.
We might have to open this hole back up.
He slipped off the bridge there.
Is he in the molten?
Is he in the sea?
Is he gone?
He's slowly falling towards it as you guys are talking.
It seems like he's almost moving in slow motion.
We're just waiting for an action to be taken.
I'm never gonna like tell you to not talk,
you know, in character.
It's like, it's always what I want.
So I'm never gonna cut you off.
Just imagine that it's happening really fast
and everything else action wise, very slow.
So John, what's your theory about what's going on here?
Exactly.
I'm glad you asked that actually.
I've got no fucking clue, man.
I was gonna ask.
I will cut you off.
Clark Bishop, it's your turn.
What do you do?
I mean, I got nothing.
I mean, can I keep searching for a thing
that's 10 yards long?
I don't know how to save a guy
that's falling 10 yards away from me.
Hey, Joe, you probably don't know how to save someone
far away, huh?
Yeah.
Remember guys how I'm doing the huh thing?
Huh?
How to save a life.
So yeah, Keith is in the fray falling down
and Clark is looking through.
Man, you could really, I mean, a cable car would be able to.
Here's what I wanna do.
I wanna look for something big and flat
that might float down there
and I could try and throw it under Keith
to like stop his fall.
This is, I don't know, a multi-roll maneuver maybe.
Not one, it's an odd one.
No way.
It's an odd one.
The green dice or what I?
Fuck yes, dude.
Hell yes, dude.
Joe just always has one set of dice
sitting on an odd one so that he can squeeze the camera down.
I've been waiting for two years for this.
Fuck yes, dude.
Okay, cool.
Well, what do you find?
What's the perfect item?
An old door is what I came to mind.
I'm picturing Titanic.
I don't wanna throw this lifeboat of a door down there.
Fuck yeah, you find an old door.
It looks really light.
I hold it up and show John.
John, what you gonna do?
And I'm trying to motion that I'm wanting to throw it out.
If you start throwing it at the end of your turn,
I will, at the start of my turn, open up the door again
and hope to time it right so it just sails right on through.
John says that with his eyes
and so Clark begins throwing.
Thomas just looked into the camera with big eyes.
Man, this is such a cool idea.
It's a shame Keith's gonna fall right into the water
at the beginning of his next turn.
All right, so it is Dawn's turn.
Am I rolling to grab?
Yeah, yeah, or whatever you wanna do.
You see Keith ahead of you as slipping and falling.
Are you gonna just grab two-handed onto the railing?
Can I do a special maneuver right now?
I love it when you ask that.
I consent.
Don D. Pattymore seeing this Keith fella
falling in front of him,
I guess in slow motion as I'm also jumping.
Like I love thinking of, it's very anime of us
to have all of us thinking very complete sentences
and all this action's happening.
Having full conversations somehow in a two-second span.
He starts chanting to himself,
vis-a-girl, vis-a-girl, vis-a-girl,
over and over again.
Okay, go ahead and roll dexterity to grab on.
Oh my God.
You got a 24 on a 55.
Oh, hell yeah.
Do you wanna describe grabbing onto this railing, Justin?
Yeah, I just, well.
I fuckin' grab it.
Yeah, I fuckin' grab it, bro.
I do what Keith did except I succeed.
And I light a cigarette in my mouth while I'm doing it.
In slow motion.
Okay, rad.
Jon, roll a natural.
Jon compelled as if,
it's almost like he's sharing a will with Clark.
He just knows to go to the door
and he rolls a 64 on a 67.
And just in time, he slides his hand down the door
and, or down the wall,
and a door-sized slot just opens
right as the door goes flying through.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Fucking incredible.
I am not gonna lie,
I was very much looking forward to Clark
just throwing a door into the wall.
Yeah, exactly.
What'd you do that for, Clark?
No, this is great, this is great.
I'm glad you guys are succeeding, I guess.
That, I mean, yeah, you've never seen Jon's eyes so big
and he's just staring at Clark in disbelief.
As this door flies through this little door-sized slot
in the wall and begins making its way down to the water
under Keith Vigna, Jack Russell is going to roll a naught 7
and he grabs on directly next to,
it's like we get another shot of what just happened
of the three men running and jumping
where Keith goes, hits, falls, and immediately,
Don grabs, and then immediately,
Jack Russell grabs right next to Don
and so the two of them are hanging from this railing.
Jack Russell is just pulling himself up,
going, oh, this is fucking shit.
And he's trying to pull himself up
and Don is a chancy, chancy boy.
Below the ball, you see these two twins,
one with a bowl cut, the other one with a pig tail.
They're running overalls.
And each of them has a massive smile on their face
and they reach into their little pockets in their overalls
and they each pull out a lollipop.
I think I just pissed myself.
That was scary.
Can you imagine?
Behind the ball, it's tendrils finding support
in the silvery, shimmery sea,
making this weird like,
noise is going to fling some of the melting steel
with one of its tendrils.
It's going to splash.
And it rolled a 23, like Michael Jordan.
You'd never wanted to get in the pool with Michael,
all time greatest splasher.
He could do the thing where he puts his hands
and squeezes them and it shoots right at your face.
You know what I'm talking about?
I do, my dad did that shit all the time.
Michael Jordan was the Scottie Pippen of doing that.
The splash is timed perfectly.
And this door made out of this black texture,
this colorful black texture flying perfectly
through the air to save Keith Vigna
from falling into this metal gets completely engulfed.
This melting steel wraps itself around this door
and it is no longer the liquid that it was previously.
It is now a metal door and the metal door falls,
hits the ocean and begins sinking as Keith Vigna falls.
Keith, your feet hit first.
I was going to say, is there any way
that my cargo shorts could act as parachutes
in this crazy world we're in right now
to slow my fall just a little bit?
In this crazy messed up world we're in.
He can't tell if that's better than the fact
that he was about to kill you.
Let's take a vote, Joe, Thomas, Justin.
If the cargo shorts can become parachutes.
I'll close my eyes so that I don't know who voted for what.
Yeah, put a thumbs up.
Put a thumbs up if you think that Keith touches down
into the metal sea and put a thumbs down
if you think parachute shorts.
All right, it's been decided.
Keith, your feet touch first.
Okay.
The pain is unimaginable.
It is the hottest.
It's giving off no temperature change to the air around it
but as your toes dip in, you can't feel anything at all
and your mind goes completely numb
and there's just this piercing noise
going through the back of your head, just this.
The shock immediately changes as the rest of you
slowly, slowly, agonizingly melts into this ocean.
Up to your knees now, your shins are fully melting.
You don't even know what it would be like
inside of your shorts but you think your legs
might just not even exist anymore.
You're just becoming part of this ocean itself
and your stomach hurts.
Your mouth immediately has the taste of metal
inside of it, blood and metal
and you can smell butter.
Smells like butter?
That's weird.
What do you scream out as your torso begins?
Don, use the phone on me!
Fuck yeah.
And you will continue melting in on your next turn
and by the end of your next turn,
you will be fully submerged in the shimmering silver sea.
Clark Bishop, it's your turn.
Clark Bishop, come on down.
Everything going good out there?
Did he land on the door?
That was good timing with you opening up that.
We got him, right?
You know, mission accomplished.
Yeah.
High five me, man.
John, weekly high fives you.
Every week?
This is our weekly high five.
It may or may not be about what just happened with Keith,
which may or may not have been successful.
I may or may not have just seen one of the most
horrific things I could ever hope to imagine
as he may or may not have melted into the ocean.
And Keith is just screaming at the top of his lungs
until it gets to his lungs and then it's just gurgles.
Keith, everyone knows you're in over your head,
over your head.
See, he's so excited that he got caught by the door.
He's so excited.
He's screaming for joy, right?
Clark, at the end of the day, it was a great throw.
You did your bit as good as anyone could have asked you,
but unforeseen circumstances came up
and now he's being swallowed into that goo there.
I can smell him cooking from here, actually.
Is that what that butter toast thing is?
Yeah, yeah, that's his blubber.
He was, you know, he was an inside boy.
Not fat, but certainly not fit.
Can we do anything?
Are you telling me that Keith's dead?
No, you can look out the hole.
You can see him dying out there and screaming.
This is still your turn.
So any idea you have is as good as.
We still got time.
Clark is going to search through this magical room
one more time for something long
that he can throw out there to maybe pull him in with.
You find a door.
I've been looking through this room to find helpful things.
God damn it, I can't find anything.
It's an 82.
There's so much junk in here, but it's also useless.
You find a putter.
How about this?
A putter.
Is it long enough?
You just whang him on the head.
Just hit him in the head.
Don, use the owl.
Phone on me.
All right, good turn.
Don D. Pettymore.
Don is going to continue his chant.
Can you give me that one more time?
Biza girl, biza girl, biza girl.
That was three times.
Cause you're special to me.
Thanks number 17.
Damn it.
I don't have 17 friends.
All right, and so.
Yeah, you were all fools to worry.
So, Don is hanging.
And as he's hanging, his chant begins reverberating
through this entire place.
You all feel yourselves freeze,
both in space and in time.
As the world begins to rewind.
Oh my God.
You feel yourselves moving backwards,
making the exact same movements,
only this time in reverse.
Clark sets a putter down on the floor
in the piston bunk yard.
Keith screams out.
His legs exist once again.
His stomach is content.
The taste of blood in his mouth vanishes
and the smell of butter melts away.
His feet lift up out of the endless ocean of pain
and the shock dissipates.
A shiny metal door emerges
from out of the shimmering silver sea
and flings off its steel covering
to reveal a colorful black texture.
The little twins put lollipops back in their wrappers
and into their overalls.
The unnaturally hued door sends a spray of liquid metal
toward the feral ball that inhabited Julie Maxwell
and then flies back up into the junkyard bunker
just as John closes a hem made hole in the wall.
Clark catches the door and promptly places it
under some junk on the floor.
Keith's body ascends toward the second stilted bunkers hatch
and his sweaty hands grab
and immediately release the railing
as he is thrust backwards onto the rising bridge
and time freezes once again
before suddenly stumbling forward
in its typical intoxicated manner
and Keith leaps toward the hatch,
reaches out for the railing
and we'll hear that roll on the next episode.
Woo.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I fail.
Oh well then it just happens again.
Okay.
Oh should I crit fail?
It was a 48 on a 60 just so you know.
Oh then we learn now.
I thought you were just gonna end it right there.
Keith grabs onto the hatch, opens it, grabs the phone,
saves everyone in the world and podcasts over.
I'm glad you wrote that.
Thank you very much.
That's the end.
Good game.
That was wild.
That was a great ending.
Good round.
You guys wanna play again?
I do.
Like you mean like season two?
What if we just played this again?
Let's just do this again.
Let's just start.
I bet you guys would do better.
Oh yeah.
Fucking right off the bat.
Maggie, it's your birthday.
You're under arrest.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
["Livin' In"]