I'm feeling like a damn sandwich here, y'all.
I am the meat that is between the good numbers six and nine,
the bridge between the celestial numerals
that make us all feel so nice.
That's right, y'all, this is episode 78.
And I'm building a bridge of vocal vibrations
live from 694.2 PTBP.
The numbers always tell the truth,
especially when they are the good numbers,
the nice numbers.
Speaking of numbers, we got one special message
from one very special listener.
This week's Howler with Wolf is from Zach,
who tagged that pretending pod
on his Instagram story for once.
He writes,
Hey Wolf, long time listener, first time Howler.
Howler howls.
Did you do it?
Did you howl?
Okay, now I want to hear you do a real long howl.
And it starts real confident,
like you're the only wolf in the whole dumpster.
But then as the howl goes on,
you become less and less sure of yourself.
Like you're stoned and underdressed at a wedding
that you weren't invited to until like the week before
when you ran into your old friend's fiance
at the coffee shop.
And she invited you after acting
like it was a total accident.
You were left off the guest list in the first place.
Now, do that now.
Okay, thanks, love you, bye.
P.S. Hey Joe, Justin, Luke, and Thomas,
I think y'all pretty funny and nice and cute to boot.
Now listen here, Zachary.
I do not howl on command for any man,
except for beautiful trash beings
who wish to roll in the filth with me, you dig?
I've also never been invited to a wedding,
but that has never stopped me
from enjoying myself to the fullest.
Full of love, full of trash, forever and evermore.
That sounds like holy matrimony to me, y'all.
Emphasis on the moan.
I love you too, Zach.
And one day I will eat your soul,
but before I do, I'll give you a little forehead kiss.
Stop it, stop what you're doing right now.
Pull over the car, dry off those hands,
and put down the damn quesadilla.
Go to Twitter, search at pretending pod.
Go to Instagram, search at pretending pod.
It's literally the exact same thing
that Jesus told his bro-mies.
Put down the quesadilla and follow me.
Or keep just listening, I guess,
but don't disappoint ol' Wolfie like that.
Tell your online friends about the show
and tag at pretending pod.
In terms of perspective,
let's try to look at this from Drew's.
It's time for the news.
Drew drove to the city in the midst
of a reconstruction of contention
that implemented puddle teaming,
the act of placing small man-made pools
filled with fish around town.
Drew admitted he didn't come up with this plan.
Rather, it was Pastor Adam Kane
who has seemingly assumed control of contention.
Drew went on to say the pastor
was using fish to collect the ooze.
Drew chastised the officers for leaving contention
during this phenomenally strange and harrowing time,
but John Lee Pettymore the 3rd
saw a vision of Drew bringing the radio, helmet,
and briefcase full of money
to the First Church of Contention,
and he freaked out on Drew for turning on his coworkers
until Drew showed them a round scar on his belly
from where he had been tortured.
When they patted down Drew,
they found a bloody piece of cheap carpet.
Drew told them, deadpan,
that choking on the carpet until he almost died
was how he found them.
It didn't take long
for the former contingent police officers
to torture Drew as well,
asking him to prove his assertion
by telling them where Tildy B. Mitchell is.
He said he saw only a small dark prison in his vision.
John went batshit and tried to pull off his own head.
Clark chased after him,
and Tyler, Kerry Page's energetic black lab,
came bounding toward the group from behind a barn,
taking us now to Clark's oldest loose end.
Honk if you know this, Wolf's boldest goose friend.
It's a brand new hit, a lone crack tone.
It's kazoo with no backbone.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah, it's a new episode.
Yeah, it's a new episode.
We have to record a new episode now.
Oh, behind the scenes.
Everybody listening out there.
It hasn't been a whole week
since we recorded the last episode.
Nope.
What have you guys been up to
since we recorded the last episode?
It feels like it's been a week.
I've been reading drill tweets.
I took a stroll over the restroom over there
and came back.
It was a good jaunt.
I've just been on Reddit.
I opened up another bubbly.
What flavor?
It's aha, it's strawberry cucumber.
Who makes aha?
I don't care.
What do you have, Joe?
I bought cranberry raspberry flavored La Croix.
I haven't tried it yet, though,
but I hadn't seen that flavor before.
I haven't seen that either.
Yeah, cran-raz.
Just so you know, it's the Coca-Cola company.
Hey, will you crack one right now?
I could've sworn that the package said cran-raz,
but this says razz cranberry.
It did a reverse of the thing.
I don't know why.
Here we go.
Oh!
Ooh, that's a crisp one
ripping the head off of that bad boy.
Oh, it's foaming everywhere.
Oh my God, Joe is just pouring it all over his forehead
while he shakes his golden locks back and forth.
Wow.
It's good.
And welcome to episode 78
here at Pretending To Be People.
You guys have had a week to think on what happened
in the last episode.
Any thoughts pop up?
I'm worried that you're gonna make me play Tyler
and Clark at the same time.
So I've been preparing.
I've been going in and out of character as fast as I can.
Can we see some of that?
No.
Just a little taste.
It's good to see the Contingent Boys.
Good to see you too, Tyler.
See, I've been practicing.
It's flawless, right?
Contrast really makes Clark Bishop's voice.
John Wayne-y?
Wayne-y.
Didn't we just leave the city?
How did Tyler get up here?
We pulled over, I think, outside Contingent.
It was like a dirt road, right?
Yeah, you guys were like halfway there, maybe.
He did make some distance though, it sounds like.
Yeah, what, like 30 miles?
When we did our Contingent Critter Coalition,
was that the date?
What date did that take place on?
Do you remember?
I think it was December 5th.
What day is it today?
I think it's December 6th.
Well, Luke, it's been a whole week since the last episode.
What have you thought about in the past week
about what is happening and what you should do on this one?
You know, not much.
Probably be more mean to Drew.
Were you mean to Drew back in the day, five days ago?
Not really, no.
I wasn't trying to be mean to him,
I was just more interested in the case than his whole being.
Yeah, you've seen a lot of misery and despair at this point.
Misery signals.
Okie doke, I'm ready to make shit up as I go.
Alrighty, well you guys are in the misery business,
so let's open up shop.
Tyler!
Is that Tyler?
That's Karen Page's dog, that's, guys,
that's the dog I was supposed to find.
That's it, it's right there.
I pat Clark in the back and says,
looks like you found him.
Mission accomplished, we can go home now.
Hey Drew, how do you know who Tyler is?
You all can see Drew Andrews
just filled brimming with affection.
Well, Tyler's just the greatest dog in the world
and I could've sworn that he'd been eaten by homeless people
but, I mean, he's Councilman Kerry Page's dog, right?
Drew, that's correct, it's weird though
because she floated the same homeless thing
that you just said.
Oh yeah, I guess I remember you telling me about that.
I'm confused though, how did you know this dog was Tyler?
John, I mean, I did put signs all over the neighborhood.
He probably saw it on the copier or something.
It just seems like you know this dog.
Is that accurate, Drew?
Well, yeah, it's like Clark said,
I saw the pictures on the copier.
Humant!
Okay, everybody roll humant.
Yeah.
Pass.
Ah, 11.
62 on 80.
I fail a 78 on a 30.
Okay, I'm gonna kick you out, Drew.
Okay.
Hey, Luke and Thomas.
Yo.
Zach.
Thomas, John Lee Pettymore especially,
when you hear Drew talking about Tyler,
it's not Drew, that's not Drew talking about Tyler.
It's not his voice, it's not his cadence.
I mean, it is his voice,
but it's not his personality that's coming through.
Damn it, didn't I spend 10 luck
to try to figure out if this was Drew or not?
Yeah, well, I guess actually it was more so
like you asked if you could trust Drew
and I answered that question more so
instead of like, is it Drew as a question?
Whatever, I made my choice.
Okay, let's get Joe back in here.
Drew, Drew, you seem awfully fond of a dog
that you saw on a poster.
He's probably just happy
that I'm able to close my case, guys.
Yes, yeah, it's definitely that I'm happy for Clark Bishop
because he was really worried about not finding that dog
because Councilwoman Carrie Pages is a very respected person
in the contention community.
Thank you not to interrupt me right now, please.
Drew, you would not have known that that was Tyler
based off a black and white picture from a poster.
That could be any dog, this doesn't add up.
Well, it's a black lab and it's a black and white picture.
I feel like that doesn't discredit it.
It's less that you recognize the dog
and it's more that you seem to know about this dog
that you've never met.
You seem to have genuine affection
for a dog you've only seen on a poster.
Well, Councilwoman Carrie Pages
is an excellent member of our community
and the fact that she has a dog means that that dog
must be one of the greatest dogs
that could be around for sure.
Hey, Carrie.
Yeah, what?
And as Keith Vigna says, Carrie and Drew says,
what, Clark Bishop's eyes widen.
I need everybody to roll sanity.
What?
Fail, but not over my power.
Fail, not over my power.
I also fail, but not over my power.
Everybody lose one sanity as Tyler runs up to Drew Andrews.
I believe still in handcuffs.
Oh yeah, he's still in handcuffs.
Drew gets down on his knees and starts like nuzzling
as Tyler runs right up and begins kissing
and licking all over Drew Andrews.
Drew, Tyler really does know you pretty well.
This ain't Drew, Clark.
They called, yeah, you, what?
Councilwoman Pages, how the hell did you get
in the body of our associate?
Clark's eyes widen even further.
What, what?
I am simply here to bring back the three of you
to contention and I didn't think that this was gonna be
that much of an issue.
Jesus, it's like with you people
and I'm just glad that Tyler is here.
If you would, if you would just come back,
I think we could do a lot of good together.
It's just that we needed your help
and we didn't know exactly how to get it
and so we just need, we figured Drew might be the best way
to get you guys to come back.
I don't know about these guys,
but I don't take very kindly to tricks being played on me.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, what do you guys think?
I don't like it.
Clark looks like he's trying to do
a lot of math in his head.
How did you get switched?
Yeah, how did you become Drew?
The radio.
Right, that makes sense.
Where's Drew then?
Is he okay?
You see a flicker in Drew's eyes.
If you ever wanna see Drew Andrews again,
you're gonna come back to contention with me.
So you tortured poor Drew and he wouldn't flip on us.
So you had to switch his body with yours?
Is that what happened?
He shrugs his shoulders.
I poke the wound.
Yeah, I was gonna say I punch him in the gut
where that wound was.
Poke and punch, same time.
No, God.
Please, please don't hurt me.
Please don't hurt me, I'll do it.
I'll even act like you guys don't even know Drew anymore.
I didn't think about this.
There's three of you, there's only one of me.
Please just don't hurt Tyler
and we could all go back to contention
and I can help you, I can help you.
I can help you, thank you.
Council woman, first of all, we're not gonna hurt Tyler,
but we might take him away from you forever.
Well, that would be hurting him
because we're so connected.
I don't know.
I think he'd be real happy
after we fed him steaks for a few days.
You wouldn't.
He might forget all about you.
Drew starts crying.
Council woman, now,
why don't you tell us what the preacher wants?
I already told you, we're just trying to help.
Can I humid that?
No.
All right, go ahead and roll.
Keith.
64 on 80.
Well, okay, so he's trying to collect all the residue, right?
So that there's no more out in contention
so that we can pull away all the puddles
and we can open up contention again.
You think he just wants to collect the residue
and then do nothing with it?
How can he keep it safe, contained?
I'm not in charge of that.
I think we gotta go talk to this guy.
You never stopped to think, did you?
Drew, I mean, Carrie?
Drew, Carrie?
Drew, Drew, Drew.
I was trying not to laugh.
Welcome to pretending to be people
where everything is made up and the roles don't matter.
You got put into the body of Drew
with a radio that had tubes on it
by, I assume, Pastor Adam Kane.
Was this all just like a Tuesday afternoon for you?
How did you react to all the...
Are you aware of the world around you
that you've now entered?
Oh, I think she's aware, Clark.
You've been with the pastor for quite a while, haven't you?
Well, when you guys weren't doing anything,
we decided that we needed to team up
to make change happen, something substantial
that could actually take care of business in this time.
I don't like this excuse.
I don't like that line of reasoning at all.
Carrie, walk me through the day
that Pastor Adam Kane said to you,
I need you to switch bodies with this guy here
using this radio.
How did that set with you?
That was just earlier today,
and honestly, I'm pretty heads in at that point,
so I don't know if you've noticed,
but the world is different now,
and you either adapt or you die.
Oh, we know.
I lean in and whisper,
is this because I couldn't find your dog soon enough?
Is this because of me?
Clark, I have no ill will against you
now that my dog is back.
All right, so how about this?
What if we, you know,
we're gonna send Tyler away,
somewhere where you can never find him
and you'll never see him again.
Now, we're not gonna hurt him,
but yeah, unless you become a mole for us.
That's what I said I would do.
Yes, we're on the same page.
Well, I know. It was your idea.
It was your idea. Okay, I love it.
It can be your idea too.
I just want you to know
that that's the leverage we have against you,
is that you won't ever see your dog again.
This brief reunion will be merely a painful moment in time
in which you get to see what might've been.
Drew and Tyler have their heads,
their foreheads pressed right up against each other.
Drew kind of like does one final push into Tyler's forehead
and then leans back and looks you dead in the eyes
and is like, I will do anything to be,
I will do anything to keep Tyler safe.
That's what I like to hear.
Boys, I think we ought to head back to contention.
It sounds like there's even more trouble brewing down there.
Oh, hey, why don't you tell us how you got this car?
We know it's not yours.
It was in the police department parking lot.
Yeah, old Trent left it there.
I think Grand Theft Auto is,
or tampering with a motor vehicle
is the least of our concern right now.
I'm gonna put Drew Carey in the back of the car,
get back in the passenger seat and look at the guys.
Who's driving?
Let's put her in the trunk
and put the dog in the front seat.
Okay.
I love that.
I'll drive.
Are you keeping Drew tied up?
Are you keeping him handcuffed?
Yes.
And are you doing anything with his legs?
Leg cuffed.
Yep.
Oh, damn.
It seems like that might cause more trouble than it helps.
He's gonna be able to be mobile when we get places.
Yeah, when we get places.
We're driving back, we're halfway to contention.
You afraid he's gonna walk out of the trunk?
If he's got his legs,
he might be able to kick his way out.
But if we leg cuff him,
then all he can do is wiggle like an ineffective worm
back there.
Handcuffs with attached ankle cuffs
were pretty common in the 70s.
So that's what Clark has on his old school
contention police officer uniform.
I got these here.
I'm imagining handcuffs on his wrist,
handcuffs on his ankles,
and then two handcuffs connecting those handcuffs
like behind his back like a hog tied.
Yeah.
Rigged and ready to go.
Boys, can we go to my hotel?
There's something I really need to show you.
Yeah, we're driving now.
We're in charge of our own destinies.
Of course we can do that.
Do you guys have any other plans?
We're gonna have to deal with the pastor at some point,
but I've been meaning to get back
and show you guys this for a minute.
Let's just do it.
Yeah, that's fine, sure.
And I gotta let Bean out.
He's probably ripped up the carpet
or peed and pooped in there.
I don't know if he even has food left.
We should probably give your dog
to someone who's gonna take care of it.
Him and Tyler can go to a farm.
Not really though, I love Bean.
All right, let's go to contention.
The highway between the city
and the small town of contention,
if it truly can be called a highway,
the part nearest to contention
hasn't seen road repair in decades.
Those from contention know to forfeit the radio
during certain stretches of road
because the rough old concrete is so loud,
the damage to the speakers as well as to your ears
is never worth it.
That's just something you're all used to.
What you're not used to is a blockade
made of splintered church pews stopping you from exiting
and the sign from Subtropolis torn down and spray painted.
It's like leaning up against this blockade,
has a big arrow to the right and says,
detour, please keep right.
I need you all to roll alertness or search,
whichever's higher or Thomas, you can roll drive
if that one's higher in order to see this
in time to do anything about it.
I slow down and I wanna say that
I feel like this is a trap.
I fail.
I rolled a six on a 60.
I rolled a 35 on a 70 drive.
So I just, I slow to a stop before we have to turn off
and I say something doesn't feel right.
I think we're about to get children of mend.
In the distance, you see that the detour leads down
some crunchy December grass and onto the service road,
just to the right, just to the north of the exit ramp.
But there is certainly some sort of situation
set up on this service road.
A crane sits off to the side of this makeshift entrance
to contention.
It's boom and jib hanging over the middle of the road
where its payload sits.
A substitute gate made of those big ass construction tubes.
So basically the crane is there to let cars into contention
by lifting all these tubes.
Like sauna tubes, the kind of things you fill with concrete?
No, the big concrete.
Big plastic tubes.
If we were in the matrix and we shot them,
they would go rolling across the road
and cars would crash into them.
Gotcha.
But the highway itself is clear.
It's just the exit ramp that has all this construction
going on, right?
So we could keep going down the highway unobstructed,
come around maybe the backside or something like that.
So yeah, we just keep driving.
Fuck the detour.
We look for a back way into town.
Yeah.
Or at least one that doesn't have a giant crane in the way.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
If this is the main entrance,
then it stands to reason that the others
are probably less secure than this.
That's what I'm hoping at least, yeah.
It's worth scouting.
Plus we're the cops and unless the pastor
has explicitly said to not let us in.
We know this town doesn't feel too kindly
about us right now.
I think we're the cops is about the worst thing
that could come out of anyone's mouth trying to get in.
Like why the fuck did you leave?
Why aren't you here in the first place?
But doesn't it kind of sound like
Pastor Adam Cain's running the show now and he wants us?
If we could not alert him to our presence,
that'd be the best for now.
I agree 100%.
I'm just saying I think if push came to shove,
we could probably get through this barrier.
Let's try to find another way around and get to my hotel.
So if you could all pull up the map real quick.
Yeah, I've got the map.
I want you to see essentially why Hotel Motel
might be one of the harder places to get into.
I see what you mean.
Yeah, it's right by the exit.
We don't have to drive anywhere.
Let's just pull, let's go back down the highway
the way we came a little bit,
pull off the side of the road
and then just walk to the Hotel Motel.
Yeah, that works.
Are you leaving Tyler in the car?
No, we're leaving Drew Carey in the trunk,
but we're taking Tyler with us.
You don't think we should take Drew Carey with us?
We hogtied him pretty good.
Wasn't our whole conversation though,
was that she was gonna be on our side and help us now
because we threatened her dog.
But I don't know, I mean,
it just seems like she's more of a liability
while we run a dude Drew's thing real quick.
You mean Keith's thing?
Yeah, it feels like the safest place for her to be
would be in this trunk.
I'm just saying we're not gonna be at the hotel for long.
Yeah, we're just missing in and out.
I just gotta get something.
Okay, yeah.
You can, somebody can stay here and guard,
guard him, them if you want, but I don't know.
Let's just all go and make it real quick
and get back to the car.
Here's my only fear,
is that things don't seem to go well for us.
So what if Drew Carey's trapped in the trunk for a while?
Well, that's her own fault for becoming, you know,
a pawn of this evil goo like a collecting pastor.
But we also were just saying that she could be helpful.
Like, are we abandoning the idea
that that could be helpful to us?
Right now, I think she's the most helpful in that trunk.
If she feels like she's in a situation
where we're leading her,
trying to be stealthy to the hotel,
and she can just scream like,
hey, hey, they're here,
and sick a bunch of people on us.
True.
That's true.
True, true.
Okay.
All right, that's it.
Let's go.
Let's go to the hotel on foot with Tyler, right?
We're bringing Tyler with us?
Yeah.
Clark goes around to the trunk and pats on it.
We'll be right back.
We're taking Tyler, so don't get any funny ideas
about getting out of there.
Wait, where are you going right now?
Please, thank you.
Tell me, please.
Nope, nope.
We don't want you,
if any of your friends come along and find this truck,
we don't want you leading them to us,
so we'll be back within 15 minutes, half an hour,
and you just sit tight.
Clark's gonna be staying here with you,
and then I wink at them.
And I'm putting some headphones in,
and I'm just gonna sit silently to myself
in the front seat up there.
Yeah, he's listening to an audio book,
so you don't disturb him or anything,
or he won't be able to enjoy that.
Great job.
That's exactly right.
You just don't say nothing.
All right, let's go, boys.
Boy.
I meant Keith and Tyler.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
And then we all head off to the hotel motel.
Is there anything in the car we can use
to make a makeshift leash for Tyler?
Oh, for sure, seat belt.
There's a light cardigan in the back,
and I tie that around his collar.
One sleeve tied around the collar,
the other sleeve I'm holding on to.
Okay.
Cardigan leash.
I love it.
All right, Keith, you know,
I probably should have humanted you
or done something to make sure
that your motives were good and leaning us
away from our main goals back to your hotel room.
But I didn't, so let's just get this over with.
Okey-dokey, who's got the worst stealth?
Mine's 50.
Mine's 10.
Oh my God.
Why?
I've got 30.
Okay, so I'm gonna have John and Clark roll
if you guys succeed, you'll be able to assist
by giving a plus 20 each on a success to Keith.
10.
So that is a plus 20 to Keith's 10.
I failed, a 40.
All right, Keith, you're gonna roll under 30.
83.
Clark Bishop, Keith Vigna, John Lee,
Pettymore the 3rd, and Tyler
are walking across the highway.
I need everybody to roll alertness.
32 on a 60.
90 on a 60.
87 on a 70.
All righty, just got Thomas here.
Thomas, you see across the highway
when you're like on the highway itself,
it's the highest point that you've been at.
And looking across the town of contention,
there's not much of a skyline in contention, right?
Not too many tall buildings here,
but you do notice that surrounding what you know
as the campus of First Church of Contention,
there is, that doesn't look right, it can't,
it's moving, it's a wall.
You imagine this is what it looked like
if Moses actually had parted the Red Sea,
as you see a moat in the air that is surrounding
the campus of the First Church of Contention.
And in the water are many different kinds of fish
that are all swimming about.
I need you to roll sanity.
Ooh, fail.
Lose one sanity as you realize
what you are going up against.
This is the kind of unnatural
that you have not witnessed something this controlled,
right, like everything that you've seen
has been just haphazard, seemingly chaotic.
But this, this was formed and this is held.
This is scary.
That's what you're supposed to do in horror, right?
Is you say, this is scary.
This is scary.
You're scared now.
Do you feel it inside of you where you're scared?
Oh yeah.
All right, I'm gonna, did you roll over your power?
No.
Okay, I'm gonna bring them back.
Sorry, I forgot to tell you guys
I was putting you in the waiting room.
Well, and they should have just been there because.
Yeah, immediately.
Yeah, I stop at my track and I tap you on the shoulders
and point to the first church of contention
and I say, hey guys, take a look
at what's going on around the church.
Both of you roll sanity for me.
For looking at the church?
Yep.
I fail.
Do you fail over your power either one of you?
No.
So you each lose one sanity.
How close to the church are we?
Quite a ways from the church.
Okay, I see it on the map now.
I mean 20 blocks maybe?
Yeah.
Or like five.
Oh yeah, like five blocks, sorry.
Above the skyline of contention,
which is basically non-existent,
I think the highest thing in the town previous to this
was probably the church's cross
on top of their steeple.
Currently above that, you see a massive wall of water
that is surrounding the entire land that the church sits on
and it is exactly like what you think it might look like
if you made a wall out of water.
Yeah, exactly.
It's exactly what it would look like
if you made a wall out of water
and there are fish swimming all through it
it's cool some of them literally jump out of the water
and then gravity pulls them back in sideways
into the wall of water.
And oh, I forgot to mention, it's scary.
You've never seen this kind of unnatural power
controlled like this.
It seems to not be chaotic, it is purposeful.
Clark starts walking toward it.
Clark, what are you doing?
You didn't, did you see all that?
There's fish in there, they're just flopping around.
Look at that, I gotta see this thing.
Yeah, I mean, let's just swing by the hotel real quick
and then we can go there.
Yeah, Clark, that's kind of where all our,
seemingly all our enemies are.
I mean, except our human enemies,
the ooze is its own thing.
Yeah, see, Tyler agrees.
We should just go run by the hotel real quick
and check things out.
But you're saying that we'll be able to get up there
close to it later on maybe.
Yeah, yeah.
See some of those fish.
Oh yeah, we'll take them fish.
That'd be neat as hell.
All right, yeah, let's go.
A regular ichthyologist is Clark Bishop.
You know it.
Pick the pace up a little bit
and start more than jogging towards the hotel.
Yeah, I follow.
As you guys get to hotel motel
you see that all the doors are open.
I sprint to my room and in the parking lot.
Look down here, it looks like a dog
tried to get into this room.
It looks like one burst from the inside outward
in this one here.
Yeah, can we reconstruct the series of events
that happened here?
It's several critters working together it seems.
It looks like a bird hit the window here.
Wow, this is something strange went on.
Maybe it's, do I see a cat around anywhere?
You guys are seeing that from a distance
and just wonderfully ignoring the scene
that's in the parking lot of hotel motel
which before you is, there's a dunking booth
filled with fish and sitting above the water
there's a young boy, a large boy with dumpling cheeks
and rounded ears that accentuate the roundness of his face
and he is slowly surveying the area
with a furrowed brow above glassy, darting eyes
while consistently stuffing his face
with a cheesy ziti scooped up
from a mixing bowl in his lap.
It seems like this husky fella is some kind of lookout.
They said they were using children and crazy folks
to look out for the ooze.
And see he's got his little tank of fish there
that he can just dump down into
in case it comes by.
Roll alertness for me, Thomas.
Seven.
And you notice alongside that astute observation
there is a walkie talkie that is mounted
on the netting of this dunk tank
so that it could be used
if someone was standing in the dunk tank.
Walkie talkie.
What's he, what's the kid wearing?
What is the kid wearing?
He is wearing.
I'm mostly asking, is he wearing like a swimsuit
so that he would be happy to be dunked
or is he just wearing civilian clothing?
No, he's just wearing normal clothes.
What'd you say, Thomas?
Said lack a week.
Like Meatwad and some awkward teen hunger force.
It's just a thing.
So what happens?
We tell you what happens.
Hey fellas, see that walkie talkie he's got there?
Yeah.
Seems like he could alert the church to our presence
so we might wanna, we might wanna duck down.
How are we gonna sneak around him?
Yeah, you could draw stealth.
Is anybody feeling particularly sneaky?
Is this a working carnival dunk tank?
Like does it have a target that we could hit
and dunk the kid?
Yeah, let's say that it does.
All right, can any of us throw?
We could shoot.
That's true.
I've got a 60 firearms, what do you got?
I'm feeling a little better than that.
All right, Keith, take the shot.
Well, I mean, what's your plan here?
If we dunk him, he's gonna say that he got dunked
and hurt a gunshot.
Right, but it gives us time and his confusion to run by.
He won't necessarily see what dunked him.
That's true.
And if you, you know, fuck up and hit the kid,
then we don't really have a problem either way, so.
That's true.
But as a, just throwing it out there,
another option is that we're here to get something
from Keith. Just shoot the kid
instead of fucking around with the dunk tank?
You're right, you're right.
Keith, why don't you,
you're not wearing a uniform or anything.
Why don't you walk up there, show him, I guess,
your hotel room key or whatever.
I mean, he's looking out for goo, right?
I mean, that's ostensibly what he's looking out for.
I could try to just obscure my face.
Give me. Is Keith clean-shaven?
Scraggly, but it's been a couple days since I shaved, so.
I grab a big thing of mud and I just rub it
all over your face where a beard would be.
I allow it to happen.
I have the mud beard on and I want to just quickly
walk over to my hotel room.
And if it helps, I do have some disguise points.
Clark, you, me, and the dog will hunker down here
and we'll see how Keith gets along.
If he gets into any trouble with this boy,
the boy's like, hey, that's Officer Vigna.
You know, we'll dunk him or shoot him
or do what we have to do.
Exactly.
We've taken care of kids before, so.
Uh, I didn't know that.
I thought you meant take care of him like we dunk him.
I'm not, I don't think I want to kill a kid today.
Like I said, whatever we have to do,
I'm just, I'm glad you're my partner in this
because we've been there before.
We've done through, we've, you know,
we've gone through this, so I know you'll do
what must be done when the time comes.
I didn't do it. I didn't do it last time.
It was a thing that happened that we were there for,
but I wasn't, like I would've,
I would've preferred it not to have happened,
but I, I'm with you.
We're here.
We're on the exact same page, buddy.
I know you're with me, killer.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Keith, roll a disguise.
There was a face of really happy
and then a face of maybe shock.
A 23 on a 30.
Yeah, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
As you walk by, you see these very glassy,
very darting eyes of this total chub,
look you up and down and then immediately pay you no mind
as he continues to survey the land.
And you walk into a room that has been ransacked.
Bean is not here.
Shit.
And the window, as you all observed earlier,
has been busted out.
I immediately go directly to the safe.
So, hotel safes, motel safes.
I think you can just pick them up, right?
Some of them.
It depends, yep.
So, Luke, how much luck do you have?
35.
That sucks.
Go ahead and roll luck to see if your safe
is in hotel motel.
22.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And Bean is inside.
Whew, I was gonna be so disappointed.
I was too, honestly, I was gonna be pissed.
I was like, please roll.
Okay, crit, crit success, it is there.
Yeah, I'm trying to think of something
that would make it better.
Oh, you don't have to, you don't have to,
this kid is completely preoccupied
when you come out with it.
Like, he is. The safe?
I'm like, I don't need the whole safe.
Oh, right.
Oh, shit, yeah, that's what I was thinking.
I was like, okay, so Keith carries this safe out.
Fuck me, so.
Guys, look, the safe was still there.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
That's all I needed.
We didn't take it.
We could put stuff in it.
Are you glad we came?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
All right, do your thing.
I open up the safe,
take out the watch that I had put in there,
I put it in my pocket, and I head back to the guys.
Yeah, and this kid pays you absolutely no mind
because of your critical success,
and you make it back,
and Tyler greets you with a warm lick on the face.
Okay, guys, do you wanna walk to the church
or go back to the car, but either way.
Keith, why the fuck did we come out here in the first place?
I need you to see something.
Well, one of you guys put this on,
and I reach into my pocket and hold out the watch.
Yeah, sure, that's a nice watch, and I put it on.
Okay, John Lee Pettymore the Thirth puts it on,
and I'm gonna send the other two to the waiting room.
Peace out.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Hey, Thomas.
Hello, Zach.
Thomas, it feels like the consciousness
of John Lee Pettymore is changing the channel
just like back and forth and back and forth
all between these different scenes,
and you begin to phase out of your reality
as this watch slips onto your wrist,
and you seem to be somewhere else entirely,
and you feel wet grass and dirt on your fingers,
and then the wet grass turns dry, so dry,
and the dirt turns to dust,
and you look up, and you see contention
as an old mining town in the late 1800s,
and you look next to you,
and you see a man lying face down on the ground,
not moving, and then all of a sudden,
you're looking at a door in the ground,
like a sealed metal door that was mostly buried,
and on the door is an inscription,
and it says, Pettymore Forevermore,
and then the watch is slipped off of your wrist,
and you come back to reality.
John Lee Pettymore the third puts this watch on,
and then quickly pulls the watch off his wrist.
Keith, what the hell is this?
What'd you see?
What does that mean?
I saw contention in its early days.
I saw a man on the ground face down,
and I saw a door.
A door in the ground?
A door in the ground, yeah.
Did you read it?
Did it say anything on it?
It said, Pettymore Forevermore.
When I put that on the first time,
I saw a door in the ground, but it had beans on it.
The door is just covered in beans.
That watch, my father gave that watch to Ferguson as a kid.
Why don't we see what happens when Clark puts it on,
and I like slap it on your wrist.
What do you mean?
What do I, you guys are seeing?
Bye guys.
Look.
Hey Joe.
Hello.
As Clark Bishop has this watch slapped on his wrist,
it feels like your consciousness
is just flipping through the channels,
and you begin to phase out of your reality,
and you're somewhere else entirely,
and you feel wet grass and dirt on your fingers.
The wet grass and dirt turns to dry, dry dust.
And you've seen pictures of contention from the late 1800s,
but you've never been there.
And looking to your left, you see a man who's not moving
face down on the ground next to you.
You're back in this wet grass and dirt,
and you see Maggie Cook's house,
and in the backyard there's a door floating in the air.
And then all of a sudden you're looking at this door
that's mostly buried, sealed, metal door,
and there's an inscription on it.
It says one, five, two, two, five, one, eight, one,
nine, five, five, one, eight,
which you immediately can recognize as overseer.
That's on the door in the ground?
Yep.
Okay, okay, okay.
I don't get it, but okay.
That makes sense.
I mean, I kinda get it.
I kinda get it.
John Lee Pettymore slaps this watch
onto Clark Bishop's wrist, and his eyes go blank,
and then not hardly any time passes
before the watch slips off the wrist
and Clark Bishop looks at you.
Did you see the door?
What did yours say?
Door, door, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was the numbers, it was numbers, it was.
What numbers?
It was the ones they spelled overseer.
Oh, shit, well, that's you, Clark.
Was the door in the ground?
Yeah, yeah.
Did you see anything else?
Yeah, I saw Maggie's house.
I was standing out there in front of it.
You know, she lives right there on Bean's Pond,
and I saw a door, and it was floating above Bean's Pond,
and then suddenly I was looking down at door in the ground,
and that's where the numbers were.
The numbers spelled out overseer,
and I saw the dusty, it looked like really old contention,
and there was that guy face down, like you said.
When I was in the belly of that beast, I had a vision.
Well, I saw my brother in Bean's Pond,
but there was no water in it,
and he was looking at a door in the ground
in the bottom of Bean's Pond.
If I interpreted my visions correctly,
I think you're onto something.
Bean's Pond is involved in some way.
Before I brought it up,
I wanted you guys to see that watch,
but I think we need to go there.
Yeah, I mean.
What do you guys think is the bigger fish
that we need to fry?
Well, once the pastor knows we're here, he knows we're here,
and we're not gonna be able to get much done.
But we do need to save Drew from him.
I don't know, boys.
Maybe if we find the door, it'll help us.
It's gotta mean something.
If we happen to choose wrong,
we'll hopefully just reset, right?
I mean.
We got all the time in the world.
I would hope so.
In increments of two hours every day.
We never know when our last, you know, what if it stops?
Well, we were lucky to have gotten this far, I think.
You know.
Really, any time after our first deaths is a blessing,
so let's just be thankful for what we got,
you know.
Don't beat yourself up over losing something
you don't even have yet, you know what I mean?
Well, I mean, I think we oughta go find the doors.
It's been on my mind for days.
Yeah, let's fucking knock on these doors.
So we're heading to Bean's Pond, eh?
Yeah, and I mean, we gotta get to the bottom of it,
but the water might be there, and I point to the wall.
Have you put the watch on more than once, Keith?
No, as soon as I put it on and I locked it up,
as soon as I took it off.
Okay, Zach, just in the interest of podcast time,
if I put this on, will I have the same vision again
or a different vision?
That seems like a big question.
I know, but if the answer is just the same,
we can move right along, but.
I think you have to say you'll do it, and then see what happens.
Since you asked me that, here, give me that back,
and I take the watch and put it on one more time.
reality blinks and flickers in a now familiar but still unsettling way and you're standing
over a man's body who's face down in the dry cracked dirt the smell of piss and shit wafts
through the humid summer air and looking down the road to your perceived destination you
recognize your hometown of contention back to the body on the ground your hands are trembling
as you roll him over a dead man in his mid-20s stiff as a glass of moonshine dressed in the
fashion of the day which is the late 1800s and a tri-folded piece of parchment falls
out of this deceased man's jacket pocket it's a job advertisement for the contention mining
company and it reads we is hiring able bodies readying untapped site plenty of work hesitate
not
try
bye