Hello, all of my sweet little ones.
It's your caretaker from another dimension, Wolf the Dog.
And I'm here to nuzzle you until you grow big and strong
and become capable of great and grand things.
Then you can repay me bit by bit
with just a little teeny tiny bit of your life force.
Just a little bit.
You won't even notice it, I promise, until you do.
And I am sapping y'all live from 694.2 PTBP,
the radio station that you listen to,
the only one that makes sounds at night
to drive away the old ones.
Sometimes y'all write me things, and this time,
I guess I'll read it.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Jaron
in Springfield, Oregon,
the real Springfield the Simpsons was based on,
who wrote up a lovingly sopping five-star review
on their podcast app of choice,
which is a nice way to support this podcast that you like
and are currently listening to.
Well done, Jaron.
Never heard of any Simpsons,
so not sure what you're on about.
Jaron writes,
Well, we've been talking about this entire time.
The password to get in will be fuck the zuck.
See you there.
P.S. Keep up the good work, my guys.
My favorite RPG podcast by far.
Just became the proud owner
of a Splashylvania Fastpass myself.
Well, thanks, Jaron from Oregon,
but I'll be declining your invitation
because I am far too busy taking care of Wolf the dog,
my dog, Wolf the dog.
I also finally figured out what the internet is.
It's an interdimensional net
used for catching the plasma carp from the galactic streams.
Yeah, I know things.
I guess you could say
I'm a little bit of an internet expert myself.
If you want to ride up something
for your big, bad Wolfie to hell,
tag at pretending pod on Twitter or Instagram.
Tag pretending to be people on Facebook
or write up a five star review
on the podcast app of your choice.
Screenshot that absolute gift
and send it on for Wolfie to see and smell and taste.
And if you want to support this show
and unlock 37 bonus episodes,
all while getting us closer and closer to our goal
of getting back to the weekly releases that you crave,
head on over to patreon.com slash pretending pod.
Now, in fact, you can find us
on a few different places on the internet for merch
or to listen to the soundtrack
or to engage with this nasty community.
You're gonna want to go to the show notes.
How many times have you heard me say that?
A bunch, I bet.
And have you ever clicked in
and actually looked at those little links
or the little episode blurb that my producer writes up
for every single one of these episodes?
It takes him so long to type up.
You should cherish it.
Admire it.
I know I do.
Well, either way, it's time for the news.
Last time, our intrepid heroes used each other's strength
and the limp body of Vernon Covington, the landlord,
to escape from the It Pit.
And when they finally got out,
Beck Wilder couldn't move on until Cal Colorado
and Julia Summers removed their jackets?
Hmm, weird.
The can crew then crept quickly through the woods
on the far east side of Grover's Gorge,
heading south until they met the enormous plant wall.
Lush, verdant, and apparently quite easy to maneuver within
without starting a commotion.
There was, however, a commotion in Grover's Gorge
due to the sloshingly soaked current mayor,
Chuck Bidwell, walking confidently south through the town.
The team from City Action News
slinked out the metal hatch door
and backed toward Godel's Gate to Grover's Gorge,
the single, simple, steel-trained car
that crosses the foggy crevasse
with the unnaturally smooth cliff face on either side
and a church stuck upside down
where it fell into this chasm so many years ago.
You know what?
Y'all deserve a brand new theme song,
a fresh jam, if you will.
Let's unwrap this tasty snack together.
It's Alter Girl with My Life is Great
and it's all my fault.
It's all my fault
Cause my life is great
And it's all mine
And it's all my fault
What about my hair?
Oh. Oh, yeah, it caught on fire.
Joe lit his face on fire.
It's cool. We'll post it on social media.
It's dope.
Yeah, go to our social media right now
if you don't follow us or if you do
and check out a fun video of Joe's face catching a blaze.
It's just a party trick I do sometimes,
specifically on camera.
Yeah, it's important.
It really went up, didn't it?
Do you put anything in your beard?
Nope.
Yeah, gasoline.
It went up very quickly.
It looked like it had an accelerant in it,
but it doesn't.
It's just dry and brittle.
I hadn't smelled burnt hair in a long time
and that was crazy.
Yeah, then we smelt it for a while.
I think I just got used to it
because I'm like, oh, it's gone
and then go outside and come back in.
I'm like, oh, it definitely smells like burnt hair.
I was smelling it the next day.
That's because there was still burnt hair on your face.
Yep.
How does it feel?
It's fine.
It's 100% fine, except that I did singe my eyelashes
and they feel weird still, but they're going to be fine.
Like crusty?
I've done that smoke in a bowl before.
Hey, same.
The whole front of my hair went up on New Year's Eve one year
when I was standing outside.
It was real windy.
I've only curled my eyelashes, but that's impressive.
Oh, I got the whole thing.
And the first thought that I had,
cause I didn't even smell it,
but I looked at myself in a mirror later and always
and I was like, did I get like Cheeto puff in my hair?
Like dust?
It was orange?
It was like a little, I guess cause I have like brownish hair.
I had like brownish hair.
I know I actually can picture the...
The curly Q crusties.
New Year's 01 was crazy.
Everybody thought, you know, Y2K was going to end it all
the year before.
He was still talking about it though.
Oh, so you guys just pass through the door?
The door?
The SpongeBob portal.
The SpongeBob portal door.
Well, I did some research on what those doors are called.
Nice.
Yeah.
And apparently...
And now you're voting Republican.
You would believe the insane restrictions
that the fucking libs have put on the big ass door industry.
What did you learn?
The entrances are called doors.
Wait, wait, wait.
Like the, the watertight things that come together are called dogs.
Dows.
Dogs.
Where?
The watertight things that come together.
So like the seal.
You mean like the helical like...
The cams is what I'm reading on the internet.
This is a former US Submariner typing on Reddit.
What was that?
Submariner.
Whatever.
And they said dog the door.
Yeah, that just means, I think that means secure it, right?
Spin the wheel to engage the cams in the closed position.
Like the pins.
The pins.
So it's not called the dog.
Yeah, that's clearly a verb.
Okay.
So the pins that like lock it into place?
But not the door itself, which is what you just said earlier.
It's called a door, I think.
And then the parts around are dogs.
So dog the doors.
I adore with my dogs.
I adore my dogs.
Nice.
Y'all.
A dog door.
See, that just opens up more confusion now.
Cause when you say dog door, we're going to all start crawling.
Yeah.
I'm crawling right now.
On the train?
Very good.
Let's go there.
Cal Colorado, Beck Wilder, Julius Summers, and Stevie are all standing in a simple steel
single train car sized train station on an unnecessarily massive bridge, 20 meters tall
and 100 meters long.
This bridge that crosses this enormous massive ravine is a minimalist construction showcasing
the steel that seems to be your only way back over this deep, wide, and foggy ravine.
The fog seems to be growing thicker and taller with every second.
And soon it will be a wall that this simple steel single train car will need to penetrate
to get to the other side.
The creaking hatch-like submarine looking door that leads back.
Zach, we were going to just let penetrate fly.
Did you want us to, uh, where did you have a beat written in there?
No, no.
It says and standing.
So there's a, there's a hatch.
Pause for the boys.
Pause for the dirty boys.
And a sopping wet.
Is this the kind of hat you can dog?
Chug Bidwell in his snug, now snugger green, now darker green polo steps confidently through
the door, just dripping.
Suddenly Stevie, their eyes get huge with realization.
Holy fucking shit.
There's no backup for the backup mayor.
And she begins like she's going to sprint out of the train car toward the soggy current
mayor of Grover's gorge.
We're going to move in dexterity order.
They were in the car with us and now they are sprinting out of the car.
They are about to start sprinting, but we're going to go into decks order.
So if one of you has higher decks than Stevie.
But their intention is to leave the car?
Their intention is to leave the car.
Yep.
As they holler out, holy fucking shit.
There's no backup for the backup mayor.
What happens if there's no mayor?
God gets loose, I guess.
And we got to go dexterity.
Who's got what?
75.
Oh, you're definitely going first.
50.
50 and?
45.
So it's going to go Julia Summers, Stevie, and then down the line, we got Beck, Beck
Wilder, Cal Colorado, Julia Summers.
What do you do?
He grasps at them.
Okay.
What do you want me to roll?
I'd like you to roll on armed combat.
Yeah, I don't win.
Stevie rolled a success.
I rolled an 83 on a 60.
That's not going to do it.
So as you reach out and grasp for Stevie, they dip out and take off running off out of this
single steel, simple train car sized simple train station and toward the sopping wet current
mayor of Grover's Gorge.
It is Beck Wilder's turn.
Beck, we've all resigned ourselves to trying to get the fuck out of here.
I don't think that he's on the train.
He's just going to go to the door and yell out to them.
Stevie, dude, we got to go.
We can maybe install a new mayor when we get back or something.
Would that be helpful?
We need to leave.
No, it's got to happen now.
Cal kind of brushes past Beck and he can't run very fast, but he's, you know, bad left
knee.
But yeah, he's starting to chase after Stevie and he's shouting, Stevie, I don't think this
is very prudent.
Have you really considered if this is the best course of action?
Why don't you just wait up a minute there?
Hold on, Stevie.
I'm really serious, guys.
This is very serious.
You can roll persuade both of you combined and you can combine your role against her.
Can I have said no, don't go and also roll?
I fail mine a 65 on a 50.
I also rolled a 65 on a 80.
Nice.
Very good.
So you are giving it your all, but I gave her a plus 20 because you had a predetermined
outcome in mind.
I gave her a plus 20 because the thing that she knows is very stout.
And I gave her a 50.
What did she roll?
For a human.
Luke, what did she roll?
A critical fail.
77 on a 70.
So she stops dead in her tracks.
I think you're getting through to it, man.
They turn around, they look at Cal.
Well, now I'm not sure if stopping them was even a good idea.
Wait, why did you want to, what were you going to do?
Okay.
Sopping wet, Chuck Bidwell is just walking confidently, carefully, and slowly toward
the edge of the cliff with one eye kind of looking over.
He's kind of glancing over Stevie, giving her a very dirty eyes.
Where's the other eye looking?
Now, both of them, both of them together, one of them and the other one.
Two eyes.
He's got two eyes on Stevie.
And he's just walking away and walking toward the edge of the cliff while you guys, they've
turned around and they look at you.
Well, Julius, you're right there too, right?
Yeah.
Now I feel like I've made a mistake.
Should you run after him, Stevie?
Um, cut that part out.
Chuck Bidwell continues to walk.
She still hasn't answered my question.
If we don't stop him from jumping off this cliff and hitting himself, he will be unleashed.
He's been trying to do this the whole time.
That's why he's the mayor.
It's this weird, some sort of fucking spell or some shit that's actually real where he's
the mayor and he stays the mayor and it stays the mayor as long as there's a mayor.
But if he dies, there's no mayor and it's loose on everyone.
They put it in the turtle.
Turtles are slow.
And they live for a long time.
Yeah.
And they typically don't kill themselves.
God turtle.
God.
Stevie should go.
Stevie, go get him.
Whatever you say.
And she, and she turns around.
She turns around.
You got it, boss.
Stevie plants their heels into the ground.
She takes off.
Oh, by the way, Stevie uses just like she, they pronouns.
So either one that you decide to use is fine.
Word.
Oh, cool.
Tight.
And when Stevie collides with the wet polo clad Chuck Bidwell, Stevie is trying to hold
on and restrain Chuck Bidwell from walking any further.
However, Chuck Bidwell continues his gate as Stevie continues to plant her heels into
the ground and they're just trying to hold on.
So at this point, because of the dilly dallying, you've got one roll.
You've only got one roll.
Do not let it pass you by.
The classic crap.
Julius is gonna realize what they said and sprint and try to knock him backwards away
from the gorge.
Okay, go ahead and roll.
Roll what?
Because he's just walking slowly.
You can just roll strength if that's higher than unarmed combat.
I'll do an unarmed combat.
Cause you're trying to push.
I got a 31 on a 60.
Got a 52 on a 70.
Damn.
So you go to push onto the front and these thighs, man, what's going on with them?
They're tired from squeezing the life out of Vernon.
These thighs of mine, they're tired of squashing.
Tired from pushing Vernon.
Julius is just a little worn out from, you know, he basically maxed out at the gym today.
On Vernon's head.
And now you are just trying to hold on, but Chuck Bidwell continues.
Darth Vader like walk toward this edge.
Darth Vader win.
Oh, um, 92.
Oh yeah.
The Olympics.
Atlanta?
Come on.
96.
Whatever.
And Colorado, uh, Beck Wilder has.
Zach's referencing when he saw him walking in a parade one time in 1992.
That was the Darth Vader walk.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Thanksgiving, the year I was born.
He wasn't allowed in the parade.
So people were trying to hold him back.
That Darth Vader walked with such strength and vigor.
Beck Wilder.
I'm doing the same thing.
Stevie has convinced me that I've already seen this crazy shit happen.
And I don't want more of that.
And it sounds like it's going to be real bad if I do.
So he wants to, uh, I want to go over there and try and help block like a, is it a frontline
man?
Yeah.
Like an offensive lineman offensive lineman.
I want to, I want to kind of get into stance.
Okay.
Now are you doing pass blocking or brush blocking?
So pass blocking is going to be kind of on your heels, trying to keep them in front of
you and rush blocking is going to be driving the group forward.
Rush, rush blocking, rush blocking, trying to maybe even get them to the ground.
Once I, once I center mass him.
Yeah.
Like one of the greatest offensive linemen of all time.
Orlando pace.
That's what I was thinking.
Yeah.
And you just lumber over there.
He was like 300 pounds and quicker in 15 yards than Marshall folk.
No shit.
2000.
Yeah dude.
That's cool.
Wildly fast.
Explosive.
A lot, a lot like Beck.
300 pounds.
I don't know what I was rolling on.
Was it good?
But it's good.
Well, what are you trying to use?
I mean, it's either strength or I don't know, like athletics.
Let's go strength.
21 on a 55.
Okay.
Chuck, but it all failed.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
78 over 70.
Then yeah, I'm driving him back.
I don't know if it's strong enough to knock him down, but I'm at least digging in my heels
and he, he was not moving forward.
You have stopped the progress of Chuck Bidwell and it is Cal Colorado's turn.
Dope, dope, dope.
When he comes, he comes panting up like a little out of breath.
And I think he just like grabs on to Julius's shoulders and yanks back and brings like the
whole group with them.
Love it.
Go ahead and roll.
Hopefully you bring the whole group with you in a good way.
What would you like me to roll?
The same thing as them, either a strength or an unarmed combat.
Pass a strength roll with 21.
I've got you beat with a 26.
Ooh, a close one.
Very close.
Well, now I'm embarrassed that I said the, the thing.
The thing about pulling them back.
Cal Colorado runs up and grabs Julius by the shoulders and attempts to pull the whole group
back.
But, uh, he, he merely.
What?
Julius is in the front.
So that makes sense that, but he, I wasn't a little confused about the pulling backwards
part.
Okay.
So in my mind, Stevie is on the back holding back.
Julius was in the front, trying to push him forward.
And then Beck came up behind Julius and was pile driving the two of them.
Yeah, he was.
Well then no one to me grabbing Julius's shoulders.
Exactly.
It didn't help.
But thankfully you got the momentum on your side.
And so I think we're all feeling pretty good about the outcome of this.
I'm grabbing Stevie's shoulders then.
Me and Julius are, we're between Chuck Bidwell and the chasm is at our back.
Yes, that is correct.
Yes, absolutely.
And it is going to continue with Julius Summers.
This is a good old fashioned tug of war.
It's a good old fashioned tug.
We got a good old fashioned tug of war.
He's only one.
Oh, like that old show Squid Game.
Away.
Still haven't seen it.
Julius is going to continue pushing back and try to give a little tickle to maybe distract.
Now we're talking.
Distract him a little bit.
Armpit, prostate, where are you talking?
A 70 on a 60.
You only put 60 in tickle?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's not going to do it.
As you go to tickle him, you feel the wettest.
Where are you getting in?
Well, it doesn't matter.
It's going to be wet.
It's going to be nasty.
I had my arms on his shoulders, like pushing back and I took one hand off to tickle him
and I put it up into his armpit.
But like the polo is like sopping wet and the tickle.
Well, it's like squeezing a ShamWow.
Right.
It's just there's too much pressure to tickle.
It just feels like I'm poking his armpit.
Gross.
Yeah, absolutely.
He's like, ouch.
Stevie attempts the same.
Will it tickle?
Everybody, tickle him.
Tickle fight.
To the same result.
Finger in armpit, wiggling around, but just poking and sopping wet you.
Beck, we need more tickles.
Oh dude, I'm really good at tickling.
Hang on.
I'm 31 good at tickling.
He's going to spend luck to make that a 42, which is a success.
How does Dougal look?
What cool thing did he do?
Chuck Bidwell continues with one foot over the edge like he you're holding on now.
You've had to move out of the way in order to not get pushed off the back yourselves
and it is all up to Cal Colorado.
Cal Colorado says, hey, look over there and I want to roll persuade.
Success.
I rolled a hundred.
Holy shit.
Right?
That's what that is?
All zeros.
Oops.
So my plan was to shout, hey, look over there and then slap lasagna in his eyes with my
other hand.
But instead I slip trying to get lasagna out of my pockets.
Where you're pointing is just down.
Hey, look down there.
Gladly.
He looks down there.
Sorry guys.
This is one of those let go or don't situations.
Raise your hand if you're audio medium.
Say a holler at if you're letting go of Chuck of Chuck as he is strongly moving over the
edge.
Basically you're choosing whether or not you're going over.
He's not making an attempt to grab at any of you.
However, you do see that he's making an attempt to grab for Stevie.
Can I try and intercept that?
Would I have a chance?
Yeah, let's do it.
This is your moment.
You're not going to stop him from going over because that ship is sailed, but you can stop
him from grabbing.
Just want to slap his hand away.
Because he is going for a very firm grasp based on the rules that I rolled.
It's an 18.
I don't know what you wanted to have that on.
Okay.
He succeeded with a 43.
Can I go for a slap too?
Uh, yeah, absolutely.
Go ahead and roll.
Actually, I want to make this one last tickle.
One last push for a tickle.
A 50 on a 60.
Oh, that is a good enough to tickle the grass leaves.
As he reaches out, you tickle like the inside of his wrist.
Well, yeah, as he's falling, the pressure of the tickle decreases enough just to get
to the perfect tickle pressure.
So with your hand inside his, it goes, it goes from poke to tickle.
The gradient of tickle.
Yeah.
It's turned all the way up to tickle and I get that one good tickle in before there's
before I'm not touching his armpit at all.
And like an involuntary laugh escapes as he lets go of Stevie.
Like this is like weird noise comes out of his throat.
And like releases Stevie as he just falls backwards and looks at you with these like
dead eyes.
Connor Ratliff.
Yeah.
Great podcast.
Have us on.
We'd cast you.
Oh, he would be a great Chuck Bidwell.
He would be a great Chuck Bidwell.
You listening Connor?
Dead eyed motherfucker.
As Chuck falls backwards in the classic fall backwards pose.
With kind of a blurry image behind him of the smooth cavernous crevasse.
And eventually he looking up the sound of body mix when he's ashes on a canyon floor.
I've seen a lot of wily coyote.
I think it's just a.
And when he lands each of you see something incomprehensible.
Your brain does cloud.
Your brain simply won't comprehend it.
Skull and crossbones.
The dust cloud with skull and crossbones.
The crossbones fills your stomachs with dread.
Your hands get clammy.
Your sight seems compromised.
And you feel an air blasting boom so loud that you wonder for a split moment.
If you'll ever hear again.
And I need you each to roll con times five.
To stay conscious.
I pass.
I critically fail.
It's a 77.
You're not going to believe this, but I also critically failed with an 88.
Jesus Christ.
I got a four.
Okay shit.
Thomas and Joe take our headphones off.
Take your pants off.
Take your pants or plans.
Strip Delta.
Boom.
Luke, you feel this reverberation in your chest that shakes your entire skeleton inside your body
and just vibrates your entire being.
Your vision goes completely.
Wackity wackity wack.
And suddenly it's extremely dark.
It was a perfectly bright day here in this gorge.
And now it is extremely dark.
I need you to roll grip.
In this darkness, you see that the rest of the can crew, Cal Colorado, Beck Wilder, and Stevie
have all fallen to the ground, seemingly unconscious.
I pass with a 39 on a 44.
You only lose one grip.
Julius kind of like shakes it off and clears his vision a little bit and then is going
to try to rush over to his coworkers on the ground and see what's up to kind of try to
slap him away.
Okay.
You're kind of slapping at him.
You see the camera has fallen to the side of Beck Wilder.
You see, you know, Cal's an older guy.
He seems to have fallen okay.
He doesn't seem to like have broken anything in the fall.
Stevie's just completely out.
None of them are getting back up.
And you hear this rumble coming from the bottom of the chasm.
Julius reaches to his phone thinking about making a TikTok, but then sees that the camera
is on the ground and Beck is incapacitated and real footage is better than TikTok footage.
So he's going to grab the camera and he's going to point it at the sound.
Okay.
He's going to walk to walk with camera on his shoulder, you know, looking at the display,
a wall of fog ahead of you.
And the fog is rising up like a push pop being just lifted from something coming up as the
rumbling is growing louder and louder from below.
Yeah.
He's going to kind of, he's going to walk to the, to the ledge, but then kind of use
the camera so he doesn't have to, you know, completely look over it, but aim the camera,
see if he can see anything through the fog as the fog lifts.
Julia Summers through the viewfinder of this camera sees, what does that smell?
What does that smell?
I got weed from work today.
Yeah.
It's dank.
It's like, it's musty, but it's also.
He kind of like smacks his lips a little bit and it's like, he just sucking on salt.
That's exactly right.
I need you to witness this thing.
And in order to witness it, I need you to either ask me one question or three yes, no
questions.
Okay.
I already know that I get a salty taste in my mouth.
Yep.
I know that it sounds like disembodied voices that aren't really saying anything.
And I know that as you remember that you begin hearing it and I know that it's a liquidy
human formed this thing.
Yep.
Sorry, give me a second.
I'll just, I'll do yes or no.
Make it quick.
Okay.
That's three.
Do I see it now?
Yes.
Is it coming at me?
Does it give off any light since it's so dark in here?
Yes.
This incomprehensible humanoid wet energy structure erupts out of this chasm, lifting
the fog above its head as it rises its shoulders next, you see an enormous torso and you're
staring between the legs of this.
What?
Julius takes a knee to brace himself with the camera and aims the camera up at it.
And as you aim the camera up.
Fluid monster god turtle thing.
You hear all of these voices coming out of the hand that is reaching out toward you.
It's the size of a suburban.
It's coming to scoop you up.
Suburban.
Julius is going to take the camera off his shoulder and set it down on the ground toward
the camera is still kind of facing it.
He's going to run.
Okay.
Roll a roll for athletics.
I succeed with a 43.
It was a 69.
No.
I promise.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Holy shit.
Where do you run?
How do you, how do you get away?
I'm going to run.
That's what you want.
I'm going to run back out into Grover's gorge.
Holy fucking shit, dude.
Holy fucking.
You turn the wheel.
Let's go doggies.
Doggies.
You dog the door.
While he's dogging the door, he looks back at his friends and he just goes, Oh, I'll
try to save you.
Okay.
I'd have you roll again, but you rolled the 69.
So you've dogged the door.
Yeah.
He just like flips it and it just spins on its own.
Yes.
And it immediately opens and you grab it on the other side.
Slam it shut.
Dog those doors from the other side.
You are now inside.
Luke just mouthed what the fuck to no one in this room right now.
Just looked at, I don't know what.
Holy fucking shit, dude.
I panicked as you would.
No game plan.
This is what you would call out of the frying pan and into the fire.
Yeah.
Julius like closes the door and locks it, seals it back up again, turns around and looks
at Grover's Gorge and just.
Okay.
You're still like in this big plant space and I'm going to roll the 69 over and say
that you did this all quite stealthily and are able to just kind of blend back into this
wall.
So you're looking out at honestly a pretty normal situation in Grover's Gorge from what
you've seen.
And by that, I mean when you first arrived, not later.
Julius knows that he can't go back into the main part of town and the only person he knows
here that might have any chance of giving a shit about what is going on specifically
with Stevie is Fox God.
Oh my God.
We're going to the GIZ?
Going to the GIZ.
Holy shit.
Okay.
How are you going to get there?
Basically your options are you can, I mean, cross over the track, this bouncy synthetic
colorful material, or you can kind of go around to a sidewalk situation over near the GIZs,
or you can cut all the way through the wall and then go around the backside of the GIZs.
I mean, I would, I'm thinking he's probably the stealthiest option would be to cut around
and go back, but there's not, I don't, I feel he thinks this is pretty fucking urgent.
Okay.
You might get caught.
So I'll give you a straight up stealth against the
perception of the town.
If you go straight there, if you, if you kind of cut around and use the sidewalk, if you
go around back, I'll give you a plus 40 to your stealth.
Okay.
Yeah.
He's going to cut around back and, and just be like, try to be stealthy, but he's booking
it.
Roll that stealth with a plus 40.
They, what did you get?
I got a 47 on an 80.
What do you think the town perception should be on the way in?
It was 80.
What did I roll?
Shit.
He could succeeded with 77.
Okay.
You're creeping through the brush and flowers.
No, I'm not creeping.
I'm running.
You're sprinting through this wall, sprinting, sprinting, sprinting, running, running, running.
And as you head around the corner behind these GIZs, you see there's a privacy fence in the
backyard, right?
So you keep going around the back of the privacy fence and you run down.
Now you're running kind of North South based on when you first arrived.
Right.
And you're running toward the far side away.
You're trying to remember where the GIZ was that Fox went into.
And as you're trying to remember, you trip on something in the ground and you look down
and you see a fucking Jackalope.
Nope.
No, there's like a metal cage that is halfway coming out of the ground just a little bit.
And at the head of this body length metal cage is a tombstone.
And as I fall on the ground, right in front of the tombstone, what do I read?
It says, oh.
Julius Sommers.
Julius Sommers Sommers Sommers Sommers Sommers Sommers Sommers Sommers Sommers Sommers.
Wait, fuck.
What is the name?
What's the name?
Is it too late to do something?
Yeah, of course it is.
What's the name on this tombstone?
Just give me a good last name.
Cream pie.
Nope.
Crump.
Crumpy.
Thank you.
Okay.
So it's Jeremiah Crumpy, former mayor of Grover's Gorge.
And as you trip, you hear a voice call out.
Hi there.
Julius looks around to see where hi there's coming from.
Hello?
Looking over the privacy fence, you see that there is a man standing on his back porch
in one of the GIZs that you were running past.
He's in a very like fine robe that's monochromatic with green accents.
And he holds up a cup of coffee to you.
Um, aren't you one of them fellas that was about to be on trial?
Aren't you supposed to be over there in the it bit?
Um, I'm not sure about that.
I actually just got into town from the train station.
I have a very important delivery for Fox Gotel and I've got to get to him.
Oh!
Uh, go ahead and roll.
Uh, either disguise or persuade.
Dude.
I got an ought one.
Oh my god!
I'm not gonna move it.
Okay.
But you can look if you want.
Oh!
That's really handy because look what I fucking rolled.
A 22 crit success.
Yes, but an ought one is the best crit success.
It's 669 but you already rolled.
Holy fuck.
Okay, so with an ought one, he's like,
No way!
Yeah, uh, I just was pointed in this direction.
Could you show me where he is?
Where his GIZ is?
Oh yeah, for sure.
He's actually next door.
Fantastic.
I was in such a hurry I seemed to trip over this mayor.
Oh yeah, Jeremiah Ripp!
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Crampy.
Here's a good one, but not long for this world, you know?
Do you mind if I hop your fence?
Oh no, I mean, look at the gate.
Julius looks at the gate and he's like,
Oh yeah, yeah, sorry.
You know, in a rush, not thinking straight.
It's okay, have a good one.
And he heads back into his GIZ.
Well done.
Holy fuck, uh, Julius fucking uses that gate.
All right, you head into the backyard of Fox Gottles GIZ.
It is absolute mayhem of cool, like, dumb toys and shit.
He's got like a basketball hoop with a trampoline next to it.
He's got a pool.
He's got a hot tub.
He's got one of those, like, you sit in it and it looks like a monster truck and you
drive it and it flips all around.
You know, he's got one of those.
Two of those.
That's crazy.
I can't believe he has three of those.
And there's an actual monster truck there too.
Damn, Julius almost trips over a hoverboard, but doesn't.
Can you describe the GIZ?
Oh yeah, from the back, it's got a nice upper deck and then a nice lower porch underneath
that's covered.
And there is like a huge bar with a built-in grill and a tabletop kind of situation.
Lots of windows in this bad boy?
Fair amount of windows, you know, want to get that natural light in there.
Can I see any movement or anybody in the house?
Yeah, Fox is dancing.
What music do I hear?
In one of the rooms, it's like, you just hear a boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Just kind of on repeat and he's just kind of getting it.
Under his breath, Julius mutters,
Everybody.
And Julius is going to take his shot and go, he's going to close his door.
Just no knock or anything.
I'm going straight in.
No fucking way, dude.
Oh shit.
Hey, what's up, my guy?
You came in through the back?
That is really something else.
I, uh, wait, did he talk more like this?
I think.
I think so.
Oh wow.
No way.
Oh my goodness.
It is fairly wonderful to see you.
Good, sir.
Where are your compatriots?
And you came in through the back.
Wowzers.
Julius goes to give him like the clap, clap, bro hug.
Yeah, clap, bro.
Yes, of course.
We are friends now.
Fox, we need your help.
Whoa, whoa.
Slow down there, buddy.
What's going on?
Do you know about the mayor?
Lovely turtle.
Yes.
Best turtle.
Best mayor.
Are you aware of the whole mayor lore?
The mayor lore.
The God.
Told, do you want to finish that, sir?
It's my last name.
Were you halfway through it?
Julius thinks this makes this a whole lot harder.
Is there an army in Grover's Gorge?
No, no, no.
We have no need for an army.
We have the landlord.
Mr. Vernon Covington takes care of all of our aggressive needs.
Julius is doing what I'm doing, and he's just kind of like licking his lips and kind of
just, what the fuck am I going to do?
I had plans for if you failed a bunch of things, but the succeeding is...
It's unusual.
It's nuts.
Fox, I'm going to be straight with you.
Please.
We don't have a lot of time.
My coworkers...
Sure.
The can people.
And Stevie.
Yes?
Faith.
He kind of turns his head to the side like a dog when you say squirrel.
I said faith, not squirrel.
Squirrel?
Your faith.
Yes, my dearly departed sister Faith.
She's actually alive.
Stevie is Faith, but she might be dearly departed soon if you don't help.
Whoa, okay, okay, okay.
I've still got a grip on what's going on here, so I'd say that I will help.
I don't believe you that my sister is Stevie that didn't even look like her.
If something were to happen to Sandro, who would be the mayor?
Chuck Bidwell.
If something happened to Chuck, who would be the mayor?
Well, he kind of scratches his chin, looks around at all of his things.
Do you want to play VR?
Maybe later.
Gee, who, who, who?
Oh, right, yes.
You were asking about who would be mayor if it weren't Chuck Bidwell.
Well, there's got to be a line in case, you know, something, a line of succession in case
something awful happened.
No, I don't think there is.
Would you want to be the mayor?
I suppose I could be the mayor.
Fantastic.
I, I would vote for you.
Let's hold an election right now.
Hmm.
Well, this is a wild thought.
I wasn't expecting to become mayor today.
Well, why wouldn't Chuck just be mayor?
This is purely hypothetical.
Hypothetical.
I mean, I didn't even run in the election.
Did anyone else besides Chuck?
No, of course not.
Well, I mean, you, you've got a really cool house.
I think you should be mayor.
Wow.
Flattery works on this guy.
Let's do this, buddy.
Cool.
Come with me to certify you in case you had to be the third in line for mayor.
Okay.
Let's go do that.
How do we do that?
By talking to your sister.
Okay.
Hmm.
She's in the train station.
She just had come back and she was about to see us off.
Okay.
Let's go now though.
And let's take these hoverboards.
I like the hoverboards.
I like the hoverboard idea.
I do want to play VR.
I'm sure that you have a high-tech VR.
What about AR?
Strap it on augmented reality and you can play as we go.
Okay.
Roll persuade with a plus 40.
Cause that was brilliant.
I got a 97 on a 100.
Oh shit.
That's incredible.
He failed.
Let's go.
Julius and Fox both strap on like Oculus has like futuristic.
Got all got chilis headsets.
Turn on the AR function.
And it's like looking through your own eyes, but he has programmed it for us to like, we're
like Pac-Man and we're running.
No, we're like Sonic.
And we're collecting rings as we run towards the train station.
Have you played this one before?
It's got a crazy monster.
Once you collect enough rings.
Well, yes, of course.
I always try to get the septum Gordman, the septum Gordman's head to cut them off.
Fantastic.
Get the rings.
Let's go.
Oh my God.
Okay.
So you're running out the front door.
I figured we would just take the same path I took here.
Oh, why?
Why would we go out the back?
More rings.
You brilliant son of a bitch.
And you guys dip out ring collectors on your way through his backyard around the back area
over the corpse with the metal cage around it.
The corpse, the bear.
It's a corpse.
The corpse, the burial site, the bone skeleton, the plot.
Yeah.
With the metal cage around it, head back around the sides and toward that doggy doggy door
and out out here.
Well, we've got to go in.
We've got to go in.
And Julius gives the door a little spin and opens it up.
Okay.
Perfect.
The boys will come back for the rest.
Fuck yeah, dude.
In the back.
Or maybe just like through the skull directly through the brain, get stabbed in the head,
but not hard enough to go through.
Break your bones.
Well, we've got Thomas and Joe back in the room now.
So what happened?
I need everyone to roll an alertness check for me.
Oh shit.
Me too.
Yep.
Fail.
I pass a seven on a 40.
53 on a 70.
Thomas, take off your headphones for me real quick.
Beck Wilder, Julius Summers.
Let's start with Beck Wilder.
You come to your stomach still just queasy, your hands wet and cold.
You're feeling completely disoriented, but you hear this rumble and this noise and this
strange kind of like maybe, oh, what do you, what is that?
And Luke, I need you to take off your headphones too.
You can either ask me one question or three yes, no questions about what it is that you
see down at the bottom of this enormous chasm as you come to and look over the edge.
Can I ask the one question, what do I see at the bottom of this ledge?
Certainly.
I want to ask that.
Okay.
What do you know about this, this thing, this kind of energy that you saw?
I saw that it was super circus, like it was wet and it made Chuck physically wet.
It does the same thing this time where it just kind of like, you see this
like strangely moving wet energy there at the bottom of the chasm and it shoots like a spray,
like a jet stream through the windows of the church, the upside down church,
the upside down church that is at the bottom of this chasm off to your right side.
And I need you to roll grip.
Uh, I fail.
Okay.
You're going to roll a D6 and add one for seeing this extremely unnatural sight
as your brain tries to figure out and kind of make it something that you recognize.
I rolled a five.
Five plus one is six.
So start putting those in order as you lose six grip,
fight, flight, freeze, and take off your headphones, please.
Luke is back.
I'm back, back again.
As you walk in, you see something moving at the bottom of the chasm.
You smell that salty sea spray.
You hear those voices calling out.
And at this point you can once again ask one question or three yes, no questions.
Okay.
How fast has it gone?
Well, it was enormous before, right?
Right.
It was extremely enormous.
Now it's like still kind of similar looking, but it's down at the bottom and it's making its way.
It's still enormous, bigger than a human making its way through the valley toward the church
off to the right side, the upside down church stuck in this unnaturally smooth chasm.
So how, I guess that was how fast is it moving?
This enormous humanoid was sprinting at almost 143 miles per hour.
And then it dives through the glass and into pouring itself into this upside down church.
Roll grip.
Fail.
Roll a D six and add one, please.
It's incomprehensible.
Your mind cannot handle what you see.
Two plus one is three.
As you lose three grip, your hold on reality loosens just so.
That puts me at a 40.
Jesus.
That's low.
With a breaking point at 36.
Oh boy, let's bring them all back.
Beck Wilder, I need you to place an order, fight, flight, and freeze.
It's a freeze number one, flight number two, and fight.
Fight is it?
Yeah, fight is number three.
All right, roll that D six.
It's a six.
Okay.
And what was your top freeze?
Freeze.
Cal stands up from tying his shoe and says, what's going on, fellas?
You feel clammy hands.
You feel your stomach is still completely unsettled.
Your vision is kind of off your head, shaking, vibrating almost still.
And you see Beck Wilder staring directly, completely frozen down toward the church.
And when you look in that direction, you see where you had previously seen like this beautiful
stained glass in the front of this church.
Now you see it has been completely broken and there's a hole in the stained glass that
leads into this church.
Who would do that to a church?
Teens.
You see that Fox Godel is here with Julius Summers and Stevie is coming too.
It's good to see you again, Fox Godel, obviously.
Also Fox and Julius are both wearing VR headsets.
Oh yeah.
We're collecting rings.
How many do you have so far, Julius?
He's rolling.
I only managed to pick up 11.
Oh, I have 79.
That is considerably more than you, sir.
Yes.
Julius was telling me that we're going to make me mayor.
I'm sorry.
What?
When was this discussed?
How long was I tying my shoe?
Trust me, Fox is the mayor now.
He's the emergency mandated mayor of Grover's Gorge.
Stevie, Stevie.
Hold on.
What?
What's going on here?
I don't know.
I feel fucking bad and weird.
What happened?
That noise.
What was that?
It was God.
God.
Beck, did you see God while I was gone?
Beck is just staring down into the church still, but he nods.
Beck, what?
Again?
Beck, did you get it on camera?
I got it on camera.
I feel around for my camera.
Well, your camera was placed back down next to you.
And as we have determined in this game, when Beck is conscious, he is filming.
So yes, you shot what you saw.
Dope.
Yeah.
Dudes.
Yeah, I got it.
I think I got it, dudes.
Show me.
Show me God.
Are we safe?
Should we go?
What?
Fox?
I mean, we're going to make you the mayor.
How would that help?
Stevie, you said that the mayor...
He's already released.
We'd have to do the whole thing to get him back in.
I don't know.
What's the whole thing?
I don't know, but it was a...
I don't know any of it.
I don't know.
Well, does Fox know?
Know what, my good man?
He doesn't.
Where'd you come from, dude?
Yeah, we're...
Oh, I was just hanging out, giving my old record player the spins and just giving my
hips a good loosening when old Julius popped in and suggested we do some AR while making
me the new mayor for some reason.
Or not even the new mayor, but just another backup, was it, behind Chuck Bidwell?
What do you mean Julius showed up?
He's been standing here by us this whole time.
Yeah, I look at Cal.
How long were we out, dude?
Can both of you roll grip, please?
Ooh, I pass.
I'm getting older and sometimes I lose bits of time.
I fail hard, a 97.
Okay, so you're going to lose zero grip, Cal.
However, Beck Wilder, you're going to roll a D4.
It's a one.
Okay, you only lose one grip.
That brings me down to 51.
Stevie, I panicked.
I just thought that the thing had to be in the mayor and if we made someone the mayor,
it would have to go back in.
Okay, that seems right.
Yeah, okay.
How do we make him the mayor?
That doesn't seem right to me.
Well, this is Godel Gorge.
I feel like you guys have, you know, can call Godel Law and make an emergency mandate.
On God.
On God, dude.
Okay.
I'm not as confident as you, Julius.
I'm not, but it's the only thing I could think of.
I hereby, as the oldest Godel in Grover's Gorge.
And Julius is like pointing at Fox.
Declare Fox Godel as the mayor of Grover's Gorge.
Why not you, Stevie?
And as she finishes saying that.
Stevie's older than Fox?
Now she is.
I don't think I caught that earlier.
I was picturing her being the younger sister.
I think I caught that.
Luke and Joe, take off your headphones real quick.
Thomas.
A wildly frenetic, wet energy.
Comes flying out of the church, out of the giant canyon and into Fox Godel, throwing
him backwards, back towards the plant wall.
You can either ask me one question or three yes, no questions about what you see, what
you smell, what you hear, what you feel as this thing kind of zips past you and you're
trying to perceive it, but it's really hard.
Almost like it's incomprehensible.
Has everybody else done this?
Yep.
Did they ask good questions?
Nope.
Pressure's off.
No, they did.
What's its name?
Is that something that you could tell from its appearance or sound or feel or taste?
You said I could ask you one question or three.
About how you perceive it.
Okay.
It's a good question.
What's your name?
Three yes, no questions or one question.
Would you tell me if I asked a question that's already been asked?
Okay.
What's it smell like?
Wait, no.
How do I kill it?
That's also not something you can perceive.
Why not?
How do I kill?
I want to kill God.
Zach, what's a smart question to ask?
I don't know, man.
Well, then why'd you think of this game?
I don't know.
Hey, they came up with questions.
Well.
And that's the end of the episode.
What?
Okay, I'm sure they asked what it looked like.
Did they?
I've got intense decision paralysis here.
I can't think of anything.
Just go through the senses.
I don't know.
Well, they asked, look, what does it look like?
I'm not going to tell you what they asked.
I thought you said you would.
If it had already been asked, you'd tell me to ask something.
Okay.
Luke asked me what it looks like, but okay.
All I heard was I'm not going to tell you what they asked.
Boys.
If you can hear me sign to me, I know one of them.
Okay.
How big is it?
Great question.
It is.
Wait, is it bigger than a bread box?
Yes.
How big is it?
Oh my God.
I can't think of three better questions or like two more questions.
Just fucking tell me how big it is.
It is like the amount of wet of an Olympic sized pool.
Thousands of gallons of water?
Yes.
Oh, much bigger than a bread box.
Just pouring into and through Fox Gottel, lifting him off his feet.
Higher and higher and throwing him over toward the plant wall.
I need you to roll grip.
Uh, pass again.
19.
Okay.
You just lose one grip.
Oh, well that breaks me.
All right.
Sorry about that.
That was long.
That was a workout.
That was a long time rolling my ears.
What'd you guys ask?
Cause my life is great, and it's all mine.