Salutations and vibrations, my faithful listenership.
It's your large and in-charge DJ Wolf the Dog.
I am sending vibrations of various lengths to you
live from 694.2 PTBP.
The only radio station.
It's the only one, folks.
Do not attempt to listen to any others.
They do not exist.
Hands off that dial.
Do not turn your ears away from Wolf or else.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Jared
in Houston, Texas, who tweeted about the show
and tagged at Pretending Pod.
And now he gets to send this wolfy memorandum
to Oliver in Mishawaka, Indiana.
Jared writes, to Oliver Chestnut,
you are my greatest and best friend.
We have shared laughter and love,
memories that will last until the stars are right,
and most importantly, comedy TTRPG podcasts.
The journey may be long and the old ones may be near,
but so long as I walk the path with you,
it will be a road worth taking.
Whether we are vampire cops datin' their partner,
archimites checkin' out the cold Corbett house,
or Delta Green agents vibin' on reverb,
I'm glad that it was us who took those journeys.
Well, technically you took those journeys.
I was busy playin' God and found it a game worthy of me.
May your smile shine and your hair always be anime colored.
Love, Jared.
PS, Fuck Mark Zuckerberg and Fuck Jack Dorsey.
PPS, love and energy to those pretending pod fellas,
and to the original phantom of truth, Wolf the dog.
Jared, thank you for this internet mail.
I appreciate all forms of mail.
The internet kind, those ones are good.
You mainly said a lot of things about Oliver,
and that's good stuff.
We love to see it, and I hope Oliver appreciates
all the weird stuff you made me say out loud.
But the it that I love to see
is you sayin' that good, good stuff about little old me.
Smiles and kisses to you, dear Jared.
If you wanna write up somethin' for your Wolf the howl,
tag at pretending pod on Twitter or Instagram,
tag pretendin' to be people on Facebook,
or write up a five star review
on the podcast app of your choice.
Screenshot them aromatic and intimate words,
and pass it along to your vibratin' Wolf the dog.
But Wolf, how am I supposed to know
where to find the 34 bonus episodes on Patreon,
or the grace drippin' swag in the merch store,
or the rowdy conversations in the Discord,
or the comments from Luke in the subreddit,
or the songs from Wave's soundtrack on YouTube,
or the download for R.I. Peter's Cruisin'.
Now listen, you, and listen good.
Say it with me, everyone.
The links are in the show notes.
And now, it's time for two quick announcements
from my producer, who scrawled this on my mirror
and waited under the sink until I found it.
No spoilies, but this is the final episode
of the four part prequel art, The Death of a Salesman.
Pretending to be people will be back in two weeks,
on October 7th.
Bloodily pickin' back up where they left off,
in Grover's gorge.
And for those of you blessed listeners
who support us on Patreon and await new bonus episodes,
we will have two new episodes for you in the comin' weeks.
The first is a Luke run game with our dear bud Jake,
joinin' to play the one page RPG, Witness Me,
based on Mad Max Fury Road.
And the second is a Zac run game of subway runners,
a forged in the dark game where a rainbow haired gang
went to repair subway lines under the city.
Oh, and it's set in a cyberpunk future
where everyone is immortal.
Speaking of, they had so much fun with it
that Zac is runnin' part two of that subway runners game
live in the Dennison this comin' Tuesday at 7.37 p.m.
Central time.
All right, that's enough announcements.
Gimme the news.
Actually, the boys do a pretty decent recap
at the beginnin' of this one.
So for its final bow, put your hands and cheeks together
for R.I. Peter with Cruisin'.
Cruisin'.
My archetype, I know this isn't right,
but I'm a beefy boy.
It's somethin' very similar to that, but you know.
It's a beefcake.
Also, every time we do, beefcake, there we go.
Every time we do the 30 seconds of silence,
you know, in a horror movie where they're trying
not to breathe hard so that the killer doesn't find him,
that's exactly how I feel.
I saw that you put both hands over your mouth and nose.
You can breathe.
I was crying. Eyes wide.
I start crying.
Dude, you can breathe.
Just lean back from the microphone.
No one said hold your breath for 30 seconds.
It's hard to do.
Wait, let's see how old we can hold our breath.
I think you can hold your breath.
I'm not gonna try, but you guys get it.
Oh, right.
I didn't even start trying.
I'm not.
There's nothing better for a podcast.
Yeah, I think we're onto something.
Oh, Luke won, if he was ever playing.
You look like you won.
I was playing, but then I wasn't counting,
and I was like, I don't wanna do this.
I'm glad you didn't waste time counting
because I would have never accepted your count.
It was 69.
Oh, nice.
So, I know we literally just stopped recording
the last episode and we're recording the second episode now.
It's nine weeks later.
Sure.
So we know what's going on.
For the audience who may have skipped,
just forgot to listen to this episode,
and be like, what did happen in that last episode?
Yeah, in your own words,
I'm curious to hear what's happened so far.
Well, so far, you wanna recap of the whole pink-a-boo?
No, just where we're at.
Our doctor, Dr. Shark, got eaten by Quicksand and died.
Well, no, no, no.
Whose body do we have?
We have Dr. Shark's body.
No, you left Dr. Shark's body in the pool of water.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But we took it from the Quicksand.
We're weakened at Bernie's zine, Dr. Shark.
Yep, you did that for a while.
And then we replaced Dr. Shark with a...
With a doctor from the neckbeards.
That's right, whose captain died.
His captain did die, Captain Neckbeard.
Yeah, and you changed his name.
We did?
Yeah.
His name wasn't Captain Neckbeard,
or we changed the doctor's name.
No, no, no, the doctor, you changed his name.
You asked him what his name was, I think he told you,
and then he changed it.
To what, do you remember?
So you're more than welcome to change it again,
obviously.
Yay.
I think he talked like this.
Yeah, he was scared, for sure.
He was a bit scared, and he talked like this.
Once we put him on board, we started calling him
Dr. Pisspants, because he pissed his pants in fear.
Dr. Pisspants.
All right.
I think that's what it was.
And then we got on our ship, right?
You headed back out to start the race.
Oh, we stole Neckbeard's ship.
You stole Neckbeard's ship.
I think we just told their crew, like,
hey, you're with us now, right?
And you sent the...
Jesus H., Jesus Christ, and...
Yeah, we sent one of your golden...
Mrs. Knife.
And Mrs. Knife.
We sent my Emperor Tamarin monkey, Jesus Christ,
along with Dr. Shark's parrot.
That's the one.
Mrs. Knife.
Uh-huh.
To go run the ship.
And the mother of Mitch to recite the all-important word.
Mrs. Diggory is on her way there to recite the ship.
And then who do we have?
We have our cool friend we made.
Zach, pause, pause, pause.
Yeah, what's up?
Are you writing fucking Harry Potter fan fiction
this whole season?
Like, is that what you call the Diggory,
so this can all kind of fit canon into your, like,
wait till you meet Umbridge.
I take her with that.
Nice.
Okay, Mitch is the guy that we have.
Yeah.
Yeah, Mitch is on the back of the ship alongside.
Oh, yeah, Edward Spitz, the cold-blooded butler.
He's not really a butler,
but he likes to think of himself like that.
Yeah.
That's my pulp Cthulhu occupation.
I love that.
And Joe, you're playing?
Waverly.
That's right.
They call me Wavy.
Wavy Adler.
Wavy Adler, and he kind of has taken the charge
of, like, steering the ship in what is looking
to be some sort of eldritch ritual race.
Yep.
And we have to, we're pouring oil?
No, we're pouring blood, baby.
We're pouring blood out of the back in a big circle.
Okay, yeah, that's right.
That was kind of the reveal at the very end.
My very single last note is that the barrel
started gushing blood, and Mitch quote-unquote begins.
And he continues to chant.
I got a solicitor today who was saying
that to me on the phone.
Yeah, I was just about to say that sounds exactly
like the phone call.
Making a call, Joe, yeah.
Wow.
Do you want to explain that?
I got a call, Zach was setting up,
and he told us all to take off our headphones,
and as he told us that, I got a phone call
from my internet service,
because I had just recently disconnected,
and they wanted to give me a survey.
But as soon as I answered the phone,
he played that sound.
So loud.
And he played so loud out of the headphones.
And I looked at Joe like eyes wide open.
It was disorienting for everyone,
because we thought my phone was making that noise.
I watched you three idiots grapple with that.
I kind of got it right away.
Yeah, that's right.
I played it, and I was still like,
what the fuck, Joe?
To be fair, I was not sitting on the couch
with your phone, and it was blasting super loud
out of my own headphones, so I might have had
some more context clues for it.
Yeah, I was right here, and I was watching it
come out of your phone, and I was like,
hang up, Joe, hang up.
Hang up.
Like, don't keep letting that play.
So you hear that echoing from the back of this ship.
As the race begins, the smoke in the center
of the island turned from dark to white,
and the race began.
As the race began, you noticed the closest ship
to the shore of the island, Fancy Pyromancy on the Damcy,
took off at a wild rate.
They rolled a critical success on their sailing,
and they literally shoot ahead, basically completing
one third of the entire circle around the island
in this first push.
Also, in the same round, they succeeded on taking out
one of the masts on the Swing Sing Brothers two mast ship.
Now, they were the ones with the best guns.
Fancy Pyromancy on the Damcy indeed are the ones
with the best guns, that is correct.
Where are the swing boys?
Next, closest to you would be the Swing Sing Brothers
from Fancy Pyromancy on the Damcy, who's the furthest away.
The Swing Sing Brothers are next up.
You saw one of their giant pillars of wood
that holds up the bedsheets that make ships go fast.
That whole shit fell into the water.
That is a fun fact, they do just use bedsheets.
I just assumed, I've never seen cloth so big besides that.
Yeah, hey.
They haven't invented parachutes yet, have they?
Big sailing ship is gonna tell you
that they're not just bedsheets, but buddy, they are.
The crew that you have sort of taken under your wing
and as your second ship in this race could not get moving.
And you notice that they actually messed up their cannons,
they fell over, their cannons are not operational
and they were not able to move forward.
The group next to you, the Port Deserters,
these are the Union Jack flag with the bottle
sewn into the middle of it, triple X across the bottle.
I would remind my fellow pirates
that they were seen drinking heavily before the race.
Yes, and you took advantage of that.
And I do believe that Alabaster Al Chernabog,
we talked about the other two characters,
but we didn't talk about Alabaster Al.
What is he like when he's running these guns
that you laid off to just lay absolute blows
to this massive ship of the Port Deserters?
You see that it doesn't all get through
their extremely sturdy, girthy ship,
but enough of it does because of you.
You know, the ship isn't the longest, but.
This might start out a little rough, but here we go.
The way that, oh, it's gonna start out real.
No, it's nice, it's nice.
The way that he likes to run the ship,
he's very excited the whole time that he's doing it.
He cannot wait to fire that next round
until they've won the game.
So he excitedly has told them to fire off the shots
and he got so excited he forgot to tell
the rest of the crew to start reloading
because he just went and started reloading them.
But they see, they're paying attention.
What does it sound like when,
and you lead by example clearly,
so what does it sound like as you lead by example
remembering in that moment,
oh shit, I have to tell the crew?
Oi!
They all immediately look over.
Well, that's the code word that we have set up
that means reload, just.
Oi! Oi!
And bombs away, you were able to knock a fair amount
of damage onto and off of that poor deserter's ship.
And off we go to the top of round two.
We're gonna start with Joe as the rope man
and the wheel man for this large ship,
the death of a salesman.
Death of a salesman.
Do you want me to roll?
I would love for you to roll.
Just doing my ship driving?
Yeah, we're all gonna, I'm gonna roll too.
What's a sail?
Like when they have a discount.
Oh my God.
So that's a fail, it's an 80 on a 70,
but I'm gonna use one of my three luck.
Ooh, very smart man.
It's only so smart because it only makes it an eight,
which isn't great if I'm in a competition,
but it's still a success either way.
Fantastic, so that is a success.
The port deserters actually rolled a critical fail
and yet they were able to use a bonus dice to avoid that,
but they rolled a 98 instead of an 88,
which is still a failure.
The neckbeard ship finally takes off
into the waters ahead of itself
as the Swing Sing brothers do the same.
Up in the lead, you see far in the distance
away from your ship, Fancy Pyromancy on the Damned Sea,
once again succeeds and continues
towards the end of this circle.
They're almost out of your view at this point.
Yikes.
Are we not moving at all?
I can tell you cause it'll give you a good idea
of how fucked you are.
You have made it 20%, they have made it 50%.
Shit.
Wow.
Yeah.
But that's with like two crits in a row.
Crit and then a success,
but they started much closer to the shore than you,
so they're gonna be able to complete their circle
much sooner.
I thought the slowest ship was on the inside
and the fastest ship was on the outside.
The slowest ship is on the inside,
they just crit it and succeeded.
I don't think we need to worry about this
that much right now.
And so like distance wise,
you said we can barely see them.
Yeah, you can barely see them,
but just through the distance there,
you see that they absolutely wreck shop
on the Swing Sing brothers.
Oh shit.
Just, oh shit, move it till it's,
oh girl, light it up and let me see y'all.
Swing.
Ship swing.
And the Swing Sing brothers ship is moving forward
in space, obviously.
We're in space now?
Hell yeah, dude.
In between you and the Swing Sing brothers
is the neck beard ship.
And that's what they're all saying.
As the Swing Sing brothers ship moves forward,
you see it disappear behind neck beard ship.
And then when it passes through on the other side,
you see that it is basically emaciated.
It is the skeleton of a ship.
It has been absolutely ripped apart by cannons
and those wire things with the balls,
connecting with the wire,
just like taking out everyone.
Chain shot.
Benoit balls.
It's called chain shot.
Benoit balls, I'm pretty sure.
Also not to pile on,
but that's not what emaciated means.
Emaciated means.
Would be like very skinny.
Yeah, they're all really hungry.
Be hungry and starved.
Yeah.
That ship looks so hungry.
I would say this has been hacked to bits.
Yeah, like to the points where you can see its ribs.
Like a turkey on Thanksgiving.
I'm gonna stick with it.
This emaciated ship crawls across the ocean.
Ship Akimbo passed the other ship in the distance.
That was something I saw on the Discord.
You don't actually use Akimbo wrong.
People just didn't know how it could be used.
Fuck yeah.
Thanks for sticking up for me now.
Jesus.
Oh yeah, you mean where thousands of people will hear it
instead of like the two dozen on the spoilers chat?
The Sweeting Brothers.
They're dunzo beans.
They're dunzoed?
Absolutely dunzo beans.
And with that, we move on to the gunning phase
for Death of a Salesman.
You have one ship within your sights.
It is the Port Deserters.
The Port Deserters were the fast guys
that we were worried about.
And they failed their second check, yeah.
You are ahead of them.
Then yeah, we've reloaded.
We've reloaded.
And oi oi!
That means reload.
No, oi means reload.
Oi oi means fire.
Go ahead and roll.
A third of the crew is confused
and just start packing more rounds in.
Two round shot.
You're not a confederate.
You did that again.
That's a goner.
Oh, there it is.
It felt like it went down in the catch.
It's a 42 on 80.
Yeah, that'll do it.
Go ahead and roll a D4 and a D8.
We've got a two on the D4.
A two and a five.
And a five on the D8.
Makes for seven points of damage.
Again, you do a little bit more damage this time
than you did last time to the Port Deserters.
And they have finally noticed.
Oh, okay.
You hit them hard enough on this one
to where some heads are actually popping up
on the top deck.
And they're looking about.
What if their heads were popping off?
Oh yeah, actually you see one guy in the back
whose head pops out just in time
as that last cannon ball just heads him off.
You fucking patriot.
He gets absolutely
patriotic.
That seems rad.
I had not seen that movie in years.
I forgot that fucking Mel Gibson is the head
of a family of benevolent slave owners.
Yeah.
I did not, yeah.
And it's like, it's weird.
It's patriotic as hell as well.
It is, it is, yeah.
It's very American.
It's just such a choice.
Could have easily.
Dude, that guy makes a lot of those, huh?
Been from Boston.
I watched that in third grade.
Didn't pick up on that.
Did pick up on the hatchet that goes
to the guy's skull.
That's stuck with me ever since.
Yeah, that part's rad.
The guy getting fucking his head blown off
by the cannon.
Not blown off, just like flick.
Yeah, as if God's, as if God's finger came down.
Luke, oh, Alabaster Alshernabog's cannon
flicks this man's head off.
And then.
Patriot style.
The, over the intercom of this.
His head is emancipated from his body.
Team Slayer.
Thomas, next to you, Mitch Diggory is continuing
with his Er-wah-doh-nyeh-nyeh.
I used to think, made out like his words
were complicated, but it's just a fucking Little John song.
What?
Thank you, Joe.
I thought you said Elton John.
And then he's like.
And I was.
You were like racking your brain.
I was trying so hard.
I'm like, it doesn't make any sense to me.
What?
Got the headlights on the.
That's hard on the throat.
Yeah, so Edward just imagines it's like,
he's rapidly like thinking, what is the point of Mitch?
I could do this.
All them swinging bastards.
I got a ship all eat up.
It's emaciated.
Yeah.
Emaciated.
You're saying they're hungry?
No, all I'm trying to say is gone mostly.
Most of their ship is just gone.
Para-mancy on the damn sea, they show them all the shit.
There's none left.
None left was blenders anyway.
And then there were three.
They're out there dying in the water.
Look at the bastards drowning and feeding the sharks.
Boy, they're dunzo beans.
Reload, but fuck.
By dunzo beans, do you mean dunion rings?
It's exactly what I mean.
I thought so, because I made that playlist
after my last breakup and sent it to you.
In an attempt to be done with your ring around this island,
I need a roll for sailing from Sir Wavy Adler.
Can I use rope to help him?
You would not be able to fire if you use rope to help him.
I don't want to help him.
And what are sails?
I believe they are the fitted sheet specifically
so that it attaches easier to the mast,
which I learned in my head recently is the wood part.
Mask.
I got a seven.
You got a what?
Seven.
Oh, that is a success.
Yes, I believe that is a success.
I successfully did sailing.
You push even further than the port deserters
who, while lively, seem to be more concerned
about the damage you've done to their ship
than actually moving forward in any measurable way.
The neckbeards, however, do succeed and move forward.
They're actually about even with you now.
And you see that you are both catching up,
slowly but certainly surely,
to fancy pyromancy on the damn sea.
Attagah, way to go, boys.
We're catching on them.
But then.
Oh!
Through the side of the neckbeard ship,
you see a cannonball four times bigger
than you've seen on any ship you've been on
bust through your side of neckbeard ship.
So it's across from you in the water
and you just see that, and as it hits the water,
it splashes you.
They are desperately trying to patch the hole
as water is lapping up inside.
Can we see where that shot came from?
Was it the pyromancy?
It was the pyromancy, right.
Or did it come from the island?
You can certainly roll.
Can I do a spot hidden?
Yeah, we can call that spot hidden.
30 on an 80.
92 on a 70, but I've got that skill
that I can reroll the one thing.
Oh, 22!
Hell yeah.
That's a critical success.
Through the hole in the side of the ship,
you hold up.
My spyglass, yep.
And as you lengthen it out, you see,
through this hole.
And this burning blood from the guy
who got patrioted inside the ship.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you see a pair of legs walking around
without a top half, a walk past,
but just through the view,
you can make out the ship of fancy pyromancy
on the damn sea with its smoking, massive cannon
that they've dragged out.
They didn't even try to move forward this round.
No one was manning the sails.
They just dragged out this massive cannon
to take this shot.
They got the mother of all cannons
on that ship over there, boys!
Hey, Sheridu, but half the reason
we got them neckbeards is to be our sacrificial goat.
I say let them take that shot.
To distract the pyromancy,
we put everything we got next time into moving forward.
Well, let's keep their husk of a ship
between us and them as long as we can.
I pull out a whistle and blow on it,
and I know this isn't how monkeys hear,
but you don't hear any sounds coming out of the whistle.
It's my monkey whistle.
Exactly.
Oh, we didn't send, oh, sorry.
No, you wouldn't say, oh, sorry,
because you can't hear it.
Right, exactly, no, I didn't even.
I thought that was the introduction
of some new, mysterious, creepy sound effect.
What I was gonna say is,
I think we sent your Emperor Tamarind over,
but we had the, Mrs. Knife was gonna be the runner
between the ships, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
So that is a pretty good time
after we've decided to cut them off and move on.
I relay that to Mrs. Shark, who says.
Cut it off.
Moving on.
I didn't have a sick segue that time,
but I need another navigation roll.
And then is this where we could help?
Yeah, if you guys wanna take off
from firing at the port deserters,
then you can all really get in on pushing this ship forward.
I have something that I wanna do
to avoid being shot by that thing.
So let me ask you this before I waste time doing it.
You know how I like to mix chemicals and shit together?
You do know how you like to mix chemicals.
Does your character also do that?
Your character does that too, I think, yeah.
They say right what you know.
For the listeners, Luke is not a scientist.
I have a minor in biology.
Whoa, I didn't know that.
So you know what?
You're right.
Okay, so.
If you're a biologist, then what's wrong with me?
Oh, Joe just pulled down his pants.
Oh my God, there is.
There's too much of ya.
Look at that.
Oh, cool, there's way too much of ya.
Your blood's not flowing correctly.
If we were up in the Northeast, I'd call that a hoagie.
Here we call it a sub, I guess.
Are you a sub, Joe?
The people wanna know.
Hold on, real quick, I just need to let one lie
that went unaddressed be addressed.
When Luke says he has a minor in biology,
what he means is he fathered a child when he was 15
and that child themselves is now a freshman in high school
in Mrs. Atkinson's biology class.
I was definitely a virgin then, so you're wrong.
Speaking of.
Oh my God.
I've got very bad news, fellas.
Uh-oh.
It's at 88.
Can you re-roll one of them?
It's a dang old crit fail and no, Zach, I can't re-roll it.
That re-roll thing is going on.
And no, Zach, I don't wanna talk about it.
And no, Zach, I don't want any consequences.
I don't wanna talk about it right now.
And yet, as your hands are trembling,
unable to complete this task,
was Mr. Spitz able to save the day here?
With a sailing roll?
No, I didn't roll anything good.
Okay, is this a time where I could see
that things are going very wrong and now help?
Oh, I mean, I suppose.
Didn't you already roll?
He had not rolled yet.
No, I was not gonna help
because I had my own thing I was gonna do.
But now, this seems a whole lot more relevant
than what I was gonna do.
Good play.
What should I, anyway, I try to-
You have luck, man.
That's true.
What did you roll?
He rolled a 68.
I rolled a 68, which-
86 ain't gonna do it.
So, one luck won't work.
Okay, then I don't-
Do you spend the luck anyway?
I don't, I don't do that.
Make it more of a fail.
You wanted it to be, you know, more exciting.
I see that everything's going wrong
and I'm like, I don't think I can help.
That's how that works, right?
The port deserters are able to catch up a little bit.
They're not past you yet,
but they are catching up currently
and we are rolling again.
Joe, if I could get a rope use,
are you guys going to help him again?
What is the conversation happening
as you guys are failing at this sailing task?
Is the consequence of the crit fail
that we just don't move and don't fire for a round?
That is correct.
Okay, so I was gonna say that Waverly's
probably just in awe of that giant hole
that has now been punctured.
Like, that cannon scared him.
So, he just stood there agape.
Well, and honestly, I bet a lot of the crew is.
So, while we're running around trying to whip them up,
a lot of them are just like awestruck
by what they've just seen.
Yeah, I saw the giant hole being made
and I was racking my brain for weapons on board
that measure up to that at all and I couldn't.
And then when I see that everybody's fucking up us moving,
I kind of grab a rope and pull it,
but I'm just staring at the hole in the hole.
The hole in the hole.
We didn't get much of anywhere this time,
but the key to defeating that gun,
eventually, if we need to, we'll be getting close to it.
It can fire at us before we can fire at it.
Not all four of that distance, right?
I've got something whipped up
that I think might be able to help.
If Jesus Christ gets here soon
or if I can run down to the bottom, I can grab it for us.
It's a special powder that I've mixed together
that I can put on a cannon ball and shoot into their cannon.
Yeah, you told me your special powder would get herpes.
Your special powder doesn't do shit.
Lots of special powders.
I gotta go look and see what I have down there.
I'm making this shit up.
I've got it all labeled.
That's what I'm saying.
I've got it all labeled down there.
Let me go take a peek.
Let me take a turn to take a peek.
Take a turnip.
He like pops a herpes sore at you in disgust.
Oh, God.
He's like, thank you, powder.
Wow.
We are pirates.
We are disgusting.
That's awful.
That's truly awful.
It goes into one of the three giant open sores on my face,
which is depicted on my character sheet.
Do you guys feel closer?
People don't know about history is that before that moment,
herpes was like totally curable, but that's great.
This is the moment where the super strain was developed.
And then eventually when I find that I have it,
I blame it on the damn monkey.
We're also both two weeks from dying from smallpox.
So it's like, this is our last hurrah.
Fancy pyromancy actually pushes forward
to where you can no longer see them.
They have turned the corner and they have disappeared
around the other side of the island,
which is thankful for the neckbeard ship
because they weren't able to fire at them this round.
However, the neckbeard ship failed miserably on their check
to combat the drowning.
What does a boat do?
Sinks.
Yep.
And so this drowning boat.
This boat is gasping for air.
This emaciated boat is drowning.
If I had to put it in terms of like math,
I'd say they started at yay 20 or so
and are down to three hit points on the ship.
Not going well.
And they critically failed and unable to help themselves
with an additional set of crew members.
They are actually moving backwards a little bit in space.
From what we can tell,
does it look like most of that damage
came from that one shot?
Oh yes.
Okay.
Horrifying.
Truly, truly horrifying.
And the port deserters are actually picking up steam now.
They are now two successful sailing moves in a row
and it is on you guys to catch up in this moment.
That's a 37 on a 70.
We're good.
That'll do it.
And you move up forward ahead of them again.
You guys are inching ahead of each other at each time,
just pushing nose to nose in this race.
I wanna take this moment to call Mrs. Knife
and while she's flying over, say to you guys,
what do you think about evacuating some key personnel
from the neckpits, including Mitch's mom and her barrel
and you know, Jesus Christ.
Getting them back on here.
It looks like their boat's done for.
We need Jesus and if they've got enough,
I think the way we get Jesus over here,
put as many men in those boats or however we do it.
I was thinking the parrot could bring Jesus over here
but do you think the parrot could bring over a human being?
You know, so we've got little boats
that go between the boats.
Right.
Can bring people over and monkeys, really.
Right, that's what I said.
I imagine that's how you,
you said the parrot would carry them.
Well, I said we could, the same way we could.
Your question was, the parrot could maybe carry a monkey
but could it carry a man?
I was talking about boats to begin with
and then I thought about the parrot bringing the monkey over
and then I'm like, well, could the parrot bring a human over?
But yeah, boats is what I was talking about.
I don't know the capability of Dr. Shark's parrots
all that well, you know,
it's capable of in the extremes
but I'm gonna say no, it can't.
But yeah, the boats.
Bring over as many men as we can get
and I've got to go look for powders and potions.
Waverly pulls out a whistle that's like a
and that sends a few bread about boats.
Yeah, the orders are sent.
The orders are sent, yeah.
So if the parrot's coming over.
Oh, the parrot's coming over.
You can hear Miss Knife, the wings flapping hard
against this crisp summer sunshine air.
Salty, baby, it's salty.
So as the parrot flies up, I say,
Mrs. North, you've got to lead the boats.
Tell them to gather all the best men
along with Mrs. Diggory and her barrel.
You bring them back over here.
Make sure the flow doesn't stop.
Yes, do not interrupt the flow.
That is of critical importance.
Bring them back over here.
We're leaving the mech beard, the ship
and a weaker crew to their fights.
You understand?
Mrs. Knife says, cut it off.
Moving on.
Fuck yeah, dude.
And with that, she takes off back to the other ship
and we are on.
Joe, I need to know what way the Adler is up to
as you roll.
Oh shit, it's a 95.
I'm gonna have to use another luck to make it a 59.
I'm down to one luck, my boys.
But I don't feel like we can afford
not moving at this point.
No, I mean, this is the time to be spending it.
I don't know if we want to set a precedent
that we explain the luck roll,
but he was turning, he thought he was turning
toward the wind and he realized,
oh fuck, it's the wrong, I mean,
readjusted real quick.
And then he actually caught a pretty good stream.
I'm all for narrative explanations of the dice roll.
I just say that because there's times
where it may be really hard to describe.
That's true.
And that's where we get created.
I dropped the gun.
That is one thing I do like about a D20 system
over maybe the D100 is the implicit scale.
One being shitty, 20 being awesome.
You know what a 15 is, you know what a 10 is.
Sure.
You know what a five is.
I usually do that and then I times it by five.
I feel the same way about the D100 system.
Well, I would if Delta Green didn't use the weird,
like actually lower rolls are not better.
I love the blackjack rules.
It makes me so happy.
I like them too.
It's just, I don't know.
Well, the port deserters push ahead of you guys,
unfortunately.
Don't give a fuck, Zach.
He wants to talk about the fucking game we're playing.
The boat from the neckbeard ship
starts heading toward you guys.
They're actually heading at the correct angle
to meet you on your way,
but they are going to have to make it around
the port deserters ship in order to make it to you
as you are right next to each other.
I would think that there are the rules of war
where you don't shoot at a abandoning ship, you know.
A tiny little ship.
Unfortunately, we're pirates and we'll slay anything.
And so my thought is shoot them before they shoot us then.
Give it to me, baby.
I'm down in, I don't see any of this happening.
I'm down in the ship.
I need you to roll for finding the correct chemicals
to create this bomb.
Which has the chemical symbol NEMO.
I'm looking at like pre-made, you know,
stuff I've made already.
Where's the NEMO?
The Necrotic Emulsifying Master.
Ooz.
Good.
Can this be a...
No, it can't be.
I don't even want to argue that.
Uh...
Thank you, friend.
What were you going to say?
Can this be a heavy weapons roll that I just rolled?
Oh, to find it?
To find my chemicals that I'm going to use as a weapon.
No, I would say like,
if you're trying to distinguish
between your stash of chemicals,
knowing which one you use to make the heavy weapons like...
Well, yeah, I'm thinking like I've got a wall
of like just shit like I've made already.
What's your heavy weapons skill?
80.
What'd you roll?
An 86, which I could use luck to make a 68.
How would you feel if you had to find the right gun
out of a big rack of guns and used a firearm skill?
Yeah, that's correct.
Tight.
Then I do it.
I use my luck.
Use that luck, baby.
I appreciate that.
You grab the wrong one and make it to the doorway
and then something clicks in your head.
You give it a big sniff.
Well, I sniff it and I'm like,
wait, this is literally to make it.
This is a stink bomb.
And so I run back and I grabbed the one that basically
it creates a cloud where like fire cannot happen in it.
So they can't shoot any weapons.
That's what I want to grab.
It's a cloud.
It's a cloud where fire can not happen?
It's a cloud where fire can not happen.
Such a bigger ask.
Like we fire this onto their ship
and it's basically like fire extinguisher shit.
Like fire extinguisher shit explodes
and so they can't fire any of their cannons
because there's no fire.
It gets all over their stuff.
They can't get any of the wicks lit, yeah.
No wicks.
But I'm gonna keep both to where it's that
and a stink bomb so that it gets funny.
All right, well, that's awesome.
And then I run back up.
And then you run back up and that's gonna be
your turn this round.
I love that so much.
All right, well, we better get going.
Tick tock on these wicks.
What is it?
Dink, dink, the dink, dink man.
Oh, that's a critical success for the port deserters.
Fuck you.
They're about to be some sticky like smelly bitches.
You know what's really handy for you guys
is that the port deserters make it so far ahead of you
that the neckbeard ship can actually meet up with you
this round with no issue.
But I do need a sailing role from Sir Wavy Adler.
Are they aboard now?
Who?
The neckbeards.
No, not yet.
They will be next round.
When they're aboard, can they aid our sailing
like with more, literally more guys in the fucking like,
in the rigging?
If Mrs. Diggory and the monkey,
the monkey will be a lot of help, I assume.
We talked about bringing over all the best neckbeards.
Oh, you were bringing all the, I wasn't listening.
So you guys.
All right.
Why can't the lady and the monkey
help the ship go faster, Zach?
That's how sailing ships work.
You've got one old lady and a monkey.
Monkeys are way stronger than you think.
Have you never sailed, you fucking peasant?
How much advantage do you want?
Well, preferably like-
I was thinking one giant long boat full of like-
Double or triple.
The hardest pirates with the biggest know-hows.
Exactly.
We got an old lady, the boat goes faster,
you fucking mook.
Extra blood, baby.
Erupting out of the ocean,
in between you and the shore of this island,
seemingly every bit of blood that has been trailing
out of these massive barrels
on the back of all of these ships,
all the blood is beginning to bubble on the ocean's top.
And as it bubbles, it is creating a steam
that is creating a fog that is-
And masking all of your surroundings,
the ship that is just nearby.
I mean, it is right there.
They're about to board.
And then all of a sudden, gone in fog,
you are completely surrounded.
You can barely see the hand in front of your face
and you can hear your entire crew panic
over the sound of Mitch Diggory getting even louder.
And you see that fog just billowing thicker and thicker
as you continue to sail the ship.
Oh, neckbeards, ahoy, are you out there?
Roll the sanity.
I pass mine.
I also pass mine.
And I'm gonna go ahead.
You're asking me to think of a way to use my skills
to get these guys aboard.
I've got the perfect one.
I'm gonna use spot hidden again
to search them out through the fog
and guide them in with my voice basically.
And 18.
Okay, yeah, that'll do it.
They follow the sound of your voice.
Ahoy, neckbeards, ahoy, your scrawny ass is up.
Get aboard.
It's a contest to win.
And you can tell by these dark seas
that there'll be hell to pay if we don't.
It's a perfect tone to cut through this fog.
And it is now blocking out the sun completely.
So it is dark aboard your ship.
Mrs. Diggory is still, what?
With her barrel.
Yeah, I get her and the barrel set up
next to Mitch basically.
But then I have my sword out and I look at Mitch
and I say, boy, without you finishing your words,
you should nod yes and no.
If we lose this thing, are we dead?
And he nods.
If we lose this thing, are you and your mother dead?
And a tear starts welling up in his eyes.
And he nods.
Cut his throat.
It's still better to have two of them,
though I'm of your way of thinking.
I'm not around enough for you to hear me say that.
No, you popped up on board.
You popped up with your chemical mounted cannon
in your cannon.
Yeah, I look around, I'm like,
squint, I'm like, oh, cut his throat.
I'm a pirate, so.
Mrs. Knife disagrees, she prefers torture
and she suggests.
Cut the legs.
And her little wings are flapping the fog away from her,
so you can see, you can always see Mrs. Knife a little bit
as cutting through this fog, no matter where she goes.
Like fucking crackers on that season of Archer,
everybody but me hated.
I love that season.
I love that one too.
It's one of the internet's least favorites
and it's like, that's the best coma season.
Adam Reed admitted during the Dreamland one,
he was on a lot of pain pills for a surgery
and it's like a really dark and fucked up and weird tone.
What is Wavy Adler up to as he's trying to get the crew
working together while they can't see each other?
He's using that whistle that he whipped out earlier
and he's actually prepared for this.
You enter fog fairly often as a sailor,
so they kind of know how to navigate through fog.
So he's doing whistle commands that mean the things
that we've been meaning all along.
So it's like, means to get up on the ropes.
And it's just this super like absolute fog.
And each one of these people who are working on your ship
as the crew, they're just individually moving by themselves
with no idea of like what is happening.
That knows what individually means.
Yeah, but I just figured out that other people
can do that too.
I looked at Thomas and I was like, come on, don't do it.
I'm like, he's on a roll.
I almost stopped when I saw the look on your face,
but then the way Joe and Zach got got, I stand by it.
I need to roll through the fog, baby.
These whistles are making it
so you don't have to be at a penalty.
It's a 63, I passed.
Congratulations.
You need three more successes to make it
in a full circle.
Something in your pirate bones tells you
that you're exactly three successes away
from completing this circle.
Your navigational skills trying to figure out
exactly where to meet back up with it.
Please roll a navigation for me right now.
That's a pass, a 36 on an 80.
Navigation's technically my best skill.
I should have been using that more.
You can now hear in the distance right in front of you
the chanting from two other ships.
Fuck yes.
Nearby, but they're in the fog.
Okay, so I turn to Mitch and I ask him,
man, does your chanting have to be loud?
He gets a confused look on his face.
Can you whisper the chant?
Erwah, yoh, yee, yerp.
Tell mother to.
Eh.
Blerp.
Woot.
All right, boy.
Oh no.
She fucked up, she broke the chant.
Hey, hey, Zach fucked up.
Mrs. Diggory.
Oh no.
You gotta roll for Mrs. Diggory.
All right.
That was you, bro, not her.
She chugged some grog on the boat.
She got in that boat.
She was like, oh, oh no.
What'd you get?
It's an 88.
She falls overboard.
Oh my God.
She coughs and then looks down and then looks scared
and then looks at Mitch and she's like, I'm so sorry.
I'm so, I'm so sorry.
You have to keep going.
You have to keep going for us.
Now we're together, we can make this.
We can make it together.
I just put my finger to my lips
and give her a look like, we're pirates
and we're gonna kill you if you don't stop talking right now.
Your three faces are the only things
that can be seen in this massive fog around
and your hand reaches up out of nowhere
to put a finger to your mouth
and she quickly silences
and then disappears backwards into the fog.
All right.
Wavy, what do you think?
Silence all hands,
slip by noise and quiet between the fog.
We'll never know we were there.
I love this idea.
That's the idea.
Stealthy as she goes, boys.
And perhaps if-
Stealthy as she goes.
As soon as we bust out of the fog on the other side,
you give them a load of that special powder of yours.
I hand Jesus Christ like an empty iron ball.
What does Jesus Christ look like again?
He is an emperor, tamarind, penguin,
so he's got the big mustache, monkey mustache.
I thought he was a monkey.
Penguin, did I say emperor, tamarind, penguin?
Yeah, you did.
Oh, no.
Emperor, tamarind.
You sent a monkey to the other ship
and you got a penguin.
He came back and there is some fucky stuff
happening on this island.
No, it's my monkey.
And he, I hand him-
He's a fucking penguin.
This guy, he keeps calling it a monkey,
but that's a penguin.
We just let him have it.
We let him have it,
but he's going to some one of these days.
We're gonna go up too far north
and that penguin's gonna die.
So this penguin, who I see still as a monkey,
is mixing together the stinky stuff
and the not fire stuff, putting it in this iron ball.
And then I load it into my shoulder cannon.
And I wait until I can see where I'm gonna shoot it.
Awesome.
In that exact moment, as I get a roll from Wavy Adler,
you hear in the distance the crew
from Fancy Pyromancy on the Damsey.
You haven't been able to hear them yet,
but everyone is being so quiet in this fog,
except just in the distance, you hear some scrambling.
Oh, oh, oh, yes, no, oh, we cannot find it.
Oh, no, we have to make it back to the original location.
Yes, to make the circle complete.
No, we haven't quite made it back
to the original circle yet, no.
I passed the sailing roll, it's a 12.
And a navigation for me, please.
Another one?
Yes.
45 on an 80.
Oh, yes, beautiful.
Fuck yeah.
All in the same round, Fancy Pyromancy on the Damsey,
the Port Deserters, and Death of a Salesman
have all completed their circle of the island.
None of you have yet to complete the circle
by finding the other end of your blood trail,
which is now a thick, red fog that you can see.
As the fog is coming around you, you see that ahead of you,
where the fog is literally boiling up out of the ocean,
it's red, and your trails are each lighting up red,
and these massive walls going up to the sky,
but you can't even see the sky anymore.
There's nothing except for fog.
Mitch, I have one more question for you.
What do you think?
If we win,
what do we die?
He gets a big smile on his face,
and he shakes his head no.
All right, Edward Spitz is fucking stoked.
And he's gonna try to do a Spot Hidden role
to find our blood smoke in the fog.
Fuck yeah, fuck yeah.
And passes with a 25 on an eight.
Hell yeah.
Awesome, so that is gonna be your first success.
I've basically given each team three navigation successes
to find the other end of the trail.
So Edward Spitz, he used Spot Hidden,
which implies some visuals, but he's a pirate.
He uses all of his senses.
As he searches through his spyglass,
he sees nothing, but all of a sudden,
he just catches a whiff of blood on the wind,
and then sees a little wisp of red
in the direction that he smelled that.
And he tells Wavy, he's like, that way.
Wavy, go ahead and roll that navigation.
That's a 25.
As you guys push forward into this,
you hear a low rumble in the distance.
And each one of you can feel the ocean approaching.
Waves are heading toward you,
massive waves from the island side.
And then you finally get to the end of the trail.
And then you finally hear it, this massive noise,
this explosion of a ship,
wood splintering in all different directions,
and the cries of an entire ship's crew
all at once through the fog.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, no, no, oh fuck, oh shit, oh god, no!
Not ours, right?
No, it's in the distance through the fog.
Why, thank god that's not our ship.
I was really scared, I really fucking scared
the piss out of me.
I thought I looked around and I was like,
I can't see anything, and I don't know if it was.
In one group of pirates screaming in agony and terror,
sounds much like another.
Jesus Christ.
I mean, I really thought that was some more,
I thought I heard fucking Fat Johnny
just squealing his little head off.
Anyway, well fuck, have you smelled the blood yet?
I smelled it a little bit.
We're heading that way now.
I thought, I thought I could.
Holy fucking shit.
Oh, like they said that back then.
Suddenly, all the fog that isn't red completely dissipates
and you can only see these massive walls
that encircle the island.
Boom, boom, boom, out like a bullseye.
If you were looking at this from above,
it would look like a Target logo, but with more of them.
And Edward just shouts, I see it.
You notice in this moment that it seems
that the port deserters did not complete their own circle.
They completed the neck beard circle.
And in that moment, something absolutely obliterated
their ship from the inside. Holy shit.
And all of them are on the boiling ocean floor,
floor, ceiling, ocean, ocean ground.
Ocean surface.
I like roof though.
The roof of the ocean.
It probably is roof in like 99 out of a hundred languages
or some shit.
Yeah, right?
If you're a fish making the language,
it would definitely be your roof.
There's gotta be so many fish languages too.
Oh yeah.
Oh, comparatively.
We've got to break the ocean ceiling, you know?
The death of a salesman and fancy pyromancy on the damn sea
seem to be equidistant from their individual,
nice, finishing line.
Yeah.
Yeah, sorry.
I didn't want to break you for language,
but you did it right.
Yeah.
You said all those words.
I thought about telling you that you got it totally wrong
and gaslighting you.
I know.
I thought about being like Zach thinks equidistant
means the same distance.
That is not what it means, dude.
It does.
It does though.
Oh yeah.
I couldn't see my face, but I'm like, wait.
We're totally gonna make him believe that equidistant means.
Equidistant.
Sorry, I had to take off my headphones for a second.
Where were we?
We were equidistant, bro.
Oh man.
I bet even if we talk about how like this will be a bit
where we gaslight Zach into believing equidistant
doesn't mean what it means,
we could still carry it out and like get him to believe it
for a lot of the season.
What do you think?
The thing is I need to fire your cannons.
I need to fire my cannons.
I want you to describe.
Okay, yeah.
Well, I've got to get rid of this.
And so as the fog clears on this ship,
everyone sees you walking down from the top,
walking down the steps to the deck, carrying what?
The fog is dissipating at his sides
as he's slowly walking toward the front with his.
Well, walking towards the back, right?
Cause they're behind us now.
They are equidistant.
It would be the front popping out of the fog.
The side, yeah.
Yeah, and Al has basically just like a small cannon
on his shoulder.
He lights a match off the cannon,
hands it to Jesus Christ, his monkey.
Jesus Christ grabs the tip of your cannon
and angles it way higher.
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, right, penguin.
It's totally a monkey, but the pirates don't know
what a penguin is.
They're like, that's a penguin.
He's going to kill that penguin.
It lifts up the top of the cannon
to give you an extra bit of boost.
And the Timurine Monkey is going to assist your role
by lifting your cannon and showing you,
we're going to have to fire really fucking far
because we're back to the, almost the starting line.
And you remember Fancy Pyromancy on the DMC
was basically out of cannon mode.
And he was just like,
the monkey on the DMC was basically out of cannon range
when we started.
Thank God I found a monkey with geometry skills
and like way higher thinking than I have.
Let's roll this, baby.
68 on an 80.
21 on a monkey.
Oh, yes, he won.
All right, go ahead and roll.
What is this?
It's a shoulder cannon.
Yeah, it's a shoulder cannon.
It's a firing combination of stinky potion
and giant fire extinguisher potion.
Is this mounted on your shoulder
and the monkey is like adjusting its trajectory
or is the monkey on your shoulder
and the cannon's on its shoulder?
The cannon is on my right shoulder.
The monkey's on my left shoulder adjusting it for me.
Generally, I would have like two people
like bracing me to do this,
but I don't need to, so I mean, it's-
He calls them Jesus Christ,
but we call him Trajectory the Gunnery Monkey.
The monkey lights the cannon ball and we wait.
And as we're waiting, we're gonna see
if they can succeed on this navigation check
at the same time as Wavy Adler
to find out if we're gonna finish this race
before this fucking bomb goes off.
Okay.
I got a 94.
I'm gonna use my very last luck to make it a 49.
Fuck yeah.
Hell yeah.
When did you roll though?
I rolled a 59 and they have a 60.
Oh.
But because of Luke's cannon going off
in that exact moment,
as they're about to reach their blood trail,
it's right in front of them
and the fog is taking over the front of their ship,
but it hasn't quite made it to the back barrel yet.
And in that final moment, right before you fired,
the monkey tilted the cannon just a little bit further
to the back of their ship.
And you see this thing just-
Ew.
And then-
Oh God, what's that smell?
That's the stink bomb part of it
as it mixes with the blood from inside the barrel
on the back of this ship as blood explodes everywhere
and Wavy Adler leads the death of a salesman
directly through the red fog,
right through until it takes over Mitch as he says,
what?
Okay.
What?
Boom.
In that moment, the red fog that you have created
completely disappears down into the water.
Every other circle, each of them,
one at a time going toward the island,
boom, boom, boom,
fog and maybe stone, some sort of cement
you've never seen anything like it,
erupting from out of the ocean.
As each of these walls go up,
blocking off the island from view, the fog fucking like,
each one of these walls moves forward
and the island disappears from view.
The fog is the only thing that you can see.
And in that moment, I need all of you to roll sanity.
Holy shit, this is fucking awesome, dude.
I passed 33 on a 60.
I also passed a 63 on an 80.
I have 90 sanity.
The wall next to you created a massive wave
that pushes you out further to sea
and directs the tip of your boat away
from where the island once was.
The fog behind you dissipates.
There is absolutely nothing there.
What's wrong?
Well, what did we do wrong, Mitch?
Where's the island?
I don't know.
How do we win this thing?
Mother, mother, I thought that, is it over?
She walks up to him,
she's looking off the side of the ship.
She's like, I suppose it's done.
Huh?
You fucking fools.
You rich fucking fools.
You killed all these men.
It's just to throw them walls up.
Where are my riches?
Where's Wavy's riches?
Where's the gold you mentioned?
There's a big score.
That's what we were doing this for.
Where's the fucking payout?
Al is waking up from being knocked out
by the force of his shoulder cannon
and he thinks everything is done now
so he looks up at Jesus Christ, high fives him
and stands up and then looks over at you guys.
So we did it, where's the gold and shit?
That's a great fucking question, Al.
Where is the gold?
Mom, where's the gold?
Where's our power, Mrs. Tiggory?
You have all been excellent servants and-
Oh, I don't like the sound of that.
You have completed exactly what we needed from you.
Thank you.
I have nothing for you,
but I appreciate the work that you've done.
You mean other than the gold?
Yeah, right.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, take me back to port and we will get you your gold.
The wall has disappeared and you turn back
and look at where the wall once was.
No wall, no island, no fog, it's a beautiful sunny day.
No island?
No island.
And what port does she mean?
Oh, back, you know, Jamaica.
Where's your fucking husband?
He seems to be gone.
That's a bit of a relief, isn't it?
Are there still the husks of ships sinking
or are we alone on the ocean?
You are absolutely alone on the ocean.
Mitch is still on board, right?
Mitch is still on board.
Mitch, what the fuck is going on?
And I pull my knife out, but I have a smile on my face.
But jovially.
Yeah, I actually don't know.
I mean, dad said that it would be, you know,
like world changing or whatever.
And I guess it did change the world, but.
Kill some pirates and build some walls.
Build some walls to only have them fall down again.
There's nothing left.
Was your dad fond of you and your mom?
No.
Okay, I see.
I mean, yeah, in his own way.
Yeah, but he might want to get rid of you or something.
Perhaps, maybe at some point.
I just put my flintlock to Mitch's head
and I turned to Mrs. Diggory.
You better tell us the real fucking scheme here
or I'll blow your son's brains out.
Your husband changed the world, how'd he do that?
What changed?
What did we do?
She looks at Mitch.
She looks at you.
Looks back behind her over the edge of the ship.
She takes a step backward.
I'm sorry, Mitch.
She jumps backwards.
Monkey tail in hand, monkey reaching out for.
Spitz watches her go.
So Al thinks about,
Al thinks about having, grabbing Jesus's tail
and having Jesus grab her before she falls.
But what really happens is he grabs Jesus's tail
and Jesus slaps him on the side of the head
and no safe attempt.
Yeah, she succeeded for jumping off the ship
and she splashes down into the water.
She fails her jump roll so she lands safely.
On the next deck below.
No, she jumps a couple inches in the air.
She's on the roof of the water.
Wavy turns to Mitch.
But about that gold.
Yeah, I don't think.
Oh, there is no gold.
There's no fucking gold except maybe for his father.
But we won.
We won.
Yeah, we won.
We won someone else's game.
We won someone else's game, Wavy.
This game won for us.
I turn to Mitch and I say, boy, you've got two options.
He's just staring at the spot on the deck
where his mom jumped off
and his eyes are as full of water
as they possibly could be without a single drop falling.
Mitch, it's pirate time.
It's hard.
People's moms are dead on this ship.
So unless you want to join her,
you tell us where you think your father's gone.
Oh, I don't know.
I thought you were gonna ask me to be a pirate.
You're gonna be like a prisoner pirate or something.
I mean.
Or you're gonna die unless you tell us.
Wait, but I don't know.
Can I just be a pirate without being a prisoner?
What do you know about?
You're gonna die, Mitch.
I'm sorry.
What do you know about being a pirate?
You guys probably don't have anyone
who's like good at accounting.
I could do that.
I didn't make him the offer yet.
Counting though.
I don't think any of us know how to do that.
Yeah, I can count.
As I was saying,
I don't give a shit what your pirate skills are.
We'll find a use for you on this ship.
You can count.
That's irrelevant.
I'm sorry, but that's irrelevant.
No, he's already bringing out the best in me.
I'm gonna make you a bitch intern
for about like 24 months
before you'll get anywhere near accounting
after the stunt you've pulled.
Do you understand?
Are you the captain?
No, but I'm in charge of personnel.
There's no captain,
it's a pirate democracy,
except for you.
You're at the bottom.
Wait, I can't be a part of the democracy?
No, you can't vote
unless you're a full vested crew member.
I disagree with that.
I think everybody gets a vote.
After they've been vested for six months on the ship,
until then they're provisional pirate members.
Well, I don't remember it being six months.
The voice says from the back.
Well, maybe it's not quite a democracy
now that we've saved the day, huh?
I couldn't count though.
Well, that's why we need him for democracy.
HR decision, and I've got my knife to his throat.
And I say, Mitch, where might your father have gone?
I know you don't know,
tell us your best fucking guess
or slit your throat.
Oh God, probably home.
I would guess home or the last place he was,
which was on the island,
I don't know where the island is now.
Edward is losing his patience and he like-
We can try to find the island.
It's gone now.
And maybe that's where the treasure all along was.
Cause it's gone.
I don't know.
We're not gonna try to find an island school
and tell us where the fuck home is.
Wait, hang on though.
Mitch, if we wanted to find an island,
how would we do that?
You say that like that's something you know how to do.
I guess we just like sail back to where we just were.
What do you mean where we were?
We are where we were.
He points to like a spot in the beautiful sunshiny day
that it is now.
And he's like, wasn't the island like over there?
And hey, Wavey, super not.
But like, you know where the island was.
No, it was over there.
But I get your point.
Let's just go park our boat over top of it.
Maybe it's below?
Yeah, maybe we'll find the old bastards ground corpse.
I wanna pilot the ship over that direction
just to sit on top of the spot.
Go ahead and roll navigation for me.
Mm.
18, for the listener,
Zach was giving me his hardest poker face.
There was no, there was, it was-
While also making like cum noises.
But it also, it wasn't-
Those are like Michael Bobaro noises.
It was obviously, it was obviously a face
that was trying to not do either a frown or a smile.
It was very strongly trying to be
the most neutral face you could make.
You can see all my face right now.
So I have to be very particular.
You say try not to hide a frown or a smile
as if Zach would like hide his disappointment
if we guessed his little game.
You've stumbled right into it.
He's trying to hide that little fucking grin
from his bastard face.
Cause we're gonna be eaten by Xith, Cthulhu.
As soon as we fucking, anyway.
The last shot.
We did light up a target.
We're gonna go sit in the bullseye of a target.
Trust me, trust me guys, let's get over there.
You want me to navigate you.
I agree it makes sense to check out the island.
The last shot of this short story
is the death of a salesman heading toward
just a random spot in the open ocean somewhere
just Northeast of the greater Antilles
and T.S. Mayores in the North Atlantic Ocean.
Bermuda, Bahama, come on pretty mama.
Key Lago, Montego, baby why don't we go to Key Lago.
Barbados, I wanna take it down to Coco Mo.
We'll get there fast and then we'll take it slow.
That's where we wanna go.
Way down in Coco Mo.
Bahama, come on.
Dude.
No, but there's no resolution.
We don't find out.
Well, I mean.
That's a really good point.
It's like the rest of season two.
Just be sure to stock up on pirate nerd stats
and then you'll know about the history.
There you go.
Of the Dread Pirate neck beard
and the mysterious events that happened on Bullshit Island.
Also be sure to stock up on t-shirts, towels,
fanny packs, hats.
Listen, the store is launched with season two.
Get your shit.
Buy more than one for your friends,
for you just in case.
You never know how valuable this stuff's gonna be,
mint condition, so you gotta buy doubles,
you gotta buy triples.
I'm no financial expert
and this doesn't count as real financial advice,
but I will 100% guarantee that any investment you make
in a PTPP piece of merch right now
will increase 1,000 gold by the end of the decade.
That is a promise.
There you go.
We'll see you back.
We'll see you back at home.
That's the pain people say.
We'll see you back.
Hey, we'll see you back.
All I'm saying is a $43 towel today
will net you $43,000 at the end of the decade.
Wow, really?
That's such a good deal.
I was thinking more like you pay 40 bucks for it now,
it's 60 bucks in 10 years?
Just because that's what a towel would be worth probably.
Some stupid old towel.
No, but it's like a sick towel.
It's 10 years old.
It's a sick towel that you never used.
Owned by one of our listeners.
Even worse, owned by one of the hosts.
Completely disgusting.
I can smell each one of us individually nice right now.
On their own?
Oh yeah.
They said individually, didn't they?
Our smells are equidistant.
Roughly.
Good one.
Come on.
Hey, thanks everybody for listening to this short arc here in season two of pretending
to be people.
There's going to be a few more of those for some backstory and other story goodies that
carry in with the plot of the main thread of season two.
Very fucking excited.
But I am here because I am at a loss for words.
I don't know how to say how cool it was that Beth May from Dungeons and Daddies was on
our podcast.
Here's what I'll say.
Equidistant.
I think it was like just like such a surreal moment and she was so fun to be at the table
with.
It was a dream come true.
It was awesome.
It was.
We thought there's no way in hell it could happen.
And really it turns out there is no way in hell that it can happen, but really we're
thinking Beth and she was lovely, but we got to thank her friend that she thought was huge
shout out to Travis.
Big shout out to Travis.
Big shout out.
Yeah.
Travis, if you're out there, hit us up.
Let's be real friends.
Yeah.
Cause who else do you know?
Beth May already thinks we are.
Anyway, Travis, you're out there.
We're friends now.
It's like we said, thanks Beth or whatever, but thank you Travis.
No, seriously, Beth found out that we weren't the podcast she thought she was coming on
and still came on the show.
Anyway.
So cool.
Very rad.
Go listen to Dungeons and Daddies.
Yes.
Go buy her book.
I believe she said it was available in all bookstores.
I believe that's what she said.
Go to your bookstore and buy it.
I think she said like go to Barnes and Noble, have them order it and then go pick it up.
There you go.
Thomas?
I just think she's going to think what Luke said was really tragic.
Which part?
The Barnes and Noble part.
What about it's tragic?
You're supposed to actually see the joke was that you're supposed to preorder it at a small
local bookstore.
Oh.
You don't read.
You don't know.
I didn't even think about it.
Oh my God.
You fucking.
Why am I friends with you fucking idiots?
Okay.
Sorry.
Answer it.
Sorry I said Barnes and Noble.
Barnes and Noble book buying bitches.
Well, you know, support your local bookstore.
I do.
But when I think of bookstore, I think Barnes and Noble.
We got one in town.
Yeah.
But I don't buy books from there.
It's just that's where you buy books.
Because my life is great and it's all my fault.