Cock-a-doodle-doo, my chickadees.
It's your mother hen, T.J. Wolf the dog here,
to sit on you and increase your body temperatures
with the warm embrace of my bum.
I am giving you life energizing force
live from 694.2 PTBP.
The only radio station that broadcasts
to all chickens across the dimensions.
All of them hear this.
They all know what you all think about them now.
Be wary and beware.
Hey, lean in close.
Let's shake it up because I've been shook.
This is me beside myself and I'm howling with Wolf
at two you slashes who have nailed me to a wall
with a handful of dimes in my mouth.
A detailed description by user,
resistor0 underscore zero was titled,
My View of the Wolf and reads as follows.
Wolf the dog always pops up in my mind
as a crusty Chester Cheeto version wolf
covered in a restaurant trash bag grease.
That is all.
Damn, that's fucking cold.
I'm not some Chester Cheeto looking ass.
I can maybe assure you of that.
Chester Cheeto wishes he could get close
to my beauty, my grace, my grease.
And a sopping wet illustration of supposedly yours truly
was provided by user, BlueBlairyBlob.
Is this what I truly look like?
Has anyone ever actually seen me?
Can the human vision orb even perceive me?
What do y'all think I even look like?
Draw them and show them to me
and show them to the internet.
I heard you people love this worldwide web net.
Sounds a little spooky to me.
If you want to write up something for your wolf to howl,
tag at pretending pod on the internet
and reveal your true self to your internet friends.
Or I guess do something rad on Reddit.
I'm not sure I'm allowed to ask this of you,
but it'd be oily as all get out to see recommendations
for wolf the dog in 694.2 crew on big old internet places
like broad RPG subreddits and niche Facebook groups
and freaky deaky discords.
Word of mouth is the word of the mouth.
Spread the word like Uzi Fogg and cover folks
and wolf the dog.
It feels good when you know you've locked
onto a really good new catchphrase.
I'd say that calls for the news.
Last time, the church doors creaked open
and a group of uniform school children
took on the steep incline to reach the top of the gorge
on the same side where Stevie and the rest of the can crew
were checking on the sopping wet fox godel.
When the party of prep schoolers got close enough,
Beck zoomed in and saw blood on their uniforms.
And also one kid walked on all fours
and one was a kangaroo that walked like a dude.
And the last weird one was a humanoid
with the face of a pug.
And that pug face student had a Jaguar on a leash
that eventually jumped toward a bright spotlight
onto the unnaturally smooth cliff face and to its death.
And the city action news field team shot a stunning
little clip with a horrifying background.
The gang in the school uniform stood there
unmoving across the rift.
Enough with the rift.
Let's hear a riff.
It's Alter Girl with My Life Is Great
and It's All My Fault.
And it's all my fault.
Luke just said he'd say it to your faces.
If you live in Australia, suck it.
Oh my God, that's not the message.
I know that is the, that's the message.
If you live on Australia, you can probably get it.
On Australia?
If you live on Australia, you drink Fosters
out of a ditry dude shaped like a boomerang, bitch.
Oh my God.
Anyway, buckle the fuck up.
We're about to kill a kangaroo.
Specifically because it's Australian.
Dog your Barbies.
Dog your Barbies, bitches.
You better dog your Barbies.
Cause these boys from the Ozarks
are coming from you, Australia.
Coming.
Coming from you.
We're coming from you.
We get where you're coming from,
but we're going to kill your kangaroo.
You guys already left.
We're coming back.
Just kill him.
I got one job on this earth left.
Is that from something?
And I got one thing to do right.
One thing before I can pass easy.
And that's make sure that pink group pass hard.
Julius always like, anytime he went to the zoo,
he would see the kangaroos and be like,
I can do that.
I'm totally better than that.
Julius is like, shit animal.
He would look down at his thighs and be like, so what?
What about your pouch?
That pissed him off.
Cause he didn't have one.
Damn.
So he starts wearing a fanny pack
and is immensely popular at a young age.
Pretending to marsupial.
Let's go.
Let's get 30 seconds of silence actually.
Let's kill this energy.
Agreed.
I was going to say kangaroo jack, crocodile Dundee,
a cry in the dark.
There was a crocodile person over there too.
That's my bad.
Wearing a school uniform.
No, I was just saying Australian movies.
Oh, yeah.
Are there any others?
Are there any?
The Sapphires?
No.
The proposition.
Ah, the proposal.
What's the big epic with Nicole Kidman?
Mad Max.
I mean, yeah, every Mad Max is an Australian movie.
I would watch a Nicole Kidman Mad Max reboot.
She's got, you know, just like bring me
to the theater energy these days.
I don't know what it is.
What was that movie, Joe?
The sheep fucker's daughter.
I think that was it.
Welcome to episode 17 of Pretending to Be Keep.
It looks like we're trending a number one improv podcast
in Australia now.
We were a number two.
Oh, is that Luxembourg?
Shout out to Luxembourg.
Shout out.
Luxembourgish fans, we have your back
unlike those fucking Australians.
No, I'm like, I want to go to Australia.
It seems so cool.
Oh fuck, the movie was called Australia.
Oh no.
Either no one's going to listen from now on
or they're going to want this every time.
It's going to be hard to do.
Listen next week to see if we pick your country.
Listen two weeks from now.
Oops.
Or give us money and it will be next week.
So everything's fine seemingly.
Yeah, everything's fine.
Well, we just wrapped our day of shooting.
We got that last little stinger there.
It's in the can.
And now we're in the can van.
Julius was showing Cal how to use TikTok.
What time is it?
I imagine cinematically it was like the sun was setting
as all that happened, right?
Hondo, pee.
Yeah, over those angry animal kids, people.
Are they like, are they grownups?
Oh, we're in like.
The kids are the animals.
There's six normal kids and then.
I think there is six kids standing up straight.
One extra bloody kid standing up straight who had a name.
One who still has a name technically.
We just, we didn't find it out though.
Exactly, you know, I'm just describing it as people, right?
I forgot to ask them their names.
Yeah, you gotta yell out.
Hey, Stevie, do you know any of those kids' names?
No.
And you guys saw that there was also the human
with the pug head.
That's the one I liked the least.
That's the one that we killed the pet of.
That is correct.
And then there was a kangaroo.
So you're not sure of the ages from either of them.
Yeah, the kid who was on the ground is a kid crawling.
Yeah, the kid on his knuckles dragging, that's a kid.
You've got the pug man.
That is a much taller creature, humanoid,
than the children.
And then kangaroo is kangaroo.
Fully kangaroo?
I would say.
Oh no, you said walking kind of human-like.
Walking almost up on its toes to walk more human-like.
I can't wait until Slide Whistle draws the pug man.
Oh.
Please?
Please.
And we're reviewing, we're seeing this on video
as we're driving back to the.
That's right, and you're driving on these roads.
So we got everything out of the lockers without a hitch.
I was a little worried that there would be something
in the lockers. I'm not gonna do that
to you, huh? Okay.
Everything that you brought, you grabbed.
You had enough time there.
You took the time to shoot a little segment, you know,
and nothing bad happened.
It was intimidating how they just stood there silently
for like 15 minutes while we shot our segment
and then packed up leisurely.
It felt very ominous.
We do need to make sure that Fox doesn't die.
Oh, I don't wanna touch that wet freak.
Do you guys have any zip ties or something like that?
We could do his hands.
Julius already got his shoes.
And you look down and see that his shoes are tied.
Together? Together.
Not just individually, nicely.
Way to tie, that was very kind of you, to tie God's shoes.
Together, in a tripping formation.
We definitely have zip ties in the can van.
Yeah. Like that supplies.
And you would like duct tape and everything.
Yeah, you guys are awful people.
Yeah, of course.
No. No, oh, right.
We're a film crew.
We have useful things.
And she throws on the zip ties behind the back of Fox Coddle
and he is still unconscious.
And she's like, I guess we should try
to make him comfortable that way he stays this way
as long as possible.
Stevie, I don't wanna get lost
in the weeds here theologically.
You know, have you ever heard about like,
could God microwave a burrito so hot
he himself could not eat it?
Oh, whoa.
If this is really God, can he just break some zip ties?
Is he constrained by the limits of his physical form?
Well, I have to assume he was a turtle for a reason.
How do we get him back into something like a turtle?
I think we gotta like kill him when he's around a turtle.
That's the mayor.
Oh yeah, we gotta like decree the turtle,
the new mayor, then kill him.
Do we have to kill him?
Maybe not, maybe just decreeing a new mayor
makes it like automatically transfer.
Let's try.
Okay, who am I gonna make the new mayor?
Let's think about this maybe a lot more.
Beck wants to be filming out the back window,
keeping an eye and make sure we're not being followed
out of the gates of the wall.
Oh, you just keep seeing these signs
that are like dead end, road stops here,
no outlet, please stop.
There's like some danger signs.
And you're on this road all by yourselves
and there's no streets that are like coming off
of these streets, do you know what I mean?
Do you know what I mean?
Julius wants to, not all of them at the same time
because the algorithm,
but upload at least one crazy TikTok.
Let's find out which TikTok.
You took a few while we were there.
Should we actually pause and like figure out what they were?
Okay, there was the at the very end,
the year dance before we got attacked by the Jaguar.
Sure.
When we were getting onto the train.
That's right.
Technically that includes the Jaguar attack.
He hits the window as you were filming,
so it's got all that.
Right, but then there's one of us.
That's what I was talking about.
Yeah, we got on the train before we got back off
to rescue Chuck.
So there's that one and I think that one includes us
doing funny walks, sneaking.
Yes, there is the good sneaking one across the plant wall.
And I assume it also has you pointing it right in my face
as I say turn that off and get on the fucking train.
That's in that one.
There's also the one where you're in the it pitch.
Yeah, with all the crazy symbols and stuff.
Yep, behind.
Previous to that.
I'm sure I got the Jack.
Did I get the Jackalope attack?
Yes, exactly.
That is the headline here.
Jackalope attack.
It totally got me, dude.
It snuck up on me with malicious intent.
It wasn't my fault.
Sometimes spin is morally justified.
Whoa.
That's heavy.
He's gonna do the Jackalope attack.
Whichever one you think.
You know more about this kid stuff than me.
Beck, is it okay if I show this?
I think that's like probably the best one
because in the end of it,
it's just a rabbit with horns tied onto it.
It gives a taste of the thing that is crazy,
but it's not the craziest.
Or do we show something crazier and tease it?
I'm sure that one was showing Grover's Gorge
and then, oh no, Jackalope attack.
Oh no, oh no.
Once we make the choice, we should have to roll to see.
That's the song that plays when he zooms in on my leg wounds.
Oh, perfect.
So now we need to do an algorithm roll
to see how well it favors us.
How well it favors us.
Is that audio being used?
Do you think this is a straight up luck roll?
Oh yeah, defo.
Luke had a giant landing pad of a dice rolling tray
and missed the tray.
Threw it behind his head.
It fell out of my hand as I shook it.
He threw it behind his head.
Well, it's a 92.
You know what that means.
Spend some luck.
Do you have luck?
So we can go viral?
Yeah, I'll spend luck so we can go viral.
What is your, no, what's your notification sound bite?
And also give me your luck coin.
There's my luck coin.
Flick it.
Nice.
So good.
What's the notification on the phone?
Yeah, what's the noise?
Obama saying, yes, we can.
What noise do you mean though?
Like that he received the notification noise?
I assume he means it's about to start blasting off.
Yeah, I was just gonna do a bunch of them over and over.
So I guess I'll drop that in here.
Yes, we can.
Si, se puede.
Thank you, Mr. President.
And we're back.
Your phone is just lighting up.
And so is Julius's face.
Cal.
Which he's picking at furiously.
When Cal hears Obama's voice,
he like legitimately gets a tear.
I miss that man.
And we're driving.
Hey, Stevie, like now we've seen this like transfer of God
or whatever twice.
And both times it was a thing.
Their eyes just get fucking huge when you say that.
Both times it was a thing leaping off of a thing.
Is that like part of it?
Without looking away,
you're looking in the rear view mirror at Stevie's face,
which is pointed directly at the road.
No flinching, no moving, just yeah, I,
They used to say that's how it would change bodies.
The original mayor, they were so scared
that he was gonna come back like he was
that they put a cage around his coffin.
Crumpy?
That's right, Jeremiah Crumpy.
And the story goes would,
and they kind of take their hand
and do the like under the chin,
throw the hand back and forth thing.
Throw their hand back and forth.
But it's like just that they kill themselves.
It's not necessarily that they leap off of something.
Yeah, a leap of faith as it were.
I have a theory on that, but I don't want to bring it up.
Here's the deal, like do we need to keep,
Hey Zach, do you call it the leap of faith in your notes?
Did I nail that?
I'm just wondering if we need to keep Fox away from ledges.
It's a little smile.
I mean, I think it's a good idea
to keep Fox away from ledges.
Or do we have to keep them away from like fucking everything?
I think that's the probably one that we should go with.
Like we're going to have to like,
what'd you say keep them in a cage?
Well.
I've got a basement in my townhouse.
You can't jump off of that.
Do the mayors have any like any idea what's going on
or are they basically zombies?
Well, the only one that I knew was Sandro and,
Rest in peace little guy.
Until Chuck and the only thing we,
what did you get out of Chuck?
It seemed like he was pretty much driven
to throw himself off that gorge.
I met Jeremiah Krumpy, but long after he was deceased.
What do you, what are you talking about Julius?
What is this Krumpy stuff?
He's buried behind Fox's house
and I tripped over his grave.
He was the original mayor.
Yeah.
They caged his grave site.
Yeah, I thought it was a bit odd,
but I thought maybe it was to keep kids off of it.
They used to do it for witches and vampires,
you know, in the fifties.
So, I mean, we got to keep him locked up.
Yeah, that's my biggest fear is that when he gets conscious,
he's just going to start like grabbing scissors
and poking them in his eye.
Yeah, that's, and she points at the zip ties.
Man, when we get back in Cal, Colorado's on Bumble
and trying to have a dinner date,
while God is in his basement trying to kill himself.
That's going to be great.
I think we're on to something.
Tell me about that basement.
Oh no, it's not finished.
Even better.
Yeah, I guess like no one will go down there.
Oh, I thought you were, we were on the date.
No, no, God will be quite comfortable in the basement,
I think.
We're calling him God, this is God.
We're saying this is God.
No, it's just, it's Greg.
Greg.
I mean, that's just Greg.
Gregle.
Gregertle.
Don't make it weird.
I mean, it can just be Greg
and hopefully we can get this thing, whatever it is out.
Sorry, sorry.
Wait, was Greg Fox's name?
Yeah, before he got God.
Once this footage is released,
I bet some authority would want to take him.
I'm all screwed up about like what's right and wrong here
at this point.
But if it is God, do you think we have like an obligation
to like keep that to ourselves
and like make sure that he doesn't do bad things or?
I understood it as not actual God,
but he did go to church.
Whatever it is, it seems to be a very dangerous
and powerful thing.
And I think you're right, Beck.
I don't know who we can trust with this shit.
I think we leave him out of the edit,
if you know what I mean.
And maybe don't mention he came back to town.
Yeah.
I guess like our first like thing would be to try
just like declaring like you have a pet goldfish
that we can say is the new mayor and just see if that works.
No, Goldie died several weeks ago.
Oh, Cal.
Maybe something that lives a lot longer than a goldfish,
like a rock.
I do have a pet rock somewhere.
Dude, can we make a rock God?
Could you make a rock so God that even God couldn't rock it?
I'll show you a rock God.
Whom?
Bon Jovi.
Thank you.
What'd you say?
We met our editor, Cole.
Oh, nice.
Here's what I propose.
We cut the story and get the word out to the world
about what they're doing there.
I don't think we should tell anyone we have Greg.
Agreed.
But everything else?
Everything else.
Yeah.
That's for Greg's safety, the world's safety
and our own safety.
We don't know who would wanna come for us.
Right now, it's those weird fucking kids
who know we have them.
Dude, when the world sees the footage, though,
like, we are going to change the world, yo.
This is the biggest story of the last 50 years.
I'm sorry, I forgot about 9-11.
Heh.
Moment of silence.
It's obviously not as big as 9-11.
You don't think this is a bigger deal than 9-11?
This could potentially be as big as 9-11.
Do you think season two will be as big as 9-11?
This podcast is bigger than the Beatles.
Moment of silence complete.
Okay, so like, yeah, the plan is get Greg, God,
Greg God into Cal's basement.
Okay.
We'll go to the pet store, find a turtle,
and we'll just see if that works.
And like, if that doesn't work, we're back to square one,
but at least we tried something.
We obviously do that after we show the news.
Oh yeah, and like that, and like change the world
in the process, yeah, of course.
So we're gonna go, like, take the footage
and drop it off first, and then take Greg?
As the producer, that's definitely what I say.
No, no, no, we need to get Greg in the basement,
but then Stevie and I could maybe take care of him
and you two can put the cut together.
I look over at Julius, are you still at like,
two hit points, are you still like, bloody as hell?
Yes, and I'm like, picking the skin that's on my face
is like, yanking at it and like, kind of stripping it off.
We also gotta give Julius to a goddamn hospital.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, Greg, Julius.
No, no, the news before me.
You didn't happen to pack one of those,
you know, magic, God'll heal things, did you?
Oh, I didn't even think about it.
That would have been so handy, aw.
Good thing I grabbed one.
We can always count on you, Beck.
95.
You failed your role, so I do have it,
is that what you meant?
Yeah.
That's the Zach Luck role that he failed.
I guess, I mean, I wanna see this cut
before I go to the news, but I mean,
we could get rid of God first.
Julius, can I see your hands for a second?
He holds his hands up.
I wrapped some gaffer tape around him, so you can't.
Whoa!
Take your last two hit points away
by picking at your face.
He's gonna try to fight that
just because he doesn't want it to happen,
but I think that's a good idea.
All right, let's see a little unarmed combat going on here.
Uh-oh.
I got a crit success.
Oh, damn.
Well, that's just a crit success to not get.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So as you like nimbly blasted away.
You kill Calcala.
You dodge and he's, I wanna try to persuade you
that this is a good idea.
I'm like, I understand, I understand,
I should have just come at you like that,
but I think we might need to get your hands
under control here for a second
before you poltergeist your own head.
Yeah.
You can roll if you want, but because you crit,
I'm gonna go ahead and say like,
you can just like tell him to fuck off if you want.
I'll roll my persuade, like it says to,
I got a 43 on a 60.
I got a 63 on a 70.
Ooh!
Oh, no, sorry, a 36.
Oh.
Boom.
What'd you roll?
A 43.
Better than that.
So I.
Whiplash!
Picking at his face.
Okay, yeah, so, okay, good talk, Julius.
He's picking at his face,
but then Julius is like in his notes on his phone,
like writing down thoughts on different ways to cut this.
The video.
The footage, yeah.
And his face off.
All right, I need you guys to, someone,
I need you to elect a rolling leader
who has a D8 closest to them.
Luke, Luke is gonna roll the D8.
To see how many eighths of gas are in this gas tank.
More like eighths of something else,
you know what I mean?
Weed.
Eight.
Hell yeah.
Full tank.
They filled it up while we parked.
Compliments of Grover's Gulch.
Yeah, come back and see us.
You're only a few hours away.
It's about as full as a tank could possibly be
after driving this distance.
We stopped at a gas station right before we pulled off.
The same gas station is approaching on your right
and it is the first building
that you really see on this side of civilization.
You seem to be coming back onto a road
that might be used for more
than just heading out to this location.
And as you come up to this gas station,
you see that there are three black SUVs.
No, that's not fun.
There are three pink SUVs.
Now that's fun.
Spaceships.
Camels.
Kangaroos.
Helicopters.
There are three green.
Roombas.
Range Rovers.
Like bright green Range Rovers.
And they are all parked in a line at three pumps.
It's probably nothing to worry about.
Simultaneously the doors open
and men wearing monochromatic gray scale suits
with a green accent being their tie and their,
what's the thing that goes in your pocket?
Pocket square.
And their green pocket square and their green tie
get out and begin pumping gas.
What's the matter, Stevie?
That's jolly green jottles.
Golly, dream goggles.
Jolly green jottles.
I just, that, yeah, that's them.
I guess just keep your heads forward and don't.
Everybody act casual.
Julius, pretend to do a TikTok.
Julius is like writing notes on his thoughts on the edit.
That looks like a TikTok.
He just like does a little dance.
As far as Kal knows, you're doing a TikTok.
Great job, great job.
Great job.
You totally looped that roll.
And as you continue to drive,
as you're almost past this gas station,
you see one of the side doors opens from the back
of one of these green Range Rovers and out steps.
Fred Godel.
He was on his way back.
I forgot.
Oh, shit.
We knew that.
And he squints as he looks at the can van
driving back toward the city.
You guys are back in the can van, heading down the road.
You're back in the normal world.
So you're seeing homes, you're seeing normal signs.
Please stop and interview him.
Julius says, looking like,
he says it as a statement, but it's really as a question.
No, no.
No, Julius, we will die if we talk to that man.
We've also got his daughter with us right now.
And his son.
Son.
Whoa.
Let's not forget, we also have the mayor of his town.
Shit.
And?
Oh, I'm not going back.
She's driving.
Yeah, she's like, fuck that, Julius.
I'm not doing that shit.
He knew that was the correct answer, but he had to ask.
Do you think he saw you, Stevie?
She's just like frozen this whole time
in the rear view mirror, just staring.
Oh shit, Stevie, jackalope.
Ugh.
And you see a rabbit with a stick
like kind of like stuck to it almost.
Like it's.
Like some burrs.
Yeah, it kind of got caught up.
At the end of a twig.
Yeah.
Stevie, what?
She smashes it.
Oh, that poor little jackalope.
Stevie, what were the circumstances
of you leaving Grower's Gorge?
Still driving, still working in the rear view mirror.
Who's hitting shotgun?
Probably Cal.
I figured we were all in the back like figuring shit out.
Yeah, that's good.
Looking at footage and tying up Fox.
Beck is getting a shot
of whatever Stevie's response is gonna be.
Yeah, no, I saw.
You know that moment when you find out
that maybe your parents aren't good?
I don't know if you've ever had that.
Yes.
So that's a weird feeling.
And when I kind of saw what I had tied my life to,
what I was born into, I couldn't hang.
So I'd been talking to Susan.
Susan's the judge.
Susan Bloom, Judge Bloom.
And then Susan was helping.
I mean, we were trying to help, but.
Help how?
Well, I mean, you saw the it pit.
You know, we were trying to save the new visitors.
So sometimes people would just kind of appear
and it wasn't just people.
It was like all sorts of things and creatures
like we saw back there.
And we were trying to help them because what would I mean?
Vernon would take them and put them in the it pit
because that's what Fred needed.
And we didn't really see them again after that.
Because Fred needed them to be quiet
or because he needed them to die in the it pit?
I think he needed something from them.
I don't know exactly what,
but we found animal ears down there also.
Now that we've seen animal people,
it was like transforming them?
No, I mean, they were showing up like all sorts of things.
Oh, they were starting animal-ly.
Yeah, they were just popping into Grover's Gorge.
We started getting the visitors
and I mean, I got out of there quick.
Susan and I tried to do what we could,
but it wasn't too long after that.
And their eyes just kind of fade away
and you see it's something cut deep enough
to leave everything they knew behind.
And she just can't bring herself.
She, despite of all that, let you go to the it pit.
She knew that if she said anything,
she'd be in their same position.
I understand.
Stevie, we are not our families.
We can move beyond that and become our own people.
I did.
Or tried.
So why'd you go back with us?
We got what we needed.
Hell yeah, we did.
Let's shut them down.
That's the spirit of a real can news intern.
Let's show the world what they're doing.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
Through the transformative power of journalism.
I'm sleepy.
And he's like closing his eyes.
Yeah.
Julius, dude, stay with me, dude.
Stay with me, dude.
He shakes his head back awake
like he's trying to keep his eyes open.
Maybe we should drop him at a hospital.
No, no.
The way they do in the movies where they just
throw you in front of the emergency room.
Julius, I hate to tell you this.
I think Stevie's gonna have to help Beck with the cut.
You're still my super producer.
He half forcing himself to stay awake
is continuing to write his thoughts down in his notes.
The camera peeps over your shoulder
and it's just like the same letter over and over again.
It's Z, yeah.
Text, try to text what you have to Stevie.
He hits Z again on his keyboard.
Okay, I don't feel very good.
I know, little guy.
Little guy with the big thighs, eh?
We're gonna take care of you, right?
Stevie, can we go to a doctor or something?
We could get to a hospital.
Is that, and she's like kinda eyeing Greg?
Well, here's what we could do.
We could either drop him off at a hospital
or you can leave him and Greg in my basement.
I'll watch him while you and Beck make the cut.
Luke's face.
Why would you drop me off in the basement?
Well, it's whether you wanna go to a hospital or not.
I mean, Julius doesn't wanna go to the hospital.
What does Luke want?
I don't know what Luke wants.
These are just, these are the options.
Luke's along for the ride.
What does Julius want?
I'm playing the character.
Julius wants to go cut this shit together.
Fuck yeah.
He's got two hit points left, so.
You look such a mess.
It's so funny.
Like you are trying to hold on by a thread at this point
and it's still a fair amount of car ride left.
Okay, why don't you,
we'll get God situated in the basement and.
And I'll go help cut the news together.
Yeah, you'll show Stevie the ropes.
And maybe we'll call an ambulance.
Maybe we'll call an ambulance.
Yeah, yeah, man.
Roll Constitution to see if you can actually stay awake
all the way into town.
An eight on a 50.
An eight on a 50's gonna keep you.
The prospect of not being able to cut this together,
adrenaline pumps through his veins.
And the consistent rings of yes we can.
Yes, exactly.
Yes we can.
Dopamine fills his brain every time he hears that.
I can do it.
I can.
I can keep it together.
All right, as we roll into the city,
what's the first stop?
And also I'm gonna go pee again.
Sorry I drank so much liquid.
What is the first stop?
We haven't really hammered out
what our order of operations here.
I mean, Julius is gonna say the news tower or whatever.
I'm a little nervous.
I think Beck would be nervous too
about leaving Godel unconscious in the van.
That he could pop up at any moment.
I don't know if I can deal with God alone.
So Stevie can handle the cut if he passes out
or goes to the emergency room or something like that, right?
Can you stay here in the basement with me and watch God?
I mean, yeah, but like I know what all the footage is.
Like that's kind of my whole thing
is to like tell him the edit.
I mean.
Let's just bring him with us.
That is such a bad idea.
Julius nods his head.
Why don't we just lock him in your basement
and then go do the cut?
Julius nods his head.
I mean, someone has to stay with him.
I guess that'll be me.
I don't know about that, dude.
Like you said, it's God.
Like if he does wake up, what are you gonna do?
Well, that's why I asked one of you to stay with me
but you all wanna be a part of this fucking cut.
So I don't know.
Is the cut more important
than keeping God trapped in my basement?
I don't know, Beck, but.
That's my point though.
It's like, what are two people versus God?
Like what if we all leave and go get a turtle
on our way back from cutting the film footage?
Julius nods his head.
I don't know Beck,
but I don't think we can just leave him alone.
I mean, I'm gonna stay with Greg.
Especially since Julius is seemingly staying.
This is not a huge deal,
but just would you not use the upstairs bathroom
while you're there?
Is there a-
There's a downstairs bathroom.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, no, as long as there's another one.
And I don't mean on the main floor.
If you do need to go up there for any reason
to use the kitchen or anything,
I just mean the one upstairs.
There's just still some of,
there's just still,
there's some things my wife left
that I haven't really touched.
Wait, hold on.
Why'd you say, oh, that's horrifying.
Did she poop in your toilet?
Oh, if that's what you mean,
I take back the awe.
No, I think it's the way that it's messily arranged,
the way that she would have it.
So that got her hairbrush out and-
Yeah, that's what I meant too.
And she had smeared all of the walls.
No, there were, yes,
the hairbrush,
the tooth brace,
which she never closed,
some toiletries,
and of course a bowl of shit.
Please, whatever you do,
do not flush the upstairs toilet.
I just can't bring myself to flush it.
Am I the only one who thought that?
I think so.
Yeah, okay.
That's fine.
If Taylor dies,
I'm throwing all of her stuff away immediately.
In the secret house you two share together?
No, that was me as Zach.
I knew it.
Whoa.
I got that.
You were pretending to be a person?
Was that the world's fastest no back button?
So we'll get you guys all secured in my basement
and hopefully you and Greg will be fine there.
And then we'll go edit this cut together
like a news crew should.
And bring back a turtle.
And bring back a new god turtle.
Okay, sick.
So let's hear about the outside of Cal Colorado's house.
What are we pulling up to?
What's the vibe?
Oh, I mean, nice ass neighborhood.
Stately like early 20th century or late 1800s
like townhouses.
Some of them are brick.
His is painted white.
It's probably like three stories maybe.
Whoa.
And you know, it's narrow, right?
It's in the middle of the city.
And yeah, I don't know what time of year it is
but it seems like it's fall there.
It's like nice.
But it seems like it's fall.
It's like June 18th or somewhere around there.
Specifically July something.
We did start in June.
I have June 18th written down.
Today is July 5th.
Oh, okay, yeah.
So there's all these 4th of July banners and stuff.
Cal has a big American flag outside the front.
Nice.
And yeah, you see a neat little,
like a couple of like garden, whoops.
What the hell's happening?
It's the helicopter landing at the hospital.
Helicopter.
Cal says, don't worry.
That's just the helicopter landing at the hospital nearby.
Thank God it's closed.
Yeah.
So there's some nice little like window planners and shit.
Julius, I could just like run you over there
while they get situated.
That's true.
We have time.
This isn't, I mean, it was sunset when we left.
It's been a few hours.
This is not going on tonight's news.
We have all day to cut this thing.
We could definitely get you some medical attention.
That's right, yeah.
It's like 11, 1130 p.m. now at this point.
Maybe that is the order of operations now.
Yeah, it's, oh my God, it's too,
how did we not realize it's too late to go on the news?
Because it's been a pretty discombobulating day of a day,
has it not?
Julius texts his uncle to see
if his health insurance has kicked in yet.
Yeah.
Commentary.
That is a great question.
Sax, oh, Sax consulting the fucking can.
Who has insurance or nothing.
I had to check.
It's like I made a full HR department for these guys.
It's part of my world building process.
Extensive employee records.
It's like, oh, nope, sorry Julius.
That doesn't kick in until the end of the month.
Oh, City Action News,
they actually don't provide healthcare coverage.
Not to junior producers.
Then call the chopper.
Call the chopper.
No, again, it is just several blocks away.
And we're in the driveway of this beautiful brick
three-story town home.
We didn't want to leave God alone in the van.
Can we leave Julius alone in the van for a second
while we unload or?
I'll help.
What if you just sit right there for a moment?
Keep writing your notes.
Oh yeah.
So I imagine we just kind of all like take them in
and get them situated.
There's probably a nice like couch and like sofa and shit.
Julius flops down on there and continues writing his notes.
I didn't think you came down to the basement with us.
I was like blindly following behind
while I typed in my notes.
Oh, we were saying stay in the van.
Yeah, no, he's following blindly behind you.
I'm just trying to get us out of here quick, dude.
He's following you guys.
Don't you want to go to the fucking hospital?
Who's holding Fox?
How do we get there?
That's what I was saying.
I like, I imagine.
Cal and Stevie.
Yeah, exactly.
So he is still absolutely drenched.
Yeah.
Sopping, making puddles everywhere
that you're pulling him.
Cal, like you can see this place is clean
and Cal like visibly winces.
And he's like, do you guys have this?
Do you guys, do you guys got this?
I need to mop some of this up.
I'll put some tea on.
And as soon as Cal steps away and says,
You see the face of Fox,
Godel, Greg Godel, God Godel,
slowly start to twitch.
I punch him.
Roll initiative with God.
Okay, so you're just gonna roll damage
cause you're right there.
What's a fist punch?
It's a D four minus one.
Oh shit.
One minus one.
I rolled a one minus one.
You wake him up like fully.
Stevie's looking at me like, what the fuck dude?
I'm sorry, I thought I would like knock him out again.
Immediately his mouth is just foaming
and like this almost sea foam is pouring out of it.
And it smells and you think that you might actually
as the sea foam is like pouring up out
and coming out of his mouth and he's fighting.
I need a first a grip check
for this coming out of fucking nowhere.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Cal fails.
Fail.
Beck passes.
Pass.
Crit fail.
I imagine we're like on the stairwell
going down into the basement.
Yeah.
Okay, so Cal who has like been turning around fully
just like scrambles backwards up the stairs
and runs into the like into his kitchen.
But right before you do,
Joe takes off his headphones and Joe you lose zero grip.
However, the other two headphones off sir, thank you.
Julius wasn't looking until Beck yelled,
I'm gonna punch him.
So this is Joe's fault.
You're gonna lose Cal one D four plus one,
which with the crit fail means that Julius
automatically loses five grip.
I see my breaking point.
We got a breaking point
and you lose two grip Cal as the both of you see
is that fingertips reaching out through the top
by a little Stevie wonder of the sea foam at the mouth
and like maybe a finger trying to grip at the lip
and then suddenly it's gone and you just see the water
and then it's just foaming at the mouth
and there are multiple hands, multiple fingers
reaching up through the foam, trying to get out.
He closes his mouth shut tight and continues to wriggle.
I'm gonna burn Joe back.
I didn't hit my bringing point, I almost did though.
I did math wrong.
That makes sense
cause you already hit your breaking point.
Yeah, I'm two away though.
But you did lose five grip.
So Luke, I need a fight flight freeze.
I'll go top in that order flight flight freeze.
And freeze is a one.
Five.
What is that?
That's fight.
The top answer?
So what do you do?
Punch him in the nose.
Julius thinks he's this guy has to shut his mouth
and he's gonna just like go
and like put his hand over his mouth and nose.
Oh my God, okay.
You do so.
Roll unarmed combat
and he's gonna roll at a massive disadvantage
because his arms are behind his back with his wrists tied.
Not all of them.
He had a 41 on a 60.
And with the success,
Julius Summers has his hands over the mouth
and nose of Greg Gottel.
Cal was thinking something very, very similar
as he was running up those stairs.
And so he's trying to grab some duct tape
from his utility drawer in the kitchen
cause this seems untenable.
Julius, Julius, be careful.
Like don't kill him.
Like just make sure he passes out,
but then you gotta stop.
Make sure that mouth stays shut.
Help him.
Julius nods.
What are you doing back?
What am I seeing?
You are seeing Julius like plugging the nose
and mouth of this dude.
Stevie grabs and is like,
not the nose, not the nose, just the mouth.
He's not budging.
Nope.
She can't stop him.
I put my hands over both of Julius's hands
and my goal is to, when I feel Gottel passing out,
I wanna pull him away.
We can't kill him, Julius.
We can't kill him.
If we kill him, that God thing will pop into one of us
and then we're fucked.
Don't kill him, Julius.
I'll be right there.
Julius nods.
Okay, let's get a human role here
from Beck Wilder to see if you can feel
or you can go for one of the like first aid type roles
if you have that.
I'm gonna take the human.
Okay.
I pass.
12 on a 40 human.
Okay, so as Cal Colorado comes running back down the stairs
with duct tape and Stevie is trying to like push
at the arms and hands of Julius Summers,
you feel on the arms of Julius
the kind of release of consciousness from Greg Gottel.
And she's like, that's super bad for you.
What are you doing?
We got to, it's not as bad as like death though.
It's okay.
And I'm trying to pull.
Cal's got a big thing of duct tape stripped out
and he's like, okay, okay.
Real quick, Julius, move your hands.
I'm gonna tape them.
One, two.
And I started rapping and rapping and rapping.
Yo, yo, yo, my name is Cal.
My name is Cal Colorado and I'm here to say
that you're gonna wrap your mouth in a serious way.
All right, you've got duct tape all around the mouth
and jaw and neck of Greg Gottel and he is unconscious.
And Stevie is like, let's at least like, you know,
make him comfortable again.
Can we please like, this is.
And you see like she's pleading with you.
Yeah, no, of course.
Let's get him to the couch downstairs.
I just want to apologize that I hit your God brother.
No, it's, it was just a reflex like he was waking up.
Sorry, your mayor brother.
Your mayor God brother.
Your brother.
Your little mayor God brother.
She's just staring at the ground.
Looks up at both of you.
It's fine.
Let's get him secured down here.
How?
Yeah, I don't know.
Sit on him.
You've got that duct tape.
Could we like, is there like a something sturdy down here?
We could just duct tape, duct tape.
I've got some tie downs.
I've got some tie down straps and in the utility closet,
I could, we can, we can strap them to this couch.
Yeah, let's do it.
Julie's is just kind of staring off.
Okay, let's be gentle.
And Stevie is helping you use all of this roll of duct tape.
Yeah.
And all these straps and you use the rest of the roll
of duct tape to secure the.
I don't think we need the duct tape that
she wants comfort, right?
It's, I just.
As they're like putting on more and more duct tape
staring at you as you're like, I'm not sure about that.
They're like, but if they get out, they want the comfort,
but Stevie is very worried about what happens if.
Yeah.
Yeah, understandable.
So I am gonna crank these straps kind of hard
and he starts ratcheting down.
I gotta go.
She just gonna walk upstairs.
Like this is becoming a lot.
Yeah, yeah.
Could you, could you check on the T?
Yes, absolutely.
Anyone else?
All right, I'll take your silence as a no T answer.
But everyone is just dazed as, it's been a long.
Stevie ratchet also.
Stevie in the front right door of the fridge.
There's some energy drink, the kind you like Beck.
Sorry, the cat is making it sound like
I'm touching my mic stand.
It's not me, it's the cat.
So we've got him ratcheted down.
The cat touched my mic stand.
I swear it wasn't me dude.
If he's ratcheted down Beck would happily go upstairs
to grab an energy drink.
You said you liked it that time you came to my house
three and a half years ago.
So I keep some around now.
Oh dude, thanks.
Is it three and a half years old or?
No, no, I replace them every six months.
Oh dude, Cal.
That's so thoughtful of you, man.
You're a great camera man.
Oh, thanks Cal.
You're a great anchor.
Thank you, I will be again.
Dude, you're gonna be like the anchor
after this story gets out.
This is like 9-11, isn't it?
Okay, so I'm picturing.
Julius hears the word story and perks up.
I was picturing this whole time.
They're having this conversation in the kitchen
and Julius is just standing at the top of the stairs
out of view from them listening
and just picking at his face.
Oh God.
In the darkness of the basement stairwell.
One hand typing barely legible notes
on what is gonna go into the edit
and the other just peeling skin.
You do hear at that moment.
Julius, what do you like to drink?
Energy drink.
There's a whole six pack.
Would you like some?
He kind of wanders over there, still doing both things.
And now that you have Greg Godel secured in the basement
and the four of you are sharing caffeine in the kitchen.
Let's call that ambulance, huh?
It's close enough.
Yeah, let's just walk with our tea and energy drinks.
It's a nice day.
I don't have insurance.
It is nice being back in the city.
Where everyone knows your name.
Julius sniffs as in like, it's nice to smell the air again.
Does he smell regular air or is it?
It is exactly what you think it smells like.
Uh-oh.
Or that could mean, I don't know what that means.
I don't know what that means.
What do you think it smells like?
It's why I asked, I don't know.
Yeah, it smells like that.
Okay, he's happily walking to the hospital,
peeling his skin and losing blood.
No, we're, as you like you walk out the front door
and just start strolling down there
and we're like, we grab you by the shoulders
and we're like, no, no, no, no, get in the can van,
get in the can van.
Come on, we're driving you.
He allows it.
Do I stay here?
Is that okay or?
Yeah, Stevie, you stay here.
We're gonna get him some medical attention
and then as soon as they've got them checked up,
I think we're pulling an all-nighter down at the station.
Okay, all right, well, you have my number, so.
Of course.
If anything happens there, let me know.
No can intern.
I'll let you know if anything happens on my end, obviously.
You know your number one job here, right?
Don't let Greg kill himself.
Right, yes, obvious, I mean, yeah.
Stevie, if I had more time,
I would help you move my collection of antique steak knives
out of the basement, but we've really got to get,
really got to get out of here and get him to the hospital
and then get this thing cut.
I think you can handle that, right?
Hard cut to the steak knife collection in the basement
and swift cut back to you guys waving goodbye.
Here's a glass case full of like all these blocks of knives.
Full fucking wooden sets.
But there is a thing that says, do not touch on us.
Oh, that might help.
There you go.
That might help.
Okay.
I feel so much better, Julius says,
after spending some time in the hospital.
I'm glad, says Cal, Colorado,
after sitting in the waiting room playing with TikTok.
I need you to stay overnight, says the nurse.
Oh.
Julius winks and agrees.
All right.
Guess it's you and me on the edit, Beck.
And the two of you.
Like we're standing by his hospital bed while she says this?
Yeah.
Or like in the emergency room,
they just got him in the hallway on a bed.
Like ma'am, there is some news tonight.
Do you happen to recognize me?
Cal, Colorado city action news.
And I wink.
49.
So yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, oh yeah.
Call Colorado.
Um, well, as you know, the news never sleeps.
Of course not.
But this man needs to,
his face is broken in like multiple places.
We need to do CAT scans.
We need to do X-rays.
We need to draw blood.
Sounds expensive.
Let's just give me a Tylenol.
Or, you know, something stronger.
Anything that can.
Let's just get him back on his feet for now.
And then like we can bring him back.
We'll bring him back in the morning.
Right, yes.
I'll be back for sure.
1 p.m. at the latest.
She starts laughing.
She's like, I gotta be honest with you.
I'm not sure if legally I'm allowed to let him leave.
No, that makes a lot of sense.
I'm not sure if you're legally allowed to make me stay.
Okay, that's scary and fine.
Why did you come here?
For something quick.
It's the hospital.
If you want something quick, go to Walgreens.
You got better stuff than Walgreens?
Yeah, but we're gonna need to book you overnight
to put fluids in you.
This is Cal, Colorado.
If you could just help us out.
We will have him back in the morning.
But he refuses to not be a part of the news.
We're just asking, you can clean up his cuts
and make sure that.
I wanna try a persuade role on him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And go ahead and assist.
You can add a plus 20, the two of you, if you succeed.
Yep, success.
So plus 20.
Oh, and he already succeeded.
I passed my persuade.
Oh.
A 46 on a 50.
That plus 40, which puts me over, and I fail.
Oh.
We are way too convinced.
The dice work in the worst way ever.
What a shame.
She's like, uh, yeah, whatever you guys want.
And you're all like, he should stay here.
Oh.
Those are pain pills, you're putting them in pain.
Yeah, I can do like a steroid shot.
I can give you half a D6, I guess,
if you're not gonna stay overnight.
Half a D6 plus one.
Not a chance.
Wink.
Half of three is two.
So yeah, you go up from two hit points to four hit points,
which is quite substantial.
Plenty of hit points.
Well then unfortunately we do get to the point
where we're looking at you only two hit points better,
and we're like, maybe you should stay.
I thought you would be better.
It's just the fact that a couple of the cuts
have now been like pushed together with a bandaid,
like the kind of butterfly kind of holding
the pieces together.
And then currently you've got fluids going into you,
and you've also, they're gonna do blood work.
No they're not, he gets up.
Okay.
And I take these two a day, twice a day.
You know, your nurse always gives you your medicine.
I'll be back tomorrow.
It's just a little something something
from our personal stash.
You all succeeded on your persuade checks.
She's like, okay, here's some of the good stuff.
And?
Two a day, twice a day keeps the demons away.
Again, like I said, we'll be back 1 p.m.
two at the latest.
To get him, you know, the full treatment.
Maybe like 24 hours from now,
if he does want to stay up till nine to watch his segment.
I don't know.
We'll see, but.
I can watch the segment from the hospital.
That's remarkably mature of you.
Let's fucking go.
Vroom vroom, the can-van speeds.
As you're heading out down the hallway,
you hear a man hiccup and shit his pants at the same time.
Julia says, hm, cucumbers?
That could be a story.
Camera goes right back to the vroom vroom of the can-van
as you head back down to the city action news HQ.
We see the columns, we see the glass,
we see the beautiful moss, we saw the landscaping,
we see the marble-less floor as you enter.
I miss that marble.
It's the three of you, rolling in, ready to go,
as you hit the edit bay.
We are rolling Julius in in a hospital wheelchair.
Oh, nice, wheelchair to go.
We bump the doors open with his legs.
As Julius is- Roll a date for it?
As Julius is-
I run.
As Julius is wheeled in, he's thinking,
but he says it out loud.
He's like, I'll be Raylan now.
Raylan?
It's your-
That's my family's name,
but they've always considered me not a Raylan.
Julius, remember what I was telling Stevie.
You don't have to be your family.
You can be your own man.
A newsman.
Julius nods.
After what we've been through,
I definitely feel closer to you guys.
I mean, yeah, that was the craziest thing
that's ever happened in my life.
That was the third craziest thing
Let's show the people.
Wait, what, Cal?
Vivica pops out of the editing bay
and is like doing a big stretch of her shoulders
and then pops her knuckles.
And she's like, oh, hey guys, sorry.
I'm actually heading out for the night pretty beat,
but do you want me to take care of anything
for you guys before I go?
Or are you good to go?
Do we need her help on this
or do we know what we're doing?
I think Beck would know enough.
He's not an editor,
but he would know enough about how to edit.
Like he normally does want Vivica there to do the editing.
Sure.
But I think, I look at Cal and Julius,
I think maybe we should handle this one
or do you want like a professional
set of eyes on this? She gives you
an inquisitive look.
She's like, what do you mean?
Is it anything like super intense?
Vivica, how did you get your job here?
Oh, that is a big question.
Yeah, no, I went to school, applied, intern,
got the job, kept moving up, started getting paid,
get health insurance next year.
Have you ever, oh, yes.
So you're what, 10 years in?
Yeah.
Have you ever worked for the Godel company?
No.
You might want to see this.
Okay, yeah.
I mean, if you've got some juicy goss,
I'll get the tea brewing.
Vivica, do you want to edit the biggest news story
since 9-11?
She gives you just like the biggest eyes,
kind of brows waggling about.
I bet you would, but we have to do this one on our own.
Oh, you can't just leave me hanging like that, what?
Vivica, I forgot.
There's something that you can't know about
that's in this footage.
That is actually what I forgot.
She can't know about the God shit.
Fuck you guys.
And she grabs the door and heads back into the editing bay.
She goes back into the editing bay.
She's like, I'm going to edit this.
If you guys are going to be weird about it,
I want to see.
Oh, how do we decide if we can trust her?
Guys, Vivica is like one of my best friend,
coworker friends here.
She's always had my back.
And I mean, obviously she's never seen anything like this,
but-
Is she like religious?
I don't think so.
They're like looking in through the glass door
that's kind of tinted at her.
And she's like bringing the computer back up.
She's getting the programs going, yeah.
And she's good at what she does.
I mean, we're going to have a good looking piece
if she's ever fingerprints on it.
Julius was thinking about like us editing it
versus the quality of having her help us.
And it's gotta be-
It's a charming amateurism versus...
It might be the individual life,
but it will be a greatly edited segment, right?
Here's the deal though, guys.
I could just like, I think I should just like
not give her the time codes for the stuff with Fox.
Perfect.
If you can pre-scan the footage and yeah.
Yeah.
So that's in the earlier episodes,
that's one of Beck's things is that he has like an eidetic,
is an eidetic memory of like the footage that he has
where it is on the,
he knows of the timestamps of everything you shot.
So he just won't give her those timestamps.
Who was making that crazy noise?
That was me.
I had a bunch of spit in my mouth from burping a bunch
and I had to swallow it.
We have got to get Luke to a hospital, guys.
Hey, you know what I love about our podcast
and what I don't understand about fucking NPR?
Oh no.
Is the, is there liberal nonsense?
No, they obviously have gone for a certain fidelity
in their mics that picks up every bit of moisture
in your mouth or lack thereof and everybody is just like,
it's so hard to listen to sometimes.
It's me hard to listen to.
Yeah, I get hard listening to it sometimes.
That's why NPR stands for National Boner Radio.
What?
NPR.
NPR, National Boner Radio,
that would be a good shock shock.
You're listening to NPR with penis in the clit.
I'm the clit.
All right, Vivica, let's edit this thing.
We've got a long night ahead of us.
I bet.
I'll be right back.
Would you all like some coffee?
Yes.
Cal, you follow, like the camera follows Cal
to the little office kitchen
and he makes everybody some coffee.
He knows how many creams Beck takes or doesn't.
He grabs a handful of creamers and sugar
for everybody else who he doesn't know
and he stops by his office
and he pours a hefty belt of whiskey into his.
In the editing bay, Beck cracks his knuckles
and he says, okay, first it's like a,
there's a jackalip that I fall on.
You can, there's footage of that
at four minutes and three seconds.
And then there's also the time
when the god turtle fell off the stool
and that's at seven minutes and eight seconds.
Oh, and there's also the machine that heals people.
That's at three minutes and five seconds in
and he's running down the list.
Julius is looking at his notes
and it's just Z a bunch of times
that he's like, he puts his phone down
and he's just like helping rattle off
other things that happened.
The children who look like animals
but are also humans, that's it.
Go ahead and roll.
Did she crit fail a grip roll?
Yep.
We're fucking dumb.
We should have kicked her out.
That's an 88 on the grip roll.
God.
Vivica, are you with me?
You see Vivica just staring blankly at the monitors.
We may have made a mistake
onboarding Vivica to this project.
I kind of forgot that this stuff is psyche damaging.
Welcome to Godal's gorge.
Yeah, Vivica.
["My life is great and it's all my fault"]