Well, well, well.
Hello all my beautiful babies.
It's your spectral guardian, Wolf the Dog,
the DJ at the radio station known as 694.2 PTBP.
Let's not dilly-dally and go ahead and jump
into everyone's favorite part of the show.
This week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Sam Witch,
who tweeted about the show and tagged that pretending pod,
A thing you should do, lest your blessed internet guests
guess that your zest for ingesting my jests
has been wrested from your chest.
But I digress.
Sam Witch writes,
Wolf the Dog, I have followed every instruction
you've given to the letterer every week,
telling those that would be to my left and to my right
to keep the radio dial tuned to 694.2 PTBP,
despite there being none other than me
in this near featureless void.
You, Wolf the Dog, are the only exception
to the otherwise unending monotony.
Thus to you I plead, please, Wolf the Dog,
be my lifeline back to the extensive library
that led me here with its yellowed pages
and please be quiet signs.
No, that's okay, Sam Witch.
I don't think I have time to do
whatever it is you just asked me to do,
but have fun whenever and wherever you are.
Ta-ta for now.
If you want to write up something for your wolf to howl,
come on, say it with me in your brain space.
Tag at pretending pod on Twitter or Instagram
and tag pretending to be people on Facebook
or write up a five star review
on the podcast app of your choice
and make sure the proof comes across my desk.
Oh, and by the way, I heard what y'all did.
I heard y'all raised almost 800 bucks
and I heard those nasty boys
from pretending to be people rounded up, matched it
and sent a total of $1,600
to the crisis cold weather shelter
in their hometown of Springfield, Missouri.
Damn y'all, what a good job y'all did.
My producer's eye caverns have filled with salty water
because of the good y'all helped us spread
and no matter what kind of water fills your holes,
there's always the news.
Last time, Cal reached out to his contact
in the city PD, Chief McMillan,
to find out more information about the un-uniformed gobs
that stole footage from Vivica at the Cannes station.
The two officers showed up in CPD cruiser number 836
and Chief Mac used cop net to identify them
as officer Richard Riley and officer Wilson Wiley.
Tithe Rayland texted his employee and nephew,
Julius Summers and asked him to come back
to the Cannes station soon to meet in Tithe's office
and to bring Beck and Cal.
After a quick stop at Riley and Wiley's local drinking hole,
which is of course called W-A-R-E-R-We,
we're at Bucky's Kids Bar, duh,
the Cannes crew was able to bribe the night manager
for Riley and Wiley's addresses.
But at that same moment, Tithe texted again,
more impatient this time,
requesting the team's presence in his office.
Speaking of presence, here's a true gift,
a brand new tune, just for you my favorite listener,
my widdle baby.
Shh, don't tell anyone else now,
it's Alter Girl with My Life is Great and It's All My Fault.
And it's all my fault
Cause my life is great
And it's all mine
And it's all my fault
Hey Luke, who was your favorite teacher?
My favorite teacher, probably Jesus.
Joe, write that down.
Jesus?
My first pet named after my favorite teacher.
Jesus, Jesus, okay.
The street you grew up on?
Uh, oh crap, I was trying to think of like a-
Golgotha, Jesus.
I don't know enough about the Bible to have made a joke.
That's the hill that he was crucified on.
That's the hill he died on.
And he stayed dead.
Dude, I was laughing the other day.
Actually, there's some debate on that last point.
I saw somebody be like, I saw somebody online be like,
I was online, somebody was like,
so wait, he came back from the dead,
so he didn't die for our sins,
he like took a weekend off for our sins.
I'm not really familiar with the text, but he's like-
He died, he went to hell.
I don't ask me why he went to hell.
He stole the gates.
No, not the gates, that would be too much.
He stole the keys to the gates of hell.
It would be too much for him to carry.
Far too much.
Luke, this doesn't sound made up, hear him out.
So he goes to hell.
It does sound like a set up for a joke.
Okay, so Jesus dies, he goes to hell.
He steals the keys, not the gates.
It sounds like a good-ass comic book.
I get why all those people tried to turn the Bible
into a comic.
Yeah, from hell.
Yeah, Alan Moore's adaptation.
I want that-
Wait, so did Jesus really go to hell?
There are many eye witnesses to-
There are many sex knights of Christianity
who do believe that Jesus went to hell and stole the keys.
And so they just made that up and they say it
and that's what they believe.
So you worship a thief?
Wow.
I believe they say multiple times that Jesus will come back
like a thief in the night for his followers.
I want that shirt that says,
if Jesus comes back, we'll kill him again.
I want Jesus to come on my back like a thief in the night.
Is this an ad for Roman?
Did I show you guys the shirt that I bought
based on an Instagram ad?
Yes, you did.
I cannot wait to get that one.
Do you want to tell people what it is?
It's like a weird green monster guy on the phone
kind of like kicking back.
And it says, if you don't like my attitude,
call 1-800-EAT-SHIT.
Were you gonna wear that to the Christmas
you can't go to?
I was hoping that I could.
Now I'll just have to wear it to a client meeting.
No, just have to wear it, yeah.
On the family Zoom call.
No, it's not Christmas time.
It's January, mid January.
How's sober January going for you guys?
What's that?
It's December, but I already stopped mine.
I don't decide what my new year's resolution
is gonna be until, you know, usually January 3rd, so.
Mine's jerk off every day.
How are you doing this year?
In 2022.
It's the same one every year.
Yeah, you're down six days from 365,
so we're rocking 359.
How many times have you KO'd?
Wait, say the first part again.
Well, there's probably been around 358, 359 days this year.
I would say maybe not every day,
but at least enough to average one a day.
Couple Tuesdays pulling some heavy weight there.
Yeah, a couple Threesdays and Foursdays.
Thomas, how many times a day do you jerk off?
Average.
Or weird.
Yeah, at least.
I'm gonna say my-
No, no, no, say the number that makes you feel weird
in a day.
I haven't found that number yet.
I'm proud of each and every one of them.
No, no, no, by weird I mean lightheaded.
The limit does not exist.
Yeah.
One of my favorite Christmas movies.
Oh my goodness.
Die hard.
Have you guys watched the Lindsay Lohan Christmas movie?
I did, yes.
Was it bad?
Top notch.
Like recommend or like it's fine that you watched it?
On my belt.
On my belt?
Yeah, I had to notch it all the way up.
Real tight.
Did you really watch it?
Yeah, I did watch it.
It was on at my house.
I didn't put it on.
Probably your dumb wife.
My dumb, I couldn't even say it.
Taylor, my extremely intelligent and compassionate wife.
Who does dumb shit?
I think it was either her or Lindsay,
another one of our guests here at Pretending to be People.
Another one of my wives.
They put it on when we were hanging out
and then I think they hung out
and I watched the Lindsay Lohan Christmas film.
Is it like, I've been told it's like Hallmark vibes.
It very much is a Hallmark movie.
It's just on Netflix, yeah.
She bonks her head, forgets who she is.
The guy that she falls in love with
is technically taking advantage of her
because she knows how much money she's worth.
When you say technically,
do you mean he still actually really loves her?
Oh, defo.
I saw one on Peacock called Love on Rye
and this Jewish matchmaker sets these two people up
and then the drama is that they find out
that they operate competing delis.
And that is not made up.
Wait, is this a non-fiction or fiction?
TBD.
I think he's asking is it reality or?
That is what I was asking.
And that's what I was answering.
That's historical fiction is what Luke means.
Based on a true story probably.
Yeah, Argo style.
Sounds like it's based on You've Got Mail.
It's called Hanukkah on Rye.
What did you say it was?
Love on Rye?
Yeah, I was wondering if that was like a play on words
for something.
Well.
Let's dive into this motherfucker.
Let's do it.
Dive on in.
Let's do a bit of a dive in then.
Dive.
Let's do a dive into the pool.
Hey, remember what we said earlier about Scottish accents.
Oh, I said I was gonna do a dive into the pool.
Yeah, there you go.
As long as you're respectful.
It's deeper than four feet gonna do.
What's four feet?
Don't you mean a meter and a half?
Oh, this pool is about a fortnight deep.
Bet I can dive in here.
Dive on in.
You guys were on our way to talk to one of the
Richard or Wylie?
Or say their names.
Richard Wylie and William Wylie.
Wilson Wylie.
Nice.
Wilson or Richard and we've got a date with Uncle Tife.
You do have a date with Uncle Tife.
You've been out and about today going from place to place.
I believe you started over at Vivica's apartment,
headed on back to the can station,
which then led you out to a bar.
What was the bar called?
There was a little stop off there in between those
down at the park to visit an old friend of Cal's.
That's right.
An eloquent, well-spoken gentleman.
An articulate gentleman.
And he gave you the names of the...
He gave the names.
He gave us the names and he also said that
15 to 25% of his force were not cops, but gops.
Cops on the Godel payroll.
Which led us to, where are we?
Spelled W-A-R-E in the dare font.
We're at Bucky Kid's bar.
Duh.
Where we spoke to Bucky Kid's kid.
That's right.
Who pointed us to Lulu, the night manager.
L-E-A-U-X.
Lolo.
L-E-A-X.
Is it Lolo?
It's Lolo.
Pardon me.
He pointed us towards Lolo, the night manager
of where are we, we're at Bucky Kid's bar, duh.
Which started out, no one liked that.
And I think it grew on us a little bit.
I'm fine with it, as long as you're the one
who remembers how to say it.
It's like Wawa KBD, right?
Or B-K-B.
Wawa book-ba.
I don't know any of the stuff you just said.
Where are we?
We're at Bucky Kid's bar, duh.
Wawa book-ba-da is what they call it for short.
Easily remembered.
Anyway, then we called Lolo.
He hooked us up with a couple addresses.
After Cal.
Called him.
And.
Tricked him.
Didn't trick him so much.
Fin modem?
Fin modem.
Yes, sometimes you must grease the palms of truth.
And then I think we took off towards one of the addresses.
We benevolently said whichever's close to us,
so you can give us the character you want us to meet first.
And on the way there, Tife texted Julius,
said, hey, get here soon,
but we got a date for 45 minutes.
Yeah, and what are we supposed to meet Tife about?
I don't think we know, I think he just.
He just said he wants to talk to us.
Yeah, and I mean, you went into the office for a little bit.
You didn't talk to Tife.
He hasn't seen you around.
It's been a minute since you've seen Tife,
so he's probably just curious.
Didn't we tell him, though, that we were trying,
that we didn't have the footage
and we were trying to get the footage back?
He at least knows what we're out and about doing, I think.
Zach said he's probably just curious,
so it's.
I told him I was working out,
that's why I couldn't meet with him then.
It's like, I gotta see my cousin's hot gym bod.
I don't know if we did, did we tell him about the footage?
I don't know if we did.
I feel like we did, I feel like we told him
that that's why we didn't wanna meet him right away,
is that we were trying to get it back.
Didn't we say that to him?
I told him I was working out.
You knew that you didn't trust him.
I don't think we told him.
Okay, I thought we did, but it doesn't matter either way.
He'll ask us where it is if we get there.
In that moment, two possible realities were created.
So we'll be playing two different stories
from here on out coming out
on still the biweekly schedule.
It might get a little wild.
And who knows, maybe we'll go back and forward in time.
Oh, god.
Oh, timey-wimey?
Oh, timey-wimey.
If you're gonna spend any amount of time
at Richard Riley or Wilson Wiley's home,
you're not going to be able to visit there
and make it back to the can station
in time for the meeting with Tyfe.
So you have a choice at this point.
You can either show up early for the meeting
or you can go to one of these homes
and then show up late to the meeting.
What was the urgency
in getting to these places right now?
To get our footage back.
Yeah, we were trying not to show up empty-handed at least.
Yeah, have the footage when we go to work.
I think we were pretty heavily headed in the direction
of talking to one of them before we go to the meeting.
Yeah, I think so too.
I just don't know.
Joe doesn't know what we're gonna do
when we get to one of these places.
Looking at these names,
I wonder if he had a voice plan for Richard Riley
and then he's just gonna do it again
with like a lisp for Wilson Wiley.
It seems like his style.
Don't call me out like that.
Guys, we're supposed to meet with Tyfe in 45 minutes,
but I think I can hold him off if we're a little late.
Let's go to Wilson Wiley's.
Brrrrrr.
Arghhh.
Brrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Beep beep.
Brrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Watch you crazy motherfucker.
Ahhh-ooh-ha.
You are in the downtown area.
The apartment for Wilson Wiley is in a nice tall...
Yeah, do you like that?
What's this neighborhood called?
Oh, the downtown area.
Hahaha.
It's a hot July day, midday, rolling into downtown,
skyscrapers towering on either side of you.
You continue in Cal Colorado's beautiful Mercedes C-Class
with a, what was it?
A red siren on top with Bluetooth speakers,
and Julius is in the back watching Cloud Atlas.
Hahahaha.
If he had his earbuds out, he would hear Cal Colorado
talking loudly over the radio and saying,
do you like this Beck?
It's the Blues Brothers soundtrack.
Yeah, man, it's...
Well, Blues Brothers 2000.
Oh, yeah, I was gonna say it's a classic,
and that's, I mean, it's got its things too.
Yeah.
No, that's a good one, yeah.
I like it.
It's good, yeah.
Is Rubber Biscuit on that one?
Oh, no, that's on the first one.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, they do a really, really energetic cover
of funky Nassau.
All right, yeah.
I can get into it.
That's kind of at the end, though,
where it's, I don't think we'll get to it on this trip.
Okay.
You should really experience it in order.
Did we start at one?
Yeah, yeah.
Or is this where you left off last time you were in here?
We're on two.
Listen, after we finish, we'll watch the movie together.
No, I've seen it.
Wait, hook?
Hook.
Hahahaha.
Julius pauses the movie and takes his earbuds out,
and it's kind of like looking very inspired.
What is an ocean but a multitude of drops?
And then they pull up to Wylie's house.
Which is an apartment.
Oh, beautiful da, downtown area,
but that's what they're calling it.
I thought that park got cut.
Yeah, probably did.
So you guys pull into a underground parking lot
for an apartment building in the downtown area?
Da.
Da da.
And it's like really nice.
This is suspiciously nice for a cop.
I think we're dealing with a cop here.
Indeed.
There's plenty of visitor parking
and an elevator that leads you up into the building.
His apartment's on the eighth floor.
Just want to point out that we made our way downtown.
Hahahaha.
Making our way to the downtown area.
Driving fast.
Looking for Wilson Wylie.
And now I'm in the dock.
We've got Cloud Atlas.
Da na na na na na na na na.
On the DVD.
Da na na na na na na na.
Funky Nassau.
And Tom Hanks.
And Oprah.
Was she in that?
She's thinking of the color purple.
Dammit.
What do you think Cloud Atlas is?
Hahahaha.
Tell me right now.
First thoughts.
I'm picturing looks like Lake Tahoe.
Nailed it.
Unfortunately not.
That's a really good guess.
That's a good stab in the dark for any particular,
like I don't know what that is,
but that's not Cloud Atlas.
About a map maker who lives in...
That's closer.
Okay, a map maker?
No, but like a...
So you guys get out of the C class
and head over to the elevator.
There's a doorman who's actually stationed down
in the parking area and he greets you
and he's just like...
Eighth floor?
Eighth floor.
Yeah, of course.
And he clicks the up button on the elevator.
Who are you going to visit?
Oh, just an old friend.
What is your name, sir?
Dave.
Dave, I'm Cal Colorado.
City Action News.
Whoa, that's right.
I knew you looked familiar.
How are you doing today, Dave?
Wow, better now, sir.
Got any news for me?
Well, well, we might.
Let me just say we might.
Hm hm hm hm hm hm.
But that's not what we're doing here today.
Again, this is just an old family friend
we're checking up on.
Well, of course, you all have a lovely day.
You too, Dave.
I stay waving until I'm sure the elevator doors have closed
and he's gone down.
The elevator doors have closed.
You are going up.
He has stayed in the same spot.
Oh, I thought he was on the elevator with us.
He decided not to ride.
No, he was on the outside of the elevator.
He's in the...
I thought he was in it with us also.
Oh, then I guess he's in the elevator.
Eighth floor, huh?
Yeah, I thought we...
I'm not so much an elevator attendant
as a parking garage kind of guy.
There's a way to make this work in the edit
without us saying anything else.
Hahaha.
As the doors open to the eighth floor,
you see a beautiful carpet.
It's got scenes of the jungle on it.
So there's lots of different plant life
and animals kind of drawn into it.
And the scene's kind of carpet
like at the Springfield airport.
I'm thinking Zach just watched the intro
to season one of White Lotus.
I just watched season one of White Lotus last year.
It was really good.
Was there animals?
I don't remember.
Yeah, the intro is just images
of everything Zach just described.
Okay, so it's that.
It's the White Lotus season one intro.
It was the carpet that you used for that intro.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, I was just thinking about it.
Hahaha.
And there's...
You can support the podcast on Patreon
if you want more content like this.
There's sconces on the walls
in between each of these doors
that are considerably far apart.
So like White Lotus 2.
The sequel.
The sconce is in.
Okay guys, we need to find apartment 80085.
I bet it's going to be 836.
Well, let's check the text message and see.
When you go to the text, guess what it is?
836.
It's boobs.
Yeah, it's apartment 836.
What are we going to say to him?
Cal bangs on the door.
Cal Colorado, give me back my footage you son of a bitch.
Hello?
Oh fuck.
Julius's legs tense, ready for action.
On the other side of the door, you hear a small voice.
Hello, this is a nice newsman.
Hello.
Is your daddy here?
No.
Perfect, open up.
Cal like winces, but doesn't correct him.
Doesn't like.
Roll persuade.
30 pass on a 60.
This little girl succeeded as well
with a higher roll, the 47.
She says, I'm not supposed to let in any strangers.
Oh, of course not.
But I'm no stranger.
I'm Cal Colorado from the news.
You've probably seen me.
Oh man, this candy bar is super good.
I wish I had somebody to share it with.
Oh my God.
You sound like you've done this before.
You're gonna have to learn the enemy, you know?
Any horrible thoughts from Becker now?
No, he's just filming.
Such as horrible deeds.
Cal, if you wanna go ahead and roll.
Yeah, I'll roll.
That's a 67 on an 80.
Yeah, she passed as well, but only with a 30.
Cal Colorado from a TV?
That's right, I'm from your TV, sweetie.
Wow.
And the door unlocks and then the door slowly opens
and you see just the most adorable little six year old
on the other side staring up at you.
Cal turns back to you guys
and like gives you a very like pained look
and then turns back to her with a huge smile
and he's like, hi, I'm so glad to see you.
I've always wanted to meet you.
Wow, it's Mr. Cal Colorado who's on my TV
in front of me at the door.
Come in and look at my toys.
I would love to see your toys, but first I need to know.
This one's a pony and her name is Sandal.
Sandal, I like Sandal very much.
Me too.
What's this one called?
Oh, this one's Tressa.
Tressa, does Tressa know
where your daddy keeps his work things?
She like makes the horse nay.
The work things, I only know about where those are
if you can feed me.
Oh, it seems that Tressa is hungry.
Pass the candy bar over Julius.
Julius was lying.
You've got a six year old holding up a little
like miniature horse at you.
Julius feed the horse.
Beck, check your pockets.
Beck definitely has candy bars in his pockets.
He pulls one out.
Here's one for, was it Sandal or Tressa
that was so hungry?
Tressa, Tressa.
Here you go Tressa.
And I kind of am shoving the candy bar
against the horse's mouth.
Oh, it looks like she likes that.
It's an oat candy bar.
Someone roll like 50, 50 up and down.
Who's leaving a six year old home alone?
45.
That's good.
These neglectful parents.
You think that you hear a sound coming from
like the bathroom or something, but.
Then a cat hops out.
Nice.
Oh, Tressa's so hungry.
Julius, while this is happening,
is gonna do a quick once over of the.
Yeah, everybody, yeah.
Yeah.
Actually nods off.
Roll search.
31 on a 70.
Okay, hit me with what you're looking for.
Our footage, you son of a bitch.
Yeah, any sort of tech looking stuff
or anything that would, or like a safe or something.
Yeah, Cal passes too.
He's like, and tell me this one's name.
But he's like looking behind her shoulder
like all over the room.
This one's Dango.
Dango.
How'd you come up with that name?
I said it.
What a ham.
You would do very well on the news, young lady.
She immediately runs away
and is digging through toys.
Hey, remember Tressa was gonna show us
where your daddy keeps his work banks?
This one's a ham pulls out a pig.
Oh, oh, smashing.
That's what you do with a pig bank.
Did Julius find anything?
Yes, you found a safe.
Big, small.
Yes, it is a medium sized safe.
It's a Goldilocks safe.
It is in the back bedroom is the master bedroom closet.
There is a average size safe back there.
Julius is gonna try 88, five.
It does not work.
Julius, what if you tried eight, three, six?
He tries eight, three, six.
Go ahead and roll luck.
If you create, I'll give it to you.
Oh my God though.
It was a 23.
Yeah.
Like the number movie.
Does Julius start seeing numbers?
Wait, yeah, actually.
Just like the time I crashed my Scion TC.
Why are you trying eight, three, six?
There's just like a subliminal vibe in here.
Yeah.
Like it just kind of feels like.
God told them to.
Because it's the apartment number.
That's a good reason.
That's fine.
But it was boobs was the apartment number, right?
Oh, right, right, try boobs.
I did already, it didn't work.
You also see a spot on the desk where there was a laptop,
but there is currently not a laptop
and it seems like the charger is pulled up in that spot
and there's like a clip for it
and the mouse and mouse pad are there,
but there's no laptop sitting in the empty spot on the desk.
What was the kid's name?
What?
You know what?
You've told us your horsey's names.
Yeah.
And the pig's name.
What is your name?
Oh, my name?
Way-chill.
Well, Way-chill.
No, it's Way-chill.
Oh, Rachel.
That's right.
I have a cousin named Rachel.
She's smart like you.
She smiles.
Do you get left alone here very often?
No.
No?
How long ago did your parents step out?
She's just like playing with toys
and she's like, mom went down to go get some groceries
to finish up the meal and you look over
and there's like some things have been pulled out
of the fridge and like no chopping has started,
but it seems like meal prep is about to begin.
Oh, I bet that looks like a good lunch.
I think you probably have a good mom
who feeds you good nutritious food.
I'm sure your dad cares about that too.
What time would you say he left for work?
Oh, I don't see my daddy very much.
Oh.
Julius pops his head out.
Had a dad like that too.
Oh, yeah.
Remind me again when your birthday is.
Oh, my birthday?
Uh-huh.
August 3rd?
Of what year?
What?
How old are you?
The year you were born.
I'm this many.
Six, Julius.
Julius deducts six from the year that it is currently.
It's 2022.
He tries, yeah, I'm not doing that math.
It's like 1980, what am I, Stephen Hawking?
Julius tries eight, three, you said six years old?
We already did eight, three, six, we already.
Well, not, yeah, but.
This time I did it because August 3rd
and she's six years old.
Yeah, eight.
Well, not eight, three, six, but eight, three, six.
16.
Eight, three, 16.
Roll luck again.
90 is good, right?
I liked them.
Julius is gonna kick the safe.
What was that?
Ow.
Oh, that's my friend Julius.
He's very clumsy.
Are any of these animals clumsy?
Oh, yeah.
Twain?
Twain.
Twain is very clumsy.
Yeah, Twain is always twipping.
It's okay to be clumsy sometimes.
Yeah.
Beck is leaning over to Cal.
Do you think that means that the name is Twain or Train?
I have no fucking idea.
Julius tries nine, one, one.
As you're going through the safe
and just like trying repeatedly
to open it with different random numbers,
you're not having a lot of luck.
But while this conversation is happening
with the child in the main room
and you're going through all this stuff
by the desk in this back room,
you see that underneath some folders
and there's some mail
and there's a handwritten piece of paper
shoved up in the middle of it.
And it says, I always keep the safe unlocked.
Julius, Julius, just try opening it.
It says it's always kept unlocked.
It's a safe.
It's meant to be hard to get into.
You can't just pass a search check
and get into a safe.
What does your paper say?
The paper.
It just says all that explaining that about safes.
It says.
That's safes.
As a role-playing mechanic.
As a reminder, safes.
Oh yeah.
Locking.
It should be difficult.
It should feel challenging but rewarding.
Over your players to open one.
It says S.G.Naturhole.
N-A-T-U-R capital H-O-L-E.
The Naturhole, which you all know
is an abandoned baseball stadium in the city.
It was abandoned because there was a sinkhole.
I forgot about this.
In the middle of the infield
that basically eliminated the entire playing area
within the stadium.
However, the stadium seating itself.
Well, plus the triple A team,
the contingent corndogs.
That's right.
Wait, no, they can't play there.
They were.
It's a movie theater now.
Exactly.
And it's a movie theater that we called.
The Naturhole.
Shout out to Thomas Cox, not a patron.
Just on our, in our session.
Just a friend of the podcast.
In our session zero that is yet to be released.
Our session zero part two for season two.
Unofficial collaborator.
We created the abandoned baseball park.
The Naturhole.
Currently the movie theater.
Specifically for large events.
The Naturhole.
Wasn't it like also three,
like all the walls were the screen?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like an omni-plex or whatever
where you like look down into this massive screen
and you like, yeah.
It sounds like a suboptimal viewing experience.
They're still figuring it out.
I bet that's cool for five minutes.
And then there underneath where it says SG Naturhole,
it has cross streets,
which are on like the Northeast side of the Naturhole.
And it says, follow down.
Julius grabs that piece of paper.
He's just looking at it.
He grabs it and goes out into the main area with them.
Guys, I think I've found a clue.
And he looks over at the like meal prep area.
I think we should get out of here and go to that meeting.
Beck agrees, Beck.
As soon as he heard her say
that she was just popping out for groceries,
he felt like we're on a time crunch.
Oh yeah, yeah.
If you feel like we were good here,
I think we should probably make ourselves scarce.
You look over at Beck
and he's like sitting crisscross applesauce
and having his nails painted.
And he's like, oh, yeah, yeah.
You mean Cal, your own character?
I don't fucking know.
I thought you were saying I was doing that.
That would work too.
Oh, Beck.
Well, she did want to do yours next, but that's okay.
I can do them later.
Let's.
Are you leaving?
I'm so sorry.
It was so nice to meet you and all your friends.
But anytime, if you feel like you miss us,
you can just tune in to the local news
and you'll see me again.
This is Cal, Colorado saying it was nice to meet you.
Oh, yeah.
Give a little high five.
Oh, a little high five.
Boop, boop.
Julius is gonna see if he can lift up this safe.
As you go to lift up the safe with those thick thighs,
give me a strength.
You can't pick up a fucking safe.
Five on a 50.
But as you lift it up off the ground,
you see that there's no bottom on it.
Like you're just lifting the top up off.
It's like not connected to its base.
And is there anything on the ground?
Yeah, yeah, there's stacks and stacks of cash.
He's gonna take some, not all.
When you're walking out into the living room,
do you have the cash on you or have you already?
I have it, well, there's that little girl.
Yep, Julius has it in his hands and is like,
guys, he stole from us.
Wow, is that all money?
Monopoly money.
I'm not allowed to play that game yet.
Yes, it's a cutthroat game,
far too cruel for one of your age.
That's what my mom says.
Where did you get that?
Where did you get that, Julius?
The safe is bad.
The safe was no good.
No bottom.
I don't even begin to know what you mean.
He just kept points in the room,
he's like, go check it out.
I think you're pointing at me
like I don't know what he fucking said.
I don't know what it means either.
Yeah, Cal, I mean, Cal walks in there like dumbfounded
and sees all the money.
Beck follows.
Yeah, there's probably 35, 40 Gs in here.
But is that all there is?
Oh no, there's a bunch of papers and stuff too.
Julius, put that back
and start filming one of your TikToks.
He does.
Does Cal want to be in it or?
Cal just stands in front of the safe
and says, do a boomerang.
Can you still do boomerang?
Julius.
And he starts dabbing.
Julius puts down the phone and is like,
maybe we shouldn't document this.
No, no, no.
Okay, well, get pictures.
Beck, you're filming, right?
Oh yes.
We need to document that this man
has been paid off by the goddess.
Is the paperwork or anything in there
give any indication where the money came from?
I would like to flip through it as I'm filming.
Yeah, what else is going?
I'm getting scans basically of the documents.
Oh yeah, that's great.
That's what you need to do.
Roll accounting, everyone who's checking this out.
Wow, I have accounting.
Could I roll bureaucracy?
No, I'm going to go with accounting.
I got a crit success, a 33 on a 50.
Okay, that's awesome.
These figures are all a little bit over my head.
Does anybody know what these mean?
Oh, Julius.
Let me take a look.
You know what this means.
Wilson Wiley seems to be on the payroll
for some sort of a nonprofit.
And as you follow the trail of money
through all of these stacks of papers and papers
with your keen accounting skills
and that critical success, you flip through
and you can draw a direct line from the Godel company
to a shell, to a shell, to a shell, to a shell,
to this nonprofit.
The nonprofit's called Where's The Money?
I don't know, not here.
W-A-R.
W-A-R-E.
Duh.
Holy shit.
There's something big here.
What is it in a few short words?
He's on the Godel's payroll, 100%.
How do you know?
It's all in here.
And Julius holds up all the paperwork and documents,
pockets it, leaves the money.
He's like, we should go.
This just became very dangerous.
I don't know if we need to take anything with us
because I've got it all on camera.
Alertness checks, please.
Crit fail.
I pass a two on a 40.
Tell me if I got these out to hand to you also.
I fail, a 62 on a 40.
Sorry, I keep meaning to get up and get my own.
Beck, you're the only one who hears the ding.
Of the elevator?
Of the elevator.
What ding?
The egg timer on the counter.
Egg.
I get big eyes and I, Carol, Julius, that was the elevator.
I think we really need to get out of here and quick.
Oh, fuck.
Let's hoof it, boys.
Julius is gonna keep, he's gonna keep the papers,
leave everything else and hoof it.
Thank you so much for your time.
I would love to have the tea party
with you and Tereza and Rachel sometime.
Absolutely, okay.
Bye, Conquerel.
Goodbye, and remember what I said about the TV
and good luck.
She holds out her arms for a hug.
If you give her the hug, you're gonna get caught in the room.
No, no, I give her a high five in each open hand
and a thumbs up and a wink is like,
I'm running backwards out the front door.
Julius says, don't tell anyone we were here.
Nobody will believe you.
The three of you like.
Shh.
The three of you slam into the wall,
like the hall wall on the other side away from this door
as the door slams shut and you turn
and looking down the hall,
you see a woman in her mid thirties
carrying like four bags of groceries,
tote bags walking toward you with suspicious eyes
and I need whoever has the highest bureaucracy.
I got a 50.
I got a 70.
To roll.
35.
Hello, excuse me.
Hello, yes.
Is everything okay?
Yes, yes, we were looking for apartment 936.
Oh, one floor up.
This is the eighth floor.
Oh.
I told you, I thought we might have hit that.
Idiot.
He always does this.
He's quite stupid, ma'am.
Anyway, have a nice day.
She's smiling, not really paying attention.
She puts her key in the door and goes in.
And yeah, I'm like waving nervously
and frantically pressing the elevator button.
It's not coming.
No, it's right there because she just came up on it
and you hop into the elevator.
You going up to the ninth?
Yeah, I press one and as the door is closed,
I make a show of like being like,
you pressed one, not nine.
We'll have to do it all over again.
Silly man.
She's like already in her apartment.
Yeah, she's gone.
Deep cover.
How was your friend?
They were not at home, unfortunately.
We just sat outside their apartment knocking
for roughly 15 minutes.
What a shame.
Who was it again?
Oh, we call them Gramps.
We call them Gramps.
Oh, oh, Gramps.
They'll always just be Gramps to us.
You have a good one, sir.
Yeah.
We've got places to be.
Same to you.
Grabbing a little persuade on the way out.
Do I get in on that?
Yeah, 58 on an 80.
39 on a 50, yeah, 50.
You both rolled higher.
I didn't talk.
You both rolled higher and therefore he's just like,
huh, oh, I guess maybe Desmond is Gramps.
And then he's back to thinking about
whatever he's thinking about before.
Just how many times he can jerk off in a day.
Without thinking it's weird.
I'm gonna go pee again for the millionth time.
I wanna get on record real quick.
Is anybody else curious why that was a bureaucracy role
to walk past her or was that a mistake?
I think he made it up or maybe he didn't.
Yeah, I never really know.
Sometimes I think we put not enough faith in Zach
and sometimes I think we put far too much.
Yeah, that's why I'm just like, I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
Go pee, okay.
What was the last thing we said?
Wait, one, two, three, nose goes, nose goes.
I think that was me.
It was.
And we're back and you guys have just headed down
into the parking garage here,
hopping in that Mercedes C-Class and heading out,
saying goodbye to the nice gentleman
who's waiting at the elevator,
thinking about J and O.
My Dave!
How we looking on time?
Oh, time?
It is time.
You see a text on your phone right now.
What's it say?
And it just says ETA question mark
because it is time for you to be at the can station.
Tell him we're caught in construction on the freeway.
It's gonna be a little while,
but we're bringing him the story of a lifetime
and we're going to fucking Richard Riley's house.
I text type traffic
and then we head to Richard Riley's house.
Oh, shit.
We could also like make it like a Zoom call
and just do it from here.
Maybe we can find that idea.
We need the footage first, but yes, that could work.
After I send traffic, I say FaceTime question mark.
Bring, bring, bring, bring.
Okay, guys, it's time for...
Hey, what's up my fucking nephew?
How you living?
Oh, it's good to be me and it's good to be you,
but you are not here.
And you said you were gonna be here.
What the fuck is up?
Not base bro, not base bro.
Forget about it.
Yeah, I mean, it's a good thing that we got
Cloud Atlas in Cal's car
because the traffic is just crazy.
A phenomenal film takes me back to my Lake Tahoe days.
From the womb to the tomb, right?
Yes, sir, and I am hungry to see you.
Where is Cal?
Where's Beck?
Where are you?
I kind of show the car,
trying not to like let him see that the traffic
may not be as bad as we said,
but I show like Cal and Beck.
I'm like, they're in the car here with me.
Say hi, guys.
Beck gives a wave as the camera pans.
Yeah, Cal gives a little salute and says,
great to see you, Typh.
Hey, we're working on the story of a lifetime here.
I think you're gonna like what your nephew serves up to you.
Obviously, traffic's a little behind
and we're always pursuing any possible lead.
I'm sitting here driving
and I'm telling Beck what to film for some good B-roll
and also he's Googling different sources
and calling them and things.
I'm not worried about whether you're working or not.
I just gotta have the three of you come in right now.
Well, as soon as traffic permits, we'll be there,
but we're really, oh, Cal honks on his horn.
He's like, beep, beep, beep, you dummy.
Yeah, it's just real nuts out here.
Lots of wrecks, lots of construction.
Oh, wow, I think I just saw another one.
Oh.
Another one.
Ah, like I said, well, I'm hungry for you to come on back,
so get on back here.
Yeah, yeah, are you actually hungry?
We could stop and get some food for you.
No, no, absolutely.
We'll go ahead and do that.
We'll add that to the list.
Do not stop.
Oh, wow, horrible reception.
Cal's just doing that.
And I'm like, uh, oh, eh, uh.
And like Julius is like freezing his face
and like making that sound and then.
He can see like the traffic behind you moving smoothly.
Like.
Oh, that was strange.
We'll be in by the end of the day.
All right, end of the day.
I mean, I need you here right away,
straight here right now, okay?
Otherwise it's back to Barstow for you, Julius.
Cause I ain't going back to Barstow, that's all you.
I thought you said Barstool.
Ah, no, I didn't.
I don't want to work for that guy.
No, ew, ew.
Who would ever want to work for a guy like that
when you go work for me, bro?
Julius kind of looks at Cal and Beck like.
I've heard him say many times at the Foundry
that his dream job is to work for Barstool.
We'll be in ASAP.
I don't know your dream job, Julius.
You'll have to tell me after this call.
He hangs up.
He says like bye, but that he kind of hangs up.
Julius would love to work for Barstool Sports.
Hello, this is Julius Summers.
Welcome back to Call Me Daddy.
These thighs were made for Barstool.
What is that guy's name?
Dave something?
Portnoy.
I was going to say it's Portnoy.
Port something.
Portnoy, yeah.
Dave Cooley.
The drummer for, all right, let's go.
Oh, Will Ferrell.
The drummer for Will Ferrell.
Okay, I'm going to try to watch some more Cloud Atlas
before we get to Richard's house.
I mean, couldn't you be doing something more productive
like editing a TikTok?
We are at work.
I mean, I don't think Julius has any TikToks to edit.
He's going to post, he'll post a Grover's Gorge TikTok.
Nice.
A good one.
A little teaser.
Another little tease.
Yes, we can.
When you go on, you see that the previous two TikToks
that you've uploaded with Grover's Gorge footage
have been deleted.
Julius immediately goes to the settings
and changes the password for the TikTok.
Okay, I'm going to have you roll
because it might send an email
that you have to change the password to,
but it might two-factor you.
Well, you could see what email it would be sending to.
Let's just get a luck roll since we're playing a dice game.
I want under 50.
No, actually.
88.
Oh, no.
Oh, boy.
That's the worst one.
You're locked out.
You're not sure what happened,
but when you go to TikTok on your browser,
that most recent TikTok, also not there,
and a new text from Tyf, come in now.
Oh, shit.
Julius does not share that information and-
Oh, shit!
Julius thinks if they go talk to Tyf,
they're not going to, this story's done.
So he wants to get done what he can now.
How's that TikTok coming, buddy?
I'm working on it.
Forgot the password.
If you just hit forgot password,
I think it'll send you.
Zach, when you said deleted,
did you meant deleted by the user
or deleted removed by TikTok?
How would you be able to see a difference?
You would only know from the poster's end.
It would tell you if it had been removed.
Oh, yeah.
No, there wasn't a notification that it had been flagged.
Good question, because some content on there
could have definitely been flagged.
This TikTok made me feel bad.
Or misinformation, and Godel has TikTok too.
Uh-oh, vroom, vroom, right?
Vroom, vroom, vroom.
We're here.
Are we at the home of Richard Reilly
or are we at the can station?
Where do you think, sucker?
It's the mill all over again.
On your way, you get into a fiery wreck.
Yeah.
These characters die and everything they know dies with them.
I'm done with you.
You're all playing Rachel now.
Wait, Rachel.
Inside the city, there's a gated community, a suburb.
Wow, that's expensive.
That is where Richard Reilly lives.
He is an officer of the city police department
and you are pulling up to a guard house outside of a gate.
Is it Dave's twin brother?
Think about that for a second, Julius.
Wouldn't they have the same last name?
No, the guard.
I didn't catch Dave's last name.
It's a guy who looks suspiciously like Dave.
The slightly better off brother of the two.
He gets to sit down.
A little more hair.
Yeah, out.
More hair, better person.
Right.
Joe flicks his fucking Fabio, man.
Kind of looking around, I'm like, I see what you mean.
It's crazy how much hair comes out of my head
and it still looks this good.
Fuck you.
Well, hello there.
Whoa, Dave.
Oh, I've always been called that my whole life, but no.
And he taps slowly on his name badge.
Darren.
Hello, Darren.
I'm Cal Colorado from the news.
Whoa, it's been a while, sir.
We're actually doing a report on a local security agents.
Heroes.
Local security heroes.
Whoa, and you want to interview me?
I do want to interview you, Darren.
But first-
Do you have a shot of adrenaline or anything?
I'm sure we've got something back here,
but I can Venmo you and you can source that yourself.
But first we need to see an old family friend
who lives in the inside.
Could you let us in real quick so we can check on them?
They had a small gift they wanted to give.
Yeah, who are you going to see?
Oh, we just call them Gramps.
Will it work again?
Will it blend?
Will it blend, will it blend?
26 pass.
60 pass.
Fuck you.
Nice.
Gramps, Gramps, Gramps, Gramps.
Yeah, well, we're worried
there's not much more time with Gramps.
And he said he had something he really wanted to give us.
But afterwards, we'll come interview you.
Well, that makes me awfully excited
as he clicks the button and says,
tell Gramps hello and have a good day.
See you soon.
I'm sure he will be happy to hear from you.
He speaks so highly of you and all his letters.
Oh, me, wah, and you.
He's beautiful, but he's dying.
And we're looking for the house
that has like the metal archway that says Riley on it.
Gross.
Yeah, there's a big one there, huh?
And it's got like a shield on one side
and a eagle on the other.
Like, you know, laser cut into the metal.
It says Lorem Ipsum.
Yeah, you know, we just got some cool
Latin shit put up there.
Roll luck and answer the question.
Well, we have to answer the question and then roll luck.
What's the question?
The question is,
would you like there to be a car in the driveway?
Seems like something you shouldn't have decided.
I'll roll then.
A lack of preparation on your part
does not represent a crisis on ours.
There is a minivan in the driveway.
You said car.
There is a station wagon.
Damn it.
He still made a family.
That's a nice one.
Cal brings like the C class.
Actually, no, there's a shitty station wagon
in the driveway.
Oh, cause he doesn't.
He hates his family.
I hate my wife.
Cal brings the C class to like a stop nearby
and he's like peering over the steering wheel
and kind of glaring at the scene.
He's like, what do you think boys?
I mean, I think as bad as much as I've ever thought
this whole time.
We got to get the footage, but I don't know how.
I mean, do we just talk to him?
I mean, we could confront him and you know,
his reaction is kind of some sort of, you know, evidence,
but I don't know.
Maybe if we like.
I don't think this is his car.
First of all,
I think we're going to be dealing with another mom.
Yeah.
Well, I can take the mom.
Julius son, no offense,
but you should leave the mom to me.
And with that,
Julius is instilled with the confidence of the group
and rings the doorbell.
No, thank you.
Cal, Cal, use your voice.
Hit him with it, Cal.
Hello, ma'am.
It's Cal Colorado City Action News
is your husband home.
Jesus Christ.
Roll that.
That's the stuff.
Roll what?
Persuade, I think, or charisma.
33 crit success.
Holy fucking shit.
Door swings open.
Curlers, robe, cigarette.
She goes, he never is.
Cal like turns to you guys and has like a shocked look
on his face.
He's like, ah.
She turns around, starts walking away from you
and yelling over her shoulder essentially.
I thought this big house would be better
than leaving me alone in a shitty apartment.
And I guess that's right, but fuck.
Not much better it would seem.
Well, you know, a woman needs attention, care,
someone to love them.
Yes, don't we all?
Would you?
She's pouring a drink.
A bourbon neat, please.
Oh, Beck, what would you like?
Um, red bull and vodka?
And Julius, this is young Julius,
our new executive producer.
He's kind of a rising star here at Cannes.
Oh, are ya?
I'd like to think that I am,
but you know, I've got a lot to learn from the man.
Well, if it's a ladder to climb,
you'll have no problem.
As she eyes you down and down.
It's like, what does that mean?
I was like, how does she know he's a corporate striver?
She can smell it on.
She can see through into men's souls.
Julius flexes his thighs
and you can hear like a little seam rip.
Ooh, I got a little pumpin' at the lake earlier.
What business do you have with my husband?
Well, as she hands you each your drink.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
What was your name, ma'am?
Debs.
Debs Richards?
Debs Richards.
Debs, Debs Riley. Richard's wife?
Wow, is that all I am?
Of Richard?
That seems like all I am.
He drags me around to these places
to show me off black tie events
with a bunch of the worst people in the fuckin' world.
Oh, what do you mean by that?
Charities, nonprofits, you know the type.
Ah, yes.
Yeah, evil people.
Such ghouls.
What is his rank in the police force?
Wouldn't know it.
Talking to him these days, the head on him.
Just an officer.
I see, and what is he doing
at all these charity functions
with the who's who of the city?
He's rubbing elbows.
He's having a good time.
He's making friends.
Well, you used to have to,
you usually have to show up
to those kinds of things with cash.
I mean, I've hosted the Cal Colorado-
Comedy Hour.
Hold on, what should it be for?
Youth sports.
Youth sports is solid.
I've hosted the Cal Colorado Junior-
Damn it.
Debate League.
That's good.
That's really good.
I've hosted the Cal Colorado Black Tie Fundraiser
for Children's Leukemia for the last 15 years.
Oh wow, how much you make off that?
Oh, I don't make anything, ma'am.
In fact, a great deal of my own personal money
goes into it each year,
but we've raised over $20 million in that time.
Wow.
Wow, wow.
Perhaps you'd like to go with Julius this year.
She looks up at your eyes.
Yeah, we know about the thighs.
How are Julius's eyes?
Julius says, my thighs are down here.
We were supposed to pick up some important stuff
from your husband.
He said he'd be here,
but we can just, we're kind of in a hurry.
We can just grab it.
If you just point us to the office,
we'll be right, right as rain.
I don't care.
I'm in my cups and he crit succeeded, so.
Oh, when was that?
Oh, I mean, as soon as I heard you
on the other side of the door.
Oh, you mean me?
Yeah.
Oh.
I was giving you a lot of credit as a game master
and you're like, you had rolled out their interaction
as a couple earlier this morning.
He crit succeeded.
I'm like, what's that?
And he's like, don't fucking worry about it.
Don't fucking worry about it.
Yes, your husband was reviewing some footage for us
in a capacity as a expert consultant.
We needed to see a law man's opinion of things.
Footage?
No, he said he was taking the footage to the nature hole.
The nature hole?
Yeah.
Cal slams his drink and he says, thank you very much, man.
Dude.
Thanks, man.
Thanks, bro.
Thanks, man deuces.
Thank you very much, man.
It's been a pleasure to meet you.
I just remembered we're late for our interview with Darren,
your gatekeeper, but.
Oh, I love Darren.
He's a good guy, right?
Yeah, you can send him in.
Cal is like scribbling down a number and he's like,
if you have anything else you'd like to contribute
to the story, you can reach Julius here at any time.
She takes it.
She slips it into her pocket.
Julius is heading towards the door
and he says, I'll see you later, I guess.
Lorem Ipsum.
Don't blow it, kid.
No, it's charming.
Guys, we gotta get to the hole.
We've got to get to the nature hole.
The nature hole, that's where our footage is?
That's what she said, right?
Do you think it's our footage?
What other footage would he have?
That's true, he's just a cop.
He's just a stupid cop.
And the nature hole's on this piece of paper
that we found, too.
What?
The connection.
Oh yeah, you here, look.
SG, nature hole.
There's some streets here and it says, follow down.
Let's go.
Can crew away.
Thomas, Joe, take off your headphones, please.
I've got something for this.
I remember to bring my headphones
so I don't have to wiggle in my ears.
It's really tiring when it goes on for like six minutes.
Sex minutes.
Chicken off only at six.
When you Google nature hole,
drill bits on Alibaba come up.
Interesting.
That's one of my favorite bands.
Did you do that?
They opened up for Wet Lake.
Drill bits on Alibaba.
For real?
Yeah.
So, Thomas, Joe.
Cool, neither one of them reacted.
Hey, Luke.
They're good at pretending.
To what?
Hey, you get a text on your phone?
Duh.
Yeah.
It's from-
Type.
Yeah.
What's it say?
Love ya.
Nephew.
What does it say?
It does, it starts off, I love you, nephew.
I need you to come and bring Beck and Cal.
I text Beck, yeah, for sure.
Like I said, end of day.
By the end of the day.
He texts Beck, he says,
this is good news, come right now.
Is there any, can I humant a text?
I say, just like, what's it about?
A promotion, is the response.
Julius has a new number one priority.
Yeah.
Should we bird him?
Let's bird him.
Caw, caw, caw, bird, bird, bird noise, bird noise.
I am a bird.
If you're a bird.
What kind of bird are you?
I'm a bird.
What kind of bird am I?
One that eats like bugs off a rhino.
No.
Oh, should we came in too early
and now we found out that he turned into a bird.
What kind of bird are you, Joe?
Big bird.
Thomas the bird?
The kind that eats birds like you for breakfast.
Dang.
You guys are driving vroom vroom.
Cal, you are behind the wheel.
You know that the natur hole is off
in a different direction than the can station.
It's gonna make you even later to this meeting
than you already are if you head that way.
Guys, I hate to say it, but I think, you know,
we have to have jobs in order to break news
and type's not happy.
I think we ought to stop by the station
before we go out there.
Yeah.
I mean, we could even, if you feel like we have to,
we can maybe talk around the issue while we're there.
You know, that we kind of feel them out.
Yeah, maybe I left the footage at my house
or just kind of give them the run around if we have to.
I mean, you can link them to the TikToks, right?
You can show them some of what we've got.
Yeah.
Because once he sees what we have, I mean-
It's like proof of concept, yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure I'll be like,
what are you even doing in my office?
Get back out there and follow the story.
The TikToks got deleted.
What do you mean?
I didn't want to worry you or anything,
but I wanted to go to Richard's,
but I think he deleted the TikToks or someone did.
Oh, I thought you were going to interview me.
Okay, bye.
Oh, I think that we're not even close.
He said that to himself like 10 minutes
after you guys left.
They're gone.
Yeah, so-
Took him that long to say it.
I mean, I was going to tell you, I kind of had forgotten,
but I didn't want to tell you-
He combed his hair.
So that we didn't go to Richard's.
I think, you know,
somebody's been deleting the TikToks.
Tyve is not happy with us.
I think we got to go.
I think we got to go talk to him.
It sounds like he wants to shut us down.
That adds a new wrinkle that, yeah,
that sounds like he's maybe,
I'm sorry, Julius, but maybe he's in on this?
Yes, as the Blues Brothers say,
this is track four, by the way.
It's cheaper to keep her about our jobs,
but I don't know,
it sounds like he doesn't want us to do our jobs.
If we get the footage,
we could sell it to any news agency in the world.
It's true, we might need to start thinking global.
We can go beyond these bastards.
Wouldn't it be easier to just keep our jobs
and do it here, though?
We have a lead on where the footage is right now.
If we don't act, we might never get it back.
Julius has a point, though,
that if we can maybe do some creative talking to Tyve,
maybe we'll get some resources
that can help us with our actual goal.
And we can just buy some time.
I mean, he's not going to fire us immediately
if, you know, we don't really tell him exactly
if he's on Godel's side, then.
We could even play the fool and be like,
yeah, this is for the good of Godel.
Cal slams the brakes, and he says,
I didn't nearly die in that piss-shit common blood pit
just to lose the evidence of it.
No one's gonna call Cal Colorado a liar about this.
If you wanna go see Tyve, take a fucking Uber.
I'm going to the natural hole.
I'm getting my story.
Take off your headphones real quick, Thomas and Joe.
As both a player and as Julius, I am torn.
You get a new text.
It says, just you is fine.
On my way.
Birds?
Birds.
I can't have me getting fired on my resume.
I gotta go see my uncle.
Will you guys please come with me?
Yeah, um.
Beck, go with him.
Yeah, I'll come, I'll come, Julius.
Cal, we should all go together,
but we just gotta check in with Tyve.
I think he's gonna fire you anyway, Julius.
Well.
I think you tell him to go fuck himself.
If you're gonna go.
You'll get a job once you put out
the greatest news story of all time.
I gotta go, but if you're gonna go anyway,
Beck, you should be there to document it.
I can do it on my own.
It's, it's just my uncle.
Hey, remember that we lost God?
Yeah.
Yeah, no, I wouldn't let Cal go alone.
I'm just, if Julius is saying that we need to go to Tyve,
I don't, I don't know.
It feels like maybe, maybe we should go see Tyve
and then go to the natural hole.
Call him again.
Actually, I'm going to call him.
Oh, okay.
Cal calls Tyve.
Bring, bring, bring, bring.
Hey, it's my guy, Cal Colorado.
How are you?
Oh, well, not very great, Tyve.
Yeah, get your ass down here.
I got some great fucking news for you.
You wanna be sitting at that head anchor desk again?
I take the phone off speaker.
Julius is looking at Beck like, Beck is giving thumbs up.
Holy shit, holy shit.
What do you mean?
I got an opportunity.
It's promotion time, but I need you and Julius
and Beck to come in.
Why do you need us to come in?
Because we have to do the paperwork
for your new promotion, of course.
I've got to tell you, Tyve,
we're working on something really big here.
I don't care.
I think the paperwork can wait.
It's going to be great.
I need you to come in now.
It's my promotion, Tyve, so.
Well, we'll see.
Isabella feels real confident in that spot, you know?
So I want to give it to you,
but I need you guys to come in.
Tyve, you've already taken this from me once.
I don't know if I trust your word,
but if you love Julius, if you love me,
if you actually care about your job here at the news,
you're going to want to let us pursue this story.
I love my job.
I love my life.
And I need you to come in.
So it's either that,
or I think we're going to have to have some harsher words.
Tyve?
Unfortunately.
Beck has given signals to get Cal's attention.
Joe is pointing down.
He's trying to muffle the receiver.
Joe is playing in a screwable game of tricks.
Muffle the receiver.
Muffle it.
Take it off your ear and muffle it.
I take it off my ear and like make a play show
of putting it on mute.
And he's like, I know about you.
Oh shit, hell yeah, Cal.
Dude, Cal, if he's offering to make you an anchor,
that's a win-win for us because you'll have the desk.
He can't tell you shit once you're live on air.
We just run the footage.
We're talking about to tape right now.
If you're on air and I put that thing in the video bay.
But we don't have the tape.
We'll have to get it, but I'm saying.
He's got it.
Or someone working with him.
Or the people paying them both.
Don't you see?
Tyfe's in on it.
Tyfe wants to kill it.
I don't think you're wrong,
but I also think that we can still make.
The anchor job is never going to happen.
He's trying to play me.
Unless he wants to put you on anchor to shut you up
and stop investigating.
That's exactly what he wants.
I'm saying we can get you on anchor and then we use that.
He promises it to me, but then never gives it.
Don't you see?
He can't control us outside of the office.
That's exactly my point.
We're outside of the office.
He cannot control us.
But I'm saying if we go now to the natural
and he just does straight up fire us.
So what?
We post it on TikTok.
We make a new TikTok.
We're locked out of the can TikTok.
It keeps getting deleted.
We'll make a cow TikTok.
But none of this is live on air.
This is all things that they control.
We've already seen that they got TikTok under wraps.
We'll make a new TikTok.
I think that they have the ability to take that stuff down.
What I'm saying is that we have the chance
to put this in front of eyeballs,
no matter who tells you no.
Once we get you on air live.
We have that if we have the footage, no matter what.
We can ship it to a dozen news agencies.
We can put it live on as many platforms as possible.
It's not live then though.
It's all to tape and they get to decide when they run it.
Beck, I'm talking about the internet.
Yeah.
Guys, I'm gonna have to go.
Are you coming?
I would strongly advise against you going to that meeting.
Your uncle is not looking out for your best interests
and your career will live beyond this,
especially if you're part of the most legendary news story
of all time.
The movie's happening in this car, Julius.
He looks at Cloud Atlas.
Hey, hey, I know Tom Hanks is magnetic in that movie.
It's one of my favorites,
but if you ever want to be the kind of person
who produces the next Cloud Atlas
or runs City Action News or a national news station,
this story is how you get your foot in that door,
not your uncle.
If he fires you, screw him.
I'll give you every recommendation in the world.
Ty fangs up.
Oh yeah, we kept him on mute for like seven minutes.
I don't know, Cal.
I think if I'm gonna do this, it's all about who, you know?
And I don't want to be like a Snowden or something
and get sent off because of the Godel company.
I gotta go.
And yeah, Julius just kind of looks at Cal and Beck
and like Beck looks at Cal.
Cal, you know I'm gonna follow you wherever we go,
but I think that Julius has a point here.
We're going two different ways, Beck.
Who you go with is up to you.
Julius orders a Uber.
Yeah, no, Cal, I'm your cameraman.
I'll meet back up with you guys.
I'll make sure he doesn't fire you.
Julius, don't go.
A tear runs down Julius's eye
as he waits for the car to stop and gets out.
Car's been stopped.
He looks at the...
What are you waiting for?
My Harry Anderson juke.
Go on, get out of here.
As the credits roll on Cloud Atlas, Julius exits the car.
Cal is just like weeping.
Julius is crying too.
Beck just says to himself,
God, I hope he's right about this.
Luke, Julius Summers takes the Uber back
to the city action news station.
You get out and you head in
over that marbled, marvelous floor, head upstairs.
As you make your way upstairs,
you see the door to your Uncle Ty Frailand's office
is closed and you hear whistling
coming from the other side.
When you make it to the door,
and when you open up the door,
you see standing behind his desk, your Uncle Ty Frailand.
And sitting at the two chairs facing Ty's desk,
looking back toward you is a tall, mousy police officer
wearing glasses and a short, jacked, bald police officer.
Two whole new characters.
And you recognize who?
Richard Riley and Wilson Wiley.
That's right.
Confidently, he says.
And how does Julius feel in this moment?
Disappointed in himself,
yet excited at the prospect of a promotion.
Nice.
Thomas, Joe, Beck Wilder in Cal, Colorado,
head the dream team, if you will,
to the Natcher Hole in Cal, Colorado's Mercedes C-Class.
And when you pull up-
This is the start of some PTPB erotic fan fiction.
Oh my God.
It is straight for the natural.
When we go to the northeast corner.
When you head to the northeast corner,
you see that there is a subway station there.
And from the car, you see walking up
out of this subway station at just this moment,
with a wall of dark hair flowing down
over their eyes, covering their nose,
only showing their bottom black lip pierced with a hoop.
SG, Stevie Godel.
Son of a bitch, Beck.
Holy shit, it's Stevie.
Cal leans out the window and hawks a horn and goes,
Hi Stevie.
Beck is waving to you.
Over here.
Stevie, Stevie, Stevie, it's us.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
It's great, and it's all my fault.
Cause my life is great, and it's all mine.
Cause my life is great.
What I meant to say was actually,
I feel so seen right now.
Cal looks up, and crosses himself and points up.
Sammy Sosa.
What?
Nothing.
And it's all my fault.
It's all my fault.