Welcome, brothers, sisters, and siblings.
It's your ethereal pup god, Wolf the Dog.
Blessings to you all, my children.
And I'm hollerin' from the heavens and the hells at you live from 694.2 PTBP.
A station of radio.
It's definitely somewhere at some time.
You know how most companies exclude their employees for participating in drawings,
so they can't be accused of manipulating the outcome?
Apparently that's not the case here at 694.2 PTBP,
cuz this week's Howlin' with Wolf is from Joe Terry in Springfield, Missouri,
who tweeted about the show and tagged that pretending pod,
which is self-promotion when he does it,
but it's super fuckin' cool when y'all do it.
Joe Terry writes,
Hey, dog.
You know how companies exclude their employees from drawings?
I don't think they're doin' that here,
so I want you to say Studio 60 on the Sunset Strip
is an underrated Aaron Sorkin show that I wish more people saw.
Bradley Whitford and Matthew Perry turn in electric performances
as co-showrunners of a Saturday Night Live-type program.
It got one season.
I want more.
Love ya, dog.
Hope the slop is sloppy.
You will, Joe.
Sweet Joe.
I love you too, buddy.
One day we shall frolic in the slop together as one,
but you shall feed me your life force
so that I may continue to live on and grow in power.
Do not worry, dear sweet delicious Joe.
Do not tremble when the darkness fills your vision,
surrounding you,
when you feel fangs scraping along the back of your neck,
when all of your senses start to fail you
and you feel yourself slowly but surely dissolving from this time.
We will become one, Joe.
And you start to think maybe we always were.
Welcome back, Joe.
The links are in the damn show notes.
The news.
Last time, the City Action News field team
took a single simple steel train car
across an awe-inspiring bridge
that ran over an unnaturally smooth chasm
filled with fog and an upside-down church.
A pre-recorded Fred Godel from the TVs in the train car
welcomed them to Godel's Gate to Grover's Gorge.
Through the next Spongebob-y hatch door
was a town ripped from futuristic concept art of the 1950s.
The first thing Julius wanted in Grover's Gorge was an interview.
And while they talked to a great employee of the Godel Company,
a GE of the TGC,
they noticed hopping along the synthetic track they all stood on,
a jackalope,
taking you back to this mythical critter.
It's a whimsical tomb and it's time to get litter.
It's Alter Girl with My Life is Great and It's All My False.
And it's all my fault
Cause my life is great
And it's all mine
And it's all my fault
Welcome back to Pretending to Be People.
You are now listening to what I think is probably episode 7.
Mr. Joe Terry, tell me what's a weird dream that you've had?
Ever?
Yeah.
What's like the weirdest dream that you've had?
I don't have a good answer to this.
Oh, I mean, there's one I've remembered for some reason since I was a kid.
Awesome.
I'm running down the hillside and it's like the Windows XP background,
like beautiful lush green hills and beautiful clouds,
and I'm leading an army of giant ants toward like a hole at the bottom of the ground.
Are you an ant?
I hope that's a prophet.
I'm like running fast.
I'm not an ant, no, but I'm like running fast and it's like joyous.
Like it's not scary or dangerous or anything.
We're like a stampede of giant ants running toward it.
It's like the most joyous dream I've ever heard of.
Yeah, that's so cool.
I don't know if that's weird though.
What do you guys remember from where we left off?
Where are we at?
What are we doing?
Are we in the normal world?
Are we just like hanging out at the news station?
No, man.
Are we in the city?
No, we're out on assignment and shit is not normal, Zach.
We're not in the city.
We're in Walmart country.
Where the shit is really real.
We're out in the boonies and we are in an impossible town that should not exist,
surrounded by impossible geography,
and we just saw a fucking Jackalope and news team is going to get some goddamn
answers for the people.
I can tell you that.
Awesome.
So, uh, Luke,
can you describe the landscape in which you are standing currently?
Yeah, Grover's Gorge.
Nice.
Got it.
Nailed it.
You can describe the city in one word.
I would say weird.
The landscape weird.
The people weird.
It's a huge space age city with bouncy colorful synthetic walkways.
Awesome.
Nice notes.
Very good notes.
Do you have luck right now?
Uh, I don't think so.
Actually.
You have luck now.
Oh, sweet.
Sick.
I like those.
I like those thorough notes.
There's two statues.
Joe's like,
what the fuck?
No, I was trying to find a clip.
Do you guys remember,
um,
Dave Coulier hosted a show that was kind of like America's home videos,
but it had a Jackalope.
Do you remember this?
You're thinking of Bob Saget hosting America's home videos.
Are you throwing us off because Thomas took good notes?
Oh shit.
No,
this is just his little tantrum.
I have no,
I have no recollection of this.
Coulier time.
Yeah.
Um,
I'm going to start taking notes once I use my point of luck.
Just when you thought it was safe to check the mailbox,
Jackalope 3,
tower came COD.
So Dave Coulier does the Jackalope's voice
and it's just a rabbit that they've tied horns to
and they do bits with it.
It's a real dead rabbit.
It's like a taxidermy rabbit that they've attached horns to.
That's awesome.
Well,
the one that you guys are looking at here in Grover's Gorge is alive
and it is just kind of hopping on this synthetic walkway
that people are jogging and walking on.
Zach,
where is it between us and the massive square park?
Ooh,
nice.
I would say that it is in between you in the massive square park.
Oh,
you can't have more than just luck,
but I'd give it to you again.
Ooh,
I'd give it to you again.
Oh,
no,
I just want,
I just want your praise.
And what's across that massive square park where people are hanging out
in either green or yellow tinted or accented uniforms.
What's on the other side of that park?
I bet Joe knows.
Is it two big statues?
It is two big statues.
Yeah,
they're about twenty six point three meters tall.
In fact,
and they're made of green rock.
I've already said that.
What's on the other side of the statue,
labs?
Yeah,
it's a building that is made of glass and marble.
It rhymes ass.
Brass.
Grass.
Grass and ass.
Ass glass of grass.
Off to your left side from your current view,
you see housing,
beautiful,
gorgeous housing.
And then off to the right,
you can just barely make out some buildings that are poking over some perfectly cylindrical trees.
Beck,
what do you think that to the left is?
What would you say those buildings look like?
I don't know,
Zach,
what are they?
And you see a whole line of beautiful homes that are like beautiful suburban homes.
They're all unique to each other though.
They all have their own special flair to them and they're enough apart to where you think it wouldn't be an issue to like hear your neighbors or anything.
There's definitely privacy.
Do I get a vibe of like the decade that these are?
Space age was the word you used to describe this place.
And so those are to the west.
Those are to the west.
If you came from the south,
to the west,
to the west.
Headin' west like you're blowing Kanye.
Oh,
nice.
Childish Gambino line for you there.
They both like oohed and aahed.
You should have just said it was yours.
I thought it was yours.
I'm Donald Glover.
Donald Glover.
Oh,
dong lover?
Dong lover.
Okay,
these statues,
how are their dongs?
From this distance,
you would assume you're not sure how big they are proportionally based because you're just too far away to make out the subtleties of these statues.
However,
you can assume based on the enormity of the statues that the dongs might have a similar weight to them.
Interesting.
The dongs weigh as much as the statues or at least a similar amount.
They've got dense dongs.
The dongs take up.
I feel like my words are being misunderstood here.
What?
No,
not deliberately.
So two giant dong statues.
Remind me what the statues look like.
They're big penises.
Men.
They are two men.
Are they doing anything?
One is standing with hands in his pockets and the other one is standing with hands kind of on his hips.
We're kind of familiar with what the more famous Godels look like.
Yeah.
Are these the Godels?
These are these the Godels.
The one with the hands on the hips is Frank Godel Grand Granddaddy Godel.
And the one playing pocket pool with his statue hog is Fred Godel who you saw in the video in the train on the way into Grover's Gorge.
Which is his son.
Yes,
and you would just know from general worldly knowledge that Fred Godel does have both a daughter and a son.
Fox and the Hound.
Yeah,
Fox and Faith Fox and Faith Godel.
F.
Yeah,
dude.
Some people do that.
Frank Godel.
This Frank Godel that did all the mythological fighting.
That is correct.
Yes,
according to the story told on the train.
Some people name their kids mostly like their sons like the same name.
It's fucking weird as hell,
dude.
Must be confusing.
I would never name an NPC with the same name as another NPC.
No,
you wouldn't ever do that.
So you guys are all standing on this.
It's kind of a bouncy pathway.
You're talking to Jennifer who is from here.
She's a GE.
She's a great employee.
She said for the Godel company here in Grover's Gorge.
She was born and raised here and has worked for the Godel company for a few years now.
She's in her like early to mid 20s.
And now the corner of your eyes,
you all noticed a Jackalope kind of hopping across this bouncy walkway that others are exercising and jogging on.
Some people are paying it a little bit of attention,
you know,
pointing at it going woo woo.
Classic reaction to an animal.
And you see that it has a yellow ribbon tied around its head around its antlers.
Cal says,
what the hell is even that?
Woo woo yeah go GE's hungry for points.
And she kind of like motions with her hand to a couple others
and they all kind of run around and make a circle around this Jackalope that's sitting on the ground
and they hold each other's hands and they go,
I'm a GE of TGC.
I'm a GE of TCG.
Hey, I'm a GE of TGC.
I'm a GE of TGC.
And then she kind of like laughs and Saunders back to you guys.
Well, so as as they're like doing that,
I'm Cal is like motioning back and Julius forward to like run up to the circle and get a shot.
Definitely doing that.
Yeah.
Yeah as they part do we see a real Jackalope or is there visibly like glue on its fucking head
or no, but you would notice that I yeah looks like these antlers are tied on with a yellow ribbon.
Seemingly the question I had was like when they're chanting the that stuff are you on purpose saying?
No, sorry.
That was my question also,
so we should always hear it as TGC.
Yeah.
Okay, my bad because you consistently were doing it the second time you were saying it.
So I thought you were saying oh my god.
That's because I typed it wrong.
No, it's because I'm an idiot.
Same thing I was like I was like we need to ask about what what is GTC.
I knew you were just fucking up.
Thank you Thomas.
Thanks for not reading into that look double luck.
I just can't take that back baby when I think of you.
I think of you like your freaking mastermind that has every single detail planned out.
So I'm like you're hiding something from us you fucker.
He's got you so fooled.
Julius is definitely recording on his phone like trying to get up as close to the Jackalope as possible.
Is it does it seem scared?
No, it does not seem scared.
It is very very calm Beck wouldn't want to break the circle,
but he would want to put his camera between the heads of two people to film directly down.
Do they react to me doing that at all?
No, not at all.
That's a great shot.
What are you guys?
What are you guys doing?
I've asked the people around the Jackalope.
Oh, hey, what's up?
Oh, hi.
Hey, how's it going?
Uh, oh, yeah.
No, we're just celebrating our points.
Hey hungry for points.
Do you eat the Jackalope?
Oh, do you eat Jackalope?
No, rabbit stew.
I oh goodness.
No, I have you ever been to Charlie's next to the foundry.
They all kind of laugh at each other and are giggling amongst themselves and in unison.
They say we don't need to eat.
Uh, how does this Jackalope signify your points or why are you celebrating around it?
Why you are all wearing yellow?
Why is it got a yellow ribbon?
What?
No, that's a great question.
Yeah.
No, so the Jackalopes, they run free and they're not actually Jackalopes.
Yes, I noticed I thought there might be but then the last little part of me that believed in magic died.
That's so sad.
They all kind of laugh like we still have magic here and they kind of laugh some more and she's like earlier this morning.
We had a little contest where we let some rabbits run free and whoever could wrap their ribbon around the the rabbit's head and tie on the antlers to make a Jackalope got points.
I didn't tell you about the points.
The points is the best part.
Well, yeah, we asked but you never quite explained.
What do the points are in you?
Of course I get ahead of myself.
I'm just so excited and happy to be here.
Well, Jennifer, we can certainly see that.
No, so I'm so hungry for points because when we get points we could win.
Win what?
Oh, the prize at the end of each quarter, there's a prize.
The fiscal quarter?
Yeah, of course.
What is the price?
Whether the GEs or the EEs win.
I'm sorry, EEs?
Yeah, excellent employees.
There's great employees, there's excellent employees.
Those are the green ones and she kind of points around and you see some people who are wearing the same like similar really nice kind of athleisure.
But their accents are green as opposed to yellow, which is what?
What does green sound like?
What?
It was a bad joke.
Their accents are green.
Like Ireland.
Excellent employees, are they somehow higher in rank or superior to the great employees?
Oh, no, it's just a different word that also means great.
It sort of means better than great.
Not around here, it doesn't.
Okay.
How are like teams chosen?
Oh, well, when you get hired, you just kind of become either a great employee or an excellent employee.
But do you like have a say in it?
No, it's just kind of where you fit.
Do different departments have different designations?
Yeah, the excellent employees work in the lab and the great employees work in the factory.
And she points to the lab when she says the lab and the lab is the glass and grass building behind the statues on the north side.
And on the east side, just above some perfectly cylindrical trees,
she points to the top of a massive greenhouse that is peeking out above these cake pop like trees.
Jennifer, you told us earlier you were born here.
Born and raised.
Were your parents on teams as well?
Yeah, my mom was a great employee and my dad was a great employee.
Is it typical for the children of great employees to wind up on the same team as their parents or?
Not always, but in my case, it worked out.
Are you friends with any excellent employees?
Not really. We, you know, kind of work in separate places.
You know how I assume you guys all work together?
Yes, in a small van.
Well, then you're probably very close to your co-workers and less close to people you don't work directly with, right?
No, I mean, not not like as a rule.
Sometimes people you once worked closely with can stab you in the back.
Oh, with what?
Corporate politics.
Wow, that sounds really hard and sad.
Like your dad.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes, but we're not here to ask about me.
I'm just fine.
We want to know more about you, Jennifer, and what you do here.
And as you're kind of looking to Julius, you see a man wearing well-fitted athleisure,
monochromatic with green accents, approaches your group confidently with a hand outstretched.
Well, hello there, you fine interlopers.
What a coincidence indeed to run into you here.
My name is Fox Godel.
I am the son of my father, Fred Godel, the grandson of my grandfather, Frank Godel,
and the future CEO of the Godel company.
It's an absolute pleasure to meet you.
Would Julius know, has he like seen Fox outside?
Like does he go into the real world?
Oh, great question.
No, you would only know Fox Godel from some pictures that have been on like magazine covers
where he's just like posing on a sound stage with his dad just within the past year.
How old is he?
Yeah.
Fox Godel, he seems to be in his mid twenties.
Oh, and Zach, last question.
How can someone have a monochromatic outfit with colorful accents?
Oh, well that's easy.
It's just like white, gray, a few different shades of gray, black, and then has like green
accents on the side.
Not monochromatic.
Oh, fuck.
It's pretty, it's pretty.
Gray scale.
Okay.
Gray scale with green accents.
Monochromatic gray scale with green accents.
He got it on the bio farm.
Mr. Godel, it is a pleasure to meet you.
And he shakes your hand, but then when he goes to shake the hand of Mr. Beck Wilder,
he looks up at you, notices the headphones on your head and immediately his eyes glaze
over and he gets this horribly tortured look on his face.
Was the last person that did that a farmer?
Yeah.
He was.
It was the lemon or just some other guy.
It was.
It was the ticket guy.
Right.
It was actually, it was Jesse Lemon.
Okay.
It was the farmer who sold his property to Fred Godel.
Zach, can you remind me, did I know, did I figure out that that's what he was looking
at at the farm?
Did Beck know that it was his headphones?
You'd even try it.
You even took them off and stuff.
Yeah.
I need everyone to real grip as the look of this man who was just completely normal
a moment ago as clearly gone somewhere else inside of his own mind and is trapped seemingly
with the disturbing.
The lonely stoner seems to free his mind tonight.
Yeah, I definitely do not pass.
I crit fail.
Oh.
Oh, I crit failed too, dude.
99.
It was an 88.
Oh, I'm going to spend luck and the other luck you gave me.
You can't spend luck because it would just be 99 to switch.
Oh, that's right.
Well, fuck.
You just spent your luck.
No, I made it 99.
It was the luck.
It was and it is.
No, I made it 9.9.
Oh.
Julius, you are going to lose one grip.
Beck Wilder, Cal Colorado, you're going to lose two grip each.
Well, that's not so bad.
Because we saw his face.
And I think everybody recognized it was the same thing.
It was the headphones that freaked him out.
Yeah, that's what's freaking you out is that now you've run into a second person
who has had the same reaction to your headphones.
Okay, so but it's not like an intrinsic fear like I saw the face of pure evil terror.
No, it's not pure evil terror.
It's simply just...
It's wrong for someone to be scared of a headphone.
So afraid of headphones.
And then not only that, but unnaturally with the snap of a finger.
But there is no snap of any fingers.
But if you were to, just he's right back to normal looking at you smiling,
going in for a handshake.
Nice.
What the...
What was that?
I don't shake his hand because I've now critically failed this grip loss.
I think that he...
Awesome.
What are you doing?
If you fail grip, you can't shake his hand.
That's the rules.
And he kind of...
You awkwardly grab too soon and grab his fingers.
No, I don't even make a move.
And I'm just kind of like startled kind of by how scared he was of me.
And maybe I go up like, is there something on my neck?
And then I feel the headphones.
Oh, fuck.
Who is this guy?
What's going on here?
You know, he pokes you in the belly a little bit.
Uh, Julius, like...
Like Tife.
Definitely...
Oh, shit.
Yeah, like Tife.
Is there somebody in your life who's not respecting your personal boundaries?
Because poking people in the belly sucks.
That's not a cool thing to do.
I guess we just had a couple...
Is Taylor...
Real rude people on the NPCs so far.
Julius is freaked out by that, but not like a crazy amount,
but enough that he wants to like address that...
But I would like you to...
Because you just failed, you didn't critical fail,
I'm going to let you roll an alertness check here.
But again, because you did fail that check,
you're going to be at a negative 20.
Pass.
A 32, which makes it a 52, on a 70.
Fantastic.
If I could have Thomas and Joe remove their headphones in La La La,
but don't La La La, because you're in the same room.
La La La!
So what happens?
So next, they can't hear,
but the next thing that happens
is that you actually, you notice that Stevie,
her eyes are welling up with tears
as she's staring into the face of Fox Gothel
as he's having this strange experience.
Like, do I recognize that it's from his...
I mean, he's doing a real weird fucking thing here
and her eyes weren't full of tears a second ago.
Gotcha, okay.
And then you're back.
We all give him the bird.
You know what we mean.
Julius looks at Fox.
What was that...
Stevie?
Oh, you're Stevie?
It's nice to meet you.
He puts out his hand and is like,
Fox Gothel.
And you.
So what is your name?
Why did you have that look on your face?
What, this beautiful grin of mine?
So sorry if it was too charming for you.
I like point at Beck's headphones.
Yeah, and when he looks back, he breaks again
and he's just like making this really strange face.
It's just pure terror is across
and you can just see his lips quivering.
His eyes are kind of like darting back and forth.
He's not looking even at the headphones anymore
and just as soon as you notice it, he's done.
But because this just happened
and you kind of have a bit of a grip on yourselves this time,
the two of you,
because you didn't roll alertness last time,
you get to roll alertness this time,
but because you critically failed last time,
I'm going to put you at a negative 20.
Real quick, we said Jesse Lemons did sell his farm, right?
Jesse Lemon did sell his farm.
Yes.
I've got a theory, guys.
Oh my God.
I rolled a hundred.
I rolled a one.
Oh my God.
What the hell is going on tonight?
Okay.
First, we are going to do Thomas
because I don't know what to do with you.
I saw your zeros.
I was like, hell yeah, dude.
So, fuck.
Zach, can you take your headphones out and rub your ears?
I don't want to have to change shit if we get it right,
but I think people are getting Clockwork Orange here.
Like, God has some kind of device.
Headphones are a major part of it.
Yeah.
So I'm sure he's done it to control his son.
He did it to convince the farmers to sell to him.
I like that idea.
But it's in some way that they don't remember
because they seem kind of aware of themselves.
Yeah.
Do they have to put ear drops in?
Zach?
Oh, that was scary.
When you were rubbing your ears like that,
did you feel like you were back at the big boy show?
Oh, dude.
Yeah, but my heart wasn't thumping
to the point of actual anxiety.
It was so fucking great.
We were so close and so loud.
Absolutely rattling my chest cavity.
Yeah, like the way it does
when you're fucking 10 years old and you get to go to a show.
It was so cool.
It was absurd.
And we were so close to the front.
It was fucking awesome.
I had never felt this before,
but when I would breathe in through my nose,
I could feel it vibrating.
It was so weird.
So the story behind this is that I was sitting on my couch
on Saturday and Luke calls me
and says,
He's like, hey, what are you doing right now?
Well, you're about to edit the podcast.
I was about to edit, yeah.
I'm like, okay, you're going to Bentonville with us
to see Big Boy and Run the Jewels.
And then he said he'll be at my house in 10 minutes.
So I hung up and changed clothes
and then we drove to Bentonville
and watched Run the Jewels and Big Boy.
It was fucking sick as hell.
It was incredible.
That venue was pretty cool too.
No, it sucked. Walmart sucks.
Walmart does suck.
The venue sucked. The whole thing sucks.
The vans were great.
Terrible art. Yeah, the art sucks.
That coffee shop blows.
Well, it's confusing.
It is. There's seats that
doesn't look like you're supposed to sit in.
It's extremely confusing seating, Joe.
It's so confusing.
And what's also confusing
is the look on Fox Gottel's face.
Oh wait, but not to me
Oh, that's right. Joe, if I could have
you and Luke take your headphones off here.
Thomas, you're going to see
a couple things here.
First off, Stevie
is staring directly
into the face of Fox
Gottel with just
this wild sadness.
Just this deep
struggling pain.
Her eyes are welling up with
tears. So much
so that the wall is about
to break, but
the dam stays and no
tear actually rolls down her face.
How old is Stevie? Stevie looks
to be maybe in
her late 20s, early 30s.
Okay, what is the second thing I see?
The second thing isn't what you see.
It's what you remember.
You remember
yeah, this is Fox Gottel
but it's like a little piece
of trivia that you remember.
Probably from reading the news.
Or even saying it. Exactly.
Literally saying it on the news when
Fred Gottel had his second
born child
Greg.
That's kind of washing over him
but he turns around and looks at
Stevie and he mouths
Faith?
Her eyes
get fucking huge.
Fucking Gottem.
Gottel!
Sweet.
The way that I was rubbing my fingers in my ear
most of the time it was
but my finger slipped once and I heard
Thomas go MOUTH!
I bet he just said like mouth but because
you were rubbing, it was just like so
loud coming through. That's so great.
I was doing it to the beat of
My House by Flo Rida.
So I was going to say to add some character
flavor to it I was trying to think why would he fail
this alertness role and it's because
all Beck's life he's been
a goofball and
maybe the worst he's ever gotten
in response to that is disappointment
and maybe some disgust sometimes when he's
like a slob. To see
himself elicit like
carnal fear in somebody
he's like what the fuck?
There's something wrong with me all of a sudden.
I'm broken. Right. Holy shit.
Which makes you trip backwards
squishing the
rabbit underneath your
feet and falling
directly on the
antlers impaling
your upper thigh.
Fuck dude. I guess that is
a fucking crit fail.
Holy shit. You lose four
hit points as you
start bleeding out.
Get a doctor. Mr. Gothel.
Get a doctor immediately.
Fuck.
I don't actually
oh right a doctor
right. Damn it man.
Move. Thankfully someone else
comes up it's one of the people
in yellow athleisure
comes up and is like
oh my goodness do you need a doctor?
Okay right away and they pull
out this device out of their
pocket and it looks like a futuristic
like Star Trek
speaker system it's actually
you know what it's um they're called
tricorders in Star Trek. Okay no I'm not
going to do that. Does it have like a big
talkie grill kind of thing? Yeah it's
got a big talkie grill on it it's like
a 60s like little oval
anthill thing with just a like a
wah wah wah wah. Yes exactly.
Like a CB radio thing. Yeah almost like a
CB radio and she grabs it and
and clicks in and is like doctor
I need a doctor to the south side
of the park immediately
immediately we're on the track yeah we're
on the track. Beck uh
just hang on there buddy. You all see
Foxgoddle is walking away with
his hands in his pockets while whistling
Fuck. What the fuck?
Can I try to first aid him? Uh
yeah go for it. Pass. What are you
using to uh. The ribbon
from the ambush.
Yes okay uh yeah you're
actually easily able to
uh go ahead and stop the bleeding
here so Beck you're not going to bleed
out. Oh thank god. So you get this
rush of relief over
oh god
Julius my man
Julius go ahead and
roll a d4 and let's see uh
what this does for him. Just one. Just one
get one hit point back
the most important thing is that the bleeding stops
oh well that's
that's certainly uh
Fox immediately whips back around and is like
oh oh you happen to fix it
oh that's good very good okay very nice
okay um what is wrong young woman
please uh tell the people that
we don't actually need any medical assistance
over here that's that's not
not true at all no man I mean like
this is hospital worthy my dude
yes we absolutely still need the doctor
what is wrong with you
oh oh
people don't normally
talk to me like that that's strange
interesting yeah no uh you
seem fine but if you still need a doctor
or whatever that's fine too
fine dude look at this and I'm
pointing at holes in my leg right yeah
yeah like impaled on the yeah
like blood is like like I don't
think I'm gonna like die like in the next
10 minutes but like dude
yeah certainly
I suppose we should uh wait for the
uh medical authorities
uh don't think that I've forgotten
about your reaction to the headphones
his face immediately just
goes like slack jawed
and elsewhere okay roll grip
you
you almost expect it this time and
all just like roll your eyes at each other
from the ground Beck is trying to
get uh Stevie's attention
yeah what's up Beck
hey I'm so sorry keep breathing here you want some
water yeah you got water
no but I bet
can you uh and there's someone passing by
who is holding water as they're jogging
she says hey Josh uh
can we get some water over here and
uh a green jogger
jogs over and says oh yeah
absolutely and as soon as they look down
they see the headphones and their mouth
goes slack jawed and they just kind of
like phase out of existence
like their faces they're just like
oh
and then their face is completely normal and they're like
yeah here's the water
god dammit could you excuse
us for a moment uh Julius
you you better come over here
once we're all like kind of huddled up
with Stevie I say
uh Julius
Beck
I'd like you to meet
Faith Godel shut the fuck up
shut
the fuck up
shut the fuck up
please do not say my name in here
how did your brother
not can we not talk about this right here
well because it's not her brother
anymore is it Stevie
okay it's like it is my brother
but he changed his name
did he change his name or did your father
change his name I don't know he changed his name after he got
got Julius yells
at everybody hey stick your fingers
in your ears and wiggle them around a little bit
we're trying to talk over here
laughter
um
Stevie
are you the one who told us about
the pen yeah so like
I was gonna have you film the injury
is that still part of your job
or like yeah no I can absolutely
I can film the injury
that's okay yeah what are you
what's going on okay
it's not a big deal we're just gonna do this job
and then we're gonna get out of here we can talk about it when we get out of here okay
Stevie so what do the
job what's the job finding the pen
no we have to film all of
this and then we have to get it out of here
we have to film the
dark side of what's out here
where's the dark stuff happen
and I look at the
lab inquisitively
laughter
honestly I didn't think that we'd be
having this conversation this early
but Zach's like
fuck there's just some really
fucked up shit okay do you trust me
Beck looks to Cal
Stevie you are the finest
gopher we've ever had
on this crew thank you can we
trust these people with our Beck
is he safe in their hands in their
medical care yeah he'll get the best
medical care available we'll
be allowed to go with him I bet well first of all
we will not be separated
from Beck sure yeah I don't
think that'll be a problem Beck is looking
really pale and he's
slurring even more than he usually does
cause there's a thin yellow like fucking
wrapping paper ribbon
laughter
this may be like the most
fortuitous of things because this
like it is into like their like
medical facilities and
once you're there it seems like you'd have access to
a lot of things like hospitals
are like centrally located in most
facilities yeah if they
let us out it'll be at the lab so
it'll be fine Stevie
were you born here yeah
when you yeah dude when did you
get out or were the Godel children
always allowed out no I got out like a
year ago my god that's
when I think when um
I think that's when Greg got got
Beck is now thinking about
it to himself and then makes eye contact
with Stevie and then
wiggles his headphones at her
yeah
you can probably answer this
what's the deal with the food
on the train why can't any outside food
come in oh yeah that's why I got you guys
all amped up on caffeine before we
got in it's uh
you can't have any caffeine or drugs
in here all the stuff that they
have doesn't actually have caffeine in it
it's just like if you have caffeine
in your system you won't
be able to
get got
that's fucking dark
Beck is gonna be bulletproof here he
drank like 40 of these
so the people
here are all under some kind of control
yeah and that's what we're trying
to show I'm assuming it's some kind of
you've fucking seen it you've all seen it
kind of headphone device no
it's just and then Fox walks up and he's like
hey what are you guys talking about
I punch him in the face
headphones headphones headphones headphones
headphone attack headphone attack
actually yeah literally I just
oh my god
I just lift one of Beck's
earphones like away from his ear
and let it fall back and like point at it
when he comes to you guys are like walking
and we're whistling
at this point
Fox comes up and he's
kind of talking to you guys and you see
that the medical staff has
arrived and they came on
a bowl pen cart
yeah dude hell yeah
with the helmet
are they wearing green
yeah they're all wearing green
of course they are they get
Beck situated on this
on this stretcher kind of situation
comfortably sitting and
they begin walking everyone
kind of down the trail
along the west
walkway up toward the lab
toward the north side alright well
do any of you want to come see
my GIZ
your GIZ?
yes let's go see my GIZ
I'm very proud of it I think we'd have a good time
you don't want to stick around and deal with all this
medical nonsense and
sit in a waiting room or what have you
you should come check out my GIZ I've got games
I've got a pool I've got a hot tub
whatever you want we could watch a movie we could hang out
mr. Godel I assure you
can never leaves a man
behind alright well
what is your GIZ?
my Godel innovation zone
yes of course my GIZ
yes of course the best
thoughts come in your GIZ
is that where you came up with the bouncy walkways?
well of course yes
I can take credit for that I believe I
dreamt it as a child and made a
drawing that my father made a reality
that's rad
could we take a rain check on
seeing your GIZ?
we are gonna
stay with our colleague
alright I'll take the I'll take the old rain check
if you're gonna be nice about it I don't
much care for that one and he points at Cal
he's like you had a nice handshake too
but you're a bit of a dick
sir you have ignored
the medical emergency of our co-worker
you tried to
refuse a medical service
and now you seem to want to
separate us from our friend
now I assure you I could be very nice to you
and very beneficial
for your business if we
perhaps get the message you want
on the air but you have
to talk to us first why don't you come
along with us dude I can like totally
film the interview from the bed
I would like to be on camera
okay you got me there
and he continues walking alongside
of each of you
looks over at Beck and Cal
you're also very handsome
I deeply appreciate that
of course I do
wow Julius
very kind
very kind indeed
I was trying to just
write quickly down what has happened so far
and one of my favorite things I think I've ever
written in my notes is I fell on a
jackalope
it's not at all
what I expected to happen tonight
I fell on a jackalope
and we passed up a chance to see jizz
Beck fell on
a jackalope is honestly someday
how I expect to hear that actual
Beck died
holy shit
where do Scientologists go when they die
hell
on the way there you guys all see a woman
who is kind of turning the corner
she's coming from the lab
statue area right
turning the corner heading down the walkway
toward you and you see that she is
a pencil of a woman
with bouncy spiky
hair on top of her head
Mr. Gotl you have pencil people here
roll grip
yeah
literally imagining that's my number two
just about to say
I'm imagining a number two like
bouncing down the road
fresh shape
this total beaker of a woman
is just like
notices you all and then
bounces away
yeah just gonna
running though
back from whence she came
so wait wait
did she just come towards us and turn around
yep she came out
turned the corner saw you guys
immediately started running in the
opposite direction and
Fox is like oh Barbara
off to go run
and see her old husband
probably freaking out that he didn't
meet you guys at the gate huh
who is that
oh Chuck Bidwell
Chuck Bidwell and Barbara Bidwell
Chuck is our well he's not the mayor
but he's
no no of course not
I'm not the mayor but you know
Chuck is the guy who kind of
does everything that the mayor should do
yeah like a city manager
yeah kind of like that yeah
and you're saying he should have met us at the gate
well I would assume that that's why
Barbara was running off like that
she's kind of his keeper
I suppose
Cal glances back to make sure
he's been rolling this whole time
Mr. Gottle
what would a city manager handle here
do they handle taxes
well yes of course I would assume
yeah they would handle all sorts of business
sides of things but of course
taxes because of course you
pay these employees
well obviously we have to
pay our employees in
money? uh yeah
US dollars
or points which one would you
like to hear I actually
I'm a bit of
afraid to say I don't know the answer
to that question I am a bit
more of the hang out in my
GIZ and kick it kind of guy
so to your knowledge sir you
do not pay your employees anything
well I wouldn't be the one paying him now
would I I'm the future CEO
of the Gottle company but not the
current CEO as he points up at the statues
ahead he says see uh
not a statue up there yet but
sir how much does a gallon of milk cost
commissioning it
a gallon of milk
god I don't know um
pffff
seven
seven dollars
dammit he's right
is everyone here
vegan or vegetarian
well no one eats meat or meat
byproducts uh I
guess that's what you might call vegan yeah
pretty rough move when he came in there
Beck stepping
on an animal like that that's uh
not a way to make a good impression around here
this rings true for
Beck he's kind of feeling bad that he
fell on a jackalope
was the rabbit okay
I didn't even check sure
Beck yeah cool
it wasn't oh
I think he killed it it was at least
a swift end
I saw it cry
I've never like
killed an animal before
and at this point you guys have kind of made your way up
to the front here and it's a sight
to behold this is a massive
glass building
three stories tall
but extremely wide
taking up the whole north side of this
park square and
in front of it massive
26.3
meter tall statues
of this green rock
and up close you see
an immense amount of detail
hey Zach would that happen to be 69 feet
no
it does seem like
I literally just did the math in my head at 78.9
but I
did the math because I was like that's probably
we covered a lot
we got a lot of fantastic
footage of
Godel just being just incriminating
himself really
oh are you still filming from the
I never
got the camera hand off to
Stevie
but I think that made it more
a little more discreet
it's all like the cover of
Rubber Soul where it's all kind of looking up
at everybody's faces and just swiveling
it's a really rad dolly shot there
it's a walk and talk
yeah it's a total walk and talk
down low angle
Joe loves his sorkin
you know it
fuck
and as you guys are walking down at the very end
you see a
maybe not yet
pterodactyl
another jackalope
oh god
it's gonna haunt me for the rest of my life
this one has a
purple ribbon
never mind it's not the same one
Cal leans over at his TV
hey what
there's purple
is there a purple team?
Fox you notice kind of runs over
to it removes the ribbon
puts the ribbon in his pocket
and then starts walking away
from you all back
toward where you came from
kind of toward where you
he's kind of pointed at his house
he's just kind of walking away
whistling with his hands in his pockets
once again
Mr. Godle, Mr. Godle
Fox
I throw some headphones at him
roll athletics
to see if you can throw
at a negative 20
to see if you can throw a pair of headphones
and I assume you grab
I've got a 10% chance
you grab Bex
so you grab Bex
headphones from off his head
and you throw them without
unplugging them from the cord at all
and they just kind of immediately
swing into the ground
and
Fox turns around as he's whistling
and is kind of like you guys
and he's not looking he's just
yelling over his shoulder you said
you wouldn't leave your friend right?
bye it was nice to meet you
continues kind of whistling
Mr. Godle wait where are we supposed to go?
and one of the people walking
with you is like
oh we'll take care of it
and then they notice the headphones on the ground
and they're like
we just like look at our watches
and tap our feet
Bex calls after Fox also
no interview then or
and with that he's gone
you guys are now walking past
where there's this rabbit
just kind of hopping along
with a spare pair of antlers
hanging out on the ground
I'm sorry about your brother my man
yeah
not Stevie the rabbit
oh yeah I was talking to the rabbit
I thought you were talking
back at the rabbit
she was about to be like shut the fuck up
straight up
straight up was like dude the rabbits talk right
oh my god
they're not real jackalopes but they do talk
and can love
we'll travel
we hear the other one just screaming
kill me!
oh god
I'm not quite dead yet!
cow's like
oh jeez what's up doc
oh
no we're EE's not GE's actually
yes
that means you wear green
am I right?
yeah EE's excellent employees
between you and me
between Kyle Colorado and two EE's
do you feel like you're better than the great employees?
yeah I mean
it's different
tell me are you from around here?
yeah I live over there and
they point at one of these dope houses
inside this futuristic
mid century modern house
that wouldn't happen to be the home you were born in would it?
no I'm from like the outside
how long have you been in Grover's Gorge?
gosh like five years?
and do they pay you?
in money? yeah
what's your salary? if you don't mind me asking
what's your salary?
a million dollars
it was once close
and you're walking up the stairs
kind of now and this
oh like the golf carts
is that what you called it? I called it a bullpen cart
are we in a
we've been in that the whole time
yeah you've been walking him down
yeah you've been walking him down to the end
standing next to me
it does a nice little
slide into stairs
where it's got kind of rails that land
down on the stairs to where it can slide
gently up the stairs and you're walking
up the stairs and
all of the stairs that you're walking
on are grass
grass stairs leading up
and then this like small grass field
in front of this beautiful
glass building and on this grass
area is where these two I mean you're looking
up they're huge
the hogs? they're like
well I mean
how many feet did you say Luke? 78.9
yeah that's like seven stories tall
real quick these things are tall
the grass stairs
where people have traveled
up them or is the grass worn away
or is it like perfect grass?
oh it's like perfect grass
no desire paths or like dirt
not at all and you see a woman who is walking
out of the lab
currently in full
judges robes and a powdered
wig atop her head
hey that's from the thing
oh yeah
she's wearing a
pair of electric blue high
heels no green or yellow
markings anywhere? no green or yellow markings
anywhere no no she looks
like a real world judge and
no gaudel corporation trappings
absolutely not other than
perhaps the powdered wig might
make her not so much
look like a real world judge or like
I'm sorry British yeah are you aware of
the commonwealth nations? I'm not
no can you please they dress like fucking
idiots yeah they look like buffoons
and those fucking buffoons
send you away to prison
I think they make
the lawyers wear them too straight up this is
what they look like oh my
god did you not know they still did that?
no that's silly
I like that yeah
so exactly like real world judges
oh my god these guys look so
silly as she's walking
out I need everyone to roll humans
please I'm sorry she's walking out
of the factory the lab
the lab pass ooh
hard pass with the three
I failed a
79 yeah you're
fucking screaming in the back
it makes a ton of sense that you
wouldn't pick up on this sir who a judge
surprised I didn't have you rolling a negative
we're like wait
Beck Beck who's do you know that lady
and you're just like ahhhh
the
adrenaline has started to wear off a little bit
I'm going in and out of consciousness sometimes
you look back and my eyes are closed
so I passed my ass off
who is this judge?
both you and Julius notice that
the eyes of this judge
and Stevie
meet
like physically touch
laughter
as she passes
she leans in
and touches her eyeballs
they butterfly kiss
could you touch your eye
to somebody else's eye couldn't you?
yeah you can it's not
pleasant probably hurt
feels weird we'll try it later
I have contacts in then yeah it's protected
so you guys see this judge and she is
making eyes right they lock and
you notice a
strange look
come over the judge's face but
because you know who Stevie
is you see
a look of recognition
on the judge's face as she looks at
Faith Godel Stevie is
that judge going to blow your cover
no I don't think so
she knew where I was
she's been keeping me safe this whole time so I don't think
she'd fuck it up now and then who does
she work for? the Godel Company
what is your relationship to her?
she's
nice
she's understanding at least
maybe not nice
she serves as some kind of
definitely not nice actually now that I think about it
she serves as a judge for this community
yeah and at this point
you guys are walking through
these glass walls
there's seemingly no
door but the walls
kind of lift
creating an opening in the whole
front of this building and allow
you to walk through Cal says
neat you continue to walk
on grass inside
that's fucking sick there are no
stairs but suddenly there's an
incline of the same synthetic pathway
that you saw out on the track
and that incline synthetic
pathway takes you upstairs
so basically you walk up
and then you flip a yay
and you're facing back the way you came
and there's another huge wall
of glass that you're looking out and
up against that glass there are three
stools with this glass backdrop
and it faces back the way you came
looking out through the glass wall
into the beauty
and enormity of the park at
the city center of Grover's Gorge
and on the far stool
perched on its
plastron which is the belly
of a turtle
is an extremely old looking
common box turtle
its head flippers and shell
are covered in scratches
and scars
and it looks damp
a makeup artist is attempting to powder
it dry while holding
the turtle steady by its
torn up moist shell
Cal reaches a hand out to the
turtle and says, Mr. Gotle
I presume
the makeup artist is like laughing
this is just like a normal
sized box turtle or is it like big
yeah, how big is a box turtle
normally, pretty small, yeah so it's like a
big box turtle, okay
for everybody at home he was putting his hands
about this far apart, like the size of my head
not that big
yeah dude
that would be terrifying, how long
do box turtles live, oh forever
like a lobsters, and god
god was
never born though, neither were box
turtles, whoa
box turtles
yeah, you're right, box turtles
are not born, and do not
die
box turtles are angels
of our lord
and says they're right on the
wikipedia, dude
in the bible, box turtles actually look
fucking insane
you know, like a big wheel with eyeballs
god dammit, biblically accurate
turtle
its shells instead of eyes
box turtles generally
live to be about 35 years old
but some have been known to survive
for um, eternity
yeah, that's
what I thought, I say all this to the turtle
so we were led up here by this
medical staff? I thought maybe this was like a
waiting room, but then the turtle was
getting its makeup then
I thought they were
maybe disrespecting us very hard
yeah, like, we brought you to the
vet, you fucking
or just like, oh you want to interview somebody?
you want to interview, here's our employee of the month
boxy
one of the medical staff says to you
well I think you'll be doing
the interview up here and we can just have
the medical staff come up and meet you
they're based in this building, so
oh wait, the interview with mr
the mayor
oh, with the mayor, mr bidwell
no, the mayor
and they look at the turtle and they say
sandro
woah
I
hey Beck, don't step on the mayor
laughter
my life
is great
wait, Mickey Rooney Jr., Buzz Aldrin
and Neil Armstrong? and Ryan Gosling
I was saying my movie is The First Mouseketeer
which is about
Mickey Rooney Jr.
it's like the fly
but instead of a fly, it's a mouse
ew
that seems like a movie they should have tried to remake by now
I wouldn't want to live in a Cronenberg
have you ever seen the first, like the original
the old, old one? no, I haven't seen it
it's not very good
the one with Jeff Goldblum
you know that really old one
let's see, the fly remake
there's no plans that I can see
but there's an article that says
the fly continues to make a strong
pro remake argument
I, oh sorry
can I get 30 seconds to sound?
and it's all my fault
oh